<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Better days feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My better days episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My Better days feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 03:25:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>Therapy Chat : 217: A Deeper Look At Animal-Assisted Therapies with Philip Tedeschi</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you to this episode's sponsor, TherapyNotes. Get a 2-month free trial of TherapyNotes by going to &lt;a href="http://www.therapynotes.com/" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;www.TherapyNotes.com&lt;/a&gt; and using the promo code TherapyChat. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On today's episode host Laura Reagan, LCSW-C speaks to Philip Tedeschi about animal-assisted therapies. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Philip Tedeschi is the executive director of the Institute for Human-Animal Connection and a clinical professor at the Graduate School of Social Work. He is globally recognized for expertise in the clinical methods of animal-assisted Interventions and coordinates the school's animal-assisted social work certificate program for Master of Social Work (MSW) students, as well as the animals and human health professional development certificate program. He received his MSSW degree from the University of Wisconsin-Madison, where his specialization was the bio-affiliative connection between people and animals.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He studies and teaches on the intricate relationship between people, domestic and wild animals, and the natural world. Tedeschi’s research, scholarship, presentations, training and community practice work have focused on human-animal interactions, conservation social work, human ecology, causes of violence toward people and animals. Tedeschi is a certified Master Therapeutic Riding Instructor, former course director and instructor with Outward Bound, wilderness medical technician, forensic evaluator and has many years of experience in non-traditional therapeutic approaches with children, adults and families. He specializes in the therapeutic and health-promoting potential of human-animal and nature interaction, trauma-informed methods and intervention in interpersonal violence, including assessment and intervention with cruelty and animal abuse.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Resources&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://portfolio.du.edu/ptedesch"&gt;https://portfolio.du.edu/ptedesch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.amazon.com/Transforming-Trauma-Resilience-Connections-Human-Animal/dp/155753795X"&gt; https://www.amazon.com/Transforming-Trauma-Resilience-Connections-Human-Animal/dp/155753795X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leave me a message via Speakpipe by going to &lt;a href= "https://therapychatpodcast.com"&gt;https://therapychatpodcast.com&lt;/a&gt; and clicking on the green Speakpipe button.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thank you for listening to Therapy Chat! Please be sure to &lt;a href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/therapy-chat-psychotherapy-mindfulness-trauma-attachment/id1031099411?mt=2"&gt; go to iTunes&lt;/a&gt; and leave a rating and review, subscribe and download episodes. You can also download the Therapy Chat app on iTunes &lt;a href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/therapy-chat-podcast/id1225704658?mt=8"&gt; by clicking here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Podcast produced by Pete Bailey - &lt;a href= "https://petebailey.net/audio"&gt;https://petebailey.net/audio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>therapychat.podcast@gmail.com (Therapy Chat)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b1b3ca96d80e4d0cbd0b6ef1f8a2cc19</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b1b3ca96d80e4d0cbd0b6ef1f8a2cc19/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 07:51:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Think Again – a Big Think Podcast : 230. Eve Ensler (Jason Plays Favorites #2) – no way out but through</title><description>&lt;p&gt;[From February through March 22, 2020 (his last day hosting Think Again) Jason will be revisiting favorite past episodes. Jason's new show, starting May 12th, is &lt;a href="https://radiopublic.com/clever-creature-with-jason-gots-6L0pKq"&gt;Clever Creature with Jason Gots&lt;/a&gt;.]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: &lt;/strong&gt;I feel I should let listeners know that this episode of Think Again is about surviving and thriving in the face of unspeakable trauma and sexual violence. And in order to get to the thriving, we have talk about the trauma, which may be painful for some listeners and inappropriate for kids. But I don’t want to scare anybody off—I think it’s one of the most valuable conversations we’ve ever had on the show. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a human child growing up, trust is the foundation of everything. We learn how to &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Attachment_theory"&gt;regulate our emotions&lt;/a&gt;, how to see the world as relatively stable and safe through the connection with the people who care for us. Severely neglected children &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2014/02/20/280237833/orphans-lonely-beginnings-reveal-how-parents-shape-a-childs-brain"&gt;can suffer all kinds of harm&lt;/a&gt; to their ability to think, connect with others, and learn. But what happens when the caring bond is not only missing, but is horribly abused? Distorted through incest and sexual violence? How do you build a self and life after that? And let’s say you somehow manage to survive to adulthood…to thrive, even. How do you fill the place in your heart where the love and the trust is supposed to be?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My guest today has had to answer all these questions for herself. She is the playwright, author, and activist &lt;a href="https://www.eveensler.org/"&gt;Eve Ensler&lt;/a&gt;. You may know her as the creator of the Vagina Monlogues. What you might not know is that all the horrors I’m talking about happened to her as a kid. Let me take that out of the passive voice: her father did that to her, and more. And he died without saying anything remotely close to “I’m sorry”. So Eve wrote his apology for him—her book &lt;a href="http://smarturl.it/theapologybook"&gt;THE APOLOGY&lt;/a&gt; is a letter to her—to Eve—in the imagined voice of her dead father, retelling what happened, why it happened, and trying to figure out in these twisted circumstances what an apology would even mean…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Surprise conversation starters in this episode: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bigthink.com/videos/great-risk-for-great-gain-immigrants-and-innovators-are-psychologically-the-same"&gt;Jared Diamond on immigrants and innovation &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thoughts on relistening&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This episode with Eve Ensler means a lot to me. I came late to the feminist conversation about patriarchy and masculinity. About the ways men are taught to be ashamed of vulnerability, and how all that fear and shame can lead to violence. Listening back I’m struck again by this one thing she says: “Language changes everything. It’s like the word 'vagina'. If you can’t say it, you can’t see it. If you can’t see it, a lot of things can happen to it in the dark without your permission.” There is so much hope and power in the work Eve does to break the silence and encourage others to do the same. As a man, I hear it especially loud and clear when she says it’s time for men to “...make a choice. Whether they’re going to maintain allegiance to the male code or step into the next paradigm. Stopping the domination so they get to be free in this lifetime.” I hear it and I personally, enthusiastically accept that call. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jason@bigthink.com (Think Again – a Big Think Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">53cf052235794c1a883655f6e88549f3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/53cf052235794c1a883655f6e88549f3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Daily Meditation Podcast : Quality Time With Yourself</title><description>&lt;p&gt; Spend time reviewing your week.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; This is part 7 of a 7-part Friendship meditation series, episodes 1718-1724.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Give our new sip and om app a test drive for 1-week free. Receive access to 1,900+ fully guided meditations customized around a weekly theme. Select from 300+ series to fit your mood with a Clarity Journal and a Slow Down Guide customized for each theme. Brand new themes are introduced each week with brand new meditations offered daily. Connect with other meditators on the private Facebook group for app subscribers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a title="2 Week's Free sip and om iOS app" href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/sip-and-om/id1216664612?platform=iphone&amp;preserveScrollPosition=true#platform/iphone"&gt; 2 weeks for access to the iOS version:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/sip-and-om/id1216664612?platform=iphone&amp;preserveScrollPosition=true#platform/iphone&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a title="sip and om Android app" href= "https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sipandom.sipandom"&gt; 2 weeks free access to the Android version:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sipandom.sipandom&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;All meditations are created by Mary Meckley and are her original content. Please request permission to use any of Mary's content by sending an email to Mary@sipandom.com.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Resources: Music by Christopher Lloyd Clarke and Greg Keller.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Support@SipandOm.com (Daily Meditation Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">579251e0773c41be86148579fa92cee5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/579251e0773c41be86148579fa92cee5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 14:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Untangle : Valentines Week Love Fest - Encore - Love and Relationships Demystified</title><description>Daphne Rose Kingma is the best selling author of 12 books on love and relationships. She answers some tough questions on why relationships can be so challenging and shares why--spoiler alert!--expecting others to read our minds is a bad idea. She shares her juicy wisdom on navigating relationships, learning to love, how be a better partner, and more!</description><author>support@meditationstudioapp.com (Untangle)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fca2e08ad9bb476d8ba6386dc2884dcf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fca2e08ad9bb476d8ba6386dc2884dcf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 13:02:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Inspiration Rising : Own Your Story and Tell It Like It Is - Ashley Abercrombie</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ashley Abercrombie&lt;/strong&gt; is an author, speaker, old fashioned truth-teller, and so much more. Her story is powerful, her mission is specific, and her voice has been heard all over the world. Ashley fought to overcome addiction, rape, abortion, perfectionism and dysfunctional relationships to become an honest, whole and free woman (most days). She wore a mask more than half her life and considers herself too old, and too annoyed to ever put that thing on again. She is the co-host of the chart-topping podcast &lt;em&gt;Why Tho&lt;/em&gt;, author of &lt;em&gt;Rise of the Truth Teller&lt;/em&gt;, and a contributing writer for various digital outlets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In This Episode, You Will Learn:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;What it means to own your story.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How Ashley overcame deep challenges in her life.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;What it looks like to tell it like it is.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Important social issues that Ashley is deeply passionate about.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with Ashley:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ashabercrombie.org/" rel="nofollow"&gt;AshAbercrombie.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2tXusns" rel="nofollow"&gt;Rise of the Truth Teller: Own Your Story, Tell It Like It Is, and Live with Holy Gumption&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ashabercrombie.org/podcast" rel="nofollow"&gt;Why Tho Podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/ashabercrombienyc/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/AshAbercrombie" rel="nofollow"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/ashabercrombie/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pinterest.com/ashabercrombie/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Pinterest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t Miss A Single Episode:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscribe&lt;/strong&gt; on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/inspiration-rising/id1448649388" rel="nofollow"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/music/m/Iqrp5q3bagph2t23malprd3dxvy?t=Launch_Yourself_Today" rel="nofollow"&gt;Google Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/42zIsXzjCibZt49xdCRvB4" rel="nofollow"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href="https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/in-plain-sight/launch-yourself-today" rel="nofollow"&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leave a quick review&lt;/strong&gt; on any of the podcast apps to tell people what you think about the show.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take a screenshot of the podcast&lt;/strong&gt; and post it on Instagram or Instagram Stories. Tag us &lt;a href="http://www.instagram.com/insporising" rel="nofollow"&gt;@insporising&lt;/a&gt;. We’ll repost and give you a shoutout!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Support this podcast at — &lt;a rel='payment' href='https://redcircle.com/inspiration-rising/donations'&gt;https://redcircle.com/inspiration-rising/donations&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>david@insporising.com (Inspiration Rising)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7f845f71ba0c45678a98d1b65e8329d7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7f845f71ba0c45678a98d1b65e8329d7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 11:47:54 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Sugars : Episodes We Love: A Night Of Bad Stories</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Sugars returns to Portland, Oregon, for another raucous and uplifting live show. The Sugars get a surprising update from a letter writer from their past; discuss a new letter with a special guest, Omar El Akkad; and ask the audience, “What’s the ‘bad story’ you tell yourself?” “Bad Stories,” the title of Steve Almond’s new book, are the false narratives we tell ourselves that undermine our happiness. “You’ve got to revise those narratives,” encourages Cheryl Strayed. “You have the capacity for change and transformation.” This episode was originally published on April 12th, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@wbur.org (Dear Sugars)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">59f2295928304e07894fb355c70223f6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/59f2295928304e07894fb355c70223f6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 09:44:38 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Expand Your Awareness Podcast 2.0 : EP#97 Events that Shaped My Self-Image and how you can change yours</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this vulnerable episode, I'll share the events that shaped my self-image. No only that, I'll also be showing you exactly how to modify  your current self-image. The truth is, our identity and self-image completely controls our life.  Once you drop the story of your past and give yourself permission to create a new Identity, your life will transform in an extremely powerful way. Much Love &amp; Namaste &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To join The Shift Academy click here: &lt;a href= "http://aarondoughty.com/theshiftacademy" rel= "nofollow"&gt;aarondoughty.com/theshiftacademy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To Calibrate Your Vibration Click here: &lt;a href= "https://whatsmyvibration.com/" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://whatsmyvibration.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For The SHIFT Experience Webinar click here: &lt;a href= "https://events.genndi.com/register/818182175026324307/4e3eb392ee" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://events.genndi.com/register/818182175026324307/4e3eb392ee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href="https://instagram.com/aaron_doughty44/" rel="nofollow"&gt;https://instagram.com/aaron_doughty44/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Youtube: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC48MclMZIY_EaOQwatzCpvw" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC48MclMZIY_EaOQwatzCpvw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe to the Expand Your Awareness Podcast 2.0 with Aaron Doughty&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;iTunes | &lt;a href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-2-0/id1455761627?mt=2" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-2-0/id1455761627?mt=2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Spotify | &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/show/5mVETgyaXMeznNC70v71YO" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://open.spotify.com/show/5mVETgyaXMeznNC70v71YO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Stitcher | &lt;a href= "https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/aaron-doughty/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-20-with-aaron-doughty?refid=stpr" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/aaron-doughty/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-20-with-aaron-doughty?refid=stpr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>adoughty44@yahoo.com (The Expand Your Awareness Podcast 2.0)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9b97c0ade4cc455aa5b24b0b12dde015</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9b97c0ade4cc455aa5b24b0b12dde015/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>On Purpose with Jay Shetty : Jay Shetty Interviews His Wife For The Second Time (On Purpose 1 Year Anniversary)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Happy 1 Year Anniversary to On Purpose with Jay Shetty! One year ago Radhi and Jay Shetty released the first episode of On Purpose. In this episode, they get together on camera again to talk about the past year and answer frequently asked questions from Jay’s audience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video to learn what they love doing together, how Radhi conquered her fear of being on camera, and so much more in this episode of On Purpose. Text Jay Shetty 310-997-4177&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/backhand-index-pointing-right/" target="_blank"&gt;👉&lt;/a&gt; Get Jay’s Best Podcast Collection &lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/backhand-index-pointing-down/" target="_blank"&gt;👇&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://jayshetty.me/bestpodcasts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Word From Our Sponsors:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Try Zapier free by going to our special link &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://zapier.com/JAY" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zapier.com/JAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go to &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://imperfectfoods.com/JAYSHETTY" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ImperfectFoods.com/JAYSHETTY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; to get $10-OFF your next FOUR orders&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check your rate in minutes and borrow up to $40,000. That’s &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://lendingclub.com/JAY" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LendingClub.com/JAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We have a Special offer from LES MILLS On Demand where you can get 21 days FREE access to their fitness app. So don’t wait and go to &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://trylesmills.com/ONPURPOSE" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;trylesmills.com/ONPURPOSE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jayshetty@kastmedia.com (On Purpose with Jay Shetty)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cc1d1b35d8fb4e77aa3dd1636064bcb2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cc1d1b35d8fb4e77aa3dd1636064bcb2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Therapy for Black Girls : BONUS: Sisterhood in Business</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Therapy for Black Girls Podcast is a weekly conversation with Dr. Joy Harden Bradford, a Licensed Psychologist in Atlanta, Georgia, about all things mental health, personal development, and all the small decisions we can make to become the best possible version of ourselves.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is a special bonus episode of the podcast brought to you with the support of &lt;a href="https://www.pfizer.com" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Pfizer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;I am thrilled to be partnering with Pfizer on this series as we countdown to this year's Black Enterprise Women of Power Summit. I’ll be speaking in the Pfizer booth during the summit about how our mental health is impacted by our experiences in the workplace, in entrepreneurship, in leadership roles, and in relationships with others and wanted to kick these conversations off here on the podcast talking to a few women about their experiences.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;In part 1 of the series, you’ll hear my conversation with Dr. Lakeysha "Key" Hallmon. Dr. Key is the visionary behind The Village Market ATL and one of the dopest sisters I’ve ever met. She and I chatted about what sisterhood can look like in business, her definition of the modern village, practical ways we can create community with other sisters, how to truly embrace a spirit of collaboration over competition, and she shares how she tends to her mental health while also tending to her business.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Learn more about Dr. Key &amp; &lt;a href= "https://thevillagemarketatl.com/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;The Village Market ATL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Connect with Dr. Key &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Instagram : &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/drkeyhallmon" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;@drkeyhallmon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Twitter: &lt;a href= "https://www.twitter.com/drkeyhallmon" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;@drkeyhallmon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@therapyforblackgirls.com (Therapy for Black Girls)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5034f3dbfef740d5b617d4dd847b9046</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5034f3dbfef740d5b617d4dd847b9046/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>THE UPSIDE with Callie and Jeff Dauler : EPISODE 177:  CUPID, DRAW BACK YOUR BOW ...</title><description>&lt;p&gt;episode 177 / February 14, 2020&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jdauler@gmail.com (THE UPSIDE with Callie and Jeff Dauler)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a888167e00c747febb1a5281af567eac</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a888167e00c747febb1a5281af567eac/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Mindset Mentor : Does Money Buy Happiness?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;My answer to this question is going to surprise you but you want to know what it is. Also, I'll teach you why money is not what you are searching for in this life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow me on Instagram @RobDialJr &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/robdialjr/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/robdialjr/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>robdial0@gmail.com (The Mindset Mentor)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d3d98d0bc330426588b1cc9cc7faeafe</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d3d98d0bc330426588b1cc9cc7faeafe/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 21:47:21 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Before Breakfast : Little ways to say 'I love you'</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Flowers are great, but so are these ideas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Before Breakfast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">87a711d2faca4ae4801010d4f2d27b94</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/87a711d2faca4ae4801010d4f2d27b94/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Katie Piper's Extraordinary People : Dame Jessica Ennis-Hill is extraordinary!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Dame Jessica Ennis-Hill speak to Katie about how she deals with negative thoughts, balancing motherhood alongside being a professional athlete and how she became the best in the world at the seven disciplines that make up the heptathlon.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>sepodcasts@somethinelse.com (Katie Piper's Extraordinary People)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d99aab09d5fd421d9f56bbf8274563b8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d99aab09d5fd421d9f56bbf8274563b8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Success Sensei Podcast : What Colour is Your Ferrari? - ep112</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei Podcast&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would love to hear your views. Please get in touch using any of the channels below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All comments, reviews, subscribes, likes and shares are greatly appreciated. Thank you for all your continued support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Now Twice A Week: Every Wednesday there’s a brand new Success Sensei Blog, Podcast and Vlog. Every Friday we’re bringing you the Friday Blitz – a shorter, sharper, shockier Success Sensei Podcast and Vlog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Roundhouse Rob, The Success Sensei&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robert Devane is a serial entrepreneur and experienced investor as well as a former martial arts multiple World champion and professional MMA fighter with over 20 years of coaching experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more amazing FREE content please visit:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Apple itunes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://itunes.apple.com/ie/podcast/the-success-sensei-podcast/id1448626122?mt=2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Android&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://successsensei.podbean.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei Blog&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;http://www.thesuccesssensei.blogspot.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on YouTube&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCZG1Ly9zBKc5ZZ134dkjeHA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Facebook&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;http://www.facebook.com/thesuccesssensei&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Instagram&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;http://www.instagram.com/thesuccesssensei&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>redevane@yahoo.com (The Success Sensei Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bb8929af750648f696f8709d2d4257fd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bb8929af750648f696f8709d2d4257fd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 16:06:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Kind World : Kindness From Our ... Exes?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Breakups can involve complicated feelings and simmering resentments. But we asked some of our friends and colleagues to reflect back and think about the nice things their exes have done for them. We got some pretty great answers.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@wbur.org (Kind World)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7ffb0327b6e6429eb598eb92b4b99a86</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7ffb0327b6e6429eb598eb92b4b99a86/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 12:46:54 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rise &amp; Conquer Podcast : Q&amp;A with my husband! Babies? Working together? Prenup? + Tips to a lasting relationship *V Day special*</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This Valentine’s Day, Tim and I thought we’d share the love and sit down together to answer some of our most commonly asked questions! If you’ve ever been curious as to how we cope with working together, if and when we want babies, how Tim knew he wanted to propose, whether social media affects our relationship plus more… then listen in! We also provide our tips and tricks to sustaining a long-lasting relationship and how to overcome rough patches along the way!   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AD/ Want to elevate and fuel your workouts naturally? Use ‘Riseandconquer’ for 15% off your order at&lt;a href="http://www.nakedharvestsupplements.com/"&gt; www.nakedharvestsupplements.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Naked Harvest Supplements on instagram&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/nakedharvestsupplements/"&gt; @nakedharvestsupplements&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Georgie on&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/georgiestevenson/"&gt; instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow the&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/riseandconquer.podcast/"&gt; Rise and Conquer Podcast Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@georgiestevenson.net (The Rise &amp; Conquer Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3bfaee9512af49caad6362295b8214e6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3bfaee9512af49caad6362295b8214e6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 11:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Peak Mind with Michael Trainer : WIM HOF: HOW TO BREATHE FOR MINDSET AND PERFORMANCE</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Wim Hof Full episode #33: https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/wim-hof-profound-benefits-breath-cold-for-your-health/id1454600603?i=1000445607620&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>michael@peakmind.org (Peak Mind with Michael Trainer)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7f55263cbd1347cc914bfa2acce2ba61</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7f55263cbd1347cc914bfa2acce2ba61/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 10:23:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Heal, Survive &amp; Thrive! : What Happens When A Narcissist Knows You Have Figured Them Out</title><description>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;For more information on Private &amp; Group Coaching please visit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.stephanielynlifecoaching.com/services'&gt;https://www.stephanielynlifecoaching.com/services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Subscribe to my YouTube Channel for new videos every Tuesday!       &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/stephanielyncoaching'&gt;https://www.youtube.com/stephanielyncoaching&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Shop Our Clothing: &lt;a href='https://teespring.com/en-GB/stores/sl-clothing'&gt;https://teespring.com/en-GB/stores/sl-clothing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Thank you all for your love and support!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;All the best!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Stephanie&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ssylvia23@gmail.com (Heal, Survive &amp; Thrive!)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a0bab323eab94b21bfa549217dc8e9e5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a0bab323eab94b21bfa549217dc8e9e5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Energy Clearing for Life Force : Energy Clearing for Life Force "Silence the Inner Critic" Podcast #215</title><description>Energy Clearing for Life Force "Silence the Inner Critic" Podcast #215&lt;p&gt;It can be infinitely easier to see others in light and criticize ourselves. How to silence that unfriendly self talk on this episode of Energy Clearing for Life Force podcast. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>energyclearingforlife@gmail.com (Energy Clearing for Life Force)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d40390baf4454f51a2bfba8c66e792b4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d40390baf4454f51a2bfba8c66e792b4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Enneagram &amp; Coffee : 34: Behind the Curtain: How I Wrote My Book</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In today's highly requested episode Sarajane is talking about how she wrote her new book, &lt;a href= "https://publishing.andrewsmcmeel.com/book/the-honest-enneagram-know-your-type-own-your-challenges-embrace-your-growth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;The Honest Enneagram&lt;/a&gt;. She shares what the writing process looked like; how she used what she knows about her motivations as a 7 to choose the place, space, and time she would write; and the things she thought went well as well as maybe could have gone better.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Referenced in this episode:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Pre-order Sarajane's new book &lt;a href= "https://publishing.andrewsmcmeel.com/book/the-honest-enneagram-know-your-type-own-your-challenges-embrace-your-growth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can connect with Sarajane on &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/enneagramandcoffee/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href= "enneagramandcoffee.com"&gt;her website&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@enneagramandcoffee.com (Enneagram &amp; Coffee)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7310f19771404cbb8dcd0746581faec6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7310f19771404cbb8dcd0746581faec6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hope to Recharge : Choosing Higher Vibrations (Attitude of Gratitude)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today I wanted to share something with you that I have noticed about myself. In the past, I used to ask my extremely positive husband and father to “tone it down” with their positivity. I would question why they were so happy and why they intentionally chose joy everyday.  I did not understand how anyone could live in such a high vibration simply by being alive.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I later realized that by questioning their joy I was actually interfering with it. I wanted to bring them down to my level of comfort. I didn’t realize that my low energy wasn’t able to handle their happiness. As I have worked on my own gratitude and my own energy has shifted, people now ask me the same questions I use to ask them. “&lt;em&gt;How can you be so happy? How can you find so much joy?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It is difficult to walk through life and maintain joy unless you are intentional with it. There is a lot of negative energy in the world.We have the power however to amplify joy and positive energy through practices like gratitude and developing the habit of seeing the good. It’s not always easy, but now after experiencing its power I am more passionate than ever and want to share these practices with you.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Gratitude is a choice that we make. We want to support you as you make these choices yourself and walk in a lifestyle of gratitude. Find us in our private  Facebook Community: &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/"&gt;Hope to Recharge&lt;/a&gt;...because as always, together is better!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Interested in joining our monthly Mastermind? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Find out more info here! &lt;a href= "http://www.hopetorecharge.com/Mastermind"&gt;www.hopetorecharge.com/Mastermind&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Today's episode of Hope to Recharge is sponsored by &lt;a href= "http://betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge"&gt;https://Betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Betterhelp.com is the world’s leading provider of online therapy. Their mission is to make professional counseling accessible, affordable, and convenient, so anyone who struggles with life’s challenges can get help, anytime, anywhere.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Head to &lt;a href= "https://betterhelp.com/"&gt;https://Betterhelp.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href= "https://betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge"&gt;hopetorecharge&lt;/a&gt; for 10% off your first month of services. IMPORTANT: Be sure to click &lt;a href= "https://betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge"&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt; in order to get the10% off code&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Resources mentioned: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="padding-left: 40px;"&gt;A Complaint Free World by &lt;a href= "https://www.amazon.com/Will-Bowen/e/B001JRRL2I/ref=dp_byline_cont_book_1"&gt; Will Bowen&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href= "https://www.amazon.com/Complaint-Free-World-Complaining-Enjoying/dp/0770436390"&gt; https://www.amazon.com/Complaint-Free-World-Complaining-Enjoying/dp/0770436390&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="padding-left: 40px;"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="padding-left: 40px;"&gt;The Motivation Manifesto by by &lt;a href= "https://www.amazon.com/Brendon-Burchard/e/B001IGOFHY/ref=dp_byline_cont_book_1"&gt; Brendon Burchard&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Motivation-Manifesto-Brendon-Burchard/dp/1401948073"&gt; https://www.amazon.com/Motivation-Manifesto-Brendon-Burchard/dp/1401948073&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Topics Discussed:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;How to invite happiness into our lives by finding the small things to be grateful for&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;How gratitude is a choice that we make&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Choosing the right vibration that will raise your energy&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Suicide Hotlines:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;USA: 1-800-273-8255&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;USA Crisis Text: 741-741Canada: 1-833-456-4566&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;United Kingdom: 116-123&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Australia: 13-11-14&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;International Suicide Hotlines: &lt;a href= "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_suicide_crisis_lines"&gt; https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_suicide_crisis_lines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with us!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Website: &lt;a href= "https://hopetorecharge.com/"&gt;https://hopetorecharge.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Private Facebook Group: &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;WAYS TO HELP THE PODCAST&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;______________________&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe via iTunes and leave a review.  It costs nothing. &lt;a href= "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845"&gt; https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;—————————————————————————&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Spread the word via social media.   It costs nothing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our website is &lt;a href= "https://hopetorecharge.com/"&gt;https://hopetorecharge.com/&lt;/a&gt; our FB is &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/&lt;/a&gt; and our Instagram is &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe to us on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;iTunes: &lt;a href= "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845"&gt; https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Spotify: &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/show/00AIhRZOxKNOvenz32gGeK"&gt;https://open.spotify.com/show/00AIhRZOxKNOvenz32gGeK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Stitcher: &lt;a href= "https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/heather-parady-2/hope-to-recharge"&gt; https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/heather-parady-2/hope-to-recharge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Youtube: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC_DkYMcco7pSrkKk6wU5p7w"&gt; https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC_DkYMcco7pSrkKk6wU5p7w&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Google: &lt;a href= "https://play.google.com/music/listen?u=0#/ps/Izxlwulashxr3n6trjrxpjpgwce"&gt; https://play.google.com/music/listen?u=0#/ps/Izxlwulashxr3n6trjrxpjpgwce&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>matana@hopetorecharge.com (Hope to Recharge)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b7afd0501a5245cfb2c2c51ae0b10722</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b7afd0501a5245cfb2c2c51ae0b10722/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>How I Built This with Guy Raz : Live From The HIBT Summit: David Neeleman of JetBlue Airways</title><description>Our seventh episode from the 2019 &lt;em&gt;How I Built This &lt;/em&gt;Summit features David Neeleman, the founder of JetBlue Airways. In this live conversation with Guy, David talks about the benefits of having ADD, and why he thinks it's important to talk to the passengers on his airlines. We'll be releasing a few more episodes from the Summit, so keep checking your podcast feed.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (How I Built This with Guy Raz)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1367734530d142b6b354c9ffb5541c6e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1367734530d142b6b354c9ffb5541c6e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 21:01:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Be You Find Happy : E50 GUEST Mort Fortel, founder of Marriage Fitness Bootcamp shares the true secret to a happy marriage</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mort Fertel&lt;/strong&gt; is the creator of Marriage Fitness, a relationship renewal system that’s been used by millions of people in marital crisis. In addition to his success with couples, he pioneered the “&lt;a href="https://marriagemax.com/marriage-tele-boot-camp/"&gt;Lone Ranger Track&lt;/a&gt;,” which offers people with an obstinate spouse a path to reconciliation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People from all over the world schedule &lt;a href="http://www.marriagemax.com/marriage-coaching"&gt;private tele-sessions&lt;/a&gt; with Mort Fertel and seek his counsel by joining the &lt;a href="http://www.marriagemax.com/marriage-tele-boot-camp"&gt;Marriage Fitness Tele-Boot Camp&lt;/a&gt;, the most comprehensive relationship home learning program in the world. Mort Fertel is the author of &lt;a href="http://www.marriagemax.com/audio-program"&gt;Marriage Fitness Audio Learning System&lt;/a&gt; and the host of the &lt;a href="http://mort-fertel-marriage-fitness.libsyn.com/" rel="noopener" target="_blank"&gt;“Fix Your Marriage” podcast&lt;/a&gt;. Over 3 million people have subscribed to his free report “&lt;a href="http://www.marriagemax.com/free-marriage-advice"&gt;7 Secrets to Fixing Your Marriage&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mort Fertel is the subject of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5S2TOixBBSk" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Back from the Brink&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, &lt;/em&gt;a documentary written and directed by Toroes Thomas, which chronicles people in marriage crisis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mort Fertel graduated from the University of Pennsylvania in 1987, was the CEO of an international non-profit organization, and a former marathon runner. He lives with his wife and 5 children (including triplets!) in Baltimore, Maryland.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about Marriage Fitness Bootcamp &lt;a href="https://marriagemax.com/"&gt;https://marriagemax.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlock more happy with Michaela &lt;a href="http://michaelarenee.com/"&gt;http://michaelarenee.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/8b1ab7c/podcast/sponsor/acugkf/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/beyoufindhappy/message</description><author>michaela1123@yahoo.com (Be You Find Happy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3592231c2c9b48e98dc6416b3f79cf79</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3592231c2c9b48e98dc6416b3f79cf79/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Jim Fortin Podcast : E95 - The Power OF Morning Rituals</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Jim Rohn said, “Never start your day until you finish it on paper,” and I say, “Never start your day until you finish it in your mind”.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I kept this episode short and simple and I talk about my morning routine.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Most of us get “swept away” by the world the minute we open our eyes in the morning, and we lose ourselves in the world.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I cannot stress enough the importance of setting your intent every morning and soon I’ll follow up with an episode on the Power of Intention.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Visit the show notes here for more: &lt;a href="https://www.jimfortin.com/95" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.jimfortin.com/95&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Liked the episode? Please &lt;a href="https://www.jimfortin.com/apple"&gt;leave a review&lt;/a&gt; on Apple Podcasts.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; For more transformational content like this daily, connect with me on social media:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://go.jimfortin.com/insta"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://go.jimfortin.com/facebook"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Uplevel your thinking TODAY! Transform your thinking and transform your life with "&lt;a href="http://go.jimfortin.com/mtfpodcast"&gt;The Master Thought Formula&lt;/a&gt;"!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Get instant FREE access &lt;a href= "http://go.jimfortin.com/mtfpodcast"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hey, thank you for listening! If you're the kind of person who likes to help others, then share this with your friends and family. If you found value, they will too. So please share via your social media channels. Also, if you have questions, I'm here to assist.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://go.jimfortin.com/ask"&gt;Click here to send your questions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@jimfortin.com (The Jim Fortin Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a747df19c9674d8d90bb0ca54ffd863f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a747df19c9674d8d90bb0ca54ffd863f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Genuine Joy : 10: Mental Health in Minors</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode Kelsey and Matt interview Morgan Motes, a mental health counselor and behavior analyst that works exclusively with kids.&amp;nbsp; We talk about behavior, fears, anxiety, ADHD and life transitions for children and how to tell when it might be time to talk to someone!&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow Morgan at &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/littlelives.bigfeelings/"&gt;@littlelives.bigfeelings&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>kelsey@littlebitsof.com (Genuine Joy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b86cc31fdee540599ce81c407363c21b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b86cc31fdee540599ce81c407363c21b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Selfie : What To Do When You Feel Like S#@!, Loving an Addict, and Retinol Advice | Selfie Podcast Episode 115</title><description>We’re talking emergency self-care and coping skills for those moments when you are so overwhelmed that your brain is misfiring. BJ answers a listener question about how to help a partner who is struggling with addiction, and Claire gives us her best advice on dipping our toes into the world of retinol. 



In this episode we also talked about:

 	Nuuly Clothing Rental from Anthropologie
 	Graydon “The Putty” Plant-Based Moisturizer 
 	Ellia Pay Attention Essential Oil Blend
 	Weighted Hula Hoop
 	You Feel Like S#@!, A n Interactive Self-Care Guide

Photo by Tim Goedhart on Unsplash</description><author>rageagainsttheminivan@gmail.com (Selfie)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a8764fa2205948f6860cfdd87004b06b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a8764fa2205948f6860cfdd87004b06b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 01:56:11 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>goopfellas  : James Sexton: Marriage from a Divorce Lawyer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;“Relationships are chapters in a long story,” says James Sexton, author of &lt;em&gt;How to Stay in Love. &lt;/em&gt;Today, Sexton teaches us what he’s learned from twenty years as a divorce lawyer and from his own divorce. To make a marriage last: “Never stop trying to close your spouse,” says Sexton. Take preventative measures. Have a plan for how you’re going to argue and be in conflict—before you’re in conflict. Mind your plate. Pay attention. It’s not about being right. It’s about being happy. And if you’re not happy, have the courage to close one chapter and open another with compassion—for your partner and yourself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(For more, see the &lt;a href="https://url.emailprotection.link/?bjE8wTftZfcmuju01p2ThIfpQqtnH14MhSdgHSujYuuTLx1Tb_Nj20EntNjGxHRdMOk_lzqS-bT4RkIbcm-K-yQ~~"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;goopfellas&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; podcast hub.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@goop.com (goopfellas )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9758deada9c3423db890ab8e86b9181a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9758deada9c3423db890ab8e86b9181a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Oprah’s SuperSoul Conversations : Oprah and Michelle Obama: Your Life in Focus</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As a part of WW Presents &amp;ldquo;Oprah&amp;rsquo;s 2020 Vision: Your Life in Focus,&amp;rdquo; Grammy-winner, New York Times best-selling author and former First Lady of the United States Michelle Obama sits down with Oprah in front of a live audience in Brooklyn, New York. Michelle Obama discusses her memoir, &amp;ldquo;Becoming,&amp;rdquo; which held the #1 spot on the New York Times best-seller list for 58 weeks. Michelle Obama talks about what life is like for her and Barack now that they are officially empty nesters.&amp;nbsp; She also discusses the ups and downs of their 28-year marriage, reveals her favorite TV shows and talks about her new-found hobby, yoga.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@own.oprah.com (Oprah’s SuperSoul Conversations)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e246d16ea4df451eb7ca164d8644d009</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e246d16ea4df451eb7ca164d8644d009/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mental Makeover : YouTuber scandals: let's talk about them</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Let's be real: we've all indulged in gossip before. Someone you know (or maybe even don't know) has done something to upset you or someone close to you, and so you talk about it. Maybe with one person, maybe with 10, maybe with more. You feel justified in doing so, because they did something wrong, right? You want that person to be held accountable, so you seek justice in the form of forming a group of people together who know how bad that person is and doesn't want to be friends with them anymore. You've won, because you've proven that you're innocent and they're guilty. Most of the time though, these things blow over. Everyone moves on and becomes friends again. Some feelings might have been hurt, but that's about it. Now, let's consider what happens when a YouTuber has a scandal. Tens of thousands (if not millions) of people join together to actively ruin someone's career. They want them to lose their jobs, their income, their stability, their friends, their support, their sanity and sometimes, when it gets bad enough, their lives. All for what? A bad makeup launch, a misconstrued tweet, befriending the wrong person or a mistake they made when they were a teenager, over 10 years ago? Internet culture has taken a turn for the worse, and someone needs to speak up about it. Let's chat... &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you enjoyed today's episode, please leave a rating and a review and subscribe if you haven't already :) You can also follow my Instagram page &lt;a href="www.instagram.com/mentalmakeoverpodcast"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;! x&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>laurencurtis@outlook.com (Mental Makeover)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">33a51445cadb42fa85aa751bee98ab13</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/33a51445cadb42fa85aa751bee98ab13/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 21:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out : Divine Timing</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you believe everything happens in the best possible timing? Have you ever wondered if you can handle what life has thrown at you? Are you constantly trying to force things to match your timeline instead of hanging back and letting it flow? Learn how to trust in divine timing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Certified life coach, author &amp; award-winning professional life organizer Julie Coraccio shares steps and tips to support you in creating the life you choose, deserve and desire through decluttering your life, end of life planning, mindfulness and how to organize your life. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;About Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Clutter is stuck stagnant energy and prevents you from creating the life you choose, desire and deserve. We discuss clutter in all its forms: energetic, spiritual, emotional, mental &amp; physical, relationships, health, finances and more. We share tips and take action steps for clutter free living and how to organize your life and death with end of life planning. We're thinking outside the box on areas where people might not realize where clutter is blocking them. When we remove clutter from our lives we can discover our passions, lead the extraordinary lives we are all meant to live and share our gifts with the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>julie@reawakenyourbrilliance.com (Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">367761c9fd044968b82f0b4d955e21d1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/367761c9fd044968b82f0b4d955e21d1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Aggressive Life with Brian Tome : Episode 25: Michael Jr.—Stand-Up Comedian</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Everything changed the moment Michael Jr. stopped trying to get laughs from his audience. Equal parts hilarious and insightful, Brian meets his match with this widely successful stand-up comedian, podcaster, and actor. &lt;/div&gt;</description><author>podcasts@crossroads.net (The Aggressive Life with Brian Tome)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">72764f2a1d6c45e7bd82b35d3f1cb3ae</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/72764f2a1d6c45e7bd82b35d3f1cb3ae/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 03:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>RISE podcast : 133: Uncovering and Celebrating History with Brit Barron</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We're in February guys, and that means it's time to brush up on a very important part of our history - Black history! I say our history, because no matter who you are or where you come from, these stories help shape the world you live in today. And lucky for me, I'm joined by my dear friend Beans to talk about the power of the history we tell ourselves, how to broaden your circle online and beyond, and maybe a little bit about that new Taylor Swift documentary? I swear it all comes together in a supportive, totally candid, and celebratory discussion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can follow Beans @britbarron on Instagram, and be sure to say hi to her at a RISE conference all year long in 2020!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Y'all. We are still pinching ourselves about the latest news out of our podcast network - Trent freakin' Shelton has launched a brand new show with the Hollis Company! That's right, Straight Up with Trent Shelton drops new episodes EVERY WEDNESDAY! Trent brings honest, raw, life-changing wisdom straight from his heart to your ears on a weekly basis. His style is so unique, his message so powerful, we just KNOW this is going to be your new must-listen podcast. Subscribe to Straight Up with Trent Shelton on iTunes, Google, Spotify, Stitcher, or wherever you listen to podcasts by &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/trentpod"&gt;clicking this link&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave's first-ever book, Get Out Of Your Own Way, is coming this March! This book is for everyone, and we mean EVERYONE: women who loved Girl Wash Your Face, men who did or didn't read Girl Wash Your Face, personal development skeptics, personal development devotees, anyone and everyone who has a life and knows it could maybe get a little better if they could just get out of their own dang way! The best part is Dave has created some really cool extras, like a FREE e-course, for people who pre-order the book, so get to it! LET'S GOOOOOO! --&amp;gt; &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/gooyowpod"&gt;http://bit.ly/gooyowpod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AAAND, if you are looking to add gratitude + goal-setting in your life then head to our shop to grab your Start Today Journal here-- &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/2UZOglA"&gt;http://bit.ly/2UZOglA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sean@dgitalmedia.com (RISE podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">adc3ea918e2749e7b0c1a810d0b8e3f3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/adc3ea918e2749e7b0c1a810d0b8e3f3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Project Recovery : Breaking down the first 5 steps of the 12-Step Program for addiction recovery</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, Casey Scott and Dr. Matt Woolley are joined by Patrick Williams to talk about the 12-Step Program and what it means for recovering alcoholics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In part one, we dive into the first five steps including:&lt;br&gt;1) We admitted we were powerless over alcohol&amp;mdash;that our lives had become unmanageable.&lt;br&gt;2) Came to believe that a Power greater than ourselves could restore us to sanity.&lt;br&gt;3) Made a decision to turn our will and our lives over to the care of God as we understood Him.&lt;br&gt;4) Made a searching and fearless moral inventory of ourselves.&lt;br&gt;5) Admitted to God, to ourselves, and to another human being the exact nature of our wrongs.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@ksl.com (Project Recovery)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c6457a9d3bc44746902df815e48ccdc9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c6457a9d3bc44746902df815e48ccdc9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 23:10:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Soul Sugar : Dealing With Negative People &amp; Setting Boundaries</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode Carrie gives advice to her listeners about empathic tendencies, dealing with negative people, and setting boundaries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Soul Sugar. I’m your host Carrie Rad! You might know me from my videos on YouTube. I love to chat about all things self care, self love, living our very best lives, and finding our inner magic. Soul Sugar is a community of blooming soul seekers. Like sugar for your soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ CONTACT SOUL SUGAR — ➭ If you are a listener, you can get in touch with us here: soulsugarpodcast@gmail.com ➭ If you are a business, you can get in touch with us here: soulsugarco@gmail.com ➭ Follow Soul Sugar on Instagram @soulsugarco &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/soulsugarco/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/soulsugarco/&lt;/a&gt;FOLLOW CARRIE RAD — ➭ Follow Carrie Rad on Instagram @carrierad &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/carrierad/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/carrierad/&lt;/a&gt;➭ Follow Carrie Rad on YouTube: Carrie Rad &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/CarrieRad/featured"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/user/CarrieRad/featured&lt;/a&gt;⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out Hempfusion here ➭ &lt;a href="https://www.hempfusion.com/"&gt;https://www.hempfusion.com/&lt;/a&gt; USE PROMO CODE SOULSUGAR for 20% off your first order and free shipping!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts43+dfab59c@anchor.fm (Soul Sugar)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">036cbf3569a04bcf9bff5d0f399cc449</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/036cbf3569a04bcf9bff5d0f399cc449/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 20:31:49 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hidden Brain : Passion Isn't Enough</title><description>Many Americans feel an obligation to keep up with political news. But maybe we should be focusing our energies elsewhere. Political scientist Eitan Hersh says there's been a rise in "political hobbyism" in the United States. We treat politics like entertainment, following the latest updates like we follow our favorite sports teams. Instead, he says, we should think of politics as a way to acquire power and persuade our neighbors to back the issues we support.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (Hidden Brain)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4201a591cd344fb0a415a2ccc64e4c7f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4201a591cd344fb0a415a2ccc64e4c7f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 14:23:41 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Shambles Show : 10 Birthday Lessons From My 45th Year: Special Episode</title><description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;The Shambles Show is hosted by Shari Teigman&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Welcome to the Shambles Show where you get a sneak peek into the world of Shari Rambles.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Shari, a coach, creative strategist &amp; change instigator who can't wait to ramble with you on Life, on Love, Entrepreneurship and Living Out Loud in all ways- we know you will find a little (or alot!) of yourself in here.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;You're entering the crazy world of the Inner Workings of what goes on in a Maverick's mind,&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;A blend of soul wisdom, creative spark, feisty know how and an Unapologetic Fiery Passion to Inspire the Mav in You&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;May you start Fires and Forge paths to succeed in Business and In Life&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Today is a wrap up of 10 lessons I learned the hard way this year! No filters at ALL.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt; To learn more about Shari go to &lt;a href= "http://www.shariteigman.com/"&gt;www.shariteigman.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Come join Shari on FB to further the conversation at &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/sharidteigman/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/sharidteigman/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Looking to find your spark again? Come join Shari's monthly membership The Maverick Life Unleashed &lt;a href= "https://shariteigman.kartra.com/page/maverickmembership"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Ready to step up and create change FAST with Shari by your side? Apply to work with Shari 1:1 &lt;a href= "https://sharidteigman.typeform.com/to/LEBLi9"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>shari@shariteigman.com (The Shambles Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4478640ab8f849dd860a00318e9dbdfb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4478640ab8f849dd860a00318e9dbdfb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Unsolicited Advice with Ashley and Taryne : A Gentleman's Perspective ft. Taryne's Brothers: A Valentine's Day Special!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With Valentine's Day right around the corner, love is in the air! Whether you have a hot date set up or you're celebrating with friends, insights into how the opposite sex's mind operates are always valuable. Today we have Taryne's brothers Ryan &amp;amp; Brett on the show to discuss turn-ons, fashion preferences, pick-up lines, &amp;amp; more! If you've ever been confused by the complexities of the male or female mind, this episode is definitely for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To watch our podcast videos on YouTube: http://bit.ly/UAPodcastYouTube &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To send us your questions/stories, email us at: AdviceUnsolicitedPod@gmail.com &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be sure to follow us on Instagram: @UnsolicitedAdvicePod&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@studio71us.com (Unsolicited Advice with Ashley and Taryne)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ff16d5ac41874206a55d48c011ab571b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ff16d5ac41874206a55d48c011ab571b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>What It Takes : Lynn Nottage and Suzan-Lori Parks: Drama Queens</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Two of the most daring and celebrated playwrights working today talk about their lives, their work, and why they love writing for the stage. Both Lynn Nottage and Suzan-Lori Parks have won the Pulitzer Prize for plays that portray the struggles of African-Americans and working class people, but their approaches are quite different. Nottage talks here about the extensive research that grounds her, whether she's writing about Congolese women in wartime or laid-off workers in the Rust Belt. Parks talks about freeing her imagination, and entertaining her wildest ideas as if they were guests at a dinner party.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>whatittakespod@achievement.org (What It Takes)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e6a65ecaab354e6ba6a7f1a38cdc5c43</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e6a65ecaab354e6ba6a7f1a38cdc5c43/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:05:20 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Connected Life : 58: Relating Powerfully to Your Partner's Family</title><description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;In-Laws, whether we love ‘em, hate ‘em, or fall somewhere in between, as long as we’re married, they’re here to stay. We can all become immune to our own family’s deficiencies. Sometimes it takes an outsider to notice the crazy that we spent our entire lives thinking was “normal”.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Join Just and Abi as they pull from their own personal histories of dealing with each others dysfunctional family systems. Listen as they share about the ever changing dynamics that occur when a new person is brought into the mix and how that person is meant to be a gift of an objective eye.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Get ready to learn about practicing boundaries, resetting priorities, the skill of confrontation, and managing the clash of family culture!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>lfa@stumvollconsulting.com (The Connected Life)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3a7f3ecef682448cb7886deefb80a20d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3a7f3ecef682448cb7886deefb80a20d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Papaya Podcast : The One Where We Get Miscelenaeous With Elena Davies</title><description>Elena and Sarah chat about meeting up in Nashville, how their friendship began, mental health in a public platform and why she chooses to show up day after day. Elena Davies is most known for her time as a radio host and Big Brother house guest where all eyes are on you 24/7, and the world is ready to make their opinions known. Between her body, her relationship with a fellow house guest, and even how she shows emotion all up for discussion, it’s been a journey! This episode will be one to make you laugh, and leave you feeling like maybe we really don’t know how to say Saskatchewan.  &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; You can find Elena on Instagram @ElenaDavies, as well as HER podcast @Miscelenaeouspodcast     Shop Biossance at &lt;a href= "https://www.sephora.com/"&gt;Sephora.com&lt;/a&gt;          &lt;p&gt;Use the code PAPAYA at checkout to receive 20% off &lt;a href= "https://order.hismileteeth.com/thebirdspapaya"&gt;HiSmile&lt;/a&gt; today!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Produced by &lt;a href="http://www.dearmedia.com"&gt;Dear Media.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>michelle@dearmedia.com (The Papaya Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">933bcc547a9f4762b541fb504b73b1fd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/933bcc547a9f4762b541fb504b73b1fd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Unshakable Self-Confidence : The Illusion Of Separateness Blocks The Realizaton Of Your True-Self</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The trap of the ego, is believing that there is a "me" that needs to "reconnect" to "IT."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Returning guest Eli Jaxon-Bear discusses that the illusion of 'separateness' is false and can broken at any time, if the ego is willing to surrender to The Source and let it take control.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He also talks about how 'mental knowledge' is an avoidance of true surrender to your own heart.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Listen in now to this week's episode of Unshakable Self-Confidence and  break free from the fixation of the ego as its own separate thing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>billy@livingbeyondyourfears.com (Unshakable Self-Confidence)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f6a29937762f40b8925497090c015749</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f6a29937762f40b8925497090c015749/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Happy Place : Tom Kerridge</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Chef Tom Kerridge works hard and, for a long time, played hard too.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this open and honest conversation with Fearne, one of Britain's finest chefs talks about his process, his addiction to work and the sacrifices he's made along the way.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thanks to the sponsors of this series, Mindful Chef. For 25% off your first 4 boxes, plus a free recipe book from founders Myles &amp; Giles, go to &lt;a href= "mindfulchef.com/HAPPYPLACE"&gt;mindfulchef.com/HAPPYPLACE&lt;/a&gt; or use the code HAPPYPLACE at checkout.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>fearne@findyourhappyplace.co.uk (Happy Place)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6ae56dea94ca4eeba82ecb51ab2a3980</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6ae56dea94ca4eeba82ecb51ab2a3980/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>As a Woman : Episode 056: The Waiting Game</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Join host Dr. Natalie Crawford as she talks about the waiting game. Waiting happens, but it can be hard. How do you not lose yourself in the process? Stop the excuses now.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@nataliecrawfordmd.com (As a Woman)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d2764faf1ea44c5d896aaf8c3ee7d90e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d2764faf1ea44c5d896aaf8c3ee7d90e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Terrible, Thanks For Asking : Listen to This: Tremendous Upside</title><description>&lt;p&gt;What happens when an athlete’s body is in peak condition but the mind is throwing flags? On Tremendous Upside, Women&amp;#39;s Basketball Hall of Famer Chamique Holdsclaw interviews some of the most fascinating stars in sports who, like Holdsclaw herself, have faced real mental health issues. In this episode, Chamique talks with her childhood friend, NBA All-Star Metta World Peace, formerly known as Ron Artest, about anger, meditation and that infamous night in Detroit. Produced by American Public Media.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@americanpublicmedia.org (Terrible, Thanks For Asking)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3fd803ea70694823b70250750d0e7d29</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3fd803ea70694823b70250750d0e7d29/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 14:30:10 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Balance Show : EP 19 - A New Direction | Wine Down &amp; Find Your Balance</title><description>In this episode, Taylor and Chloe are joined by Ali, their new producer, to sit down and discuss the adjustment in content direction of The Balance Show. Join the girls in discussing a wide range of topics - from conspiracy theories to embarrassing biffing stories… all while sipping wine, of course. Grab your glass, this is a fun one! Cheers!&lt;br&gt;The Balance Show will continue to provide informative and relevant content, but it will all come together through and be guided by candid conversation. Free-flowing, lighthearted, uplifting and hopefully, relatable and meaningful.&lt;br&gt;Don’t forget to send in (DM) your “letters” to @thebalanceshow on Instagram about something you may have a question about or want advice on! We’re here to help you Find Your Balance! #DearBalance&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/taychayy/"&gt;@taychayy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/chloe__chamberlain/"&gt;@chloe__chamberlain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/aligay/"&gt;@aligay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/thebalanceshow/"&gt;@thebalanceshow&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/balanceathletica/"&gt;@balanceathletica&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>taylor@balanceathletica.com (The Balance Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3508704b9f464842a4a3e5f0c0cc6a47</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3508704b9f464842a4a3e5f0c0cc6a47/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Motivational Mornings  : 74: Mad Genius</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today we discuss the book Mad Genius by Randy Gage and the experiences he has gained by working with countless entrepreneurs over the years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span id="more-573"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Audible:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ve partnered with Audible, an Amazon company to get you guys a FREE audio of your choice, claim your free audiobook at www.audibletrial.com/motivationalmornings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you enjoyed this podcast please leave a Rating and a Review on iTunes!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@motivationalmornings.co (Motivational Mornings )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">71cc3aa15c764115b96c16db1eab2185</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/71cc3aa15c764115b96c16db1eab2185/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 03:00:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Curious Minds: Innovation in Life and Work : CM 154: Laura Huang On Finding Your Edge</title><description>&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Blog-Post-Laura.png"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;What happens when you actively shape how you're seen, rather than leaving it to chance?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
At some point, many of us have felt overlooked, underestimated, or even ignored in our work. We may have responded by putting our heads down and working that much harder, in the hope that someone would finally recognize our talents and skills.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Yet working harder can leave us feeling frustrated, especially when our efforts fail to change other people's perceptions. Harvard Business School Professor Laura Huang explains, "A lot of times, we think our hard work is going to speak for itself, but often we find that it doesn't. Even when we've proven ourselves and shown the ability to...provide value...we continue to have to guide the perceptions of others."&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Laura is author of the book, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Edge-Turning-Adversity-into-Advantage/dp/0525540814/ref=sr_1_1?crid=5WQP6D0WSK80&amp;amp;keywords=edge+turning+adversity+into+advantage&amp;amp;qid=1580573055&amp;amp;s=books&amp;amp;sprefix=edge+turning+%2Cstripbooks%2C199&amp;amp;sr=1-1" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Edge: Turning Adversity into Advantage&lt;/a&gt;. In this interview, she explains why we need to shape how others see us. She asserts, "People are perceiving and making attributions...all the time. If you realize...somebody's making an incorrect attribution about you, changing that...is...difficult. It's more difficult than if you...direct [it] from the get go."&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Laura has been named one of the &lt;a href="https://poetsandquants.com/2016/04/13/2016-best-40-40-professors-laura-huang-wharton-school/?pq-category=business-school-news" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;40 Best Business School Professors Under the Age of 40&lt;/a&gt;. Her work has been featured in The Financial Times, The Wall Street Journal, Forbes, and Nature.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Episode Links&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/LauraHuangLA?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;@LauraHuangLA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://hbr.org/2019/10/when-its-ok-to-trust-your-gut-on-a-big-decision" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;When Its Okay to Trust Your Gut on a Big Decision&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dave_Dahl_(entrepreneur)" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Dave Dahl of Dave's Killer Bread&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Reinforcements-How-Get-People-Help/dp/1633692353" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Reinforcements: How to Get People to Help You by Heidi Grant&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
If you Liked This Episode, You Might Also Enjoy:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/cm-134-brian-gunia-on-a-fresh-approach-to-negotiation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Brian Gunia on a Fresh Approach to Negotiation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/cm-133-rob-walker-on-the-art-of-noticing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Rob Walker on the Art of Noticing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/cm-109-heidi-grant-on-the-science-of-asking-for-help/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Heidi Grant on the Science of Asking for Help&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/cm-089-daniel-mcginn-on-performing-under-pressure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Dan McGinn Performing Under Pressure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/cm-075-andy-molinsky-on-overcoming-your-fears/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Andy Molinsky on Overcoming Your Fears&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Other Places to Find the Show&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/2nceSDKt4J9mTwomugWT2O" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/curious-minds-innovation-in-life-and-work/id10491...</description><author>gayle@gayleallen.net (Curious Minds: Innovation in Life and Work)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">66fef99af55c4536846a7f267b29b613</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/66fef99af55c4536846a7f267b29b613/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 07:20:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Manifest with Tori DeSimone : You are your Most Important Project</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi guys &amp;amp; welcome back to another ~short~ episode of #ManifestWithToriDeSimone. On today's episode we talk about filling your cup before filling others. Stripping away your roles, who are you at your core? I heard this the other day and had to share. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FaceBook Group: Manifest with Tori DeSimone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IG: @toristerling_&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;YouTube: www.youtube.com/toridesimone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Happy #ManifestMonday&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@studio71us.com (Manifest with Tori DeSimone)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">56fc811319db4ef4ba8ec0c9aaf2d860</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/56fc811319db4ef4ba8ec0c9aaf2d860/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Not The Average Joe Show : Legacy &amp; Kobe</title><description>This week we talk about the power of legacy and the importance of it based on this weeks events.

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/bac5a5c/podcast/sponsor/acugkf/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;

Support this podcast: &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/nottheaveragejoeshow/support" rel="payment"&gt;https://anchor.fm/nottheaveragejoeshow/support&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts43+bac5a5c@anchor.fm (Not The Average Joe Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">eb47217ae8104a45a85c6ff6260f8e33</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/eb47217ae8104a45a85c6ff6260f8e33/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 04:00:38 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dr. Wayne W. Dyer Podcast : What's Your Dharma?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Learn how to follow your dharma and live your purpose today with Dr. Wayne Dyer. Listen in as he talks about increasing your prosperity and finding more meaning in your life simply by changing the way you think. Dr. Wayne Dyer also gives you a preview of his upcoming Maui workshop!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>smorris@hayhouse.com (Dr. Wayne W. Dyer Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f0ac96f5772c4e668d8f18c84d0ce5e2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f0ac96f5772c4e668d8f18c84d0ce5e2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Confession Radio : Unsure In Virginia</title><description>&lt;p&gt;New Episode now!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email us your Confession&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ConfessionRadioNet@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/865379c/podcast/sponsor/acugkf/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts10+865379c@anchor.fm (Confession Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0f65c099d6bb4084963efa102d5f66d8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0f65c099d6bb4084963efa102d5f66d8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 17:45:38 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Greatest Motivational and Inspirational Speeches Ever : Contenders - Motivational Video</title><description>Subscribe: http://bit.ly/211b904
Website: http://www.mateuszm.com

If you like my work feel free to Donate: https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_donations&amp;business=a_miroslaw%40interia%2epl&amp;lc=BM&amp;item_name=Mateusz%20M&amp;no_note=0&amp;currency_code=USD&amp;bn=PP%2dDonationsBF%3abtn_donateCC_LG%2egif%3aNonHostedGuest


Facebook: http://on.fb.me/R8jxxV
Instagram: http://bit.ly/1fjzPrZ
SoundCloud: http://bit.ly/1W0ehad
Twitter: http://bit.ly/1nNEv30

Speakers:
Eric Thomas
Greg Plitt


All copyrights go to their respective owners.</description><author>thisyearweconquer@gmail.com (Greatest Motivational and Inspirational Speeches Ever)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">829e22ca91b14f73adf791783ef1cdcb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/829e22ca91b14f73adf791783ef1cdcb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 14:29:16 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>With That Being Said : It's Always You... Even When It's Them</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode of "With That Being Said", Esther and Erica share about the importance of setting AND communicating your boundaries with others. No relationship is without boundaries, so Esther and Erica discuss how you can communicate your boundaries even when it's difficult, and why they believe boundaries are actually necessary to form meaningful connections.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you enjoy "With That Being Said" and want more of Esther and Erica, check out their Instagram Live Show "Live with E+E" on Tuesday's at 12 PM EST. You can find E+E on both Esther and Erica's Instagrams (linked below).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/estherbmft/" rel="ugc noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Esther's Instagram&lt;/a&gt;: @estherbmft&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/rosewatertherapy/" rel="ugc noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Erica's Instagram&lt;/a&gt;: @rosewatertherapy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/therapyisnotadirtyword/" rel="ugc noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Therapy Is Not A Dirty Word's Instagram&lt;/a&gt;: @therapyisnotadirtyword&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have ideas for future episodes, or comments on the show, feel free to reach out to Esther and/or Erica on Instagram or at podcast@therapyisnotadirtyword.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for listening!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/718c048/podcast/sponsor/acugkf/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;

Support this podcast: &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/WithThatBeingSaid/support" rel="payment"&gt;https://anchor.fm/WithThatBeingSaid/support&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts8+718c048@anchor.fm (With That Being Said)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e278850444e542f59bf8ca462c927aed</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e278850444e542f59bf8ca462c927aed/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Happiness Patterns: a Unique Approach to Life and Love : From No-Orgazm to becoming a Sexpert and Tantrica with Helena Nista</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today we talk with Helena Nista. Author of Udemy's most popular course on Tantra, Sexpert, Sex and Intimacy Coach and Author of "Legendary Lover".&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We had a great and juicy conversation and here are some of the Questions we discussed:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How growing in Poland has affected your sexual profile? &lt;br&gt;Do you think that all the problems come from childhood? The sexual ones?&lt;br&gt;How does the work of a sex coach and a Tantra teacher differ? &lt;br&gt;What common sexual issues do you see in men and women?&lt;br&gt;Why many women struggle to orgasm?&lt;br&gt;How long does it take men to reprogram themselves for whole body orgazm?&lt;br&gt;What is the role of anus for men and women?&lt;br&gt;Does tantra work for gay couples?&lt;br&gt;What guidance can we give young parents to correctly educate their children sexually?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Learn more about Helena's work:&lt;a href="http://bit.ly/37n8Tv6"&gt; http://bit.ly/37n8Tv6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOLLOW US ON INSTAGRAM: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?v=kJmBKF_lqAs&amp;amp;redir_token=u6veBfQmeMbjS0blwPujUAYwAjl8MTU3NjY5NjYwOEAxNTc2NjEwMjA4&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;q=http%3A%2F%2Fbit.ly%2F2MmjY9J"&gt;http://bit.ly/2MmjY9J&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOLLOW US ON YOUTUBE: &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/2RlUcCU"&gt;http://bit.ly/2RlUcCU&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUBSCRIBE TO OUR PODCAST! And listen to more episodes:&lt;br&gt;—Spotify: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?v=kJmBKF_lqAs&amp;amp;redir_token=u6veBfQmeMbjS0blwPujUAYwAjl8MTU3NjY5NjYwOEAxNTc2NjEwMjA4&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fspoti.fi%2F2kepApn"&gt;https://spoti.fi/2kepApn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;—Apple Podcasts: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?v=kJmBKF_lqAs&amp;amp;redir_token=u6veBfQmeMbjS0blwPujUAYwAjl8MTU3NjY5NjYwOEAxNTc2NjEwMjA4&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fapple.co%2F2IrmXIQ"&gt;https://apple.co/2IrmXIQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;—Google Podcasts: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?v=kJmBKF_lqAs&amp;amp;redir_token=u6veBfQmeMbjS0blwPujUAYwAjl8MTU3NjY5NjYwOEAxNTc2NjEwMjA4&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;q=http%3A%2F%2Fbit.ly%2F2lymIUg"&gt;http://bit.ly/2lymIUg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;—iHeart Radio: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?v=kJmBKF_lqAs&amp;amp;redir_token=u6veBfQmeMbjS0blwPujUAYwAjl8MTU3NjY5NjYwOEAxNTc2NjEwMjA4&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fihr.fm%2F2jZ8agc"&gt;https://ihr.fm/2jZ8agc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;—Stitcher: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?v=kJmBKF_lqAs&amp;amp;redir_token=u6veBfQmeMbjS0blwPujUAYwAjl8MTU3NjY5NjYwOEAxNTc2NjEwMjA4&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;q=http%3A%2F%2Fbit.ly%2F2kqyBeK"&gt;http://bit.ly/2kqyBeK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@happinesspatterns.com (Happiness Patterns: a Unique Approach to Life and Love)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3148a5a660d1465987ab6ff693968c5c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3148a5a660d1465987ab6ff693968c5c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Adventures in Happiness with Jessica Ortner : Ep 82 – Finding Clarity in a Hectic World with Yanik Silver</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src='https://tappingsolution.s3.amazonaws.com/adv-podcast/adv-yanik.jpg' width=120&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you in a position where you feel like you are lacking clarity in your life? Maybe you want to make a change, but you’re not exactly sure what the change looks like. Join me, as I talk with my friend, Yanik Silver, creator of the Cosmic Journal and founder of the Maverick1000, and learn how you can follow your Cosmic Alarm Clock and listen to your deepest self.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yanik has developed a charming and insightful journal experience that will help you evolve allowing you to really dig into what will give you joy in life. It may be coming back to the things you once loved in life, reconnecting with your true essence or it may be as simple as incorporating more “play” into your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#8217;ll discuss this unique journaling style, which will help you align your head, your heart and your higher purpose, creating an intention that leaves room for the magic life offers and takes you on the path that you&amp;#8217;re intended to follow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://CosmicJournal.com' target='_blank' rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;img src='https://tappingsolution.s3.amazonaws.com/adv-podcast/CosmicJournal.jpg' style='max-width:100%'&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Yanik:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yanik Silver has been called a Cosmic Catalyst, a Maverick Mischief-maker and a Galactic Goofball. He redefines how business is played in the 21st century at the intersection of evolutionary growth, impact and fun. Yanik is the creator of the Cosmic Journal, author of Evolved Enterprise and the founder of Maverick1000, a global collective of visionary entrepreneurs making a serious difference in the world, without taking themselves too seriously. In fact, it’s not unusual to find him dressed as a lemur, a showgirl or even in matching mermaid tails with Sir Richard Branson. Find out more about Yanik&amp;#8217;s Cosmic Journal by visiting &lt;a href='http://CosmicJournal.com' target='_blank' rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;CosmicJournal.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="inf_infusionsoft_bottom_trigger"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thetappingsolution.com/ep-82-finding-clarity-in-a-hectic-world-with-yanik-silver/"&gt;Ep 82 &amp;#8211; Finding Clarity in a Hectic World with Yanik Silver&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thetappingsolution.com"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>positions@thetappingsolution.com (Adventures in Happiness with Jessica Ortner)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">61b46cfb3ecb4a0c95ba22abba2891ec</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/61b46cfb3ecb4a0c95ba22abba2891ec/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 09:46:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>SelfishBabe SelfishTalk Podcast : (#57) Honoring Our True Beauty Without All The Additions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey SelfishBabe, in this episode I talk about how honoring our true beauty will help you feel more beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To join the SelfishBabe Global VIP Tribe Waitlist click here: &lt;a href="https://www.olanikeeosi.com/selfishbabe-global-vip-waitlist"&gt;https://www.olanikeeosi.com/selfishbabe-global-vip-waitlist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leave me a voice message here: https://anchor.fm/selfishbabe-selfishtalk-podcast&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My company's website is Goddess Detox: &lt;a href="https://goddessdetox.org/"&gt;https://goddessdetox.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href="https://goddessdetox.org/"&gt;https://goddessdetox.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for listening, I love you.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts43+b8cfe3c@anchor.fm (SelfishBabe SelfishTalk Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fb90caccdca04c3b95f1d1a3dc340f67</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fb90caccdca04c3b95f1d1a3dc340f67/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 16:32:49 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>