<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Better days feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My better days episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My Better days feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 06:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>Daily Meditation Podcast : Love Affirmation</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Gain the clarity you need to focus on what matters most.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is part 2   of a 7-part Motivation meditation series, episodes 1697-1703.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Give our new sip and om app a test drive for 1-week free. Receive access to 1,900+ fully guided meditations customized around a weekly theme. Select from 200+ series to fit your mood with a Clarity Journal and a Slow Down Guide customized for each theme. Brand new themes are introduced each week with brand new meditations offered daily. Connect with other meditators on the private Facebook group for app subscribers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a title="2 Week's Free sip and om iOS app" href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/sip-and-om/id1216664612?platform=iphone&amp;preserveScrollPosition=true#platform/iphone"&gt; 2 weeks for access to the iOS version:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/sip-and-om/id1216664612?platform=iphone&amp;preserveScrollPosition=true#platform/iphone&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a title="sip and om Android app" href= "https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sipandom.sipandom"&gt; 2 weeks free access to the Android version:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sipandom.sipandom&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;All meditations are created by Mary Meckley and are her original content. Please request permission to use any of Mary's content by sending an email to Mary@sipandom.com.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Resources: Music by Christopher Lloyd Clarke and Greg Keller.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Support@SipandOm.com (Daily Meditation Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f2c32f06550842c9a8cf5471779ba8ee</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f2c32f06550842c9a8cf5471779ba8ee/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 14:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out : JAN THOUGHT: Who is Stealing Your Joy?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Who are you allowing to occupy space in your heart and head, robbing you of happiness and peace of mind?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Certified life coach, author &amp; award-winning professional life organizer Julie Coraccio shares steps and tips to support you in creating the life you choose, deserve and desire through decluttering your life, mindfulness and how to organize your life.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;About Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Clutter is stuck stagnant energy and prevents you from creating the life you choose, desire and deserve. We discuss clutter in all its forms: energetic, spiritual, emotional, mental &amp; physical, relationships, health, finances and more. We share tips and take action steps for clutter free living and how to organize your life and death with end of life planning. We're thinking outside the box on areas where people might not realize where clutter is blocking them. When we remove clutter from our lives we can discover our passions, lead the extraordinary lives we are all meant to live and share our gifts with the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>julie@reawakenyourbrilliance.com (Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c5b095271e744a36b9098d122fd951dc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c5b095271e744a36b9098d122fd951dc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dr. Wayne W. Dyer Podcast : Recognizing Your Dharma</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We all have a dharma, a reason for being here on this earth. Dr.Wayne Dyer discusses how to recognize our dharma and work towards getting into alignment with what we are supposed to be doing. When you bring yourself into alignment with your dharma and pay attention to the voice inside the right people and situations will show up for you.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>smorris@hayhouse.com (Dr. Wayne W. Dyer Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4eba436cbcf7445abfa6c69285466841</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4eba436cbcf7445abfa6c69285466841/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Adventures in Happiness with Jessica Ortner : Ep 81 – Setting Boundaries Will Set You Free with Nancy Levin</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src='https://tappingsolution.s3.amazonaws.com/adv-podcast/adv-levin.jpg' width='120'&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boundaries can be defined as the limits that we set around what we will or will not do, will or will not tolerate, and will or will not accept.  This is what we’re talking about in today’s episode, which is all about setting Boundaries for ourselves. Our guest today, the fabulous Nancy Levin, brings empowering insight that is relatable on so many levels. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you a people pleaser? Do you bend over backward to make sure that everyone has everything they need, and let your own wants and needs fall by the wayside? How are you willing to step up for yourself? These are just some of the questions we’ll be discussing as we talk about how you can take time and energy back, freed up to inhabit your own lives and create space for what YOU truly desire. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just remember that setting boundaries are between you and YOU…and just having this awareness will help you figure out where you’ve been sacrificing your own needs in life..in your career, your relationships and even your own well-being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.nancylevin.com/newbook' target='_blank' rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;img src='https://tappingsolution.s3.amazonaws.com/adv-podcast/boundaries-book.png' style='max-width:100%'&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Nancy:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Nancy Levin is a master coach and bestselling author of several books including her latest, Setting Boundaries Will Set You Free. Formerly the Event Director at Hay House for over a decade, Nancy now offers in-depth coaching and training programs designed to support clients in making themselves a priority and setting boundaries that stick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="inf_infusionsoft_bottom_trigger"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thetappingsolution.com/ep-81-setting-boundaries-will-set-free/"&gt;Ep 81 &amp;#8211; Setting Boundaries Will Set You Free with Nancy Levin&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thetappingsolution.com"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>positions@thetappingsolution.com (Adventures in Happiness with Jessica Ortner)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a3f1a3262a2c46188764aeff0e03fd09</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a3f1a3262a2c46188764aeff0e03fd09/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 06:33:23 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Sugars : Episodes We Love: Love &amp; Money</title><description>&lt;p&gt;When it comes to love, money is supposed to be no object. But there’s no disentangling love from anything in our lives, and income is no exception. So how do you assess the role money should play in a relationship, and what happens when your desires and means change over time? The Sugars take on 5 letters in this rapid-fire episode. This episode was originally released on July 21st, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@wbur.org (Dear Sugars)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1c5bb7d57d144d75b38e8e480f324a1f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1c5bb7d57d144d75b38e8e480f324a1f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 09:50:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Happy Place : Nadiya Hussain</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Bake Off winner, writer and presenter talks to Fearne about her upbringing, arranged marriage and the realities of being a British celebrity raised with Bangladeshi traditions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>fearne@findyourhappyplace.co.uk (Happy Place)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f3b4296b14604057a98e46ed9a852219</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f3b4296b14604057a98e46ed9a852219/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Unshakable Self-Confidence : How Do You Stop Giving Away Your Personal Power?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Why is it that we give away our personal power? How do we stop?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Brad Warner discusses how nobody has power over you unless you give it away. As well as, how taking personal responsibility for your personal power brings a healthy self-confidence. In addition, he talks about break the grip of the ego and the illusion of who we really are.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>billy@livingbeyondyourfears.com (Unshakable Self-Confidence)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">15ad25eafad04fe4a47fdeda7e270354</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/15ad25eafad04fe4a47fdeda7e270354/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Heal, Survive &amp; Thrive! : How to Spot Healthy Love</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Being in a healthy relationship or having healthy love is something we all dream of having at one point or another, but do we really know what that means or what it looks like? This week, I want to dive into healthy love. I'll give you the best tips for finding a healthy partner as well as talk about what a healthy relationship should look like!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on Private Coaching or Online Coaching please visit www.StephanieLynLifeCoaching.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Subscribe to my YouTube Channel for new videos every Tuesday! www.youtube.com/StephanieLynCoaching&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;All the best!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Stephanie&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ssylvia23@gmail.com (Heal, Survive &amp; Thrive!)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8565d2a981c24282aafadaffa9a77202</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8565d2a981c24282aafadaffa9a77202/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 15:04:49 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Selfie : Creating Space to Feel Your Feelings + Sarah’s Last Episode | Selfie Podcast Episode 111</title><description>Sarah explains her decision to step back as host, and Kristen introduces the new show format and a new co-host. We chat with Sherianna Boyle about the importance of creating space to feel our feelings.



In this episode we talked about:

 	Emotional Detox: 7 Steps to Release Toxicity and Energize Joy
 	Emotional Detox for Anxiety: 7 Steps to Release Anxiety and Energize Joy
 	The Chalet Wrap from Mer-Sea
 	Mantra Mask Hemp CBD Coconut Eye Gels
 	Sarah’s Top Clean Beauty Picks of 2019
 	Aleavia Body Cleanse 

Photo by Cristian Newman on Unsplash</description><author>rageagainsttheminivan@gmail.com (Selfie)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1fd017efbca246dca49bf6ce9c097eb0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1fd017efbca246dca49bf6ce9c097eb0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 23:01:35 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Untangle : Dr. Fred Luskin - Why Holding Grudges is Bad for your Health and How to Forgive for Good</title><description>Dr. Fred Luskin is the Director and Cofounder of the Stanford University Forgiveness Project and the author of several bestselling books including Forgive for Good, a Proven Prescription for Health and Happiness. He dives into what the science tells us about the healing powers and medical benefits of forgiveness. He shares that you don't have to actually forget or even feel good about the ‘incident’ in order to forgive, but we do have to change the story we tell ourselves about the inciting grievance. Dr. Luskin explains how to do this. It’s good stuff for those of us who might hold a grudge or two.</description><author>support@meditationstudioapp.com (Untangle)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fe2d08248ddd4b9c925d5c579938859b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fe2d08248ddd4b9c925d5c579938859b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 15:21:20 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Katie Piper's Extraordinary People : Jason Fox is extraordinary!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Jason Fox served in the&amp;nbsp;Special Forces for 20 years, dealing with many traumatic experiences – but also living for his work. After two decades he was told to leave the military services, due to suffering from PTSD and depression. He has since become a world-renowned TV presenter and author, having presented ‘SAS: Who Dares Wins’ amongst so much more. In this episode he talks about the rigours of working in the military, dealing with PTSD, and life after having his dream job (and all he knew) taken away from him.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>sepodcasts@somethinelse.com (Katie Piper's Extraordinary People)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">040343ae3dd34c23ae2e71713fad5efd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/040343ae3dd34c23ae2e71713fad5efd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 19:00:58 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>