<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Better days feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My better days episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My Better days feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 15:19:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>Think Again – a Big Think Podcast : 227. Roz Chast and Patricia Marx (cartoons, words, ukuleles) – The Beatles stole everything from us</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Thelma and Louise, Ponch and John, Pancho and Lefty, Quixote and Sancho Panza, Marx and Engels, Marx and Chast…history and literature are full of magical buddy stories. Every now and then, for reasons no one can explain, Two people come together and produce something greater, or at least very different, from the sum of their parts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m here today with one such team: the writer-cartoonist duo of &lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/patricia-marx"&gt;Patricia Marx&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/roz-chast"&gt;Roz Chast&lt;/a&gt;. They’re both longtime contributors to the New Yorker and fearsome humorists in their own rights. But together they form a third fearsome thing, a thing which has created books such as Why Don’t You Write My Eulogy Now So I Can Correct it: A Mother’s Suggestions, And their latest: &lt;a href="https://celadonbooks.com/books/you-can-only-yell-at-me-for-one-thing-at-a-time/"&gt;You Can Only Yell At Me For One Thing At A Time: Rules for Couples&lt;/a&gt;. They’re also the enigmatic figures behind yet a fourth thing, the legendary ukulele band Ukelear Meltdown. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;– &lt;a href="http://jasongots.com"&gt;Jason Gots&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jason@bigthink.com (Think Again – a Big Think Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5b7b7d207fad492f9235aa569a86e2e8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5b7b7d207fad492f9235aa569a86e2e8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Daily Meditation Podcast : Improve Your Life</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Reflect on your week to improve your life.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is part 7  of a 7-part Love meditation series, episodes 1697-1703.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Give our new sip and om app a test drive for 1-week free. Receive access to 1,900+ fully guided meditations customized around a weekly theme. Select from 200+ series to fit your mood with a Clarity Journal and a Slow Down Guide customized for each theme. Brand new themes are introduced each week with brand new meditations offered daily. Connect with other meditators on the private Facebook group for app subscribers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a title="2 Week's Free sip and om iOS app" href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/sip-and-om/id1216664612?platform=iphone&amp;preserveScrollPosition=true#platform/iphone"&gt; 2 weeks for access to the iOS version:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/sip-and-om/id1216664612?platform=iphone&amp;preserveScrollPosition=true#platform/iphone&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a title="sip and om Android app" href= "https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sipandom.sipandom"&gt; 2 weeks free access to the Android version:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sipandom.sipandom&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;All meditations are created by Mary Meckley and are her original content. Please request permission to use any of Mary's content by sending an email to Mary@sipandom.com.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Resources: Music by Christopher Lloyd Clarke and Greg Keller.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Support@SipandOm.com (Daily Meditation Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">51c35fe358974b26a9651c8448a54100</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/51c35fe358974b26a9651c8448a54100/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 20:11:54 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Selfie : The Difficult Task of Being Present | Selfie Podcast Episode 112</title><description>Kristen is chatting with our new cohost Roo Powell about the difficulty of being present, and interviews Philip Shephard about the concept of embodiment and radical wholeness. We also introduce BJ Hickman, our new resident therapist who will be taking your questions (ask them here!)



In this episode we talked about:

 	Radical Wholeness: The Embodied Present and the Ordinary Grace of Being 
 	New Self, New World: Recovering Our Senses in the Twenty-First Century
 	TEPP
 	The Strava App
 	GoFiltr Alkaline Water
 	Scrumptious Wicks 
 	The Davinci Wedge
 	Klova Patches

Photo by Brooke Cagle on Unsplash</description><author>rageagainsttheminivan@gmail.com (Selfie)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">de95936c208b47d989e897bdd53303d1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/de95936c208b47d989e897bdd53303d1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 14:35:50 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Sugars : Episodes We Love: Young &amp; Isolated</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Feeling like an outsider is one of the hallmarks of adolescence. But in today’s episode, we hear from two 16-year-olds who have cause to feel especially isolated. One girl is home-schooled and suffers from social anxiety. Another feels disconnected from her best friend, who has suddenly become popular at school. Both letter writers wonder if they’ll ever feel comfortable in their own skin. Shirley Manson, the lead singer of the alternative rock band Garbage, joins the Sugars to discuss her own journey as an outsider. This episode was originally published on July 14th, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@wbur.org (Dear Sugars)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cecb25f1ba0d496bb1c481568eb8ffd5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cecb25f1ba0d496bb1c481568eb8ffd5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 13:26:40 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Expand Your Awareness Podcast 2.0 : EP#91 The Detachment Episode that Made You Like Buddha and changed your life forever</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Reality starts to transform in magical ways once you master the art of detachment. The truth is ...all suffering arises due to attachment and desire. In this powerful episode I'll show you exactly how to free up your energy so that you create the life you prefer in an extremely detached manner. Much Love!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To join The Shift Academy click here: &lt;a href= "http://aarondoughty.com/theshiftacademy" rel= "nofollow"&gt;aarondoughty.com/theshiftacademy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To Calibrate Your Vibration Click here: &lt;a href= "https://whatsmyvibration.com/" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://whatsmyvibration.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For The SHIFT Experience Webinar click here: &lt;a href= "https://events.genndi.com/register/818182175026324307/4e3eb392ee" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://events.genndi.com/register/818182175026324307/4e3eb392ee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href="https://instagram.com/aaron_doughty44/" rel="nofollow"&gt;https://instagram.com/aaron_doughty44/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Youtube: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC48MclMZIY_EaOQwatzCpvw" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC48MclMZIY_EaOQwatzCpvw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe to the Expand Your Awareness Podcast 2.0 with Aaron Doughty&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;iTunes | &lt;a href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-2-0/id1455761627?mt=2" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-2-0/id1455761627?mt=2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Spotify | &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/show/5mVETgyaXMeznNC70v71YO" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://open.spotify.com/show/5mVETgyaXMeznNC70v71YO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Stitcher | &lt;a href= "https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/aaron-doughty/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-20-with-aaron-doughty?refid=stpr" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/aaron-doughty/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-20-with-aaron-doughty?refid=stpr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>adoughty44@yahoo.com (The Expand Your Awareness Podcast 2.0)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2be5167312c542fdb583514b76ca63f7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2be5167312c542fdb583514b76ca63f7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>On Purpose with Jay Shetty : 3 Mistakes We Make Reading Books &amp; 3 Techniques For Reading More and Faster</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Can one person read 365 books in one year?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this episode of On Purpose, Jay Shetty discusses how he read a book a day during a one-year period and shares his 4-S strategy to reading that anyone can use to tackle their reading list.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shetty also shared his insights on the mistakes people make when reading and how to avoid them. The key to reading more and enjoying it isn’t willpower or reading cover to cover. Watch now to learn Jay Shetty’s insights on reading more. Text Jay Shetty 310-997-4177&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to have YOUR best year yet?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join me for my Free Online Workshop: 5 Intentions for a Purpose-Filled Year&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://jayshetty.me/purpose" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://jayshetty.me/purpose&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Word From Our Sponsors:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go to &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://gabi.com/JAY" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gabi.com/JAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; And for a limited time, if they can’t find you savings on your insurance, you’ll get a $10 Amazon gift card.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go to &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://zapier.com/JAY" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zapier.com/JAY &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;for your free 14-day trial.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check your rate in minutes and borrow up to $40,000. That’s &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://lendingclub.com/JAY" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LendingClub.com/JAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go to &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://imperfectfoods.com/JAYSHETTY" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ImperfectFoods.com/JAYSHETTY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; to get $10 OFF your next FOUR orders and enter JAYSHETTY at checkout.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jayshetty@kastmedia.com (On Purpose with Jay Shetty)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f5ab5a1d2f624b7aad14066976d3b1e7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f5ab5a1d2f624b7aad14066976d3b1e7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Habit Based Lifestyle : EP151 Habit Of Being Uncomfortable</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Everybody is committed to their resolutions, but are you truly committed to growth? If you say you are fixated on growth, then you will grow in all areas. If you are committed to growth, then you must prepare yourself to be uncomfortable. &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;There are many difficulties along the path of change. The struggles will test you if you are genuinely committed to the results you want. They will challenge you and put you in an uncomfortable position away from your comfort zone. You will ask yourself if this is what you want. And many times, people will falter and back out. &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Listen and learn how to get used to the habit of being uncomfortable, to grow and harness your true potential.&lt;/p&gt;  -- Are you looking to connect with a group of like-minded habit hacking people? Join my private Facebook group along with 100's of others in my habit-based lifestyle secrets page &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/307809586529906/" rev= "en_rl_none"&gt;https://www.Facebook.Com/groups/307809586529906/&lt;/a&gt; where I'll be dropping daily habits, tips, and tricks every single week.     Want more information on our programs and other ways to get involved check out my website &lt;a href="http://jesseewell.com/" rev= "en_rl_none"&gt;http://jesseewell.com/&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href= "http://www.habitbasedlifestyle.com/"&gt;www.Habitbasedlifestyle.com&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>jesse@habitbasedlifestyle.com (Habit Based Lifestyle)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">60d3223fada14b799a2ff9cb61f05aab</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/60d3223fada14b799a2ff9cb61f05aab/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>THE UPSIDE with Callie and Jeff Dauler : EPISODE 156: FREE STUFF FRIDAY NUMBER ONE</title><description>&lt;p&gt;episode 156 / January 24, 2020&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jdauler@gmail.com (THE UPSIDE with Callie and Jeff Dauler)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">951e83a3f1a94d4482afecd46d40bd69</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/951e83a3f1a94d4482afecd46d40bd69/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Mindset Mentor : 3 Steps to Live Fearlessly</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Fear is the only thing holding you back from the life of your dreams. In this episode, I am going to teach you my 3 keys to getting past your fear so that you can become the person you have always wanted to be, so that you can build the life that you have always wanted to build.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow me on Instagram @RobDialJr &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/robdialjr/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/robdialjr/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Try out Athletic Greens here &lt;a href="http://athleticgreens.com/dial" target="_blank"&gt;http://athleticgreens.com/dial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>robdial0@gmail.com (The Mindset Mentor)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e2c6a639666848d488775d817193a727</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e2c6a639666848d488775d817193a727/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 21:19:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Before Breakfast : Get back on track</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You don't have to give up on a resolution after a setback&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Before Breakfast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c5c04376718b4538aef23b2c663eb433</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c5c04376718b4538aef23b2c663eb433/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Katie Piper's Extraordinary People : Hilary Ineomo-Marcus is extraordinary!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hilary Ineomo-Marcus has been forced to lead a life of uncertainty, fearing deportation at any time over the last four years. He speaks about his time in prison, the pressure it put on him and his family and the anxiety it’s caused. Despite this situation caused by the Home Office, Hilary's incredibly positive outlook, is truly extraordinary.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>sepodcasts@somethinelse.com (Katie Piper's Extraordinary People)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d64342a7996f46368658dc1ce9ce7daa</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d64342a7996f46368658dc1ce9ce7daa/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Therapy Chat : 214: Friend Or Foe? The Brain Cell That Can Be Both - With Donna Jackson Nakazawa</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you to this episode's sponsor, TherapyNotes. Get a 2-month free trial of TherapyNotes by going to &lt;a href="http://www.therapynotes.com/" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;www.TherapyNotes.com&lt;/a&gt; and using the promo code TherapyChat. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;On today's episode host Laura Reagan, LCSW-C speaks to Donna Jackson Nakazawa about her forthcoming book, The Angel and The Assassin: The Tiny Brain Cell That Changed the Course of Medicine. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Donna Jackson Nakazawa is an award-winning journalist and internationally-recognized speaker whose work explores the intersection of neuroscience, immunology, and human emotion. Her mission is to translate emerging science in ways that help those with chronic conditions find healing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;She is the author of six books, including her forthcoming book, The Angel and The Assassin: The Tiny Brain Cell That Changed the Course of Medicine (Random House/Ballantine, January 2020), which illuminates the newly-understood role of microglia – an elusive type of brain cell capable of Jekyll and Hyde behavior. When triggered, microglia can morph into destroyers and take down synapses, causing depression, anxiety, and Alzheimer’s. But under the right circumstances, they can be angelic healers, repairing the brain in ways that can help alleviate symptoms and prevent disease. Hailed as “riveting,” “stunning,” and “visionary,” The Angel and the Assassin elucidates the biological basis behind the mind-body connection and offers us a radically reconceived picture of human health.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Donna’s other books include Childhood Disrupted: How Your Biography Becomes Your Biology, and How You Can Heal (Atria / Simon &amp; Schuster, 2015), The Last Best Cure (Hudson Street Press / Penguin, 2013), The Autoimmune Epidemic (Touchstone / Simon &amp; Schuster, 2009), and Does Anybody Else Look Like Me? A Parent’s Guide to Raising Multicultural Children (Perseus, 2003). Her writing has been published in The Washington Post, Health Affairs, Aeon, More, Parenting, AARP Magazine, Glamour, and elsewhere. She blogs for Psychology Today and HuffPost.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In addition to her work as a science journalist, Donna has been a keynote speaker at numerous universities, conferences and hospitals. Her keynote lectures include the 2019 Care Plus Annual Conference, 2018 Rutgers University Behavioral Health Care Conference, 2018 Golisano Children’s Hospital Annual Pediatric Conference, 2017 Royal Society of Medicine SIRPA Conference on Chronic Pain and Emotion, 2017 Learning and the Brain Conference, 2016 Johns Hopkins Conference on Trauma-Informed Healing, and the 2012 International Congress on Autoimmunity. She has appeared on The Today Show, National Public Radio, NBC News, and ABC News.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Resources&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://donnajacksonnakazawa.com"&gt;https://donnajacksonnakazawa.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leave me a message via Speakpipe by going to &lt;a href= "https://therapychatpodcast.com"&gt;https://therapychatpodcast.com&lt;/a&gt; and clicking on the green Speakpipe button.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thank you for listening to Therapy Chat! Please be sure to &lt;a href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/therapy-chat-psychotherapy-mindfulness-trauma-attachment/id1031099411?mt=2"&gt; go to iTunes&lt;/a&gt; and leave a rating and review, subscribe and download episodes. You can also download the Therapy Chat app on iTunes &lt;a href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/therapy-chat-podcast/id1225704658?mt=8"&gt; by clicking here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Podcast produced by Pete Bailey - &lt;a href= "https://petebailey.net/audio"&gt;https://petebailey.net/audio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>therapychat.podcast@gmail.com (Therapy Chat)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">115bdd29f3be4f34a30a32134abc6d87</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/115bdd29f3be4f34a30a32134abc6d87/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Success Sensei Podcast : What's The Single Best Time Management Principle?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei Podcast Episode 106 and it's The Friday BLITZ ⚡&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would love to hear your views. Please get in touch using any of the channels below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All comments, reviews, subscribes, likes and shares are greatly appreciated. Thank you for all your continued support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Now Twice A Week: Every Wednesday there’s a brand new Success Sensei Blog, Podcast and Vlog. Every Friday we’re bringing you the Friday Blitz – a shorter, sharper, shockier Success Sensei Podcast and Vlog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Roundhouse Rob, The Success Sensei&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robert Devane is a serial entrepreneur and experienced investor as well as a former martial arts multiple World champion and professional MMA fighter with over 20 years of coaching experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more amazing FREE content please visit:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Apple itunes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://itunes.apple.com/ie/podcast/the-success-sensei-podcast/id1448626122?mt=2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Android&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://successsensei.podbean.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei Blog&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;http://www.thesuccesssensei.blogspot.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on YouTube&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCZG1Ly9zBKc5ZZ134dkjeHA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Facebook&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;http://www.facebook.com/thesuccesssensei&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Instagram&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;http://www.instagram.com/thesuccesssensei&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>redevane@yahoo.com (The Success Sensei Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">db3c7b9ea6854d39a104601f082995c3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/db3c7b9ea6854d39a104601f082995c3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 16:15:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Peak Mind with Michael Trainer : MICHAEL TRAINER: RITES OF PASSAGE, MANHOOD, YOUR DIGITAL IDENTITY, PLANT MEDICINE, AND THE OPPORTUNITY OF OUR TIME /w AARON ALEXANDER (ALIGN PODCAST)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For more, subscribe now to the Peak Mind podcast:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/peak-mind-with-michael-trainer/id1454600603&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;http://www.michaeltrainer.biz&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;http://www.peakmind.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>michael@peakmind.org (Peak Mind with Michael Trainer)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cd0bc50424e7492e95604bd4be3f260d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cd0bc50424e7492e95604bd4be3f260d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 12:00:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Inspiration Rising : Hiking My Feelings to Overcome Trauma - Sydney Williams</title><description>&lt;p&gt;When former collegiate athlete and competitive skydiver, &lt;strong&gt;Sydney Williams&lt;/strong&gt;, unexpectedly found herself on the receiving end of a Type 2 diabetes diagnosis, while grappling with unresolved trauma from a decades-old sexual assault, she set out on a mission: turn her pain into power. Two hikes across Catalina Island and 80 miles later, she founded Hiking My Feelings® to help others tap into the mind-body connection and healing power of nature that helped kick her self-limiting beliefs and disease into remission. Having more than 10 years of marketing experience with Fortune 500 companies and emerging brands, Sydney serves up her “truth juice” style of storytelling to break wide open tough conversations with practical, powerful content and experiences. Over the years, she’s been featured on the SXSW stage, as well as in Huffington Post, Psychology Today, US News &amp;amp; World Report, and numerous other publications. Today, she is the author of &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2RihYj5" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hiking My Feelings: Stepping Into the Healing Power of Nature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and travels across the country empowering others to summit their personal mountains on their way to becoming Well Beings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In This Episode, You Will Learn:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;What motivated Sydney to take two long-distance hikes across Catalina Island.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How she shared a decades-old sexual assault and how she found healing.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ways that people are joining Sydney on the journey of hiking their feelings.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Why getting help for traumatic experiences is so important. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;National Sexual Assault Telephone Hotline:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;800.656.HOPE (4673)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rainn.org/" rel="nofollow"&gt;RAINN.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with Sydney:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2RihYj5" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hiking My Feelings: Stepping Into the Healing Power of Nature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hikingmyfeelings.com" rel="nofollow"&gt;HikingMyFeelings.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/hikingmyfeelings" rel="nofollow"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/staceyrobbins" rel="nofollow"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/hikingmyfeelings/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/hikingmyfeelings" rel="nofollow"&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t Miss A Single Episode:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscribe&lt;/strong&gt; on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/inspiration-rising/id1448649388" rel="nofollow"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/music/m/Iqrp5q3bagph2t23malprd3dxvy?t=Launch_Yourself_Today" rel="nofollow"&gt;Google Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/42zIsXzjCibZt49xdCRvB4" rel="nofollow"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href="https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/in-plain-sight/launch-yourself-today" rel="nofollow"&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leave a quick review&lt;/strong&gt; on any of the podcast apps to tell people what you think about the show.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take a screenshot of the podcast&lt;/strong&gt; and post it on Instagram or Instagram Stories. Tag us &lt;a href="http://www.instagram.com/insporising" rel="nofollow"&gt;@insporising&lt;/a&gt;. We’ll repost and give you a shoutout!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Support this podcast at — &lt;a rel='payment' href='https://redcircle.com/inspiration-rising/donations'&gt;https://redcircle.com/inspiration-rising/donations&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>david@insporising.com (Inspiration Rising)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ad0024230916418596030d04270fddc3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ad0024230916418596030d04270fddc3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 08:38:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Happiness Patterns: a Unique Approach to Life and Love : From No-Orgazm to becoming a Sexpert and Tantrica with Helena Nista</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today we talk with Helena Nista. Author of Udemy's most popular course on Tantra, Sexpert, Sex and Intimacy Coach and Author of "Legendary Lover".&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We had a great and juicy conversation and here are some of the Questions we discussed:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How growing in Poland has affected your sexual profile? &lt;br&gt;Do you think that all the problems come from childhood? The sexual ones?&lt;br&gt;How does the work of a sex coach and a Tantra teacher differ? &lt;br&gt;What common sexual issues do you see in men and women?&lt;br&gt;Why many women struggle to orgasm?&lt;br&gt;How long does it take men to reprogram themselves for whole body orgazm?&lt;br&gt;What is the role of anus for men and women?&lt;br&gt;Does tantra work for gay couples?&lt;br&gt;What guidance can we give young parents to correctly educate their children sexually?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Learn more about Helena's work:&lt;a href="http://bit.ly/37n8Tv6"&gt; http://bit.ly/37n8Tv6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOLLOW US ON INSTAGRAM: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?v=kJmBKF_lqAs&amp;amp;redir_token=u6veBfQmeMbjS0blwPujUAYwAjl8MTU3NjY5NjYwOEAxNTc2NjEwMjA4&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;q=http%3A%2F%2Fbit.ly%2F2MmjY9J"&gt;http://bit.ly/2MmjY9J&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOLLOW US ON YOUTUBE: &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/2RlUcCU"&gt;http://bit.ly/2RlUcCU&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUBSCRIBE TO OUR PODCAST! And listen to more episodes:&lt;br&gt;—Spotify: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?v=kJmBKF_lqAs&amp;amp;redir_token=u6veBfQmeMbjS0blwPujUAYwAjl8MTU3NjY5NjYwOEAxNTc2NjEwMjA4&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fspoti.fi%2F2kepApn"&gt;https://spoti.fi/2kepApn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;—Apple Podcasts: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?v=kJmBKF_lqAs&amp;amp;redir_token=u6veBfQmeMbjS0blwPujUAYwAjl8MTU3NjY5NjYwOEAxNTc2NjEwMjA4&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fapple.co%2F2IrmXIQ"&gt;https://apple.co/2IrmXIQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;—Google Podcasts: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?v=kJmBKF_lqAs&amp;amp;redir_token=u6veBfQmeMbjS0blwPujUAYwAjl8MTU3NjY5NjYwOEAxNTc2NjEwMjA4&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;q=http%3A%2F%2Fbit.ly%2F2lymIUg"&gt;http://bit.ly/2lymIUg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;—iHeart Radio: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?v=kJmBKF_lqAs&amp;amp;redir_token=u6veBfQmeMbjS0blwPujUAYwAjl8MTU3NjY5NjYwOEAxNTc2NjEwMjA4&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fihr.fm%2F2jZ8agc"&gt;https://ihr.fm/2jZ8agc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;—Stitcher: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?v=kJmBKF_lqAs&amp;amp;redir_token=u6veBfQmeMbjS0blwPujUAYwAjl8MTU3NjY5NjYwOEAxNTc2NjEwMjA4&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;q=http%3A%2F%2Fbit.ly%2F2kqyBeK"&gt;http://bit.ly/2kqyBeK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@happinesspatterns.com (Happiness Patterns: a Unique Approach to Life and Love)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3148a5a660d1465987ab6ff693968c5c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3148a5a660d1465987ab6ff693968c5c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Enneagram &amp; Coffee : 31. Soul Child Theory</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Sarajane starts the episode by speaking to all the theories surrounding the enneagram and why she refers to them as such. She shares how she sees it all as theory, takes what works for her and encourages us to do the same. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;She then talks about Sandra Maitri's theory of the soul child, which essentially teaches that as children we were the number that we go to in rest and somewhere along the line we received the message that it was not okay to be that way so we developed our dominant type pattern as a response. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Referenced in this episode:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sandramaitri.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;Sandra Maitri&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sarajane-case.mykajabi.com/club-enneagram" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Club Enneagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can connect with Sarajane on IG &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/enneagramandcoffee/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;@enneagramandcofffee&lt;/a&gt; or at &lt;a href= "http://www.enneagramandcoffee.com"&gt;www.enneagramandcoffee.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@enneagramandcoffee.com (Enneagram &amp; Coffee)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a6ac063d40a8486f8eeba419f482e7df</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a6ac063d40a8486f8eeba419f482e7df/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Energy Clearing for Life Force : Energy Clearing for Life Force "Ask Big Asks Visualization to Luxury" Podcast #212</title><description>Energy Clearing for Life Force "Ask Big Asks Visualization to Luxury" Podcast #212&lt;p&gt;In this episode, we are clearing out more of the junk from poverty stuck into our cellular memories; past lives; history; parents values; and so on and so on! This is a meditation to deeply embrace new abundance. It's also going to shift you into seeing beauty around you. Priceless!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>energyclearingforlife@gmail.com (Energy Clearing for Life Force)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8308ad4016734f8996a4ec4f07d13c53</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8308ad4016734f8996a4ec4f07d13c53/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:11:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hope to Recharge : Thanking Ourselves (Attitude of Gratitude)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today I wanted to speak about self gratitude and why we should say “thank you” to ourselves. Now when you first hear that, you may be thinking that it sounds self-centered or egotistical to thank yourself. However on today’s episode of Attitude of Gratitude I want to highlight a few critical reasons why you &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; implement this powerful practice.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Over the weekend I was tempted to not show up on a promise that I made to myself. Sometimes it is easier to break commitments to yourself when we would never do that to someone we care about. When I became aware of what I was doing, I decided to keep the promise I had made and after doing so, I actually took the time to acknowledge what I had done and thanked myself for showing up.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Today I share with you why this practice will change your life and how it lays a foundation for you to become a happier and more well rounded individual. You cannot love others and show up for others until you show that same love towards yourself. Practicing self-love lays a foundation for all the other relationships in your life&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We hope that this episode encourages you to thank yourself and acknowledge the ways you have showed up for yourself. We would love to hear from you! What do you think about this practice? Do you thank yourself? Connect with us in our private Facebook group &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/"&gt;Hope to Recharge&lt;/a&gt; because as always...together is better!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Interested in joining our monthly Mastermind? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Find out more info here! &lt;a href= "http://www.hopetorecharge.com/Mastermind"&gt;www.hopetorecharge.com/Mastermind&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Today's episode of Hope to Recharge is sponsored by &lt;a href= "http://betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge"&gt;https://Betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Betterhelp.com is the world’s leading provider of online therapy. Their mission is to make professional counseling accessible, affordable, and convenient, so anyone who struggles with life’s challenges can get help, anytime, anywhere.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Head to &lt;a href= "https://betterhelp.com/"&gt;https://Betterhelp.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href= "https://betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge"&gt;hopetorecharge&lt;/a&gt; for 10% off your first month of services. IMPORTANT: Be sure to click &lt;a href= "https://betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge"&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt; in order to get the 10% off code&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Topics Discussed:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;The power of showing up for ourselves&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;A personal story on how I used gratitude toward myself&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Practicing self-forgiveness when you do not show up for yourself&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Suicide Hotlines:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;USA: 1-800-273-8255&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;USA Crisis Text: 741-741Canada: 1-833-456-4566&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;United Kingdom: 116-123&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Australia: 13-11-14&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;International Suicide Hotlines: &lt;a href= "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_suicide_crisis_lines"&gt; https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_suicide_crisis_lines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with us!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Website: &lt;a href= "https://hopetorecharge.com/"&gt;https://hopetorecharge.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Private Facebook Group: &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;WAYS TO HELP THE PODCAST&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;______________________&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe via iTunes and leave a review.  It costs nothing. &lt;a href= "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845"&gt; https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;—————————————————————————&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Spread the word via social media.   It costs nothing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our website is &lt;a href= "https://hopetorecharge.com/"&gt;https://hopetorecharge.com/&lt;/a&gt; our FB is &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/&lt;/a&gt; and our Instagram is &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe to us on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;iTunes: &lt;a href= "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845"&gt; https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Spotify: &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/show/00AIhRZOxKNOvenz32gGeK"&gt;https://open.spotify.com/show/00AIhRZOxKNOvenz32gGeK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Stitcher: &lt;a href= "https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/heather-parady-2/hope-to-recharge"&gt; https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/heather-parady-2/hope-to-recharge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Youtube: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC_DkYMcco7pSrkKk6wU5p7w"&gt; https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC_DkYMcco7pSrkKk6wU5p7w&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Google: &lt;a href= "https://play.google.com/music/listen?u=0#/ps/Izxlwulashxr3n6trjrxpjpgwce"&gt; https://play.google.com/music/listen?u=0#/ps/Izxlwulashxr3n6trjrxpjpgwce&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>matana@hopetorecharge.com (Hope to Recharge)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9f21be69a52c4a03baab330eb7f8f4da</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9f21be69a52c4a03baab330eb7f8f4da/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Be You Find Happy : E47 Savannah and Auntie Debra - why change is sometimes a ROYAL pain the arse</title><description>&lt;p&gt;What kind of BRIT (mind you, like 1/4%) would Michaela be if she didn't talk the ROYALS and their choice to step back from the ROYAL family on a podcast called BE YOU FIND HAPPY? In this episode Michaela invites Savannah back for some real life conversations about change, and what walking away from your family means. AND also invites her Aunt Debra, who was born and raised in the UK to help her better understand the monarchy and why Harry staying put is so important to the Royals. Don't miss this episode for good ole fashioned BE YOU FIND HAPPY fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#sussexroyals #reallife #changeisgood #beyou&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.michaelarenee.com/"&gt;Connect with Michaela&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And here's the link on Buzz Feed that Michaela chats about &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/ellievhall/meghan-markle-kate-middleton-double-standards-royal"&gt;https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/ellievhall/meghan-markle-kate-middleton-double-standards-royal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/8b1ab7c/podcast/sponsor/acugkf/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/beyoufindhappy/message</description><author>info@michaelarenee.com (Be You Find Happy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fb5f6646d4ca43619ae4a534d45102f2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fb5f6646d4ca43619ae4a534d45102f2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Jim Fortin Podcast : Ep 89: Your Weaknesses Aren’t Trapping You, Your Indoctrination And Habits Are</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, I talk about why you failed in the past when you’ve tried to change. It has nothing to do with weakness, it simply has to do with knowing how to work with your brain.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I often tell people, "You’re not at the mercy of your circumstances, you’re at the mercy of your interpretations." And, it’s vital that you not personalize your habits and your interpretations because you’re then working against yourself in your quest for change and transformation. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Visit the show notes here for more: &lt;a href="https://www.jimfortin.com/89" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.jimfortin.com/89&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Liked the episode? Please &lt;a href="https://www.jimfortin.com/apple"&gt;leave a review&lt;/a&gt; on Apple Podcasts.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; For more transformational content like this daily, connect with me on social media:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://go.jimfortin.com/insta"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://go.jimfortin.com/facebook"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Uplevel your thinking TODAY! Transform your thinking and transform your life with "&lt;a href="http://go.jimfortin.com/mtfpodcast"&gt;The Master Thought Formula&lt;/a&gt;"!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Get instant FREE access &lt;a href= "http://go.jimfortin.com/mtfpodcast"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hey, thank you for listening! If you're the kind of person who likes to help others, then share this with your friends and family. If you found value, they will too. So please share via your social media channels. Also, if you have questions, I'm here to assist.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://go.jimfortin.com/ask"&gt;Click here to send your questions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@jimfortin.com (The Jim Fortin Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c98f6bc54d764909b40897fb448dd405</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c98f6bc54d764909b40897fb448dd405/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>goopfellas  : When Boys and Men Talk About Sex</title><description>&lt;p&gt;“From the get-go, boys are raised in a more emotionally impoverished landscape than girls,” says Peggy Orenstein, author of &lt;em&gt;Girls and Sex &lt;/em&gt;and her latest, &lt;em&gt;Boys and Sex. &lt;/em&gt;Orenstein’s research on how girls, boys, women, and men view sex, love, porn, the hook-up culture, and modern masculinity is: fascinating. In this episode, she shares from the many conversations she’s had about sex and vulnerability that have changed her own perspective, and certainly ours. How and from where do we learn about intimacy? What might we need to re-learn? Orenstein’s work is impactful whether or not you have children, but if you do, hear out what she has to say about talking with your kids about sex. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(For more, see the &lt;a href="https://url.emailprotection.link/?bjE8wTftZfcmuju01p2ThIfpQqtnH14MhSdgHSujYuuTLx1Tb_Nj20EntNjGxHRdMOk_lzqS-bT4RkIbcm-K-yQ~~"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;goopfellas&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; podcast hub.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@goop.com (goopfellas )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">62487658bbc94451a6d80d30ba352f52</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/62487658bbc94451a6d80d30ba352f52/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Oprah’s SuperSoul Conversations : Oprah and Amy Schumer: Your Life in Focus</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As a part of&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;WW Presents Oprah&amp;rsquo;s 2020 Vision: Your Life in Focus Tour&lt;/em&gt;,&amp;nbsp;Peabody- and Emmy-winning comedian, actress and New York Times best-selling author&amp;nbsp;Amy&amp;nbsp;Schumer&amp;nbsp;sits down with Oprah in front of a live audience in Charlotte, North Carolina.&amp;nbsp;Amy&amp;nbsp;gets personal about her struggles with IVF, explains why she believes all women are warriors and talks about her revealing social media posts.&amp;nbsp; Amy also shares her thoughts on marriage, being authentic and how she learned to love herself. Amy is also a Grammy, Tony and Golden Globe nominee.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@own.oprah.com (Oprah’s SuperSoul Conversations)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">108065cc86734035b82018299db9c36b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/108065cc86734035b82018299db9c36b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mental Makeover : Q&amp;A with The Skin Fairy: pimple popping and pore strips, are they really that bad?</title><description>&lt;div&gt;As many of you will know, I have been seeing Carmen McNamara aka The Skin Fairy for at least 4 or 5 years now. She's helped me tremendously throughout the years, but more so now since going off the contraceptive pill and experiencing hormonal breakouts. I have received so many messages asking if I could interview her and pick her brains, so that's exactly what I'm doing in this episode! I asked you guys what questions you'd like for her to answer, and then I picked the most commonly asked or interesting ones. I hope you enjoy! You can find Carmen on Instagram at @theskinfairy_, @skinfairyclinic and &lt;a href="https://www.skinfairyclinic.com.au/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;www.skinfairyclinic.com.au&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>laurencurtis@outlook.com (Mental Makeover)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">38ca24848fbb4e1eac0c68a669e322d8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/38ca24848fbb4e1eac0c68a669e322d8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Heal, Survive &amp; Thrive! : Understand Your Love Language</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For more information on Private &amp; Group Coaching please visit &lt;a href='https://www.stephanielynlifecoaching.com/services'&gt;https://www.stephanielynlifecoaching.com/services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NEW Course --- 9 Weeks to Emotional Healing - It is Time to Heal and Create a New Life!  &lt;a href='https://www.stephanielynlifecoaching.com/heal-your-emotional-wounds'&gt;https://www.stephanielynlifecoaching.com/heal-your-emotional-wounds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Subscribe to my YouTube Channel for new videos every Tuesday!        &lt;a href='http://www.youtube.com/StephanieLynCoaching'&gt;https://www.youtube.com/stephanielyncoaching&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Thank you all for your love and support!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;All the best!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Stephanie&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ssylvia23@gmail.com (Heal, Survive &amp; Thrive!)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e853265892814e19a47d3d4bda5b1bda</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e853265892814e19a47d3d4bda5b1bda/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 10:43:30 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out : Is This the Hill You Want to Die On?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you focusing on small arguments instead of issues that are of greater concern? Do you find yourself getting caught up in petty arguments on social media? Would you like to have peace of mind instead of constant drama? Learn how to focus on choosing your battles.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Certified life coach, author &amp; award-winning professional life organizer Julie Coraccio shares steps and tips to support you in creating the life you choose, deserve and desire through decluttering your life, mindfulness and how to organize your life.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;About Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Clutter is stuck stagnant energy and prevents you from creating the life you choose, desire and deserve. We discuss clutter in all its forms: energetic, spiritual, emotional, mental &amp; physical, relationships, health, finances and more. We share tips and take action steps for clutter free living and how to organize your life and death with end of life planning. We're thinking outside the box on areas where people might not realize where clutter is blocking them. When we remove clutter from our lives we can discover our passions, lead the extraordinary lives we are all meant to live and share our gifts with the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>julie@reawakenyourbrilliance.com (Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">39ffe5598693461c89f762f8c700fad6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/39ffe5598693461c89f762f8c700fad6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Adventures in Happiness with Jessica Ortner : Ep 82 – Finding Clarity in a Hectic World with Yanik Silver</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src='https://tappingsolution.s3.amazonaws.com/adv-podcast/adv-yanik.jpg' width=120&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you in a position where you feel like you are lacking clarity in your life? Maybe you want to make a change, but you’re not exactly sure what the change looks like. Join me, as I talk with my friend, Yanik Silver, creator of the Cosmic Journal and founder of the Maverick1000, and learn how you can follow your Cosmic Alarm Clock and listen to your deepest self.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yanik has developed a charming and insightful journal experience that will help you evolve allowing you to really dig into what will give you joy in life. It may be coming back to the things you once loved in life, reconnecting with your true essence or it may be as simple as incorporating more “play” into your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#8217;ll discuss this unique journaling style, which will help you align your head, your heart and your higher purpose, creating an intention that leaves room for the magic life offers and takes you on the path that you&amp;#8217;re intended to follow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://CosmicJournal.com' target='_blank' rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;img src='https://tappingsolution.s3.amazonaws.com/adv-podcast/CosmicJournal.jpg' style='max-width:100%'&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Yanik:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yanik Silver has been called a Cosmic Catalyst, a Maverick Mischief-maker and a Galactic Goofball. He redefines how business is played in the 21st century at the intersection of evolutionary growth, impact and fun. Yanik is the creator of the Cosmic Journal, author of Evolved Enterprise and the founder of Maverick1000, a global collective of visionary entrepreneurs making a serious difference in the world, without taking themselves too seriously. In fact, it’s not unusual to find him dressed as a lemur, a showgirl or even in matching mermaid tails with Sir Richard Branson. Find out more about Yanik&amp;#8217;s Cosmic Journal by visiting &lt;a href='http://CosmicJournal.com' target='_blank' rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;CosmicJournal.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="inf_infusionsoft_bottom_trigger"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thetappingsolution.com/ep-82-finding-clarity-in-a-hectic-world-with-yanik-silver/"&gt;Ep 82 &amp;#8211; Finding Clarity in a Hectic World with Yanik Silver&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thetappingsolution.com"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>positions@thetappingsolution.com (Adventures in Happiness with Jessica Ortner)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">61b46cfb3ecb4a0c95ba22abba2891ec</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/61b46cfb3ecb4a0c95ba22abba2891ec/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 09:46:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Aggressive Life with Brian Tome : Episode 22: Mike Fisher—Former NHL Captain</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Mike Fisher is a force of nature. The former captain of the Nashville Predators, avid hunter, and half of a high-profile marriage, gives a rare glimpse into his aggressive life. &lt;/div&gt;</description><author>podcasts@crossroads.net (The Aggressive Life with Brian Tome)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3522938cf48543aca324b1572b89f911</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3522938cf48543aca324b1572b89f911/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 03:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>RISE podcast : 130: How to Stop Caring What Others Think with Ben Horowitz</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today Rachel sits down and geeks out with entrepreneur and venture capitalist Ben Horowitz to talk about tuning out the advice of others in the fearless pursuit of your own personal truth. They also give some really good advice on leadership, including the example of Wartime General vs Peacetime General, and leading a team that's zagging when everyone else in the field is still zigging. You're NOT gonna want to miss this one!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can find Ben Horowitz's books as well as other incredible content &lt;a href="https://a16z.com/author/ben-horowitz/"&gt;at his website&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave's first-ever book, Get Out Of Your Own Way, is coming this March! This book is for everyone, and we mean EVERYONE: women who loved Girl Wash Your Face, men who did or didn't read Girl Wash Your Face, personal development skeptics, personal development devotees, anyone and everyone who has a life and knows it could maybe get a little better if they could just get out of their own dang way! The best part is Dave has created some really cool extras, like a FREE e-course, for people who pre-order the book, so get to it! LET'S GOOOOOO! --&amp;gt; &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/gooyowpod"&gt;http://bit.ly/gooyowpod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AAAND, if you are looking to add gratitude + goal-setting in your life then head to our shop to grab your Start Today Journal here-- &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/2UZOglA"&gt;http://bit.ly/2UZOglA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sean@dgitalmedia.com (RISE podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6596c7404f97406180f41c0c690e63f0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6596c7404f97406180f41c0c690e63f0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Project Recovery : The real dangers of pornography addiction with Jason and Lauren</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In part one of this week's episode of Project Recovery, Casey and Dr. Matt are joined by Lauren and Jason Mauchley to talk about Jason's addiction to pornography and masturbation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We dive into the problem with waiting to have "the talk" until you're married, the issues with miseducating the public on the perils of pornography, and how Jason struggled with his addiction growing up.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@ksl.com (Project Recovery)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6f9b5ca9788343778de2f1a921d095b9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6f9b5ca9788343778de2f1a921d095b9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 23:10:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>SelfishBabe SelfishTalk Podcast : (#57) Honoring Our True Beauty Without All The Additions</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey SelfishBabe, in this episode I talk about how honoring our true beauty will help you feel more beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To join the SelfishBabe Global VIP Tribe Waitlist click here: &lt;a href="https://www.olanikeeosi.com/selfishbabe-global-vip-waitlist"&gt;https://www.olanikeeosi.com/selfishbabe-global-vip-waitlist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leave me a voice message here: https://anchor.fm/selfishbabe-selfishtalk-podcast&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My company's website is Goddess Detox: &lt;a href="https://goddessdetox.org/"&gt;https://goddessdetox.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href="https://goddessdetox.org/"&gt;https://goddessdetox.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for listening, I love you.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts43+b8cfe3c@anchor.fm (SelfishBabe SelfishTalk Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fb90caccdca04c3b95f1d1a3dc340f67</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fb90caccdca04c3b95f1d1a3dc340f67/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 16:32:49 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Untangle : Untangle - Encore - MJ Ryan</title><description>Best selling author and change expert M.J. Ryan shares how to mindfully realize your goals this year. Her book, "Habit Changers", is chock full of ideas on how you can permanently change your negative habits to positive ones to become happier and more successful. She shares simple and actionable strategies to kick-start the new year.</description><author>support@meditationstudioapp.com (Untangle)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e0ce1ef9741a4fa99a1d1d4e8efab46e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e0ce1ef9741a4fa99a1d1d4e8efab46e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 14:56:41 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hidden Brain : The Cassandra Curse</title><description>After a disaster happens, we want to know whether something could have been done to avoid it. Did anyone see this coming? Many times, the answer is yes. So why didn't the warnings lead to action? This week, we revisit a favorite 2018 episode about the psychology of warnings. We visit a smelly Alaskan tunnel, hear about a gory (and fictional) murder plot, and even listen to some &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Os_bSwg02J4"&gt;ABBA&lt;/a&gt;.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (Hidden Brain)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">47975026ed814338a15bafc013d7c816</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/47975026ed814338a15bafc013d7c816/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 13:00:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Curious Minds: Innovation in Life and Work : CM 153: Janelle Shane on How Artificial Intelligence Works</title><description>&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Blog-Post-Janelle.png"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;What happens when you teach an AI to write knock-knock jokes, recipes, and pick-up lines?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
It's a rare week that goes by without someone talking about the power, and the perils, of artificial intelligence. But if you're not an expert in machine learning, how do you separate fact from fiction? That's where Janelle Shane's expertise comes in.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Janelle is the author of the book, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/You-Look-Like-Thing-Love/dp/0316525243/ref=sr_1_1?keywords=janelle+shane&amp;amp;qid=1579538715&amp;amp;s=books&amp;amp;sr=1-1" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;You Look Like a Thing and I Love You: How Artificial Intelligence Works and Why It's Making the World a Weirder Place&lt;/a&gt;. As she describes how an AI learns, she reveals the gap between what researchers strive to do and what's currently possible. Janelle explains, "The AI in science fiction is almost exclusively this kind of human level, general AI, that's really smart, at least as smart as a human, and then the stuff we have in the real world is a lot simpler."&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Janelle runs amusing AI experiments, in order to learn how machine learning works and where its limits begin. She shares stories of what happened when she trained AIs to tell knock-knock jokes, invent new recipes, and write pick-up lines. Along the way, she describes the ups and the downs of working with AIs to solve problems: "The pro is you might get an answer that you didn't expect. The con is also that you might get an answer that you didn't expect."&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Janelle's work has appeared in publications like The New York Times, Slate, The New Yorker, The Atlantic, and many more. In addition, she keeps readers up to date on recent projects and AI hilarity on her website, aiweirdness.com.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The Host&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
You can learn more about Curious Minds Host and Creator, Gayle Allen, and Producer and Editor, Rob Mancabelli, &lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/show-hosts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Episode Links&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://aiweirdness.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;aiweirdness.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.egr.msu.edu/~goodman/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Erik Goodman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0691180148/ref=dbs_a_def_rwt_bibl_vppi_i1" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Artificial You: AI and the Future of Your Mind by Susan Schneider&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://business101.com/an-ai-expert-explains-why-theres-always-a-giraffe-in-artificial-intelligence/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;An AI Expert Explains Why There's Always a Giraffe in Artificial Intelligence&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://openai.com/blog/better-language-models/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;GPT-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://worldin.economist.com/edition/2020/article/17521/artificial-intelligence-predicts-future" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;An Artificial Intelligence Predicts the Future&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Lifecycle-Software-Objects-Ted-Chiang/dp/1596063173" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;On the Life Cycle of Software Objects by Ted Chiang&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
If You Enjoyed this Episode, You Might Also Like:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/cm-128-kartik-hosanagar-on-how-algorithms-shape-our-lives/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Kartik Hosanagar on How Algorithms Shape Our Lives&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/cm-145-susan-schneider-on-the-future-of-your-mind/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Susan Schneider on the Future of Your Mind&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/cm-148-adam-waytz-on-the-power-of-human/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Adam Waytz o...</description><author>gayle@gayleallen.net (Curious Minds: Innovation in Life and Work)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fb9e747870be44a8810381a1b1972b6d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fb9e747870be44a8810381a1b1972b6d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 09:45:36 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Manifest with Tori DeSimone : How my Parents Let me Dropout of College | why college wasn't for me &amp; making a plan</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi guys, happy #ManifestMonday! Today we talk about one of my most asked questions, HOW I DROPPED OUT! College is not for everybody and this is how I did it. I am not encouraging you to drop out because honestly it's not everybody's path, but I knew it was mine &amp;amp; here's how.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FaceBook group: Manifest with Tori DeSimone&lt;br&gt;IG: @toristerling_&lt;br&gt;YouTube: www.youtube.com/toridesimone&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tsdsterling@gmail.com (Manifest with Tori DeSimone)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8ef28fd0a90b4d1f8bd9804d2b21705a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8ef28fd0a90b4d1f8bd9804d2b21705a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Unsolicited Advice with Ashley and Taryne : Fake Friends Showing Fake Love to Me</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Friends can be a source of joy and part of a healthy, happy life. They can also be the source of stress, familial strife, and sadness. Today, we discuss the unparalleled importance of having friends, regardless of how much work those relationships may require. Friends, indeed, make the world go round.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To watch our podcast videos on YouTube: http://bit.ly/UAPodcastYouTube &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To send us your questions/stories, email us at: AdviceUnsolicitedPod@gmail.com &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be sure to follow us on Instagram: @UnsolicitedAdvicePod&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@studio71us.com (Unsolicited Advice with Ashley and Taryne)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8ddf478d7add4a608c6af4f818754de9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8ddf478d7add4a608c6af4f818754de9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Connected Life : Episode 55-Keys to Becoming a Great Friend</title><description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;In order to truly feel alive and happy, friendships are a vital part of life. Unfortunately, there’s not many “how to” guides on friendship. We definitely know when we don’t feel like someone is being a good friend, but do we know what it is to BE a good friend?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;In this episode Abi and Justin break down fundamental keys to becoming a great friend. They share vital ways to love others and help to equip you to be the friend that you always wanted to have. Get ready to redefine the word friendship and find deeper connections than you’ve ever imagined!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>lfa@stumvollconsulting.com (The Connected Life)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">195422aada6943cb9b03d17d164c8b88</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/195422aada6943cb9b03d17d164c8b88/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Papaya Podcast : The One With About Beauty Products With Breaking Beauty Podcast!</title><description>This week we sit down with beauty experts Jill Dunn &amp; Carlene Higgins and chat all things… well, beauty! Long-time magazine beauty editors Jill &amp; Carlene have witnessed so many changes to the beauty industry, so they broke out of their traditional media channels with a podcast about breakthrough products, people and moments in beauty.  Their expertise lends to an interesting and indulgent conversation around beauty products, the industry, founders and entrepreneurs that are breaking ground, and exactly WHAT is on their top shelves.  &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Make sure you tune into their podcast, and follow them @BreakingBeautyPodcast! &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Products mentioned in this episode: &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Carlene’s Top Shelf: Cle De Peau Hydro Softening Lotion Cle De Peau Protecting Fortifying Emulsion Shiseido Benefiance Wrinkle Smoothing Day Cream SPF 23 Beauty Blender Maybelline Urban Dream Cover  Charlotte Tilbury Airbrush Finish Foundation Charlotte Tilbury Cheek To Cheek Charlotte Tilbury Instant Look In A Palette &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Jill’s Top Shelf: Skinceutical C E Ferulic Serum The Ordinary Niacinamide 10% + Zinc 1% It Cosmetics! Your Skin But Better CC Cream SPF 50 Dior DiorShow Mascara L’Oreal Paris Voluminous Lash Paradise Mascara Pixi Glow Tonic Dermalogica Daily Microfoliant Olay Regenerist Microsculpting Cream Neutrogena Hydro Boost    Produced by &lt;a href= "http://www.dearmedia.com"&gt;Dear Media. &lt;/a&gt;</description><author>michelle@dearmedia.com (The Papaya Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">904bad5d3fd444deb0f2ebe1f43007dd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/904bad5d3fd444deb0f2ebe1f43007dd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Unshakable Self-Confidence : Learning To Love Yourself and Your Body Increases Self-Confidence</title><description>&lt;p&gt;How does loving yourself and accepting your body help you avoid toxic relationships?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Denise Wiesner talks about how to change our 'negative narrative' in our heads, how to get unstuck from trauma, as well as how to love yourself, without any guilt or shame.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Listen in now to learn how you can start loving yourself T-O-D-A-Y!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>billy@livingbeyondyourfears.com (Unshakable Self-Confidence)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3097ce51ddf64996b9971d4100eed875</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3097ce51ddf64996b9971d4100eed875/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>How I Built This with Guy Raz : Happy Family Organics: Shazi Visram</title><description>While she was a student at business school, Shazi Visram ran into an old friend-- a new mother of twins.  The friend confided she felt like a bad mom because she had no time to make her kids healthy meals.  That gave Shazi her initial idea: why not make organic pureed baby food, and sell it frozen instead of jarred? People told her she was crazy to take on Gerber, but she convinced dozens of friends and family to invest in Happy Baby. 15 years later, the brand is known as Happy Family Organics and reportedly makes more than $250 million a year. PLUS in our post-script "How You Built That," after learning that many restaurants use gallons of running water to defrost food, Dylan Wolff invented CNSRV WTR-- a recirculating tub that keeps water from going down the drain.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (How I Built This with Guy Raz)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d55a565c684845be9705162d5e5a73a6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d55a565c684845be9705162d5e5a73a6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 21:01:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>As a Woman : Episode 053: Friendship with Dr. Renee Paro</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Join host Dr. Natalie Crawford as she discusses friendship with Dr. Renee Paro. Renee is a pediatric cardiologist who is passionate about health education and self care. Listen to her talk about her path in medicine, her struggle with infertility, and how she decided to launch the Reconciling Medicine Podcast and Dr. Vegetable non-profit with her husband John. Learn what it means to be a good friend, show up, and leave the world a little brighter.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@nataliecrawfordmd.com (As a Woman)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">353a68c776af4f43ad6cd69b182abe3f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/353a68c776af4f43ad6cd69b182abe3f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dr. Wayne W. Dyer Podcast : Recognizing Your Dharma</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We all have a dharma, a reason for being here on this earth. Dr.Wayne Dyer discusses how to recognize our dharma and work towards getting into alignment with what we are supposed to be doing. When you bring yourself into alignment with your dharma and pay attention to the voice inside the right people and situations will show up for you.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>smorris@hayhouse.com (Dr. Wayne W. Dyer Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4eba436cbcf7445abfa6c69285466841</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4eba436cbcf7445abfa6c69285466841/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Not The Average Joe Show : Update!</title><description>A quick update about the show!

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/bac5a5c/podcast/sponsor/acugkf/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;

Support this podcast: &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/nottheaveragejoeshow/support" rel="payment"&gt;https://anchor.fm/nottheaveragejoeshow/support&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts43+bac5a5c@anchor.fm (Not The Average Joe Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3f72b064ce5f4e0eae866a6e70cd8a78</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3f72b064ce5f4e0eae866a6e70cd8a78/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 21:16:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>With That Being Said : Episode with James Bland</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode of "With That Being Said", Esther and Erica talk with special guest James Bland! James is a content creator, film maker, actor, writer, producer, and director. He is the creator, show runner and star of the award winning digital drama, Giants.&amp;nbsp;Esther, Erica and James discuss the stigma around mental health, especially in communities of color, and how James is using his platform in Hollywood to help end it. They also discuss the truth about what mental illness looks like, the importance of being real, and (of course!) Esther and Erica ask James about his experience at the Emmy's!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find James on Instagram and Twitter: @jrbland&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can watch Giants on Issa Rae's Youtube Channel &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLVo7nGot4fPi_1MFfZSLROrc6BhjXSffI"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, or on Cleo TV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find Giants on Instagram and Twitter: @giantstheseries&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or visit Giant's website &lt;a href="https://giantstheseries.com/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you enjoy "With That Being Said" and want more of Esther and Erica, check out their Instagram Live Show "Live with E+E" on Tuesday's at 12 PM EST. You can find E+E on both Esther and Erica's Instagrams (linked below).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/estherbmft/"&gt;Esther's Instagram&lt;/a&gt;: @estherbmft&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/rosewatertherapy/"&gt;Erica's Instagram&lt;/a&gt;: @rosewatertherapy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/therapyisnotadirtyword/"&gt;Therapy Is Not A Dirty Word's Instagram&lt;/a&gt;: @therapyisnotadirtyword&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Links mentioned in the episode:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/therapy-is-not-a-dirty-word-q-a-happy-hour-washington-dc-tickets-79566213687"&gt;Therapy is Not a Dirty Word Happy Hour Events&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/718c048/podcast/sponsor/acugkf/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;

Support this podcast: &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/WithThatBeingSaid/support" rel="payment"&gt;https://anchor.fm/WithThatBeingSaid/support&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts8+718c048@anchor.fm (With That Being Said)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e21e3d1c5c304e658f34f362c155e06e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e21e3d1c5c304e658f34f362c155e06e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Kind World : The "Thank You Project"</title><description>&lt;p&gt;When Writer Nancy Davis Kho decided to spend an entire year writing "thank-you" letters, she didn't expect just how transformative it would be. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@wbur.org (Kind World)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e811343d8dfe4c238c6daa18ebbfb7f3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e811343d8dfe4c238c6daa18ebbfb7f3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 14:43:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>What It Takes : Bill Gates, Sergey Brin and Larry Page: Tech Titans</title><description>&lt;p&gt;These three visionaries changed the way we live our daily lives. You'll hear remarkable archival recordings of each, when they were young successful entrepreneurs, but before history had proven the scale of their impact. Bill Gates, co-founder of Microsoft, describes how, as a teenager, he first envisioned the potential for computers to become fixtures in our homes. Larry Page and Sergey Brin, founders of Google, talk about their accidental discovery of the algorithm that would allow us to search and make sense of the new world-wide web's information explosion. And they all talk about taking risks to embrace the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>whatittakespod@achievement.org (What It Takes)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c1cca616c8f449178bf50ce3f3c77479</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c1cca616c8f449178bf50ce3f3c77479/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:05:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Happy Place : Nadiya Hussain</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Bake Off winner, writer and presenter talks to Fearne about her upbringing, arranged marriage and the realities of being a British celebrity raised with Bangladeshi traditions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>fearne@findyourhappyplace.co.uk (Happy Place)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f3b4296b14604057a98e46ed9a852219</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f3b4296b14604057a98e46ed9a852219/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Shambles Show : What On Earth Is A Mindset Anyway?</title><description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;The Shambles Show is hosted by Shari Teigman&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Welcome to the Shambles Show where you get a sneak peek into the world of Shari Rambles.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Shari, a coach, creative strategist &amp; change instigator who can't wait to ramble with you on Life, on Love, Entrepreneurship and Living Out Loud in all ways- we know you will find a little (or alot!) of yourself in here.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;You're entering the crazy world of the Inner Workings of what goes on in a Maverick's mind,&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;A blend of soul wisdom, creative spark, feisty know how and an Unapologetic Fiery Passion to Inspire the Mav in You&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;May you start Fires and Forge paths to succeed in Business and In Life&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Today I am explaining what exactly a mindset is. So many people walk around each day deciding their mindset is fixed or even worse, owns THEM. Not a chance! Once you realize what a mind is make up of, you can choose differently and see possibility in a different way. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt; To learn more about Shari go to &lt;a href= "http://www.shariteigman.com/"&gt;www.shariteigman.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Come join Shari on FB to further the conversation at &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/sharidteigman/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/sharidteigman/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Looking to find your spark again? Come join Shari's monthly membership The Maverick Life Unleashed &lt;a href= "https://shariteigman.kartra.com/page/maverickmembership"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Ready to step up and create change FAST with Shari by your side? Apply to work with Shari 1:1 &lt;a href= "https://sharidteigman.typeform.com/to/LEBLi9"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>shari@shariteigman.com (The Shambles Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1c0ed241e1f545588fc83fe9dd70f57d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1c0ed241e1f545588fc83fe9dd70f57d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Motivational Mornings  : 73: Range</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today we discuss the book Range by David Epstein and why generalists are becoming more valuable in a specialized world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span id="more-570"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Audible: We’ve partnered with Audible, an Amazon company to get you guys a FREE audio of your choice, claim your free audiobook at www.audibletrial.com/motivationalmornings If you enjoyed this podcast please leave a Rating and a Review on iTunes!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@motivationalmornings.co (Motivational Mornings )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5ef01bfb1c0c475e87ec887a8236d9e0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5ef01bfb1c0c475e87ec887a8236d9e0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 04:38:48 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rise &amp; Conquer Podcast : How to Level Up in 2020: Start doing this mindshift now</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Level up in 2020 with these simple mindset shifts that can transform your year! It’s time to take yourself seriously &amp; start showing up! This episode also includes journal prompts that will help you get clear on what you really want &amp; need from 2020.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;@riseandconquer.podcast&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;www.georgiestevenson.net/podcast&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@georgiestevenson.net (The Rise &amp; Conquer Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">97be32f7c9fa456989fb7b00b2468298</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/97be32f7c9fa456989fb7b00b2468298/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 11:58:30 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Balance Show : EP 18 - Danyele Wilson | Wine Down Wednesday</title><description>Danyele Wilson, AKA “D", has been an elite leader with Balance from the start. D is known for her inspirational AF Instagram stories, impressive strength workout routines, and goofy dancing Balance hauls. We took some time to sit and discuss all types of questions with D over some wine. Tune in for LOL-worthy and lighthearted humor rounded out with meaningful and thought-provoking stories. Cheers to 2020!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have a question or a topic you’d like to hear covered in the show? Reach out to our hosts directly at the accounts below or reach us at podcast@balanceathletica.com.&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/danyelewilson/"&gt;@danyelewilson&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/taychayy/"&gt;@taychayy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/chloe__chamberlain/"&gt;@chloe__chamberlain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/aligay/"&gt;@aligay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/thebalanceshow/"&gt;@thebalanceshow&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/balanceathletica/"&gt;@balanceathletica&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>taylor@balanceathletica.com (The Balance Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">634b37a980d74802b36b27567ba578f2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/634b37a980d74802b36b27567ba578f2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>