<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Better days feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My better days episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My Better days feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 15:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>Think Again – a Big Think Podcast : 233. Terry Gilliam (Jason Plays Favorites #4) – the impossible dream</title><description>&lt;p&gt;[From February through March 22, 2020 (his last day hosting Think Again) Jason will be revisiting favorite past episodes. Jason's new show, starting May 12th, is &lt;a href="https://radiopublic.com/clever-creature-with-jason-gots-6L0pKq"&gt;Clever Creature with Jason Gots&lt;/a&gt;.]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Faith in anything is its own special form of madness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s a challenge to entropy, and entropy takes no challenge lightly. If there’s any better metaphor for this struggle than trying to make a big budget movie with even a shred of integrity, I haven’t found it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the one hand, you’ve got this impossible dream. This faith in the beautiful thing that’s supposed to emerge at at the end of the process. On the other hand, the process is a hellish sausage-making machine of studio bosses, financing, and acts of god like four days of flash flooding in the middle of your big shoot. You might as well be Don Quixote, doing battle with a windmill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What kind of masochist would put themselves through that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My guest today, &lt;a href="http://www.terrygilliamweb.com/"&gt;Terry Gilliam&lt;/a&gt;, is that very masochist. And we should be grateful, because his stomach for the fight has given us movies like THE FISHER KING, BRAZIL, 12 MONKEYS and MONTY PYTHON’s THE LIFE OF BRIAN. And now, almost 30 years after his first, biblically disastrous attempt to make it, &lt;a href="http://www.quixotemovie.com/"&gt;THE MAN WHO KILLED DON QUIXOTE&lt;/a&gt;. Starring Adam Driver and Jonathan Pryce, the movie is as funny, thrilling, and unpretentiously deep as the best of Gilliam’s work. It’s also kind of like one of those Russian matryoshka dolls: a film inside a film inside a film, all of them metaphors for the holy folly of believing in anything at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Man Who Killed Don Quixote is out April 19th in select theaters and on demand video. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Surprise conversation starters in this episode: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bigthink.com/videos/is-time-real-or-is-it-an-illusion"&gt;Michelle Thaller on whether time is real or an illusion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jason@bigthink.com (Think Again – a Big Think Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">665b2376470d4004b6741dc50167b6d5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/665b2376470d4004b6741dc50167b6d5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Daily Meditation Podcast : Get a Better Perspective on Life</title><description>Get more in touch with yourself in this 30-minute bonus episode, including a guided meditation.   This is part 7 of a 7-part Manage Anxiety Meditation Series, episodes 1739-1745.    Give our new sip and om app a test drive for 1-week free. Receive access to 1,900+ fully guided meditations customized around a weekly theme. Select from 300+ series to fit your mood with a Clarity Journal and a Slow Down Guide customized for each theme. Brand new themes are introduced each week with brand new meditations offered daily. Connect with other meditators on the private Facebook group for app subscribers.  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a title="2 Week's Free sip and om iOS app" href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/sip-and-om/id1216664612?platform=iphone&amp;preserveScrollPosition=true#platform/iphone"&gt; 2 weeks for access to the iOS version:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/sip-and-om/id1216664612?platform=iphone&amp;preserveScrollPosition=true#platform/iphone&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a title="sip and om Android app" href= "https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sipandom.sipandom"&gt; 2 weeks free access to the Android version:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sipandom.sipandom&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;All meditations are created by Mary Meckley and are her original content. Please request permission to use any of Mary's content by sending an email to Mary@sipandom.com.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Resources: Music by Christopher Lloyd Clarke and Greg Keller.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Support@SipandOm.com (Daily Meditation Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d9b3df862170471885acf1c8cd25dd62</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d9b3df862170471885acf1c8cd25dd62/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 17:19:25 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Sugars : Dear Sugars Presents: WorkLife With Adam Grant</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Sugars wants to tell you about another great podcast:  WorkLife with Adam Grant from TED.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the episode, Adam Grant speaks with Cheryl Strayed about getting and giving advice about our work lives. Season 3 launches next week, so get ready for ideas about how to procrastinate less, fight burnout, fix broken job interviews, and negotiate better.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@wbur.org (Dear Sugars)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cc457b634e3347d58be3056e503a3ab2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cc457b634e3347d58be3056e503a3ab2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 13:11:58 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Expand Your Awareness Podcast 2.0 : EP#103 Starseeds: A Relatable Explanation that will change your life</title><description>&lt;p&gt;If you normally would't be open to content about Starseeds, you are exactly where you need to be. In this special episode I'll share a relatable starseed explanation so you finally understand more about starseeds. Simply listen to this episode with an open mind, knowing that it has the powerful to expand your consciousness in a powerful way. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For the most amazing sleep of your life, use my 15% discount code "AARON15" to get Organifi Gold Chocolate here:  &lt;a href= "https://www.organifishop.com/pages/aaron15" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://www.organifishop.com/pages/aaron15&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For some of my favorite starseed content: &lt;a href= "https://www.gaia.com/portal/aaron"&gt;https://www.gaia.com/portal/aaron&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href="https://instagram.com/aaron_doughty44/" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://instagram.com/aaron_doughty44/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Youtube: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC48MclMZIY_EaOQwatzCpvw" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC48MclMZIY_EaOQwatzCpvw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe to the Expand Your Awareness Podcast 2.0 with Aaron Doughty&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;iTunes | &lt;a href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-2-0/id1455761627?mt=2" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-2-0/id1455761627?mt=2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Spotify | &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/show/5mVETgyaXMeznNC70v71YO" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://open.spotify.com/show/5mVETgyaXMeznNC70v71YO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Stitcher | &lt;a href= "https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/aaron-doughty/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-20-with-aaron-doughty?refid=stpr" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/aaron-doughty/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-20-with-aaron-doughty?refid=stpr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>adoughty44@yahoo.com (The Expand Your Awareness Podcast 2.0)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0e8326870f8a4d439ec11d5de5563614</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0e8326870f8a4d439ec11d5de5563614/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>On Purpose with Jay Shetty : 11 Lessons For Relationships, Healing &amp; Overcoming Fear</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Jay Shetty is passionate about the four pillars of happiness and fulfillment: self, love, work, and service. Although there’s no “magic pill” for happiness, Shetty believes that laser focus on the health of these four pillars will lead to success and productivity in all areas of your life.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this episode, he tackles 11 questions that have been weighing heavily on his audience. Listen in to hear him give answers to big life questions that so many have.&amp;nbsp; Text Jay Shetty 310-997-4177&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Word From Our Sponsors:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go to &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://kiwico.com/JAY" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;kiwico.com/JAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; to get YOUR FIRST MONTH FREE on select crates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Try Zapier free by going to our special link &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://zapier.com/JAY" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zapier.com/JAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check your rate in minutes and borrow up to $40,000 at &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://lendingclub.com/JAY" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LendingClub.com/JAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take your game to the next level with Beet Elite by going to &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://livehuman.com/onpurpose" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LiveHuman.com/onpurpose&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; and get 20% off your first purchase &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jayshetty@kastmedia.com (On Purpose with Jay Shetty)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">af6e8a1f9d3c4e41aaeeb1c65f33d8cb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/af6e8a1f9d3c4e41aaeeb1c65f33d8cb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Habit Based Lifestyle : EP167 Roommate Verses Teammate</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Have you noticed that you and your partner aren’t connecting anymore? Do you sometimes realize that both of you no longer have the same goals in mind? As years go by in a marriage, there’s a tendency for couples to lose sight of how to make things work. They no longer keep goals and aspirations. Roommates don’t have the determination to work everything out with their companions, while teammates exhaust every plan possible to achieve success. So, today, ask yourself, are you roommates or are you teammates trying to win at life? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt; Are you looking to connect with a group of like-minded habit hacking people? Join my private Facebook group along with 100's of others in my habit-based lifestyle secrets page &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/307809586529906/" rev= "en_rl_none"&gt;https://www.Facebook.Com/groups/307809586529906/&lt;/a&gt; where I'll be dropping daily habits, tips, and tricks every single week.     Want more information on our programs and other ways to get involved check out my website &lt;a href="http://jesseewell.com/" rev= "en_rl_none"&gt;http://jesseewell.com/&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href= "http://www.habitbasedlifestyle.com/"&gt;www.Habitbasedlifestyle.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jesse@habitbasedlifestyle.com (Habit Based Lifestyle)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3e2b08e4f2ec4093973f7329aaebac88</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3e2b08e4f2ec4093973f7329aaebac88/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>THE UPSIDE with Callie and Jeff Dauler : EPISODE 198:  LUCK FAVORS THE BRAVE</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Welcome to episode 198 of THE UPSIDE with Callie and Jeff Dauler(original release date: March 6, 2020)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jeff is grateful for: CBD for dogs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Callie is grateful for: Jeff&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On this episode:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;STOP TAKING YOUR PHONE TO THE BATHROOM. I'll back up my reasoning with science&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also, stop touching your face&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Topic from therapy: bravery is about the journey, not the end result&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So you've left your kids at home by accident...but have you ever taken off on a flight and left them at the airport?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jeff thinks one fact about grocery stores is going to be a game changer for the new Supermarket Sweep&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are makeup apps that will make you look like you have makeup on when you don't- important info. when you're working from home!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FREE STUFF FRIDAY: we give the text-to-win code for a $200 gift card to ABLE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alex Trebeck has an inspirational message for his fans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of our listeners leaves a heartfelt message about her journey of moving forward after tragedy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also, it's daylight savings time. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Want to weigh in on the show topics? Call us and leave a message! 800-434-5454&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here are all of today’s links:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two beauty apps we mentioned on the show today are no longer around. Whomp whomp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why we love our Free Stuff Friday giveaway partner:  &lt;a href="https://www.livefashionable.com/pages/about-able"&gt;https://www.livefashionable.com/pages/about-able&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alex Trebeck's message to fans: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W_5_60PMjjo"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W_5_60PMjjo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dinner A'Fare&lt;/strong&gt;: The easiest way to feed your family! Simply pick your delivery date, receive your meals, and enjoy dinner. Fresh ingredients, delicious recipes, and on your table in 30 minutes or less, with no washing / measuring / chopping. And easy clean up! Kids (and adult picky eaters) love how easy it is to leave some ingredients out, foodies love the sophisticated flavors. First time customers get $30 off using the promo code UPSIDE when checking out at &lt;a href="https://www.dinnerafare.com/"&gt;dinnerafare.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frame It Easy&lt;/strong&gt;: Frame It Easy is a website where you can get easy to order, affordable custom picture frames delivered right to your door. All their frames are made in the USA with high quality materials, and each frame is custom created just for you at any size. They are the most affordable place to buy custom picture frames online. You can even upload your art and have them print and frame it for you! 10% off your order if you visit &lt;a href="http://www.frameiteasy.com/upside"&gt;frameiteasy.com/upside&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hempfusion&lt;/strong&gt;: CBD is all over the place, but if you don't get a quality product, you won't get the results you are expecting. Hempfusion is full-spectrum hemp CBD, with omegas, terpenes, and other supportive nutrients. These aren't just trace amounts, like some other full-spectrum CBD, but enough Terpenes + Omegas in order to deliver maximum health impact. Use UPSIDE at &lt;a href="https://cms.megaphone.fm/organizations/eca2bba6-5eac-11e8-b750-a344e2023286/podcasts/e20e0e4c-ca6d-11e9-9813-f3f84a9cf0ab/episodes/hempfusion.com"&gt;hempfusion.com&lt;/a&gt; for 20% off and free shipping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Butcher Box&lt;/strong&gt;: Take one more thing off your to-do list! Get high-quality meat delivered right to your door every single month. Grass fed beef, free-range chicken, heritage breed pork, and wild-caught salmon are all on the menu! Shipping is free in the continental US, and you get $20 off your first box AND 2 lbs ground beef free in every box for the lifetime of your subscription if you use the promo code UPSIDE when you check out. &lt;a href="http://www.butcherbox.com/upside"&gt;www.ButcherBox.com/upside&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;note: Offer codes and promotions listed in show notes are guaranteed to be valid only on the original release day, unless otherwise indicated. Most partners keep their offers valid for at least 30 days past the release date. Try them anytime … but no promises! Contests will always have an entry period, and that is given when the contest is announced. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;SUBSCRIBES, FOLLOWS, and FIVE-STAR REVIEWS are always appreciated.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ALWAYS GRATEFUL FOR YOU!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jdauler@gmail.com (THE UPSIDE with Callie and Jeff Dauler)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">db5d10d715e04e22b32d746236abbb8a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/db5d10d715e04e22b32d746236abbb8a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Mindset Mentor : Death Brings Urgency to Your Life</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Most people are afraid of death but what if I told you that contemplating death could bring so much urgency in your life that you would never procrastinate again? In this episode, we are going to chat about it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow me on Instagram @RobDialJr  &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/robdialjr/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/robdialjr/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@robdial.com (The Mindset Mentor)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4b85b86af4914ac18835f7a515cc1a84</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4b85b86af4914ac18835f7a515cc1a84/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 21:07:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Before Breakfast : How to ‘have it all’</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Work and life don’t have to be in opposition&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Before Breakfast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7c6afb2cff6445029997380d42aad4bc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7c6afb2cff6445029997380d42aad4bc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Motivational Mornings  : 75: Mindset</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today we discuss the book Mindset by Dr. Carol Dweck and how she uses countless examples directly from her work as a psychologist and researcher to understand the difference between the growth and fixed mind-state.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Audible: We’ve partnered with Audible, an Amazon company to get you guys a FREE audio of your choice, claim your free audiobook at www.audibletrial.com/motivationalmornings&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you enjoyed this podcast please leave a Rating and a Review on iTunes!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@motivationalmornings.co (Motivational Mornings )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">227e859f91c24b02b176a3c659170cea</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/227e859f91c24b02b176a3c659170cea/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 20:02:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Success Sensei Podcast : Do You Even Know Who You Are?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei Podcast&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would love to hear your views. Please get in touch using any of the channels below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All comments, reviews, subscribes, likes and shares are greatly appreciated. Thank you for all your continued support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Now Twice A Week: Every Wednesday there’s a brand new Success Sensei Blog, Podcast and Vlog. Every Friday we’re bringing you the Friday Blitz – a shorter, sharper, shockier Success Sensei Podcast and Vlog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Roundhouse Rob, The Success Sensei&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robert Devane is a serial entrepreneur and experienced investor as well as a former martial arts multiple World champion and professional MMA fighter with over 20 years of coaching experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more amazing FREE content please visit:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Apple itunes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://itunes.apple.com/ie/podcast/the-success-sensei-podcast/id1448626122?mt=2'&gt;https://itunes.apple.com/ie/podcast/the-success-sensei-podcast/id1448626122?mt=2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Android&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://successsensei.podbean.com/'&gt;https://successsensei.podbean.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei Blog&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.thesuccesssensei.blogspot.com/'&gt;http://www.thesuccesssensei.blogspot.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on YouTube&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCZG1Ly9zBKc5ZZ134dkjeHA'&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCZG1Ly9zBKc5ZZ134dkjeHA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Facebook&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.facebook.com/thesuccesssensei'&gt;http://www.facebook.com/thesuccesssensei&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Instagram&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.instagram.com/thesuccesssensei'&gt;http://www.instagram.com/thesuccesssensei&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>redevane@yahoo.com (The Success Sensei Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">189ef4d0231446f3bf10b47ec83ac8cc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/189ef4d0231446f3bf10b47ec83ac8cc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Inspiration Rising : 103: Overcoming Shame and Increasing Your Confidence - Elle Russ</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;#34;Empowered to Rise&amp;#34; by David Trotter - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.insporising.com/book" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;available on Amazon now!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Elle Russ&lt;/strong&gt; is a bestselling author, TV/Film writer, and seasoned life coach. She is the author of &lt;em&gt;Confident As Fu*k&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;The Paleo Thyroid Solution&lt;/em&gt; – a book which has helped thousands of people around the world reclaim their health. Elle is also the show host for NYT’s bestselling author Mark Sisson’s popular Primal Blueprint Podcast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elle began her writing career in sketch comedy and is an alumna of the world-famous comedy theater, The Second City – Chicago, and also a main company alumna of the renowned Acme Comedy Theater in Hollywood, where she wrote and performed in over 100 live sketch comedy and improv shows. Her extensive writing resumé includes TV &amp;amp; Film scripts, books, and articles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In This Episode, You Will Learn:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;How Elle uniquely defines confidence.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How downer people are dragging you down. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ways that shame prevents us from being confidence.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Practical steps to increase your confidence.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with Kate:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.elleruss.com" rel="nofollow"&gt;ElleRuss.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/39slgqM" rel="nofollow"&gt;Confident As Fu*k: How to ditch bad vibes, clean up your past, and cultivate confidence in order to make your dreams a reality&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2PR406O" rel="nofollow"&gt;The Paleo Thyroid Solution: Stop Feeling Fat, Foggy, And Fatigued At The Hands Of Uninformed Doctors - Reclaim Your Health!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://blog.primalblueprint.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Primal Blueprint Podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/elleruss/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/_elleruss" rel="nofollow"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/_elleruss/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.imdb.com/name/nm1224826/" rel="nofollow"&gt;IMDB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t Miss A Single Episode:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscribe&lt;/strong&gt; on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/inspiration-rising/id1448649388" rel="nofollow"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/music/m/Iqrp5q3bagph2t23malprd3dxvy?t=Launch_Yourself_Today" rel="nofollow"&gt;Google Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/42zIsXzjCibZt49xdCRvB4" rel="nofollow"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href="https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/in-plain-sight/launch-yourself-today" rel="nofollow"&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leave a quick review&lt;/strong&gt; on any of the podcast apps to tell people what you think about the show.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take a screenshot of the podcast&lt;/strong&gt; and post it on Instagram or Instagram Stories. Tag us &lt;a href="http://www.instagram.com/insporising" rel="nofollow"&gt;@insporising&lt;/a&gt;. We’ll repost and give you a shoutout!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Support this podcast at — &lt;a rel='payment' href='https://redcircle.com/inspiration-rising/donations'&gt;https://redcircle.com/inspiration-rising/donations&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>david@insporising.com (Inspiration Rising)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1d0a15365b15470892ec7d887b042218</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1d0a15365b15470892ec7d887b042218/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 15:29:18 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rise &amp; Conquer Podcast : Stop EMOTIONAL EATING and kick perfectionism to the curb with Leanne Ward, AKA 'The Fitness Dietician'</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Let’s face it. Gut health, emotional eating and perfectionism are all really hard things to rise and conquer… In this ep, I pick the brains of Leanne Ward AKA The Fitness Dietician, who happens to be an expert on all three!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leanne serves up the facts, with no traces of wishy washy BS, to provide you with actionable steps on getting down to the root cause of your emotional eating and strategies you can implement to keep your gut health in check! She also shares her 10% better philosophy that will help you say CYA to perfectionism forever. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can find Leanne on Instagram &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/the_fitness_dietitian/?hl=en"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AD// Want to elevate and fuel your workouts naturally? Use ‘Riseandconquer’ for 15% off your order at&lt;a href="http://www.nakedharvestsupplements.com/"&gt; www.nakedharvestsupplements.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Naked Harvest Supplements on &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/nakedharvestsupplements/"&gt;instagram &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Georgie on&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/georgiestevenson/"&gt; instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow the&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/riseandconquer.podcast/"&gt; Rise and Conquer Podcast Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@georgiestevenson.net (The Rise &amp; Conquer Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">90f5baa841104887b62c473ea25aaf9e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/90f5baa841104887b62c473ea25aaf9e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 13:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mental Makeover : Why I'm going to therapy</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This is something I never thought I'd be talking about because I never thought I'd be doing it in the first place. For me, therapy always seemed like something you'd only seek out if you were dealing with a lot of physical or emotional trauma, depression or anxiety. I didn't think I had any justifiable reason to go. I was comparing my pain with the pain of others, and mine never seemed significant enough against theirs. In today's episode I talk you through my entire process - from my assumptions about therapy; what led me to start considering it as a valid option; making my first appointment; what the experience was like and best of all, some of the amazing life-changing lessons I've learnt so far. This is a big one for me to share, so if you &lt;i&gt;did&lt;/i&gt; enjoy, I would be super grateful if you could leave a rating or a review - thank you so much :) x&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>laurencurtis@outlook.com (Mental Makeover)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">eaea5c1f2dcb41fd8729d851c14d4e29</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/eaea5c1f2dcb41fd8729d851c14d4e29/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 10:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Heal, Survive &amp; Thrive! : What Happens If You Continue A Relationship With A Narcissist</title><description>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;For more information on Private &amp; Group Coaching please visit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.stephanielynlifecoaching.com/services'&gt;https://www.stephanielynlifecoaching.com/services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Subscribe to my YouTube Channel for new videos every Tuesday!       &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/stephanielyncoaching'&gt;https://www.youtube.com/stephanielyncoaching&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Follow me on Instagram: &lt;a href='https://www.instagram.com/stephanielyncoaching/'&gt;https://www.instagram.com/stephanielyncoaching/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Thank you all for your love and support!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;All the best!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Stephanie&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ssylvia23@gmail.com (Heal, Survive &amp; Thrive!)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">adc59cc80c034485a4c30edc11269159</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/adc59cc80c034485a4c30edc11269159/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Enneagram &amp; Coffee : 36. Bonus Episode: The Enneagram Summit</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this bonus episode Sarajane is breaking down the upcoming Enneagram Summit that will start on March 16, 2020. And it is going to be amazing! She tells us all about the topics that will be covered, the experts that will be sharing their life and expertise, and how you can get tickets! You are not going to want to miss it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get your ticket &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/Enneagram-Summit"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can connect with Sarajane on &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/enneagramandcoffee/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.enneagramandcoffee.com/"&gt;her website&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@enneagramandcoffee.com (Enneagram &amp; Coffee)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f7a237a604084ee7b506ac9edb193c36</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f7a237a604084ee7b506ac9edb193c36/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 07:37:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Energy Clearing for Life Force : Energy Clearing for Life Force "Clearing Blocks for Money, Creativity &amp; Sexual Energy" Podcast #218</title><description>Energy Clearing for Life Force "Clearing Blocks for Money, Creativity &amp; Sexual Energy" Podcast #218&lt;p&gt;In this beautiful second chakra clearing for flow with money, creativity and sexual energy you're going to flow more life force into your world.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>energyclearingforlife@gmail.com (Energy Clearing for Life Force)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ee501bd6140a4623b9050c3e6f91b4c1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ee501bd6140a4623b9050c3e6f91b4c1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hope to Recharge : Practicing Gratitude (Attitude of Gratitude)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As Brene Brown says, &lt;em&gt;“There is never joy without gratitude, they are both connected!”&lt;/em&gt; I have been experiencing that a lot lately. So I decided on today’s episode of Attitude of Gratitude, not to teach about gratitude like we normally do, but instead PRACTICE gratitude with you, the listener. Are you ready?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Whether it was taking the time to listen every week, leave a review, write a comment, or give me a suggestion on how to make this show better. I wouldn’t be here if it wasn’t for you. I wanted to spend a moment and share with you what your support means to me.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thank you for trusting in my voice, my thoughts, my journey, and allowing me to share in my experiences so that I can help others. We are all in this together, I cannot do it alone.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I also am going to share a challenge with you for the next week where you too can practice gratitude and pay it forward. The more kindness and gratitude we can spread in this world the better it will be. Find us over on Facebook, &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/"&gt;Hope to Recharge&lt;/a&gt;, and share with us what you are grateful for this week. As always, together is better.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Today's episode of Hope to Recharge is sponsored by &lt;a href= "http://betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge"&gt;https://Betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Betterhelp.com is the world’s leading provider of online therapy. Their mission is to make professional counseling accessible, affordable, and convenient, so anyone who struggles with life’s challenges can get help, anytime, anywhere.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Head to &lt;a href= "https://betterhelp.com/"&gt;https://Betterhelp.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href= "https://betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge"&gt;hopetorecharge&lt;/a&gt; for 10% off your first month of services. IMPORTANT: Be sure to click &lt;a href= "https://betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge"&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt; in order to get the10% off code&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Interested in joining our monthly Mastermind? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Find out more info here! &lt;a href= "http://www.hopetorecharge.com/Mastermind"&gt;www.hopetorecharge.com/Mastermind&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Topics Discussed:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;A personal thank you to my podcast community&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;The link between gratitude and joy&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Gratitude challenge for your week&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Suicide Hotlines:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;USA: 1-800-273-8255&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;USA Crisis Text: 741-741Canada: 1-833-456-4566&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;United Kingdom: 116-123&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Australia: 13-11-14&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;International Suicide Hotlines: &lt;a href= "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_suicide_crisis_lines"&gt; https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_suicide_crisis_lines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with us!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Website: &lt;a href= "https://hopetorecharge.com/"&gt;https://hopetorecharge.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Private Facebook Group: &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;WAYS TO HELP THE PODCAST&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;______________________&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe via iTunes and leave a review.  It costs nothing. &lt;a href= "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845"&gt; https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;—————————————————————————&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Spread the word via social media.   It costs nothing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our website is &lt;a href= "https://hopetorecharge.com/"&gt;https://hopetorecharge.com/&lt;/a&gt; our FB is &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/&lt;/a&gt; and our Instagram is &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe to us on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;iTunes: &lt;a href= "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845"&gt; https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Spotify: &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/show/00AIhRZOxKNOvenz32gGeK"&gt;https://open.spotify.com/show/00AIhRZOxKNOvenz32gGeK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Stitcher: &lt;a href= "https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/heather-parady-2/hope-to-recharge"&gt; https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/heather-parady-2/hope-to-recharge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Youtube: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC_DkYMcco7pSrkKk6wU5p7w"&gt; https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC_DkYMcco7pSrkKk6wU5p7w&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Google: &lt;a href= "https://play.google.com/music/listen?u=0#/ps/Izxlwulashxr3n6trjrxpjpgwce"&gt; https://play.google.com/music/listen?u=0#/ps/Izxlwulashxr3n6trjrxpjpgwce&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>matana@hopetorecharge.com (Hope to Recharge)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">aec9b63c864143f385897762ca5441d2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/aec9b63c864143f385897762ca5441d2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Celeste The Therapist : S3 EP155: Why knowing your story is so important</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this bonus episode, I discuss the importance of understanding your self and how your past plays a major role in your present. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Relationship Goals: A guide to a health relationship is an 8 step course that will give you the eight key factors that can help you with developing a healthy relationship with your partner. Start the course now: &lt;a href= "https://celeste-s-school-0ed0.thinkific.com/pages/coming_soon" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://celeste-s-school-0ed0.thinkific.com/pages/coming_soon&lt;/a&gt; use coupon code Podcast to receive 10% off the course.  &lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; &lt;li data-leveltext="" data-font="Symbol" data-listid="11" aria-setsize="-1" data-aria-posinset="6" data-aria-level="1"&gt; Want to support the podcast? Don't forget to grab merchandise, Celeste’s guided journal “365 days of intentional living” or Relationship Goals &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li data-leveltext="" data-font="Symbol" data-listid="11" aria-setsize="-1" data-aria-posinset="6" data-aria-level="1"&gt; www.CelesteTheTherapist.com/shop&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul style="font-weight: 400;"&gt; &lt;li data-leveltext="" data-font="Symbol" data-listid="11" aria-setsize="-1" data-aria-posinset="7" data-aria-level="1"&gt; If you have questions or would like to discuss podcast sponsorship, email me at info@CelesteTheTherapist.com &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li data-leveltext="" data-font="Symbol" data-listid="11" aria-setsize="-1" data-aria-posinset="8" data-aria-level="1"&gt; Make sure to follow me on social media: &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li data-leveltext="" data-font="Symbol" data-listid="11" aria-setsize="-1" data-aria-posinset="9" data-aria-level="1"&gt; &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/_ItsMeCeleste_"&gt;Twitter: @_itsmeceleste_ &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li data-leveltext="" data-font="Symbol" data-listid="11" aria-setsize="-1" data-aria-posinset="10" data-aria-level="1"&gt; &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/CelesteTheTherapist/"&gt; Instagram: @CelesteTheTherapist &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li data-leveltext="" data-font="Symbol" data-listid="11" aria-setsize="-1" data-aria-posinset="11" data-aria-level="1"&gt; &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/CelesteViciereLMHC/?ref=bookmarks"&gt; Facebook: @Celeste&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/CelesteViciereLMHC/?ref=bookmarks"&gt;ViciereLMH&lt;/a&gt;C &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li data-leveltext="" data-font="Symbol" data-listid="11" aria-setsize="-1" data-aria-posinset="11" data-aria-level="1"&gt; &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC32_vIk8nm19d_x2fA2-LNQ/featured?view_as=subscriber"&gt;  Youtube: @CelesteViciereLMHC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>info@CelesteTheTherapist.com (Celeste The Therapist)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f7601685cad74ce1ab677813f679f90a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f7601685cad74ce1ab677813f679f90a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 18:48:46 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Peak Mind with Michael Trainer : THE POWER OF COMMITMENT</title><description>&lt;p&gt;http://www.peakmind.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;@michaeltrainer&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>michael@peakmind.org (Peak Mind with Michael Trainer)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4b2f5d81965a4e20b70080fa0c934119</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4b2f5d81965a4e20b70080fa0c934119/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 17:20:20 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Adventures in Happiness with Jessica Ortner : Ep 83 – Be More With Less</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src='https://tappingsolution.s3.amazonaws.com/adv-podcast/adv-carver.jpg' width=120&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our lives can seem so overwhelming, and oftentimes, the more choices that we have, the more stress that we feel. Today we’re going to take a step back and look at how making little changes can give you BIG results! To help us along the way, is my friend Courtney Carver. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you ever ask yourself, “How can I make things easier in my life?, How can I eliminate the feelings of stress and overwhelm?” In today’s world where we’re bombarded with new things every day and change is a constant, feeling stress has become our new normal and how many people feel all day long. We may not even recognize that it is happening, or maybe we just accept it as part of the “life package”.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re going to examine how having “too much” might be unknowingly causing you this anxiety and what steps we can take to get rid of the excess and let go! Courtney’s blog, Be More with Less, shares so many wonderful ideas to simplify your life and her new book, Project 333: The Minimalist Fashion Challenge That Proves Less Really is So Much More, will challenge you to change your closet and your life! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src='https://tappingsolution.s3.amazonaws.com/adv-podcast/project-333-book.png' style='max-width:100%' width=400&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Courtney:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Courtney Carver launched her blog “Be More with Less” in 2010 and is one of the top bloggers in the world on the subject of minimalism. She has been featured in countless articles, podcasts, and interviews on simplicity, and is the creator of the minimalist fashion challenge, Project 333, which is now a book with TarcherPerigee, an imprint of Penguin Random House.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are a few of my favorite blog posts on Be More with Less:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://bemorewithless.com/begin' target='_blank' rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://bemorewithless.com/begin/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href='https://bemorewithless.com/declutter-struggle' target='_blank' rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://bemorewithless.com/declutter-struggle/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href='https://bemorewithless.com/love-again' target='_blank' rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://bemorewithless.com/love-again/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="inf_infusionsoft_bottom_trigger"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thetappingsolution.com/ep-83-less/"&gt;Ep 83 &amp;#8211; Be More With Less&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thetappingsolution.com"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>positions@thetappingsolution.com (Adventures in Happiness with Jessica Ortner)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b656f66941784888bafa77f2e93babd1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b656f66941784888bafa77f2e93babd1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 13:01:56 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Be You Find Happy : E53 GUEST Dr. Glenn Barney cracks the myths behind chiropractic care</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Michaela found Dr. Barney through her own struggles with pain from an injury, she since has referred people who couldn't stand up straight or walk without a cane and they are now back to fully functioning.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Barney’s journey to his chiropractic profession started 25+ years ago while he was studying to become a dentist. He suffered a knee injury while playing sports and was told that knee replacement was his only option. He believed there had to be a more conservative, less invasive approach, and set out to find an alternative. He found it. He worked with a sports medicine chiropractor followed by physical therapy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That was a defining moment for Dr. Barney. He found recovery and rehabilitation for his knee without surgery, and he found a new career path.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Barney’s passion, vast nutritional knowledge, healing approach to wellness, and thorough, higher level of care can change your life’s story too. Just ask his many happy, healthy patients. And yes, 25 years later, Dr. Barney’s knee remains in top shape. He continues to push the limits with athletics and sports – even water skiing on his feet!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To set an appointment with Dr Barney visit &lt;a href="https://www.chirosport.net/index.php"&gt;https://www.chirosport.net/index.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To connect with Michaela visit &lt;a href="http://michaelarenee.com/"&gt;http://michaelarenee.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/8b1ab7c/podcast/sponsor/acugkf/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/beyoufindhappy/message</description><author>michaela1123@yahoo.com (Be You Find Happy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0f4eeeb86a31407e8a74c5b6afe81ba5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0f4eeeb86a31407e8a74c5b6afe81ba5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Jim Fortin Podcast : Ep 101: ENCORE Episode: How Lisa Went From A “Hot Mess” To A High Six-Figure Earner</title><description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re struggling with your relationship or business growth then you’re going to love this episode.in this episode, I talked to Lisa who acknowledged that her life was a “hot mess.” She was not maximizing her business growth, her marriage was very troubled and she was working through many of her own issues. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you feel like you’re swimming upstream in life, your relationship is taxed and your business is not growing - then this episode is for you.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.jimfortin.com/bedohavep/"&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; Sign up for my free Be Do Have training on March 5</description><author>info@jimfortin.com (The Jim Fortin Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3393e45f30d34b379872af0dc75e8698</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3393e45f30d34b379872af0dc75e8698/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Therapy for Black Girls : Session 145: Managing Anxiety About the Coronavirus</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Therapy for Black Girls Podcast is a weekly conversation with Dr. Joy Harden Bradford, a Licensed Psychologist in Atlanta, Georgia, about all things mental health, personal development, and all the small decisions we can make to become the best possible version of ourselves.&lt;/p&gt; In this week's episode I'm sharing 7 tips to help manage your anxiety related to the coronavirus.     If you're looking for a therapist in your area, check out the directory at &lt;a href= "https://www.therapyforblackgirls.com/directory" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.therapyforblackgirls.com/directory&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1583384135743000&amp;usg=AFQjCNGRyQBka8Z-e3bb3KdfhuaSeItvXA"&gt;https://www.therapyforblackgirls.com/directory&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;p&gt;Don't forget to grab a t-shirt, sweatshirt, mug, our breakup workbook, or a copy of our guided affirmation track at &lt;a href= "http://therapyforblackgirls.com/shop" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=http://therapyforblackgirls.com/shop&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1583384135743000&amp;usg=AFQjCNGPI7m3SBPZeEXvjX1XviAVHP9hlw"&gt; therapyforblackgirls.com/shop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To take the concepts from the podcast to the next level in a community of supportive sisters, join us in &lt;a href= "https://therapy-for-black-girls.mn.co/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://therapy-for-black-girls.mn.co/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1583384135743000&amp;usg=AFQjCNFJ_Pkv2hUrUiPc6eMgzAvWMuvVDA"&gt; The Yellow Couch Collective&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you have questions or would like to discuss podcast sponsorship, email us at &lt;a href= "mailto:podcast@therapyforblackgirls.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;podcast@therapyforblackgirls.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The hashtag for the podcast is #TBGinSession.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Make sure to follow us on social media:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Twitter: &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/therapy4bgirls" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.twitter.com/therapy4bgirls&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1583384135743000&amp;usg=AFQjCNF2LbRYFFwnVb5WItDI-1jBNdBEWQ"&gt;@therapy4bgirls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href= "http://www.instagram.com/therapyforblackgirls" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.instagram.com/therapyforblackgirls&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1583384135743000&amp;usg=AFQjCNH_-5bLIoqdJFWJMwq0CQ-3bWrwEA"&gt;@therapyforblackgirls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Facebook: &lt;a href= "http://www.facebook.com/therapyforblackgirls" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.facebook.com/therapyforblackgirls&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1583384135743000&amp;usg=AFQjCNHxpV0ImWiRhH9R4fE1SBIq_-77Cg"&gt;@therapyforblackgirls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@therapyforblackgirls.com (Therapy for Black Girls)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">15133b010af442d3bbed6e96e51b8a44</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/15133b010af442d3bbed6e96e51b8a44/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Oprah’s SuperSoul Conversations : Oprah and Jennifer Lopez: Your Life in Focus</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As a part of&amp;nbsp;WW&amp;nbsp;Presents &amp;ldquo;Oprah&amp;rsquo;s 2020 Vision: Your Life in Focus Tour,&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;Grammy -, Golden Globe- and Screen Actors Guild Award-nominee Jennifer Lopez sits down with Oprah in front of a live audience in Los Angeles. A business mogul and four-time platinum recording artist, Jennifer opens up about motherhood, sharing the Super Bowl stage with her daughter and why she said yes to fianc&amp;eacute;, former MLB All-Star Alex Rodriguez. She also shares her thoughts on not receiving an Oscar nomination for&amp;nbsp;her role in &lt;em&gt;Hustlers&lt;/em&gt;, reviving the iconic green Versace dress 20&amp;nbsp;years after first wearing it and&amp;nbsp;redefining what it means to be 50.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@own.oprah.com (Oprah’s SuperSoul Conversations)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">36a7c32f03cc49d68f48a361e33ec7e2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/36a7c32f03cc49d68f48a361e33ec7e2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Selfie : Overcoming PTSD and a Therapist’s Advice on Anxiety | Selfie Podcast Episode 118</title><description>Roo and Kristen are both dealing with PTSD and talk about how it has affected their lives. BJ addresses the number one mental health topic in our community: anxiety. And Claire offers her best recommendations for moisturizing body oil.

In this episode we also talked about: 

 	Fab Slabs Anti Bacterial Cutting Boards
 	CLEARstem VITAMINscrub Daily Exfoliation
 	TikTok App
 	Better Than Before by Gretchen Rubin
 	Honest Company Body Oil
 	All Good Organic Coconut Oil Skin Food w/Lavender Essential Oil
 	Earth Love Glowing Places Body Oil
 	SheaMoisture Coconut &amp; Hibiscus Bath, Body &amp; Massage Oil

CBD has many benefit, and we are big proponents. But not all CBD is created equal. Unlike other CBD brands, who offer just CBD, Hempfusion is CBD plus omegas plus terpenes plus other natural ingredients to help you feel 100%. HempFusion’s specific blend of natural ingredients help with stress, sleep, and energy, and it can be shipped anywhere in the US.  Use the promo code SELFIE for 20% off of your first order and free shipping at hempfusion.com.

 

Photo by Freshh Connection on Unsplash</description><author>rageagainsttheminivan@gmail.com (Selfie)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">efd5737236fd4e8398b0972d847c8f90</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/efd5737236fd4e8398b0972d847c8f90/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 21:30:11 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Untangle : Ariel Garten - Guided Exercise - Kill the Inner Critic</title><description>Here's a practical technique to get rid of that annoying voice in your head that's undermining you. Untangle's host Ariel Garten guides a short practice that helps you identify the inner critic, push back, and banish that critic from your brain. It works amazingly well and can be used any time that little creep shows up!</description><author>support@meditationstudioapp.com (Untangle)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c00964cc4be643b9b7cea9e623b64ba7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c00964cc4be643b9b7cea9e623b64ba7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 13:02:48 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out : How to Be 50 &amp; Fabulous At Any Age</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you really mean what you say? Are you able to have good boundaries? What is an acceptable answer to any question or request?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Learn some life lessons that you can apply at any age.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To learn how Julie can support you: &lt;a href= "https://reawakenyourbrilliance.com/"&gt;https://reawakenyourbrilliance.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Certified life coach, author &amp; award-winning professional life organizer Julie Coraccio shares steps and tips to support you in creating the life you choose, deserve and desire through decluttering your life, end of life planning, mindfulness and how to organize your life. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;About Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Clutter is stuck stagnant energy and prevents you from creating the life you choose, desire and deserve. We discuss clutter in all its forms: energetic, spiritual, emotional, mental &amp; physical, relationships, health, finances and more. We share tips and take action steps for clutter free living and how to organize your life and death with end of life planning. We're thinking outside the box on areas where people might not realize where clutter is blocking them. When we remove clutter from our lives we can discover our passions, lead the extraordinary lives we are all meant to live and share our gifts with the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>julie@reawakenyourbrilliance.com (Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7372ea86d74f4d9c87d2a202a9f116f4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7372ea86d74f4d9c87d2a202a9f116f4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Aggressive Life with Brian Tome : Episode 28: Britney Ruby Miller—President Jeff Ruby Culinary Entertainment</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Starting as a hostess in high school, Britney Ruby Miller worked her way up the ladder into the corner office. As President of Jeff Ruby Culinary Entertainment, she leads over 700 employees, at seven restaurants, spread across three states. She's a driven leader who's passionate about foster care, blowing customers away, and blazing new trails into the future... and she schools Brian on why it's so hard to get french fries right. &lt;/div&gt;</description><author>podcasts@crossroads.net (The Aggressive Life with Brian Tome)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">184048fb5c0f45278812b788cff0281b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/184048fb5c0f45278812b788cff0281b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 03:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>RISE podcast : 136: Rachel Hollis LIVE from RISE Business - Four H's and an O</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We're gearing up for our first-ever INTERNATIONAL women's conference, so we wanted to bring you some fire business strategy from our fearless leader herself. This keynote was delivered last fall at our RISE Business conference and was designed to help business leaders and entrepreneurs at any level reassess their progress and their strategies, as only Rachel can. This year we're bringing RISE Business back home to Austin! Learn more here: &lt;a href="https://thehollisco.com/pages/rise-business-2020"&gt;https://thehollisco.com/pages/rise-business-2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to put the lessons from this podcast into ACTION! Our next women's conference is coming to Toronto on March 5-7th, and it promises to be a LIFE-CHANGER! What can you expect by coming to a RISE conference? Expect to be energized and motivated. Expect to cry and make new friends (fun fact: most of our attendees come alone - but they don't leave that way). Expect to reconnect with those dreams and goals you’ve been carrying around for years, without any idea of what to do with them. Expect to be inspired to RISE! Get your tickets here -&amp;gt; &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/risepodtoronto"&gt;http://bit.ly/risepodtoronto&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Y'all. We are still pinching ourselves about the latest news out of our podcast network - Trent freakin' Shelton has launched a brand new show with the Hollis Company! That's right, Straight Up with Trent Shelton drops new episodes EVERY WEDNESDAY! Trent brings honest, raw, life-changing wisdom straight from his heart to your ears on a weekly basis. His style is so unique, his message so powerful, we just KNOW this is going to be your new must-listen podcast. Subscribe to Straight Up with Trent Shelton on iTunes, Google, Spotify, Stitcher, or wherever you listen to podcasts by clicking here -&amp;gt; &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/trentpod"&gt;http://bit.ly/trentpod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave's first-ever book, Get Out Of Your Own Way, is coming this March! This book is for everyone, and we mean EVERYONE: women who loved Girl Wash Your Face, men who did or didn't read Girl Wash Your Face, personal development skeptics, personal development devotees, anyone and everyone who has a life and knows it could maybe get a little better if they could just get out of their own dang way! The best part is Dave has created some really cool extras, like a FREE e-course, for people who pre-order the book, so get to it! LET'S GOOOOOO! -&amp;gt; &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/gooyowpod"&gt;http://bit.ly/gooyowpod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sean@dgitalmedia.com (RISE podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1af58df56ef347efa347b01c7e194ad8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1af58df56ef347efa347b01c7e194ad8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Project Recovery : Joel Huff describes how the acting industry fueled his substance abuse</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Casey Scott&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Dr. Matt Woolley&lt;/strong&gt; are joined by &lt;strong&gt;Joel Huff&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Program Director at Pinnacle Recovery Center)&lt;/em&gt; to talk about how he believes that he was genetically predisposed to alcohol after tasting it at a very young age.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We also dive into his struggle with substance abuse throughout high school and how the acting industry and his theatre success affected his drinking habits as a young adult.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@ksl.com (Project Recovery)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b1ccb838a5d9420799da375cf0b04680</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b1ccb838a5d9420799da375cf0b04680/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 23:10:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Soul Sugar : A Real &amp; Raw Conversation w/ My Fiance About Self Care &amp; Individuality While In a Relationship</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A real and raw conversation. In this episode Carrie and Alex chat candidly about self care and individuality while in a relationship.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Soul Sugar. I’m your host Carrie Rad! You might know me from my videos on YouTube. I love to chat about all things self care, self love, living our very best lives, and finding our inner magic. Soul Sugar is a community of blooming soul seekers. Like sugar for your soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ CONTACT SOUL SUGAR — ➭ If you are a listener, you can get in touch with us here: soulsugarpodcast@gmail.com ➭ If you are a business, you can get in touch with us here: soulsugarco@gmail.com ➭ Follow Soul Sugar on Instagram @soulsugarco &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/soulsugarco/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/soulsugarco/&lt;/a&gt;FOLLOW CARRIE RAD — ➭ Follow Carrie Rad on Instagram @carrierad &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/carrierad/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/carrierad/&lt;/a&gt;➭ Follow Carrie Rad on YouTube: Carrie Rad &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/CarrieRad/featured"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/user/CarrieRad/featured&lt;/a&gt;⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts43+dfab59c@anchor.fm (Soul Sugar)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7250e50ab17c4e32bc98a615fca5a951</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7250e50ab17c4e32bc98a615fca5a951/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 20:19:23 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hidden Brain : The Tale of the Cowboy Philosopher</title><description>In 2009, an old man died in a California nursing home. His obituary included not just his given name, but a long list of the pseudonyms he'd been known to use. In this episode, which we originally released in 2019, we trace the life of Riley Shepard, a hillbilly musician, writer, small-time con man and, perhaps, a genius.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (Hidden Brain)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ff532032714c4b76a3b6798d8217768d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ff532032714c4b76a3b6798d8217768d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 16:19:27 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Terrible, Thanks For Asking : It Hurts</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Grief. Addiction. Endometriosis. It’s a trifecta of hurt for Jessica, who just wants the pain to stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can catch up with TTFA on &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/ttfapodcast/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ttfapodcast"&gt;Twitter &lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/ttfapodcast"&gt;Facebook &lt;/a&gt;using @ttfapodcast. Nora&amp;#39;s Instagram is @&lt;a href="https://instagram.com/noraborealis"&gt;noraborealis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TTFA is public media. Which means we are supported by you. You can join us with a contribution at &lt;a href="http://ttfa.org/donate"&gt;ttfa.org/donate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the &lt;a href="https://www.ttfa.org/story/2020/03/02/it-hurts-transcript"&gt;transcript for this episode here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And check out our sponsors this week:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still Kickin’: &lt;a href="https://stillkickin.co/"&gt;stillkickin.co&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Council of Dads: You can watch &lt;em&gt;Council of Dads &lt;/em&gt;on &lt;a href="https://www.nbc.com/council-of-dads"&gt;NBC&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FeMNist Day: Get your tickets to FeMNist Day at &lt;a href="https://femnistday.com/"&gt;femnistday.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This Is Uncomfortable: &lt;a href="https://www.marketplace.org/shows/this-is-uncomfortable-reema-khrais/"&gt;marketplace.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@americanpublicmedia.org (Terrible, Thanks For Asking)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9b57b0b69cbf45fa8c8fc0d5f27889bd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9b57b0b69cbf45fa8c8fc0d5f27889bd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 08:11:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Unsolicited Advice with Ashley and Taryne : Shame, Shame, I Know Your Name</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Whether it's shame from a horrible incident that was beyond your control, or the shame of a disrespectful roommate, we all encounter guilt and remorse in our daily lives. But it's how we choose to deal with that shame and overcome it that truly defines us. So look within, see that beautiful person inside, and let's conquer the now, people!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To watch our podcast videos on YouTube: http://bit.ly/UAPodcastYouTube &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To send us your questions/stories, email us at: AdviceUnsolicitedPod@gmail.com &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be sure to follow us on Instagram: @UnsolicitedAdvicePod   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;                                  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@studio71us.com (Unsolicited Advice with Ashley and Taryne)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">10e1cc16d14c47aea7b7d411b60c846d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/10e1cc16d14c47aea7b7d411b60c846d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Connected Life : 61: The Journey to Healing-Revelations From Pain Pt 2 of 4</title><description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;We have two options when we go through hard things; see the pain as an invitation into wholeness, or get stuck in hopelessness, fear, and heart ache.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;For part two of this four part series, Justin and Abi discuss the revelations Abi had through the last year of sickness. Abi’s health issues forced her into a world of deeper vulnerability, and gave space for grief to surface that produced healing in places she’s felt orphaned and alone.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;They share how allowing themselves to grieve the wrongs of the past didn’t mean they wallowed in their pain, but rather gave themselves the comfort that their souls had desperately needed so that they could truly move forward.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Get ready for a dose of hope as Abi and Justin continue to share the powerful lessons they’ve gathered from enduring and overcoming suffering within their own lives.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;And don't forget to check out &lt;a href= "http://www.stumvollconsulting.com/courses/thecompassionproject"&gt; www.stumvollconsulting.com/courses/thecompassionproject&lt;/a&gt; to get your hands on The Compassion Project &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p2"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>lfa@stumvollconsulting.com (The Connected Life)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e552984fbb4c4b0e8a78058c42f8c67a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e552984fbb4c4b0e8a78058c42f8c67a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Manifest with Tori DeSimone : You are more than your looks | Journey to Self Love &amp; The Pressure of Being a Girl</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi guys, I hope you enjoy this real and raw episode of me just talking in the car today. No notes, just my thoughts. I hope some of you found peace in this episode and can relate to some extend. Have a great Monday!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IG: @toristerling_&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stride IG: @stridespinandfitness&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@studio71us.com (Manifest with Tori DeSimone)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0ae485da77e04e74aa657952404e689a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0ae485da77e04e74aa657952404e689a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Unshakable Self-Confidence : The Power Of Rituals In Strengthening Your Intuition</title><description>&lt;p&gt;How can the powers of rituals strengthen your trust in your intuition, which will change your life?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Today, Dondeena Bradley and I discuss that very topic.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You will hear how a mediation practice will help you realign yourself with your true empathic intuitive self. How a dedicated morning practice of “I AM’s” can set the course of your day and start to create change in your life, as well as, what to do when you find yourself surrounded by energy-draining people and relationships.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>billy@livingbeyondyourfears.com (Unshakable Self-Confidence)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1433a2582ed9436399cc66003caffc05</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1433a2582ed9436399cc66003caffc05/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>How I Built This with Guy Raz : Video Artist: Casey Neistat</title><description>When Casey Neistat was a teenager, the odds were against him; he had dropped out of high school, was washing dishes to pay rent, and was a father by age 17. But he eventually scraped together enough money to buy a camera and an iMac, and began churning out short films that went viral even before YouTube took off. Despite having to start his career over several times – Casey Neistat became a brand name in social media and advertising, and is now one of the biggest names on YouTube, with an audience of nearly 12 million.  PLUS in our post-script "How You Built That," Pat Erley explains how struggling with a perpetually stopped-up sink inspired him to design Dripsie, a no-clog sink strainer.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (How I Built This with Guy Raz)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">094687ac578749c19e6ae06d60435bdc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/094687ac578749c19e6ae06d60435bdc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 21:01:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Happy Place : Flo Perry</title><description>How have we got to 62 episodes without mentioning sex? Flo Perry, author of How To Have Feminist Sex, drops by to discuss with Fearne some of our hang-ups and what we can do to celebrate our bodies in a more healthy and celebratory way.   Warning: strong sex references</description><author>fearne@findyourhappyplace.co.uk (Happy Place)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">222abb69e88f465680f3d3609af776cb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/222abb69e88f465680f3d3609af776cb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Curious Minds: Innovation in Life and Work : CM 156: Lydia Denworth on the Science of Friendship</title><description>&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Blog-Post-Lydia.png"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;What actions would you take if you knew how important friendships were for your health?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Most of us recognize that friendships play an important role in our lives. Yet few of us realize how crucial they are for our health and well-being. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In this interview, &lt;a href="https://lydiadenworth.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Lydia Denworth&lt;/a&gt;, author of the book, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Friendship-Evolution-Biology-Extraordinary-Fundamental/dp/0393651541" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Friendship: The Evolution, Biology, and Extraordinary Power of Life's Fundamental Bond&lt;/a&gt;, shares fascinating research on the science of friendship. She argues that, "Friendship is as important as diet and exercise for both our psychological and physical health."&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In our conversation, Lydia explains ways of assessing whether our friendships are healthy. She also describes the neuroscience of friendship. For example, she discusses a remarkable study where researchers looked at participants' brain patterns while watching snippets of different videos. Their analysis yielded a surprising finding, as Lydia explains, "Just by looking at the brain processing, they could predict who was friends with who."&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Lydia Denworth is a contributing editor for &lt;a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Scientific American&lt;/a&gt;, writes the &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/brain-waves" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Brain Waves&lt;/a&gt; blog for Psychology Today, and is the author of two previous books, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Toxic-Truth-Scientist-Doctor-Battle/dp/0807000329" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Toxic Truth&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Can-Hear-You-Whisper-Intimate/dp/0525953795/ref=tmm_hrd_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=&amp;amp;sr=" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;I Can Hear You Whisper&lt;/a&gt;. Her work has appeared in publications that include, The Atlantic, The New York Times, and The Wall Street Journal.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Host and Producer&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
You can learn more about Curious Minds Host and Creator, Gayle Allen, and Producer and Editor, Rob Mancabelli, &lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/show-hosts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Episode Links:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Bowlby" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;John Bowlby&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Hinde" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Robert Hinde&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jane_Goodall" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Jane Goodall&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dian_Fossey" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Dian Fossey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2588649/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;The Social Brain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.hsph.harvard.edu/lisa-berkman/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Lisa Berkman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Framingham_Heart_Study" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Framingham Heart Study&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alameda_County_Study" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Alameda County Study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.psc.isr.umich.edu/people/profile/478/James_S_House" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;James House&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_T._Cacioppo" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;John T. Cacioppo&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.semel.ucla.edu/cousins/team/steve-cole" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Steve Cole&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.</description><author>gayle@gayleallen.net (Curious Minds: Innovation in Life and Work)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">98aca3fddcb04041bdc1ee67557cf011</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/98aca3fddcb04041bdc1ee67557cf011/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 13:46:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>As a Woman : Episode 059: Negotiation</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Join host Dr. Natalie Crawford as she talks about negotiation. Learn that knowing what you need is power, and you deserve to ask for it. Listen as she discusses her own job transition and what she learned along the way. Also - if we are talking contracts, hire a lawyer. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@nataliecrawfordmd.com (As a Woman)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">96206de48ec44c7891d504a280274335</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/96206de48ec44c7891d504a280274335/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 06:18:43 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Therapy Chat : 219: Attachment, Somatic Work + Sensory Processing In Therapy With Paula Scatoloni + Rachel Lewis-Marlow</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you to this episode's sponsor, TherapyNotes. Get a 2-month free trial of TherapyNotes by going to &lt;a href="http://www.therapynotes.com/" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;www.TherapyNotes.com&lt;/a&gt; and using the promo code TherapyChat. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On today's episode host Laura Reagan, LCSW-C speaks to Paula Scatoloni and Rachel Lewis-Marlow about attachment, somatic work and sensory processing in therapy. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Paula Scatoloni, LCSW, CEDS, SEP is a somatic-based psychotherapist, Certified Eating Disorders Specialist, and Somatic Experiencing™ practitioner in Durham, NC. She has a private practice in Chapel Hill, NC and has worked in the field of eating disorders for over two decades. Prior to developing Embodied Recovery, Paula co-developed the first intensive outpatient program for eating disorders with Dr. Anita Johnston author, Eating In the Light of the Moon. She also served as the Eating Disorder Coordinator at Duke University for nine years where she developed campus policies and managed a multidisciplinary treatment team. She is a certified Shake Your Soul ® instructor and has provided mindful movement classes at Carolina House Treatment Center. Paula has taught extensively on the etiology and treatment of eating disorders through classes, workshops, professional trainings, and conferences. She is currently an SEP assistant and session provider. She has training in Bodywork and Somatic Education (BASE) and additional models for somatic work with developmental trauma. She is a faculty member at the NC Center for Resiliency in Chapel Hill, NC and has been collaborating with researchers for the past four years to develop a study on the efficacy of somatic therapy within the eating disorder population.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Rachel Lewis-Marlow, MS, EdS, LPC, LMBT is a somatically integrative psychotherapist, dually licensed in counseling and therapeutic massage and bodywork. She is a Certified Advanced Practitioner in Sensorimotor Psychotherapy and has advanced training and 25 + years of experience in diverse somatic therapies including Craniosacral Therapy, Energetic Osteopathy, Oncology massage and Aromatherapy. Rachel worked as a primary therapist at Carolina House for 4 years. There she developed the Embodying Recovery group therapy protocol which formed the basis for her contribution to the EMBODIED RECOVERY treatment model. Rachel is a private consultant to eating disorders treatment facilities. She provides ongoing training and supervision to clinical and support staff in the programmatic implementation of the EMBODIED RECOVERY model. She is currently consulting for Carolina House in their residential, partial hospitalization and intensive outpatient treatment programs. In her private practice in Chapel Hill, NC, Rachel works with trauma, eating disorders, and dissociative disorders. She has extensive experience as a teacher and presenter, focusing on accessing the body’s unique capacity to give voice to the subconscious and to lay the foundation for healing and maintaining psychological and physical health.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Resources&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.craigheacockmd.com/"&gt;ht&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href= "https://embodiedrecovery.org/"&gt;https://embodiedrecovery.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt; Leave me a message via Speakpipe by going to &lt;a style= "font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;" href= "https://therapychatpodcast.com"&gt;https://therapychatpodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;  and clicking on the green Speakpipe button.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thank you for listening to Therapy Chat! Please be sure to &lt;a href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/therapy-chat-psychotherapy-mindfulness-trauma-attachment/id1031099411?mt=2"&gt; go to iTunes&lt;/a&gt; and leave a rating and review, subscribe and download episodes. You can also download the Therapy Chat app on iTunes &lt;a href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/therapy-chat-podcast/id1225704658?mt=8"&gt; by clicking here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Podcast produced by Pete Bailey - &lt;a href= "https://petebailey.net/audio"&gt;https://petebailey.net/audio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>therapychat.podcast@gmail.com (Therapy Chat)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0306882a37d34a459a79449513d317bf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0306882a37d34a459a79449513d317bf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 05:04:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Katie Piper's Extraordinary People : Kevin Clifton is extraordinary!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Strictly Come Dancing professional dancer Kevin Clifton speaks with Katie about the struggles he has faced in the past; how he lacks confidence, dealing with depression and how he became disillusioned with dance. Kevin speaks openly about life in the spotlight and how he manages to balance his life, not putting all his eggs in one basket.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>sepodcasts@somethinelse.com (Katie Piper's Extraordinary People)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5946d1afb3c3497491f4af1ccdc1db2b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5946d1afb3c3497491f4af1ccdc1db2b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Balance Show : EP 20 - Retreat Recap, Leader Search, Ghost Stories, + Advice For You</title><description>The girls do a quick recap of the Elite Leader retreat in Breckenridge, explain the Leader Search and what type of person/people Balance is looking to bring on, share ghost stories, and answer some listener questions. Grab your glass and get ready to laugh! Cheers!&lt;br&gt;Tune in for some more detail on the Leader Search in regards to what type of person/people Balance is looking to bring on in this leader search. More info can be found at &lt;a href="https://www.balanceathletica.com/pages/leadersearch2020"&gt;https://www.balanceathletica.com/pages/leadersearch2020&lt;/a&gt;. If you missed this year’s… keep an eye out for next year! We hope you enjoyed this podcast! Please remember to give us a rating and review and never hesitate to let us know what you’d like us to cover in future podcasts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t forget to send in (DM) your “letters” to @thebalanceshow on Instagram about something you may have a question about or want advice on! We’re here to help you Find Your Balance! #DearBalance&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/taychayy/"&gt;@taychayy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/chloe__chamberlain/"&gt;@chloe__chamberlain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/aligay/"&gt;@aligay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/thebalanceshow/"&gt;@thebalanceshow&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/balanceathletica/"&gt;@balanceathletica&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>taylor@balanceathletica.com (The Balance Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e6d5ae6ace48423dbe229ec5d236982f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e6d5ae6ace48423dbe229ec5d236982f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Kind World : More Good News: New Season Starts 3/10</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We know there's a lot going on in the news, and sometimes, it's hard to see the good when so much seems bad. But here at Kind World, we know there are still compassionate people doing amazing things for others every day -- small good deeds and life-changing acts of kindness. Our new season starts March 10.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@wbur.org (Kind World)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1ab6a9d12eb4420782526f4766adef31</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1ab6a9d12eb4420782526f4766adef31/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 09:42:39 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>What It Takes : Buddy Guy: I’ve Got the Blues</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For 50 years, he has carried the torch for the blues. Buddy Guy learned by listening to the greats that came before him, and then he made the blues his own.  He is one of the greatest guitarists of all time, and an extraordinary showman, who inspired a generation of rock n' rollers, including Jimmy Hendrix, Eric Clapton, Jimmy Page, and countless others.  He talks here about his early days picking cotton in rural Louisiana, about making his first guitar with strings pulled from a window screen, and about his abiding friendship with BB King.  As Buddy Guy says: "If you haven't had the blues, just keep living." &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>whatittakespod@achievement.org (What It Takes)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">53c52600179640939f91243a66d69569</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/53c52600179640939f91243a66d69569/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:05:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Genuine Joy : 10: Mental Health in Minors</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode Kelsey and Matt interview Morgan Motes, a mental health counselor and behavior analyst that works exclusively with kids.&amp;nbsp; We talk about behavior, fears, anxiety, ADHD and life transitions for children and how to tell when it might be time to talk to someone!&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow Morgan at &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/littlelives.bigfeelings/"&gt;@littlelives.bigfeelings&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>kelsey@littlebitsof.com (Genuine Joy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b86cc31fdee540599ce81c407363c21b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b86cc31fdee540599ce81c407363c21b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Shambles Show : 10 Birthday Lessons From My 45th Year: Special Episode</title><description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;The Shambles Show is hosted by Shari Teigman&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Welcome to the Shambles Show where you get a sneak peek into the world of Shari Rambles.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Shari, a coach, creative strategist &amp; change instigator who can't wait to ramble with you on Life, on Love, Entrepreneurship and Living Out Loud in all ways- we know you will find a little (or alot!) of yourself in here.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;You're entering the crazy world of the Inner Workings of what goes on in a Maverick's mind,&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;A blend of soul wisdom, creative spark, feisty know how and an Unapologetic Fiery Passion to Inspire the Mav in You&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;May you start Fires and Forge paths to succeed in Business and In Life&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Today is a wrap up of 10 lessons I learned the hard way this year! No filters at ALL.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt; To learn more about Shari go to &lt;a href= "http://www.shariteigman.com/"&gt;www.shariteigman.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Come join Shari on FB to further the conversation at &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/sharidteigman/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/sharidteigman/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Looking to find your spark again? Come join Shari's monthly membership The Maverick Life Unleashed &lt;a href= "https://shariteigman.kartra.com/page/maverickmembership"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Ready to step up and create change FAST with Shari by your side? Apply to work with Shari 1:1 &lt;a href= "https://sharidteigman.typeform.com/to/LEBLi9"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>shari@shariteigman.com (The Shambles Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4478640ab8f849dd860a00318e9dbdfb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4478640ab8f849dd860a00318e9dbdfb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>