<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Better days feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My better days episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My Better days feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 17:18:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>Manifest with Tori DeSimone : How my Parents Let me Dropout of College | why college wasn't for me &amp; making a plan</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi guys, happy #ManifestMonday! Today we talk about one of my most asked questions, HOW I DROPPED OUT! College is not for everybody and this is how I did it. I am not encouraging you to drop out because honestly it's not everybody's path, but I knew it was mine &amp;amp; here's how.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FaceBook group: Manifest with Tori DeSimone&lt;br&gt;IG: @toristerling_&lt;br&gt;YouTube: www.youtube.com/toridesimone&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tsdsterling@gmail.com (Manifest with Tori DeSimone)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8ef28fd0a90b4d1f8bd9804d2b21705a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8ef28fd0a90b4d1f8bd9804d2b21705a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Jim Fortin Podcast : Ep 88: I keep trying to change my identity but I fall back into my old patterns. What causes this?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, I refer you back to a few others and then share the simple attitude you must embrace to create long term change in life.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you’ve tried to change before and failed you’ll love this short episode. It’s not your fault, it’s your brain and you’re not getting the changes you want because you’re working against your brain’s natural function.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Visit the show notes here for more: &lt;a href="https://www.jimfortin.com/88" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.jimfortin.com/88&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Liked the episode? Please &lt;a href="https://www.jimfortin.com/apple"&gt;leave a review&lt;/a&gt; on Apple Podcasts.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; For more transformational content like this daily, connect with me on social media:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://go.jimfortin.com/insta"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://go.jimfortin.com/facebook"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Uplevel your thinking TODAY! Transform your thinking and transform your life with "&lt;a href="http://go.jimfortin.com/mtfpodcast"&gt;The Master Thought Formula&lt;/a&gt;"!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Get instant FREE access &lt;a href= "http://go.jimfortin.com/mtfpodcast"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hey, thank you for listening! If you're the kind of person who likes to help others, then share this with your friends and family. If you found value, they will too. So please share via your social media channels. Also, if you have questions, I'm here to assist.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://go.jimfortin.com/ask"&gt;Click here to send your questions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@jimfortin.com (The Jim Fortin Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f463ae757c1c4b9e99ed7977b3d0615d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f463ae757c1c4b9e99ed7977b3d0615d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>On Purpose with Jay Shetty : Dave Asprey : ON How To Build A Young Brain And Body For Life</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On this episode of On Purpose, I sat down with Dave Asprey. Dave is the Founder &amp;amp; CEO of Bulletproof 360, creator of Bulletproof Coffee, and a two-time &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; bestselling author.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave will be sharing his incredible transformation from being overweight, tired and unsatisfied to Super-Human. He plans on living to at least 180-years-old and wants to help you maximize your performance. You’ll learn the foods that your brain loves and how to slow aging down! Text Jay Shetty 310-997-4177&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to have YOUR best year yet?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join me for my Free Online Workshop: 5 Intentions for a Purpose-Filled Year&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://jayshetty.me/purpose" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://jayshetty.me/purpose&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Word From Our Sponsors:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jump over to &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://athleticgreens.com/purpose" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;athleticgreens.com/purpose&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; and claim my special offer today - 20 FREE travel packs valued at $79 with your first purchase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go to &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://simplisafe.com/ONPURPOSE" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SimpliSafe.com/ONPURPOSE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; today to get FREE shipping on your order, plus a sixty-day, money- back guarantee.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jayshetty@kastmedia.com (On Purpose with Jay Shetty)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5d753109f9d94f6b9528ab66684d3a56</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5d753109f9d94f6b9528ab66684d3a56/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Unsolicited Advice with Ashley and Taryne : Fake Friends Showing Fake Love to Me</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Friends can be a source of joy and part of a healthy, happy life. They can also be the source of stress, familial strife, and sadness. Today, we discuss the unparalleled importance of having friends, regardless of how much work those relationships may require. Friends, indeed, make the world go round.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To watch our podcast videos on YouTube: http://bit.ly/UAPodcastYouTube &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To send us your questions/stories, email us at: AdviceUnsolicitedPod@gmail.com &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be sure to follow us on Instagram: @UnsolicitedAdvicePod&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@studio71us.com (Unsolicited Advice with Ashley and Taryne)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8ddf478d7add4a608c6af4f818754de9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8ddf478d7add4a608c6af4f818754de9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Connected Life : Episode 55-Keys to Becoming a Great Friend</title><description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;In order to truly feel alive and happy, friendships are a vital part of life. Unfortunately, there’s not many “how to” guides on friendship. We definitely know when we don’t feel like someone is being a good friend, but do we know what it is to BE a good friend?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;In this episode Abi and Justin break down fundamental keys to becoming a great friend. They share vital ways to love others and help to equip you to be the friend that you always wanted to have. Get ready to redefine the word friendship and find deeper connections than you’ve ever imagined!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>lfa@stumvollconsulting.com (The Connected Life)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">195422aada6943cb9b03d17d164c8b88</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/195422aada6943cb9b03d17d164c8b88/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Papaya Podcast : The One With About Beauty Products With Breaking Beauty Podcast!</title><description>This week we sit down with beauty experts Jill Dunn &amp; Carlene Higgins and chat all things… well, beauty! Long-time magazine beauty editors Jill &amp; Carlene have witnessed so many changes to the beauty industry, so they broke out of their traditional media channels with a podcast about breakthrough products, people and moments in beauty.  Their expertise lends to an interesting and indulgent conversation around beauty products, the industry, founders and entrepreneurs that are breaking ground, and exactly WHAT is on their top shelves.  &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Make sure you tune into their podcast, and follow them @BreakingBeautyPodcast! &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Products mentioned in this episode: &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Carlene’s Top Shelf: Cle De Peau Hydro Softening Lotion Cle De Peau Protecting Fortifying Emulsion Shiseido Benefiance Wrinkle Smoothing Day Cream SPF 23 Beauty Blender Maybelline Urban Dream Cover  Charlotte Tilbury Airbrush Finish Foundation Charlotte Tilbury Cheek To Cheek Charlotte Tilbury Instant Look In A Palette &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Jill’s Top Shelf: Skinceutical C E Ferulic Serum The Ordinary Niacinamide 10% + Zinc 1% It Cosmetics! Your Skin But Better CC Cream SPF 50 Dior DiorShow Mascara L’Oreal Paris Voluminous Lash Paradise Mascara Pixi Glow Tonic Dermalogica Daily Microfoliant Olay Regenerist Microsculpting Cream Neutrogena Hydro Boost    Produced by &lt;a href= "http://www.dearmedia.com"&gt;Dear Media. &lt;/a&gt;</description><author>michelle@dearmedia.com (The Papaya Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">904bad5d3fd444deb0f2ebe1f43007dd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/904bad5d3fd444deb0f2ebe1f43007dd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>THE UPSIDE with Callie and Jeff Dauler : EPISODE 151:  HACKING RESOLUTIONS AND FAT DOGS</title><description>&lt;p&gt;episode 151 / January 20, 2020&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jdauler@gmail.com (THE UPSIDE with Callie and Jeff Dauler)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0a30967f174241cfb3354f397dbfe551</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0a30967f174241cfb3354f397dbfe551/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>How I Built This with Guy Raz : Happy Family Organics: Shazi Visram</title><description>While she was a student at business school, Shazi Visram ran into an old friend-- a new mother of twins.  The friend confided she felt like a bad mom because she had no time to make her kids healthy meals.  That gave Shazi her initial idea: why not make organic pureed baby food, and sell it frozen instead of jarred? People told her she was crazy to take on Gerber, but she convinced dozens of friends and family to invest in Happy Baby. 15 years later, the brand is known as Happy Family Organics and reportedly makes more than $250 million a year. PLUS in our post-script "How You Built That," after learning that many restaurants use gallons of running water to defrost food, Dylan Wolff invented CNSRV WTR-- a recirculating tub that keeps water from going down the drain.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (How I Built This with Guy Raz)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d55a565c684845be9705162d5e5a73a6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d55a565c684845be9705162d5e5a73a6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 21:01:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Before Breakfast : Ask about your colleagues’ goals</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Learn people’s dreams so you can help them reach them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Before Breakfast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cd6c71577d8b47eeb136b6e14d8ede12</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cd6c71577d8b47eeb136b6e14d8ede12/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Mindset Mentor : Are You Living in Heaven or Hell?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you get stressed out, anxious, sad, depressed, emotional, or pissed off? If so, you might be creating your own version of hell on Earth. In this episode, I am going to tell you how to fix that so that you can create your own version of heaven!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow me on Instagram @RobDialJr &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/robdialjr/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/robdialjr/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out Linkedin Jobs  &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/dial" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/dial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>robdial0@gmail.com (The Mindset Mentor)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bd81f66520874477a454f0b814895ff1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bd81f66520874477a454f0b814895ff1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 20:18:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Daily Meditation Podcast : Love Affirmation</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Gain the clarity you need to focus on what matters most.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is part 2   of a 7-part Motivation meditation series, episodes 1697-1703.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Give our new sip and om app a test drive for 1-week free. Receive access to 1,900+ fully guided meditations customized around a weekly theme. Select from 200+ series to fit your mood with a Clarity Journal and a Slow Down Guide customized for each theme. Brand new themes are introduced each week with brand new meditations offered daily. Connect with other meditators on the private Facebook group for app subscribers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a title="2 Week's Free sip and om iOS app" href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/sip-and-om/id1216664612?platform=iphone&amp;preserveScrollPosition=true#platform/iphone"&gt; 2 weeks for access to the iOS version:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/sip-and-om/id1216664612?platform=iphone&amp;preserveScrollPosition=true#platform/iphone&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a title="sip and om Android app" href= "https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sipandom.sipandom"&gt; 2 weeks free access to the Android version:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sipandom.sipandom&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;All meditations are created by Mary Meckley and are her original content. Please request permission to use any of Mary's content by sending an email to Mary@sipandom.com.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Resources: Music by Christopher Lloyd Clarke and Greg Keller.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Support@SipandOm.com (Daily Meditation Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f2c32f06550842c9a8cf5471779ba8ee</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f2c32f06550842c9a8cf5471779ba8ee/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 14:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>As a Woman : Episode 053: Friendship with Dr. Renee Paro</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Join host Dr. Natalie Crawford as she discusses friendship with Dr. Renee Paro. Renee is a pediatric cardiologist who is passionate about health education and self care. Listen to her talk about her path in medicine, her struggle with infertility, and how she decided to launch the Reconciling Medicine Podcast and Dr. Vegetable non-profit with her husband John. Learn what it means to be a good friend, show up, and leave the world a little brighter.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@nataliecrawfordmd.com (As a Woman)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">353a68c776af4f43ad6cd69b182abe3f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/353a68c776af4f43ad6cd69b182abe3f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dr. Wayne W. Dyer Podcast : Recognizing Your Dharma</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We all have a dharma, a reason for being here on this earth. Dr.Wayne Dyer discusses how to recognize our dharma and work towards getting into alignment with what we are supposed to be doing. When you bring yourself into alignment with your dharma and pay attention to the voice inside the right people and situations will show up for you.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>smorris@hayhouse.com (Dr. Wayne W. Dyer Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4eba436cbcf7445abfa6c69285466841</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4eba436cbcf7445abfa6c69285466841/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out : JAN THOUGHT: Who is Stealing Your Joy?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Who are you allowing to occupy space in your heart and head, robbing you of happiness and peace of mind?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Certified life coach, author &amp; award-winning professional life organizer Julie Coraccio shares steps and tips to support you in creating the life you choose, deserve and desire through decluttering your life, mindfulness and how to organize your life.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;About Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Clutter is stuck stagnant energy and prevents you from creating the life you choose, desire and deserve. We discuss clutter in all its forms: energetic, spiritual, emotional, mental &amp; physical, relationships, health, finances and more. We share tips and take action steps for clutter free living and how to organize your life and death with end of life planning. We're thinking outside the box on areas where people might not realize where clutter is blocking them. When we remove clutter from our lives we can discover our passions, lead the extraordinary lives we are all meant to live and share our gifts with the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>julie@reawakenyourbrilliance.com (Clear Your Clutter Inside &amp; Out)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c5b095271e744a36b9098d122fd951dc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c5b095271e744a36b9098d122fd951dc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Think Again – a Big Think Podcast : 226. Joseph Goldstein (dharma teacher) – doubt comes masquerading as wisdom</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Freedom. Everyone wants it, but knowing where to look for it is another matter. And to make matters worse, the world is full of things that feel like freedom but might just get us more tangled up in everything we’re trying to escape. How much freedom can money buy? How much money? How free are you on a tropical vacation? Would uploading your consciousness into the cloud and downloading it into a robot avatar on Alpha Centauri make you more free? How about falling in love again? How about three margaritas with friends? Or six? How about falling in love again? A better government? Less government? No government at all? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m here today with &lt;a href="https://www.dharma.org/teacher/joseph-goldstein/"&gt;Joseph Goldstein&lt;/a&gt;, a beloved teacher of Buddhist ideas and practice in the West and a personal inspiration to me, to talk about freedom of the mind and spirit—and the kinds of effort and insight that can lead there. Joseph is the co-founder of &lt;a href="https://www.dharma.org/"&gt;Insight Meditation Society&lt;/a&gt; in Barre, Massachusetts and the author, most recently, of &lt;a href="https://www.soundstrue.com/store/mindfulness-3372.html"&gt;Mindfulness: a Practical Guide to Awakening&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-	&lt;a href="http://jasongots.com"&gt;Jason Gots&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jason@bigthink.com (Think Again – a Big Think Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">125db20097ce439bbc7661b74b215ba8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/125db20097ce439bbc7661b74b215ba8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Not The Average Joe Show : Update!</title><description>A quick update about the show!

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/bac5a5c/podcast/sponsor/acugkf/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;

Support this podcast: &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/nottheaveragejoeshow/support" rel="payment"&gt;https://anchor.fm/nottheaveragejoeshow/support&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts43+bac5a5c@anchor.fm (Not The Average Joe Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3f72b064ce5f4e0eae866a6e70cd8a78</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3f72b064ce5f4e0eae866a6e70cd8a78/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 21:16:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Sugars : Episodes We Love: Love &amp; Money</title><description>&lt;p&gt;When it comes to love, money is supposed to be no object. But there’s no disentangling love from anything in our lives, and income is no exception. So how do you assess the role money should play in a relationship, and what happens when your desires and means change over time? The Sugars take on 5 letters in this rapid-fire episode. This episode was originally released on July 21st, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@wbur.org (Dear Sugars)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1c5bb7d57d144d75b38e8e480f324a1f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1c5bb7d57d144d75b38e8e480f324a1f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 09:50:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Therapy Chat : 213: Challenging Preconceptions Of Dissociation</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you to this episode's sponsor, TherapyNotes. Get a 2-month free trial of TherapyNotes by going to &lt;a href="http://www.therapynotes.com/" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;www.TherapyNotes.com&lt;/a&gt; and using the promo code TherapyChat. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;On today's episode host Laura Reagan, LCSW-C speaks to Christine Forner about challenging the preconceptions of dissociation. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Christine Forner (Ba, Bsw, Msw, Rsw). Has been in the healing profession in one form or another since the age of 16 where she worked on a crisis line for teens. Christine spent the first part of her career in the front lines working at local sexual assault centres, long term therapeutic setting and shelters for domestic violence survivors. Since 2011, Christine has worked in her own private practice, which specializes in complex trauma and dissociative disorders.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Christine has over thirty years of working with individuals with Trauma, Post Traumatic Stress Disorders, Traumatic Dissociation, Developmental Trauma and Dissociative Disorders, with specialized training in EMDR, Sensorimotor Psychotherapy, Psychotherapeutic Meditation techniques, Neurofeedback and Havening. Christine is also the current clinical supervisor for WayPoints, a center in Fort McMurry, Alberta that specializes in sexual assault and domestic violence.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Christine teaches locally and at an international level on the issue of dissociation, complex trauma, and the intersection of dissociation and mindfulness. Christine is the current President for the International Society for the Study of Trauma and Dissociation. Christine has also served on the board of the ISSTD since 2010 and was the ISSTD treasurer from 2011-2017. She is the author of Dissociation, Mindfulness and Creative Meditations: Trauma informed practices to facilitate growth (Routledge, 2017). As well as avidly working with those who have been hurt the most, Christine has dedicated her professional life to educating others on the logic, normality and commonality of dissociation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The summation of her work is to educate practitioners about the vital importance of their presence, patients and care with those who have been through the most severe and brutal injuries so that they get treated with dignity and compassion. The four qualities of presence, patience, dignity and compassion applied to every aspect of the therapeutic process can result in profound inner healing; something every human deserves to experience.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Resources&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.isst-d.org/"&gt;https://www.isst-d.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leave me a message via Speakpipe by going to &lt;a href= "https://therapychatpodcast.com"&gt;https://therapychatpodcast.com&lt;/a&gt; and clicking on the green Speakpipe button.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thank you for listening to Therapy Chat! Please be sure to &lt;a href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/therapy-chat-psychotherapy-mindfulness-trauma-attachment/id1031099411?mt=2"&gt; go to iTunes&lt;/a&gt; and leave a rating and review, subscribe and download episodes. You can also download the Therapy Chat app on iTunes &lt;a href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/therapy-chat-podcast/id1225704658?mt=8"&gt; by clicking here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Podcast produced by Pete Bailey - &lt;a href= "https://petebailey.net/audio"&gt;https://petebailey.net/audio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>therapychat.podcast@gmail.com (Therapy Chat)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7d39951ce91745fdb189e4065e855c83</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7d39951ce91745fdb189e4065e855c83/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 07:43:23 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Expand Your Awareness Podcast 2.0 : EP#89 The Episode where you realize you are a Lightworker and find out EXACTLY your mission</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This episode is specifically designed to help you realize that you are a Lightworker. There is a massive shift in consciousness taking place on Planet Earth right now, and If you are reading this right now ...you are part of the shift! We all have a higher mission in life ...and in this special episode I'll help to reveal exactly what it is. Much Love &amp; Namaste &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To Calibrate Your Vibration Click here: &lt;a href= "https://whatsmyvibration.com/" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://whatsmyvibration.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To join The Shift Academy click here: &lt;a href= "http://aarondoughty.com/theshiftacademy" rel= "nofollow"&gt;aarondoughty.com/theshiftacademy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For The SHIFT Experience Webinar click here: &lt;a href= "https://events.genndi.com/register/818182175026324307/4e3eb392ee" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://events.genndi.com/register/818182175026324307/4e3eb392ee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href="https://instagram.com/aaron_doughty44/" rel="nofollow"&gt;https://instagram.com/aaron_doughty44/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Youtube: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC48MclMZIY_EaOQwatzCpvw" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC48MclMZIY_EaOQwatzCpvw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe to the Expand Your Awareness Podcast 2.0 with Aaron Doughty&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;iTunes | &lt;a href= "https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-2-0/id1455761627?mt=2" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-2-0/id1455761627?mt=2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Spotify | &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/show/5mVETgyaXMeznNC70v71YO" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://open.spotify.com/show/5mVETgyaXMeznNC70v71YO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Stitcher | &lt;a href= "https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/aaron-doughty/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-20-with-aaron-doughty?refid=stpr" rel= "nofollow"&gt;https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/aaron-doughty/the-expand-your-awareness-podcast-20-with-aaron-doughty?refid=stpr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>adoughty44@yahoo.com (The Expand Your Awareness Podcast 2.0)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e6d8b3718277423a85fc9042afae88ed</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e6d8b3718277423a85fc9042afae88ed/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The CreateU Experience : Let It Go!</title><description>Letting go is one of the most difficult things that we will ever face in our entire lives. That could be letting go of a business that you love or pretty much anything that you're passionate about. On today’s show, Brendan Meyers talks about this sensitive matter and gives an example of something that's going on in his life that he’s letting go of – a toxic relationship. 2020 is a new year with new opportunities. Take a look inside and ask yourself what you need to let go of so you can take hold of and focus on new things that truly serve you.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Review this podcast on iTunes using this link -- &lt;a href="http://www.createuagency.com/podcast-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;http://www.createuagency.com/podcast-giveaway&lt;/a&gt; -- and receive 7 FREE gifts---</description><author>podcast@createuagency.com (The CreateU Experience)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4940f85c68d04f6da42a492c6c11b920</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4940f85c68d04f6da42a492c6c11b920/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Habit Based Lifestyle : EP148 Habit Of Taking Life So Serious</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Have you reached a point in your life wherein you always take things too seriously? Sometimes worry is the culprit of all things negative. When you worry too much about how other people think or say about you, it takes away the joy and replaces it with fear, shyness, and a bad mood. The key to starting living life is to realize that not everything and everyone needs a reaction, and not every moment needs an opinion. Before you start the day or when you come home from a tiring day, look at yourself in the mirror and smile or dance or sing a song. Allow your body and mind to lose control and let everything go. Life is too short. Be happy.&lt;/p&gt; -- Are you looking to connect with a group of like-minded habit hacking people? Join my private Facebook group along with 100's of others in my habit-based lifestyle secrets page &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/307809586529906/" rev= "en_rl_none"&gt;https://www.Facebook.Com/groups/307809586529906/&lt;/a&gt; where I'll be dropping daily habits, tips, and tricks every single week.     Want more information on our programs and other ways to get involved check out my website &lt;a href="http://jesseewell.com/" rev= "en_rl_none"&gt;http://jesseewell.com/&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href= "http://www.habitbasedlifestyle.com/"&gt;www.Habitbasedlifestyle.com&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>jesse@habitbasedlifestyle.com (Habit Based Lifestyle)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">560c7dcd774a443288adb5ba6fc81ae7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/560c7dcd774a443288adb5ba6fc81ae7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Success Sensei Podcast : What Happens If You Don't Know What You Want?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei Podcast&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would love to hear your views. Please get in touch using any of the channels below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All comments, reviews, subscribes, likes and shares are greatly appreciated. Thank you for all your continued support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Now Twice A Week: Every Wednesday there’s a brand new Success Sensei Blog, Podcast and Vlog. Every Friday we’re bringing you the Friday Blitz – a shorter, sharper, shockier Success Sensei Podcast and Vlog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Roundhouse Rob, The Success Sensei&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Robert Devane is a serial entrepreneur and experienced investor as well as a former martial arts multiple World champion and professional MMA fighter with over 20 years of coaching experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more amazing FREE content please visit:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Apple itunes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://itunes.apple.com/ie/podcast/the-success-sensei-podcast/id1448626122?mt=2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Android&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://successsensei.podbean.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei Blog&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;http://www.thesuccesssensei.blogspot.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on YouTube&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCZG1Ly9zBKc5ZZ134dkjeHA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Facebook&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;http://www.facebook.com/thesuccesssensei&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Success Sensei on Instagram&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;http://www.instagram.com/thesuccesssensei&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>redevane@yahoo.com (The Success Sensei Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">805fe4a0137b48b4b28c7213bfc96978</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/805fe4a0137b48b4b28c7213bfc96978/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 16:27:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Energy Clearing for Life Force : Energy Clearing for Life Force "Focus on Peace: Messages from Dr. Martin Luther King" Podcast #211</title><description>Energy Clearing for Life Force "Focus on Peace: Messages from Dr. Martin Luther King" Podcast #211&lt;p&gt;On today's show, Erica connects to the experience of peace no matter what is going on. It's a solemn connectivity to source energy and the messages from the late Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. She also shares gifts from the book "I Have a New Dream: Messages of Peace and Unity."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://amzn.to/2tcAWOZ'&gt;Get the book today! &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>energyclearingforlife@gmail.com (Energy Clearing for Life Force)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f289f128889141d7b9301a68b879b834</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f289f128889141d7b9301a68b879b834/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 10:11:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Enneagram &amp; Coffee : 30: Type Six Breakdown</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode Sarajane is breaking down Type 6 - the loyalist. Type 6s are motivated by security, support from others, and fighting against anxiety. They're often your most loyal friend.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Sarajane discusses the type 6's motivation, fear, and worldview. She shares the common behaviors that show up when they're at rest and when they're stressed. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This episode also dives into subtypes, wings, and common mistypes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Referenced in this episode:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://sarajane-case.mykajabi.com/offers/zysXzr8d/checkout" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Goal Mapping and Productive Progress Bundle SALE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can connect with Sarajane on IG &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/enneagramandcoffee/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;@enneagramandcoffee&lt;/a&gt; or at www.enneagramandcoffee.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@enneagramandcoffee.com (Enneagram &amp; Coffee)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0960e7991e5849df863509edee37fbb3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0960e7991e5849df863509edee37fbb3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Peak Mind with Michael Trainer : DR G: PROTOCAL FOR OPTIMAL WELLNESS AND PROTECTION FROM ENVIRONMENTAL TOXINS AND</title><description>&lt;h2&gt;Episode Summary&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow @michaeltrainer and @doctor.g_ and let us know your take aways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;http://www.peakmind.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.lifecykel.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life Cykel is an evolutionary focused mycelium biotechnology company that engineers positive solutions to real world problems. By harvesting the Circular Economy and using its valuable fuel in partnership with mushrooms, we are able to offer incredible products and services for our health and planetary harmony. Some of our best examples include the National Mushroom Network, Mushroom Honey and Beemunity, our product that supports the immunity of bees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;discount code: PEAKMIND20&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;http://www.butcherbox.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CODE: PEAKMIND&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is ButcherBox:&lt;/strong&gt; ButcherBox is a meat subscription company that distributes high quality meat you can trust; 100% grass-fed and pasture raised beef, free-range organic chicken, heritage breed pork, and wild caught Alaskan salmon directly to your door. ButcherBox believes in better. Their mission is to create a world where everyone wins with meat that is better for you, your family, the animals, the farmers, the business, and our planet. All of their products are humanely raised and never given antibiotics or added hormones ever.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Our Beef:&lt;/strong&gt; ButcherBox Beef is 100% grass-fed, grass-finished and raised free from antibiotics and added hormones. It is also humanely raised and pasture raised.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#"&gt;Show Less&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>michael@peakmind.org (Peak Mind with Michael Trainer)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">437da6fb7dda447dbd8e16a9d43163a3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/437da6fb7dda447dbd8e16a9d43163a3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:11 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hope to Recharge : Gratitude is a Choice (Attitude of Gratitude)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever had a strong expectation that something was going to turn out a certain way only to be disappointed that it went in a completely different direction? Maybe your hopes were up that something would happen and when it didn’t, you were left extremely frustrated. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In today’s episode I share a new perspective on dealing with change and how we can find gratitude in moments when things turn out differently than what we expect.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This past week, I was in Israel at a Think Tank working on a new product that I am developing. I went into the meetings with a certain expectation of their outcomes and was confident that my ideas would manifest in a certain way. When they did not, I was incredibly grateful because I truly believe things were happening FOR me and were leading me down a better path.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I share with you this story because it is important for us to take a big picture approach in looking at our lives and even the disappointments that we face. Although that may sound like a daunting task, we can slowly develop this mindset through a daily gratitude practice. Gratitude changes us from the inside out!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I hope today’s episode encourages you to shift to gratitude not only when things are going as you anticipated but also when things are difficult and you might be tempted to feel frustrated and down. The more you choose gratitude the more it becomes a part of you. Amazing things will happen for you...when you live a life of gratitude.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We would LOVE to support you and be a part of your journey. Find us on Facebook at &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/"&gt;Hope to Recharge&lt;/a&gt;. Because as always, together is better!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Interested in joining our monthly Mastermind? Find out more info here! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.hopetorecharge.com/Mastermind"&gt;www.hopetorecharge.com/Mastermind&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Today's episode of Hope to Recharge is sponsored by &lt;a href= "http://betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge"&gt;https://Betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Betterhelp.com is the world’s leading provider of online therapy. Their mission is to make professional counseling accessible, affordable, and convenient, so anyone who struggles with life’s challenges can get help, anytime, anywhere.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Head to &lt;a href= "https://betterhelp.com/"&gt;https://Betterhelp.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href= "https://betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge"&gt;hopetorecharge&lt;/a&gt; for 10% off your first month of services. IMPORTANT: Be sure to click &lt;a href= "https://betterhelp.com/hopetorecharge"&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt; in order to get the10% off code&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Resources mentioned: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The Secret: &lt;a href= "https://www.amazon.com/Simon-Schuster-Audio-The-Secret/dp/B000LC3JX2"&gt; https://www.amazon.com/Simon-Schuster-Audio-The-Secret/dp/B000LC3JX2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Topics Discussed:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;How to find gratitude when things change&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;How to find the good in what could be disappointing moments&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;A personal tip on finding gratitude when your mind is cluttered&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Suicide Hotlines:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;USA: 1-800-273-8255&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;USA Crisis Text: 741-741Canada: 1-833-456-4566&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;United Kingdom: 116-123&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Australia: 13-11-14&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;International Suicide Hotlines: &lt;a href= "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_suicide_crisis_lines"&gt; https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_suicide_crisis_lines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with us!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Website: &lt;a href= "https://hopetorecharge.com/"&gt;https://hopetorecharge.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Private Facebook Group: &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;WAYS TO HELP THE PODCAST&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;______________________&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe via iTunes and leave a review.  It costs nothing. &lt;a href= "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845"&gt; https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;—————————————————————————&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Spread the word via social media.   It costs nothing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our website is &lt;a href= "https://hopetorecharge.com/"&gt;https://hopetorecharge.com/&lt;/a&gt; our FB is &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/2079694042156503/&lt;/a&gt; and our Instagram is &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/matanajacobs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;--------------------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe to us on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;iTunes: &lt;a href= "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845"&gt; https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/hope-to-recharge/id1464788845&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Spotify: &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/show/00AIhRZOxKNOvenz32gGeK"&gt;https://open.spotify.com/show/00AIhRZOxKNOvenz32gGeK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Stitcher: &lt;a href= "https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/heather-parady-2/hope-to-recharge"&gt; https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/heather-parady-2/hope-to-recharge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Youtube: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC_DkYMcco7pSrkKk6wU5p7w"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC_DkYMcco7pSrkKk6wU5p7w&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Google: &lt;a href= "https://play.google.com/music/listen?u=0#/ps/Izxlwulashxr3n6trjrxpjpgwce"&gt; https://play.google.com/music/listen?u=0#/ps/Izxlwulashxr3n6trjrxpjpgwc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>matana@hopetorecharge.com (Hope to Recharge)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4eeae1e884b94e7db09c97299cddd7c2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4eeae1e884b94e7db09c97299cddd7c2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Inspiration Rising : Judginess Works Until It Doesn't - Stacey Robbins</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stacey Robbins&lt;/strong&gt; is an integrated wellness coach, speaker, and author of &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2B23paL" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;em&gt;An Unconventional Life: Where Messes and Magic Collide&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2WpRY5R" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;em&gt;You’re Not Crazy and You’re Not Alone&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2UnOUpg" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bloom Beautiful&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. She creates experiences through her international retreats and workshops, empowering women to live from what she calls their “Brave Soul Place.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her career began as a professional musician when she was 15, working as a songwriter, pianist, and vocalist in solo performance as well as with many other talented artists, but when she was 27 hit a health bump that dramatically shifted her life. After a parade of misdiagnoses, gaining 100 pounds in a year and becoming so ill that she could barely get out of bed, the doctors told her to get her affairs in order.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stacey began pursuing her health from a deeply spiritual angle that led her to shine a flashlight down all the corridors of her life: Thoughts, Beliefs, Patterns, Relationships, Spiritual Practices, Self-Care, Food, and Exercise. Through that experience and years of research of a diagnosis with Hashimoto’s (an autoimmune condition that affects the thyroid and therefore every cell in your body) she has been able to speak all over the US and reach people all over the world with her healing insights that she discovered through her own sacred journey. Stacey resides in Southern California with her author, tech-geek, musician husband and their two amazing, curly-haired teenage sons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In This Episode, You Will Learn:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;What drives judginess within each of us.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The difference between being in relationship &lt;em&gt;with&lt;/em&gt; someone and &lt;em&gt;to&lt;/em&gt; someone.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;What happens to our vision when we become judgy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How to release judgment and become 100% committed to the whole person.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with Stacey Robbins:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.staceyrobbins.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;www.staceyrobbins.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.staceyrobbinscoaching.com/100-day-experience" rel="nofollow"&gt;100 Day Gong Experience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/staceyrobbins/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/staceyrobbins" rel="nofollow"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/lovestaceyrobbins/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://staceyrobbins.com/coaching/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Coaching&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://staceyrobbins.com/retreats-travel/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Women&amp;#39;s Retreats to Italy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://staceyrobbins.com/hashimotos/" rel="nofollow"&gt;The Hashimoto&amp;#39;s Mind Game&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t Miss A Single Episode:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscribe&lt;/strong&gt; on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/inspiration-rising/id1448649388" rel="nofollow"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/music/m/Iqrp5q3bagph2t23malprd3dxvy?t=Launch_Yourself_Today" rel="nofollow"&gt;Google Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/42zIsXzjCibZt49xdCRvB4" rel="nofollow"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href="https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/in-plain-sight/launch-yourself-today" rel="nofollow"&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leave a quick review&lt;/strong&gt; on any of the podcast apps to tell people what you think about the show.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take a screenshot of the podcast&lt;/strong&gt; and post it on Instagram or Instagram Stories. Tag us &lt;a href="http://www.instagram.com/insporising" rel="nofollow"&gt;@insporising&lt;/a&gt;. We’ll repost and give you a shoutout!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Support this podcast at — &lt;a rel='payment' href='https://redcircle.com/inspiration-rising/donations'&gt;https://redcircle.com/inspiration-rising/donations&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>david@insporising.com (Inspiration Rising)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">751afd4bbce64afe94bf8aa20c289a10</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/751afd4bbce64afe94bf8aa20c289a10/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 20:11:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Be You Find Happy : E46 GUEST Melissa Krivachek shares the qualities of millionaires</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Melissa Krivachek trains individuals, teams and companies across the globe who find themselves lacking energy, losing money and feeling lost in the day to day cycles they’ve created for themselves, their businesses and families. Melissa has been on cover of Evolution Magazine as their Top Power Player Under 40. Melissa has also been nominated for Forbes and Inc.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Magazines prestigious list of “30 Under 30” and has been named the “Top 1% of US Executives” two years in a row by The American Council of Executives. In addition she’s made hundreds of media appearances and has been given multiple awards from the states of Iowa where she grew up and Minnesota. Melissa now travels extensively and is highly involved in philanthropy spending her time volunteering in various activities and countries around the world. Melissa has also written 10 books - 7 of which are International Best-Sellers. Finally, she was nominated to be in the 2019 “Inc. 5000” list which is a definitive ranking of America’s fastest-growing, privately held companies.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://michaelarenee.com/"&gt;Connect with Michaela&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#millionaires #beyou #melissakrivachek&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/8b1ab7c/podcast/sponsor/acugkf/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/beyoufindhappy/message</description><author>info@michaelarenee.com (Be You Find Happy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">986a94d370784bc9beef4849cf3d7b59</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/986a94d370784bc9beef4849cf3d7b59/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>goopfellas  : Taz Bhatia: What Men Don’t Know about their Hormones</title><description>&lt;p&gt;“Men are sometimes shocked to learn that they have estrogen,” says integrative medicine physician Taz Bhatia, MD. In this episode, Bhatia shares the primary health issues that she sees among her male patients—from low testosterone to other hormonal disruptions, imbalances in the gut, and nutritional deficiencies. She talks us through hormone replacement therapy—and why she thinks you need to be very careful—and which supplements she typically subscribes. She also talks about the warning signs that something is up—changes in energy, weight, libido—and why many men have a tendency to downplay what their body is telling them. For men and women, Bhatia believes that insulin resistance plays a huge role in many health conditions and that often the first step to healing or optimizing our health begins with dealing with insulin resistance and inflammation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(For more, see the &lt;a href="https://url.emailprotection.link/?bjE8wTftZfcmuju01p2ThIfpQqtnH14MhSdgHSujYuuTLx1Tb_Nj20EntNjGxHRdMOk_lzqS-bT4RkIbcm-K-yQ~~"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;goopfellas&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; podcast hub.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@goop.com (goopfellas )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">dbe4d67e52ab404f971d6f1001ded822</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/dbe4d67e52ab404f971d6f1001ded822/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Selfie : Creating Space to Feel Your Feelings + Sarah’s Last Episode | Selfie Podcast Episode 111</title><description>Sarah explains her decision to step back as host, and Kristen introduces the new show format and a new co-host. We chat with Sherianna Boyle about the importance of creating space to feel our feelings.



In this episode we talked about:

 	Emotional Detox: 7 Steps to Release Toxicity and Energize Joy
 	Emotional Detox for Anxiety: 7 Steps to Release Anxiety and Energize Joy
 	The Chalet Wrap from Mer-Sea
 	Mantra Mask Hemp CBD Coconut Eye Gels
 	Sarah’s Top Clean Beauty Picks of 2019
 	Aleavia Body Cleanse 

Photo by Cristian Newman on Unsplash</description><author>rageagainsttheminivan@gmail.com (Selfie)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1fd017efbca246dca49bf6ce9c097eb0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1fd017efbca246dca49bf6ce9c097eb0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 23:01:35 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Oprah’s SuperSoul Conversations : Oprah and Tina Fey: Your Life in Focus</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As a part of Oprah&amp;rsquo;s 2020 Vision: Your Life in Focus Tour Presented by WW&lt;em&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;Emmy-, Golden Globe- and Screen Actors Guild Award-winner&amp;nbsp;Tina&amp;nbsp;Fey&amp;nbsp;sits down with Oprah in front of a live audience in St. Paul, Minnesota. The actress, comedian, writer, producer, playwright and New York Times best-selling author discusses her lifetime WW membership and the positive impact the program has had on her personal life and career. Tina also talks about the first time she played Sarah Palin on &lt;em&gt;SNL,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;her&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Golden Globes&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;hosting gig and her hit movie and Broadway musical &lt;em&gt;Mean Girls.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Also, Tina reveals who makes her laugh and opens up about raising her two young daughters in today&amp;rsquo;s social-media age.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@own.oprah.com (Oprah’s SuperSoul Conversations)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a3a1d377ba9045b69047c23d54266f4b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a3a1d377ba9045b69047c23d54266f4b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Heal, Survive &amp; Thrive! : How to Spot Healthy Love</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Being in a healthy relationship or having healthy love is something we all dream of having at one point or another, but do we really know what that means or what it looks like? This week, I want to dive into healthy love. I'll give you the best tips for finding a healthy partner as well as talk about what a healthy relationship should look like!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on Private Coaching or Online Coaching please visit www.StephanieLynLifeCoaching.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Subscribe to my YouTube Channel for new videos every Tuesday! www.youtube.com/StephanieLynCoaching&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;All the best!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Stephanie&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ssylvia23@gmail.com (Heal, Survive &amp; Thrive!)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8565d2a981c24282aafadaffa9a77202</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8565d2a981c24282aafadaffa9a77202/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 15:04:49 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mental Makeover : Quick Flick founder Iris Smit on her mind-blowing, unconventional journey from trauma to triumph</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This episode is... mind blowing! I got goosebumps so many times and had to edit out my hundreds of "WOW" remarks (I couldn't help myself!). I really struggled to pick a title because nothing could succinctly summarise how interesting, engaging, informative, inspirational and truly unbelievable her story is. You've probably heard of The Quick Flick by now (winged eyeliner stamp for those who haven't), and maybe even her new venture Beauty Fridge. Iris Smit is only 24 and has managed to build a $15 million dollar empire in 2 years. From the outside, everything seemed perfect. Booming business; long term relationship; dream car; dream life, right? Despite every box being ticked, Iris was unhappier than she'd ever been. After experiencing horrific trauma as a child, she had no identity, no control, nothing to call her own and subsequently felt completely numb. It's the story of what came next that truly blew my mind in more ways than one. I won't spoil it because it deserves to be heard in context and in its entirety. Thank you so much to Iris (@irisjade, @thequickflick, @beautyfridge) for joining me on the podcast, I think this will remain one of my favourite episodes for a very long time x&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>laurencurtis@outlook.com (Mental Makeover)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5047a82d66bd456683a2f5338887957d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5047a82d66bd456683a2f5338887957d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 13:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>With That Being Said : Episode with James Bland</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode of "With That Being Said", Esther and Erica talk with special guest James Bland! James is a content creator, film maker, actor, writer, producer, and director. He is the creator, show runner and star of the award winning digital drama, Giants.&amp;nbsp;Esther, Erica and James discuss the stigma around mental health, especially in communities of color, and how James is using his platform in Hollywood to help end it. They also discuss the truth about what mental illness looks like, the importance of being real, and (of course!) Esther and Erica ask James about his experience at the Emmy's!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find James on Instagram and Twitter: @jrbland&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can watch Giants on Issa Rae's Youtube Channel &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLVo7nGot4fPi_1MFfZSLROrc6BhjXSffI"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, or on Cleo TV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find Giants on Instagram and Twitter: @giantstheseries&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or visit Giant's website &lt;a href="https://giantstheseries.com/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you enjoy "With That Being Said" and want more of Esther and Erica, check out their Instagram Live Show "Live with E+E" on Tuesday's at 12 PM EST. You can find E+E on both Esther and Erica's Instagrams (linked below).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/estherbmft/"&gt;Esther's Instagram&lt;/a&gt;: @estherbmft&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/rosewatertherapy/"&gt;Erica's Instagram&lt;/a&gt;: @rosewatertherapy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/therapyisnotadirtyword/"&gt;Therapy Is Not A Dirty Word's Instagram&lt;/a&gt;: @therapyisnotadirtyword&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Links mentioned in the episode:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/therapy-is-not-a-dirty-word-q-a-happy-hour-washington-dc-tickets-79566213687"&gt;Therapy is Not a Dirty Word Happy Hour Events&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/718c048/podcast/sponsor/acugkf/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;

Support this podcast: &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/WithThatBeingSaid/support" rel="payment"&gt;https://anchor.fm/WithThatBeingSaid/support&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts8+718c048@anchor.fm (With That Being Said)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e21e3d1c5c304e658f34f362c155e06e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e21e3d1c5c304e658f34f362c155e06e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Aggressive Life with Brian Tome : Episode 21: Peter Goodwin—Groove Life CEO and Founder</title><description>&lt;div&gt;From an Alaskan bear hunting guide to the founder of a wildly successful startup, Peter Goodwin's life has been defined by the aggressive moves he's made. Brian sits down with him after a tour of the Groove Life facility for a conversation you'll have to hear to believe. &lt;/div&gt;</description><author>podcasts@crossroads.net (The Aggressive Life with Brian Tome)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1c14670117404070a6919ae80de19b5c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1c14670117404070a6919ae80de19b5c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 03:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>RISE podcast : 129: Unlocking Your Potential Using Grit and Google with Colin O'Brady</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It's not every day you get to sit down with an unparalleled endurance athlete with not one, not two, but FOUR world records, but that's exactly what I did at the end of last year when I chatted with Colin O'Brady - the man who transformed his life after a terrifying trauma to become the first man to trek across Antarctica solo. In this episode he talks about how to Google your dreams (literally), finding strength in hard things, and the life-altering power of a mother's love. You don't wanna miss this one folks!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colin's first book is available TODAY! get your copy here --&amp;gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theimpossiblefirst.com"&gt;https://www.theimpossiblefirst.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave's first-ever book, Get Out Of Your Own Way, is coming this March! This book is for everyone, and we mean EVERYONE: women who loved Girl Wash Your Face, men who did or didn't read Girl Wash Your Face, personal development skeptics, personal development devotees, anyone and everyone who has a life and knows it could maybe get a little better if they could just get out of their own dang way! The best part is Dave has created some really cool extras, like a FREE e-course, for people who pre-order the book, so get to it! LET'S GOOOOOO! --&amp;gt; &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/gooyowpod"&gt;http://bit.ly/gooyowpod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AAAND, if you are looking to add gratitude + goal-setting in your life then head to our shop to grab your Start Today Journal here-- &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/2UZOglA"&gt;http://bit.ly/2UZOglA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>feeds@soundcloud.com (RISE podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">88e2164e64c34cfe81276c772c315cb3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/88e2164e64c34cfe81276c772c315cb3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Project Recovery : How ADHD led to a life-changing addiction with Kristen and Spencer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In part one of this week's episode, Casey Scott and Dr. Matt Woolley are joined by Kristen Larsen and her son, Spencer Nicholas, to talk about how Spencer's ADHD diagnosis led him to begin taking Adderall and how it became a full-fledged addiction.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also dive into how he abused his prescription to stay awake to play video games with his friends.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@ksl.com (Project Recovery)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8d311bd573174532b3ea51cb745fa2ef</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8d311bd573174532b3ea51cb745fa2ef/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 23:10:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Untangle : Dr. Fred Luskin - Why Holding Grudges is Bad for your Health and How to Forgive for Good</title><description>Dr. Fred Luskin is the Director and Cofounder of the Stanford University Forgiveness Project and the author of several bestselling books including Forgive for Good, a Proven Prescription for Health and Happiness. He dives into what the science tells us about the healing powers and medical benefits of forgiveness. He shares that you don't have to actually forget or even feel good about the ‘incident’ in order to forgive, but we do have to change the story we tell ourselves about the inciting grievance. Dr. Luskin explains how to do this. It’s good stuff for those of us who might hold a grudge or two.</description><author>support@meditationstudioapp.com (Untangle)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fe2d08248ddd4b9c925d5c579938859b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fe2d08248ddd4b9c925d5c579938859b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 15:21:20 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Kind World : The "Thank You Project"</title><description>&lt;p&gt;When Writer Nancy Davis Kho decided to spend an entire year writing "thank-you" letters, she didn't expect just how transformative it would be. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@wbur.org (Kind World)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e811343d8dfe4c238c6daa18ebbfb7f3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e811343d8dfe4c238c6daa18ebbfb7f3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 14:43:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hidden Brain : Emotional Currency</title><description>What's the point of money? The answer might seem obvious: we need it to get paid for our work, and to buy the things we need. But there's also a deeper way to look at the role of money in our lives. This week we explore an anthropologist's take on the origin story of money. What if the cash and coins we carry are not just tools for transactions, but manifestations of human relationships?</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (Hidden Brain)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3544f310075345aeb38a63dbdaf85540</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3544f310075345aeb38a63dbdaf85540/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 14:28:31 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>What It Takes : Bill Gates, Sergey Brin and Larry Page: Tech Titans</title><description>&lt;p&gt;These three visionaries changed the way we live our daily lives. You'll hear remarkable archival recordings of each, when they were young successful entrepreneurs, but before history had proven the scale of their impact. Bill Gates, co-founder of Microsoft, describes how, as a teenager, he first envisioned the potential for computers to become fixtures in our homes. Larry Page and Sergey Brin, founders of Google, talk about their accidental discovery of the algorithm that would allow us to search and make sense of the new world-wide web's information explosion. And they all talk about taking risks to embrace the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>whatittakespod@achievement.org (What It Takes)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c1cca616c8f449178bf50ce3f3c77479</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c1cca616c8f449178bf50ce3f3c77479/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:05:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Happy Place : Nadiya Hussain</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Bake Off winner, writer and presenter talks to Fearne about her upbringing, arranged marriage and the realities of being a British celebrity raised with Bangladeshi traditions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>fearne@findyourhappyplace.co.uk (Happy Place)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f3b4296b14604057a98e46ed9a852219</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f3b4296b14604057a98e46ed9a852219/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Shambles Show : What On Earth Is A Mindset Anyway?</title><description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;The Shambles Show is hosted by Shari Teigman&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Welcome to the Shambles Show where you get a sneak peek into the world of Shari Rambles.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Shari, a coach, creative strategist &amp; change instigator who can't wait to ramble with you on Life, on Love, Entrepreneurship and Living Out Loud in all ways- we know you will find a little (or alot!) of yourself in here.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;You're entering the crazy world of the Inner Workings of what goes on in a Maverick's mind,&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;A blend of soul wisdom, creative spark, feisty know how and an Unapologetic Fiery Passion to Inspire the Mav in You&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;May you start Fires and Forge paths to succeed in Business and In Life&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Today I am explaining what exactly a mindset is. So many people walk around each day deciding their mindset is fixed or even worse, owns THEM. Not a chance! Once you realize what a mind is make up of, you can choose differently and see possibility in a different way. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt; To learn more about Shari go to &lt;a href= "http://www.shariteigman.com/"&gt;www.shariteigman.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Come join Shari on FB to further the conversation at &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/sharidteigman/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/sharidteigman/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Looking to find your spark again? Come join Shari's monthly membership The Maverick Life Unleashed &lt;a href= "https://shariteigman.kartra.com/page/maverickmembership"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;Ready to step up and create change FAST with Shari by your side? Apply to work with Shari 1:1 &lt;a href= "https://sharidteigman.typeform.com/to/LEBLi9"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>shari@shariteigman.com (The Shambles Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1c0ed241e1f545588fc83fe9dd70f57d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1c0ed241e1f545588fc83fe9dd70f57d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Katie Piper's Extraordinary People : Jason Fox is extraordinary!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Jason Fox served in the&amp;nbsp;Special Forces for 20 years, dealing with many traumatic experiences – but also living for his work. After two decades he was told to leave the military services, due to suffering from PTSD and depression. He has since become a world-renowned TV presenter and author, having presented ‘SAS: Who Dares Wins’ amongst so much more. In this episode he talks about the rigours of working in the military, dealing with PTSD, and life after having his dream job (and all he knew) taken away from him.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>sepodcasts@somethinelse.com (Katie Piper's Extraordinary People)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">040343ae3dd34c23ae2e71713fad5efd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/040343ae3dd34c23ae2e71713fad5efd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 19:00:58 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Motivational Mornings  : 73: Range</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today we discuss the book Range by David Epstein and why generalists are becoming more valuable in a specialized world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span id="more-570"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Audible: We’ve partnered with Audible, an Amazon company to get you guys a FREE audio of your choice, claim your free audiobook at www.audibletrial.com/motivationalmornings If you enjoyed this podcast please leave a Rating and a Review on iTunes!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@motivationalmornings.co (Motivational Mornings )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5ef01bfb1c0c475e87ec887a8236d9e0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5ef01bfb1c0c475e87ec887a8236d9e0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 04:38:48 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>SelfishBabe SelfishTalk Podcast : (#56) All About Vaginal Detoxing With Goddess Detox Inc: Goddess Vaginal Detox Pearls and The Queen's Vaginal Steam</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey SelfishBabe this is the link to leave me a voice message or question :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://anchor.fm/selfishbabe-selfishtalk-podcast&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for listening, I love you.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>VanWhite17@icloud.com (SelfishBabe SelfishTalk Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7921e0c85a4d49c9b89d4361d9024bd3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7921e0c85a4d49c9b89d4361d9024bd3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 05:37:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Curious Minds: Innovation in Life and Work : CM 152: Wendy Wood on the Science of Habits</title><description>&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Blog-Post-Wendy.png"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;What if our success was less about channeling willpower and more about building sustainable habits?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Too often, when we think about goals we've failed to achieve, we blame it on a lack of willpower. Yet research has shown when we rely primarily on willpower, we're bound to fail. Willpower takes energy, and it's when our energy stores are at their lowest that we need it the most. That's when we default to our old habits, the ones we most want to change. They require a lot less energy because they've become automatic. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
If that's the case, what can we do?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://dornsife.usc.edu/wendywood" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Wendy Wood&lt;/a&gt;, author of the book, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Good-Habits-Bad-Science-Positive/dp/1250159075" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Good Habits, Bad Habits: The Science of Making Positive Changes that Stick&lt;/a&gt;, can help. Professor of Psychology and Business at the University of Southern California, she's studied the science of habits for decades. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
To begin, Wendy argues we need to give ourselves the time we need to develop new habits. We need time for our habits to become unconscious. She explains that, "People who have high levels of self-control, they don't report being distracted by temptations. They don't even see the temptations anymore because they are on autopilot."&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Drawing on decades of research, Wendy shares concrete ways we can form new habits. One of these involves environment, especially proximity. For example, researchers found that people who drove around three miles to the gym went five times as often as those who traveled five miles. Wendy shares, "It's not like the people who went five times a month were necessarily more motivated. The big difference here is the distance they had to travel. So making it easy for you to repeat a behavior seems to be key."&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Wendy has written for The Washington Post and the Los Angeles Times, and her work has been featured in The New York Times, Time magazine, and on NPR.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The Host&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
You can learn more about Curious Minds Host and Creator, Gayle Allen, and Producer and Editor, Rob Mancabelli, &lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/show-hosts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Episode Links&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ProfWendyWood" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;@ProfWendyWood&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://goodhabitsbadhabits.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;http://goodhabitsbadhabits.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Hyperfocus-More-Productive-World-Distraction/dp/0525522239" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Hyperfocus by Chris Bailey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
If You Like This Episode, You Might Also Enjoy:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/cm-131-james-clear-on-making-and-breaking-habits/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;James Clear on Making and Breaking Habits&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/cm-123-chris-bailey-on-overcoming-distraction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Chris Bailey on Overcoming Distraction&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/cm-117-john-zeratsky-on-creating-time-for-things-that-matter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;John Zeratsky on Creating Time for Things that Matter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/cm-110-laura-vanderkam-on-getting-more-done/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Laura Vanderkam on Getting More Done&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.net/cm-102-morten-hansen-on-working-smarter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Morten Hansen on Working Smarter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.gayleallen.</description><author>gayle@gayleallen.net (Curious Minds: Innovation in Life and Work)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8082217dfbea4a01ae3ea7a2538c8a99</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8082217dfbea4a01ae3ea7a2538c8a99/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 20:04:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rise &amp; Conquer Podcast : How to Level Up in 2020: Start doing this mindshift now</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Level up in 2020 with these simple mindset shifts that can transform your year! It’s time to take yourself seriously &amp; start showing up! This episode also includes journal prompts that will help you get clear on what you really want &amp; need from 2020.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;@riseandconquer.podcast&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;www.georgiestevenson.net/podcast&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@georgiestevenson.net (The Rise &amp; Conquer Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">97be32f7c9fa456989fb7b00b2468298</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/97be32f7c9fa456989fb7b00b2468298/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 11:58:30 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Adventures in Happiness with Jessica Ortner : Ep 81 – Setting Boundaries Will Set You Free with Nancy Levin</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src='https://tappingsolution.s3.amazonaws.com/adv-podcast/adv-levin.jpg' width='120'&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boundaries can be defined as the limits that we set around what we will or will not do, will or will not tolerate, and will or will not accept.  This is what we’re talking about in today’s episode, which is all about setting Boundaries for ourselves. Our guest today, the fabulous Nancy Levin, brings empowering insight that is relatable on so many levels. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you a people pleaser? Do you bend over backward to make sure that everyone has everything they need, and let your own wants and needs fall by the wayside? How are you willing to step up for yourself? These are just some of the questions we’ll be discussing as we talk about how you can take time and energy back, freed up to inhabit your own lives and create space for what YOU truly desire. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just remember that setting boundaries are between you and YOU…and just having this awareness will help you figure out where you’ve been sacrificing your own needs in life..in your career, your relationships and even your own well-being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.nancylevin.com/newbook' target='_blank' rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;img src='https://tappingsolution.s3.amazonaws.com/adv-podcast/boundaries-book.png' style='max-width:100%'&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Nancy:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Nancy Levin is a master coach and bestselling author of several books including her latest, Setting Boundaries Will Set You Free. Formerly the Event Director at Hay House for over a decade, Nancy now offers in-depth coaching and training programs designed to support clients in making themselves a priority and setting boundaries that stick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="inf_infusionsoft_bottom_trigger"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thetappingsolution.com/ep-81-setting-boundaries-will-set-free/"&gt;Ep 81 &amp;#8211; Setting Boundaries Will Set You Free with Nancy Levin&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thetappingsolution.com"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>positions@thetappingsolution.com (Adventures in Happiness with Jessica Ortner)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a3f1a3262a2c46188764aeff0e03fd09</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a3f1a3262a2c46188764aeff0e03fd09/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 06:33:23 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Balance Show : EP 19 - Danyele Wilson | Wine Down Wednesday</title><description>Danyele Wilson, AKA “D", has been an elite leader with Balance from the start. D is known for her inspirational AF Instagram stories, impressive strength workout routines, and goofy dancing Balance hauls. We took some time to sit and discuss all types of questions with D over some wine. Tune in for LOL-worthy and lighthearted humor rounded out with meaningful and thought-provoking stories. Cheers to 2020!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have a question or a topic you’d like to hear covered in the show? Reach out to our hosts directly at the accounts below or reach us at podcast@balanceathletica.com.&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/danyelewilson/"&gt;@danyelewilson&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/taychayy/"&gt;@taychayy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/chloe__chamberlain/"&gt;@chloe__chamberlain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/aligay/"&gt;@aligay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/thebalanceshow/"&gt;@thebalanceshow&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/balanceathletica/"&gt;@balanceathletica&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>taylor@balanceathletica.com (The Balance Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">634b37a980d74802b36b27567ba578f2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/634b37a980d74802b36b27567ba578f2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Terrible, Thanks For Asking : Ch-ch-ch-changes!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In life, the only thing that remains constant is change. As TTFA goes through our own major changes, we explore what change really means to us.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can catch up with TTFA on &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/ttfapodcast/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ttfapodcast"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/ttfapodcast"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; using @ttfapodcast. Nora&amp;#39;s Instagram is &lt;a href="https://instagram.com/noraborealis"&gt;@noraborealis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TTFA is public media. Which means we are supported by you. You can join us with a contribution at &lt;a href="http://ttfa.org/donate"&gt;ttfa.org/donate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@americanpublicmedia.org (Terrible, Thanks For Asking)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">64613fec08df406f9c1e975a742b9e75</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/64613fec08df406f9c1e975a742b9e75/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 10:24:07 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>