<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Cultural feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My cultural episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My Cultural feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 05:53:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>Ask An Artist : Ask an Artist Interviews Nick Bentley - Gallery Relationships from the Gallerist's Point of View</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Most artists want to get their work on the walls of a gallery, at least until someone buys it!&amp;nbsp; How do you get your work into a gallery?&amp;nbsp; What should the relationship be between you and your gallery?&amp;nbsp; Are there tings that you must never do when dealing with a gallery - and are there things that the gallery should not be doing?&amp;nbsp; In our second podcast interviewing Nick Bentley owner of Bils and Rye Gallery in Kirkbymoorside in North Yorkshire, Peter and Laura talk about how the relationship should work, how you might approach a gallery and gives some frank advice on things you should avoid.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@thetalentedmrb.co.uk (Ask An Artist)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9ab80c4836654240a61b991dbf909efb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9ab80c4836654240a61b991dbf909efb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Lunch Therapy : Ep. 24 -- Dr. Deanie Eichenstein Analyzes My Tuna Sandwich</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Buckle your seatbelts: for the first Lunch Therapy recorded in 2020, I decided to switch things around with an actual psychologist, Dr. Deanie Eichenstein, who puts my lunch under the microscope. Learn all about my pre-med years and my decision to go to law school, how I got from there to being a writer (meeting Craig in the process), and how choosing my lunch is often a question of shifting identities. We also cover how smell plays an important role for me, my fear of pooping in coffee shops, and how my people-pleasing instincts make it difficult not to go overboard at dinner parties. &lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>heyadamroberts@gmail.com (Lunch Therapy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a0a02ba2928449a895f0ddb1a7be9b54</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a0a02ba2928449a895f0ddb1a7be9b54/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Southern Glazers What Am I Drinking Podcast : Southern Glazers What Am I Drinking Podcast Episode 2 Jessica to Brian</title><description>The What Am I Drinking Podcast brings you highly credentialed experts from within the beverage industry to share what they love! What makes them and their brands unique? Find out here!  Our Instagram and Facebook @SGWSAcademy  Our email- NVBevAllies@sgws.com  &lt;span style="font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;audio controls=""&gt;&lt;source src="https://www.crntalk.com/podcast/Glazers/2019/Southern%20Glazers%20What%20Am%20I%20Drinking%20Podcast%20Episode%202%20Jessica%20to%20Brian.mp3"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;If you cannot see the audio controls, &lt;a href="https://www.crntalk.com/podcast/Glazers/2019/Southern%20Glazers%20What%20Am%20I%20Drinking%20Podcast%20Episode%202%20Jessica%20to%20Brian.mp3"&gt;listen/download the audio file here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/audio&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><author>noreply@blogger.com (Southern Glazers What Am I Drinking Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9218e62a4de04828a5a8c3148f9e840e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9218e62a4de04828a5a8c3148f9e840e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 15:10:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Catch and Kill Podcast with Ronan Farrow : Episode #5: The Hunt</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Harvey Weinstein’s criminal trial started a few days ago in New York City. The allegations against him were finally made public in October 2017, but whispers of Weinstein’s alleged abuse go back, literally, for decades. And so does the reporting on it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this episode, we’re going to look at the small but dogged community of reporters who spent years trying to break the story open, including two who got tantalizingly close - The New Yorker's, Ken Auletta, and The Hollywood Reporter's, Kim Masters. Taken together, their stories represent a decades-long, cross-country hunt for the hardest truth in Hollywood.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hiya@pineapple.fm (The Catch and Kill Podcast with Ronan Farrow)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">004c90e7c02e4eb380fad21f420fe694</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/004c90e7c02e4eb380fad21f420fe694/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Industry Seating : Ep 3: STL to Anaheim 2</title><description>STL was another burner, we get into it here and look on to Anaheim 2.</description><author>swizcore@me.com (Industry Seating)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">971d4c40a75942a3862f9a10b77d1779</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/971d4c40a75942a3862f9a10b77d1779/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 10:08:38 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Learn to Paint Podcast : Episode 7: Joan Fullerton</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, Fullerton discusses how she learned to distinguish the voice inside of her, how she teaches materials in her workshops&amp;nbsp; and why learning to critique your own work- the right way- is so important as a painter. Plus a whole lot more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>learntopaintpodcast@gmail.com (Learn to Paint Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f35d27c1191e4c00af35f11007b2cc15</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f35d27c1191e4c00af35f11007b2cc15/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 18:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Fred Minnick Show Podcast : Lindsay Ell, a Banana Fan, Finds Her Perfect Whiskey. She Also Talks About Stalkers, Losing Equipment and Her Fans</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Lindsay Ell is a dynamic musician with a bright future ahead of her. Shortly after owning the stage at the Hometown Rising Country Music and Whiskey Festival, she sat down with Fred and opened up about many personal details. What&amp;rsquo;s it like to be on the road? What does she drink? What are the challenges of being a famous musician? And most importantly, as Lindsay&amp;rsquo;s eyes gazed upon the sea of bourbon in Fred&amp;rsquo;s trailer, the whiskey critic started asking a series of questions that made her mouth water and get her excited to taste a bourbon she found quite tasty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this first episode, there&amp;rsquo;s also a little whiskey trivia and more about Fred than he intended to share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sponsors: &lt;a href="https://www.sfspiritscomp.com/"&gt;The San Francisco World Spirits Competition&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://michters.com/"&gt;Michter&amp;rsquo;s American Whiskey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;WHISKEY TRIVIA answer below the show notes....&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KEEP UP WITH FRED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free Drinks Newsletter: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.fredminnick.com&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://www.fredminnick.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bourbon Plus: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2FBourbonPlus.com&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://BourbonPlus.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spirits Network: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fexplore.spiritsnetwork.com%2Ffr&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://explore.spiritsnetwork.com/fr&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bourbon Pursuit: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2FBourbonPursuit.com&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://BourbonPursuit.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Ffredminnick%2F&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/fredminnick/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Ffred.minnick%2F&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/fred.minnick/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FFredMinnick&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://twitter.com/FredMinnick&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Books: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fs%3Fk%3Dfred%2Bminni&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://www.amazon.com/s?k=fred+minni&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOLLOW LINDSAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.lindsayell.com/"&gt;https://www.lindsayell.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/lindsayell"&gt;https://twitter.com/lindsayell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/lindsayell/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/lindsayell/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/officiallindsayell/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/officiallindsayell/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BMG granted a license to use Lindsay Ell&amp;rsquo;s music on this podcast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRIVIA Answer: President William Howard Taft&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When President William Howard Taft took office in 1909, there was mass confusion as to what whiskey was. The Pure Food &amp;amp; Drug Act had placed some limitations on medicinal marketing and given consumers an added layer of protection, but it really didn&amp;rsquo;t define whiskey types. So many distillers were adding food coloring to distilled molasses and calling it bourbon. In what became known as the Taft Decision, the president gave whiskey its first federal definitions. In his lengthy writings, he specifically called out the quality, noting:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Some time during the Civil War it was discovered that if raw whiskey as it came from the still, unrectified and without distillation, and thus containing one-half to one-sixth of 1 percent of fusel oil, was kept in oak barrels, the inside of the staves of which were charred, the tannic acid of the charred oak which found its way from the wood into the distilled spirits would color the raw white whiskey to the conventional color of American whiskey, and after some years would eliminate altogether the raw taste and the bad odor given the liquor by the fusel oil and would leave a smooth, delicate aroma, making the whiskey exceedingly palatable without the use of any additional flavoring or coloring. The whiskey thus made by one distillation and by the aging in charred oak barrels came to be known as &amp;ldquo;straight whiskey,&amp;rdquo; and to those who were good judges came to be regarded as the best and purest whiskey&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this decision, Taft is in the Kentucky Bourbon Hall of Fame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>assistant@fredminnick.com (The Fred Minnick Show Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3c40d2e4156047d381b532735bc62b7f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3c40d2e4156047d381b532735bc62b7f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 16:03:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dog Tales  : Duncan: In Search of the New World</title><description>&lt;p&gt;While most Americans know about the pilgrims who journeyed across the Atlantic aboard the Mayflower, few know of Duncan—the pilgrims' dog that witnessed many of the new nation's key formative moments, all while providing care and comfort to scared people in a new world.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>support@parcast.com (Dog Tales )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">721ba5f53646434ca9aff8c71b60cf56</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/721ba5f53646434ca9aff8c71b60cf56/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Fail With Elizabeth Day : S7, Ep3 How to Fail: Mabel</title><description>&lt;p&gt;My guest today has the middle name Alabama-Pearl, which is pretty cool but NOT QUITE AS COOL as the fact that she's a chart-topping pop-star who has racked up three top-10 hits and recently wrote one of the best Christmas songs of all time, &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hVzjR6hBArE'&gt;Loneliest Time of the Year&lt;/a&gt; (and I say that as a die-hard Mariah fan). Plus, my guest is still only 23 years old. Revolting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, that's right, it's &lt;a href='https://www.mabelofficial.com/'&gt;Mabel&lt;/a&gt;, a double Brit nominee and the creative brains behind the hit song &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9TQKyDD9Yig'&gt;Don’t Call Me Up&lt;/a&gt;, which was in the top 40 for four months. She was born in Malaga, went to school in Stockholm and now lives in London. Her creative lineage is quite something: Mabel's mother is &lt;a href='https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Neneh_Cherry'&gt;Neneh Cherry&lt;/a&gt;, her dad &lt;a href='https://www.instagram.com/theboogabear/?hl=en'&gt;Cameron McVey&lt;/a&gt; is a producer who has worked with Massive Attack, Portishead, All Saints and Sugababes, her uncle is &lt;a href='https://www.eagleeyecherry.com/'&gt;Eagle-Eye Cherry&lt;/a&gt; and her  step-grandfather is the legendary jazz musician &lt;a href='https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Don_Cherry_(trumpeter)'&gt;Don Cherry&lt;/a&gt;. But her talent and self-possession is all her own. Mabel joins me to talk about her failure to remember lyrics, her failure to stay vegan (which is hilarious) and her failure to sleep, which is a first on the podcast and I'm so glad she decided to broach the subject of insomnia as I know it effects so many of us and is such a debilitating thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Mabel, for coming on the podcast and doing your research so well that you actually read my book first. I heart you hard for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Talking of that book...the Sunday Times Top 5 bestselling book of the podcast, How To Fail: Everything I've Ever Learned From Things Going Wrong is out now in paperback and available to buy &lt;a href='https://www.amazon.co.uk/How-Fail-Everything-Learned-Things/dp/0008327327/ref=asap_bc?ie=UTF8'&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;* &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;This episode is sponsored by &lt;a href='https://welcometomeya.com/'&gt;MEYA&lt;/a&gt;, a new meditation app that uses the power of music to switch you into a meditative state. Download the app &lt;a href='https://welcometomeya.com/'&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to experience the power of MEYA mind journeys and a new way to fit meditation into your daily routine this January. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;How To Fail With Elizabeth Day is hosted by Elizabeth Day, produced by Naomi Mantin and Chris Sharp. We love hearing from you! To contact us, email &lt;a href='mailto:email:%20howtofail@gmail.com'&gt;howtofailpod@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p2"&gt;* &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Social Media:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Elizabeth Day &lt;a href='https://twitter.com/elizabday'&gt;@elizabday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Mabel &lt;a href='https://twitter.com/Mabel?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor'&gt;@Mabel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;MEYA &lt;a href='https://twitter.com/meya_app'&gt;@meya_app&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p2"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p2"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p2"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>elizabethdayjournalist@gmail.com (How To Fail With Elizabeth Day)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8c932efbc77247309d2c8a2a136e03cf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8c932efbc77247309d2c8a2a136e03cf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Splendid Table : 675: The Food of Thailand</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Explore the regional flavors of Thailand and learn why there are so many Thai restaurants in the U.S. Plus, lessons on curry paste and coconut milk.&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>contact@splendidtable.org (The Splendid Table)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c3c433e52e23449789ac38cd108c704f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c3c433e52e23449789ac38cd108c704f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Green Eggs and Dan : Introducing Food, We Need to Talk</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Food, We Need to Talk is a new podcast from WBUR about one woman's quest to end her war with food. Hosts Juna Gjata and Dr. Eddie Phillips wield solid science, medical knowledge, common sense and an endless supply of dad jokes to teach us how to eat better and feel better about it. Hint: It’s not dieting. They discuss exercise, body image, food addiction, genetics, weight loss and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen and subscribe today on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/food-we-need-to-talk/id1490621476"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; or wherever you listen to podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>listen@thepodglomerate.com (Green Eggs and Dan)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3ee9bcc77d964506bcc98ea254b0c32c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3ee9bcc77d964506bcc98ea254b0c32c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Overdue : Ep 396 - The Testaments, by Margaret Atwood</title><description>&lt;p&gt;To put it mildly, a lot of stuff has happened since we released &lt;a href="https://overduepodcast.com/episodes/2014/12/1/episode-089-the-handmaids-tale" target="_blank"&gt;our episode on The Handmaid's Tale back in 2014&lt;/a&gt;. Among that stuff is the release of The Testaments, the 2019 sequel to the original book and a companion piece of sorts to the Hulu television series.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>overduepod@gmail.com (Overdue)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e032d6b874884cbc882449c48531399b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e032d6b874884cbc882449c48531399b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind The Icing  : Gettin’ Social With It</title><description>In this episode we chat with Malek from Frosted By Malek and Ashley from Crumbs about social media and your business.</description><author>podcasts26+fb14450@anchor.fm (Behind The Icing )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">94ed501e0b4646da8c358e0c93d5bfa4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/94ed501e0b4646da8c358e0c93d5bfa4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 07:31:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hunt, Gather, Talk with Hank Shaw : Bobwhite Quail</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode of Hunt Gather Talk, we are delving deep into Gentleman Bob, the bobwhite quail. we are paying special attention to why this iconic game bird is disappearing from part of its habitat.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>scrbblr@hotmail.com (Hunt, Gather, Talk with Hank Shaw)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ad324bfd3e5c4f88b97970d2a03d289d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ad324bfd3e5c4f88b97970d2a03d289d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 05:25:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Wild Ones Wedding Photography : Evelyn Grace - Putting ‘YOU’ Into Your Brand</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Putting ‘YOU’ Into Your Brand with EVELYN GRACE&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I am a huge fan of Evelyn Grace and since chatting I am an even bigger fan. She drops so many wise words in this podcast. Listen to this podcast if you are unsure how to serve your clients better and offer more value. Evelyn is a big fan of putting the ‘you’ into your brand and I talk to her about where her sparkly confidence comes from and how we too can achieve it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;www.evelyngrace.com&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow Evie&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;www.instagram.com/evelyngrace&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Evie &amp; Lindsey Romans workshop brand where they share SO much free advice!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;www.instagram.com/theheartuniversity&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Listen to Evie &amp; Lindsey’s podcast - a must for all entrepreneurs! The Heart &amp; Hustle podcast.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-heart-hustle-podcast/id1487265198&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;------------------------&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;www.instagram.com/nicoladixonphotographyco&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;www.instagram.com/wildonescommunity&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nicola@nicoladixonphotography.com (Wild Ones Wedding Photography)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7ef6c87712e749beb393cd0a8c69bb6c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7ef6c87712e749beb393cd0a8c69bb6c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Backcountry Gallery's Wildlife Photography Podcast : Keep Shootin’, Mirrorless Future, Box Talk, VR And Tripods</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, we&amp;#8217;ll talk about the importance of knowing when to stop shooting and when to keep going. From there, we&amp;#8217;ll talk about when it&amp;#8217;s time to upgrade to mirrorless, if you should keep your boxes (yeah, it&amp;#8217;s weird), and if you should use VR / Stabilization when using a tripod.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Lots of great stuff this time, so grab a warm drink, your favorite earbuds, and take a listen.  &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://backcountrygallery.com/keep-shootin-mirrorless-future-box-talk-vr-and-tripods/"&gt;Keep Shootin&amp;#8217;, Mirrorless Future, Box Talk, VR And Tripods&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://backcountrygallery.com"&gt;Backcountry Gallery&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>steve@bcgphotos.com (Backcountry Gallery's Wildlife Photography Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">da45debbc41e4a1e928e4b081de94a0b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/da45debbc41e4a1e928e4b081de94a0b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 05:53:01 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Love of Jewelers: A Jewelry Journey Podcast : 03: Tim McCreight, Books from the Bench</title><description>&lt;p&gt;While working on his iconic volume, &lt;em&gt;The Complete Metalsmith&lt;/em&gt;, Tim McCreight imagined, “What if silver was writing this?” In 1985 he started Brynmorgen Press to provide practical, bench-tested textbooks on metalsmithing and design. Decades later his experiential approach to research led him to co-found the Toolbox Initiative, which delivers new and gently-used tools and silver to jewelers in Africa.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join Tim and Courtney as they discuss what makes a great jewelry book, the generosity of the jewelry community, and “partnering with metal.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(P.S.: You’ll also get a sneak preview of an upcoming book by Toolbox Initiative co-founder Matthieu Cheminée!)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>avantcreative@gmail.com (For the Love of Jewelers: A Jewelry Journey Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">83920c2de7f54c89b3828074c82f3647</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/83920c2de7f54c89b3828074c82f3647/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>What's Cooking with Paula Deen : Paula and Chef Jenna Kinard make a super-decadent take on PB&amp;J</title><description>P.B. and Jealous! You'll be jealous when Chef Jenna Kinard returns with Paula as the two have fun in the kitchen preparing Jenna's decadent take on PB&amp;J.&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/WhatsCookingWithPaulaDeen/~4/I8tHzTcFUJ4" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>info@compassmedianetworks.com (What's Cooking with Paula Deen)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">979d7682a17443eaafc3249a5df4aa35</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/979d7682a17443eaafc3249a5df4aa35/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Photography Radio : Magnum's Take on Pantone, Manfrotto Memory Cards, Instagram Blocks Fake Images, No Photos In Vogue</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;"Take's Take" with Take Kayo.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Every Friday Take dives into everything what's new and interesting in the world of photography - including digital, analogue, mobile, and everything in between. &lt;br&gt;Enjoy!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Today's Show Links&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.magnumphotos.com/arts-culture/design/classic-blue-magnum-archive-design-fashion-pantone/"&gt;Magnum's Take on Pantone's Classic Blue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.manfrotto.com/us-en/products/memory-cards/"&gt;Manfrotto Memory Cards&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://instagram-press.com/blog/2019/12/16/combatting-misinformation-on-instagram/"&gt;Instagram Blocking "Fake" Images&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vogue.it/moda/article/vogue-italia-gennaio-editoriale-direttore"&gt;Italian Vogue Without Images&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Featured photographer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Xyza Cruz Bacani (&lt;a href="http://www.xyzacruzbacani.com"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href="https://instagram.com/xyzacruzbacani"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head over to &lt;a href="http://www.photographyradio.com"&gt;www.photographyradio.com&lt;/a&gt; and scroll to the bottom of the page to send in your comment on today's show. We would absolutely love to hear from you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have a great light!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tomash@photographyradio.com (Photography Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">aceb75611f154d269fe471efed29a61f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/aceb75611f154d269fe471efed29a61f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Boomtown : A Thin Line | Chapter 6</title><description>&lt;p&gt;During booms, the Permian Basin sees a rise in prostitution charges. But misperceptions and stereotypes about sex work have led to policies that may actually harm the women involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SimpliSafe: &lt;/strong&gt;Get free shipping plus a 60-day money-back guarantee at &lt;a href="SimpliSafe.com/boomtown"&gt;SimpliSafe.com/boomtown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@imperativeentertainment.com (Boomtown)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a68920e9854647999ad1f92c0dec60fd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a68920e9854647999ad1f92c0dec60fd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:20:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>It Never Gets Old : Industry Lingo &amp; Listener Letters</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode Meredith gives a quick primer on all the lingo in secondhand - from resale to vintage to pre-loved. Then Meredith and Sarah respond to some listener letters: from Gucci loafers to first-time Poshmark haggling.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>hello@ingopodcast.com (It Never Gets Old)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b6575df6314148d4aac6513ddb7e647c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b6575df6314148d4aac6513ddb7e647c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 07:51:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Food In Five : The best chili ever</title><description>It's a bold statement to call some the best. But I stand behind it. This is the best chili ever. See for yourself

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/foodinfive/message</description><author>podcasts4+8152@anchor.fm (Food In Five)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">05f34a559a62492d9b786e69d9c47b71</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/05f34a559a62492d9b786e69d9c47b71/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 03:02:15 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Server Life Podcast : Episode 6 - Why do YOU serve?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Pres and Connor share some of your responses as to why you currently serve. Some of the reasons range from simply getting money to overcoming anxiety.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts33+11e2cd0c@anchor.fm (The Server Life Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">714682065b5c43f6bbc029e67218bed0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/714682065b5c43f6bbc029e67218bed0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 12:52:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Flipping the Table : S2 -  Ep#1 - Peter Hoffman, NYC’s most thoughtful activist chef</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Chef Hoffman shares his unique culinary journey, including how he catalyzed farm to table in the Big Apple.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mail@rootsofchange.org (Flipping the Table)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4cb5cbec89d1474ab3afd943333b370a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4cb5cbec89d1474ab3afd943333b370a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>888-Barbara : 09: Divorce Your Husband Tomorrow</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We all have that friend who’s divorcing her husband “tomorrow,” but my first caller this week really is! With finances to worry about, how will her divorce play out? And later, I speak with a mom who’s going through the same heartbreak I've faced: the empty nest. Together, we come up with a plan to fill the void. Listen in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Got a problem? Call me at 888-Barbara. Nothing’s off limits, so what are you waiting for?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>lila@barbaracorcoran.com (888-Barbara)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">04d98a5f87ac4963856a0942defa4ace</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/04d98a5f87ac4963856a0942defa4ace/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Austin All Day  : Sawyer &amp; Co - Chef Alex Amaro and Chef Ricky Flores (Ep.58)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Chef Alex Amaro and Chef Ricky Flores of Sawyer &amp;amp; Co join the Austin All Day podcast.&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sawyerand.co/"&gt;https://www.sawyerand.co/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="https://www.patreon.com/join/Austinallday"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>austinalldaypodcast@gmail.com (Austin All Day )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">58dc1c5ddd904a5eabf5909aaec72023</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/58dc1c5ddd904a5eabf5909aaec72023/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Young Rocker : E2: BASS PLAYER</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Young Chelsea brings us back to the strange landscape of middle school and recounts how she discovered and fell in love with her favorite band and playing bass. Old Chelsea provides some much-needed advice about making and keeping friends.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>cursin@gmail.com (Dear Young Rocker)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c3cacb3af7f24d038530bf0033e6162b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c3cacb3af7f24d038530bf0033e6162b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 21:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Art Side of Life : Ep.210: Interview with community members - Donovan, Visi and Keshna (YouTube 20k subs giveaway)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey, guys! This is another special episode with the winners of the Art Side of Life YouTube 20k giveaway. I chat with Donovan (Fantasy &amp; Mythology illustrator from Texas), Visi (Freelance illustrator from Colorado) and Keshna (Illustrator from New Jersey) about their artistic journey and tips for the artistic community. Enjoy!!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show notes: &lt;a href= "https://artsideoflife.com/community-donovan-visi-keshna" target= "_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://artsideoflife.com/community-donovan-visi-keshna&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Special offer for Art Side of Life listeners&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;💲&lt;a href="https://artsideoflife.com/make-money-pod" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;How to Make Money as an Artist Course&lt;/a&gt; - Proven ways to a creative career you will love!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;🎓&lt;a href="https://artsideoflife.com/evolve-pod" target= "_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Evolve Artist Program&lt;/a&gt; -  better than an art college education and only at a fraction of the cost - World’s Simplest Art Training Method*&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;🎨&lt;a href="https://artsideoflife.com/color-pod" target= "_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Storytelling with Color and Light Course&lt;/a&gt; - make your artworks more believable and appealing&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;📚🎧&lt;a href= "https://artsideoflife.com/audible-pod"&gt;Audible&lt;/a&gt; - 2 audiobooks FREE - learn by listening to hundreds of books&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Please note: I am Evolve's affiliate partner, meaning I get paid a small commission (at no extra cost to you) if you use my link to make a purchase. Thank you for supporting Art Side of Life!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe to Art Side of Life Podcast to get notified when I post new episodes!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://artsideoflife.com/itunes"&gt;https://artsideoflife.com/itunes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://artsideoflife.com/spotify"&gt;https://artsideoflife.com/spotify&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow me on Instagram&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/art_side_of_life/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/art_side_of_life/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/ivkam/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/ivkam/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe to Art Side of Life&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://artsideoflife.com/subscribe"&gt;https://artsideoflife.com/subscribe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thanks for listening!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Special thanks to Donovan, Visi and Keshna for joining me today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you enjoyed this interview please let me know with a review, hopefully, 5 stars because I would like to reach many artists like you!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;See you in the next episode :) Bye!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@artsideoflife.com (Art Side of Life)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">81b3c4b8a9b5472391b95e9cf4c165d1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/81b3c4b8a9b5472391b95e9cf4c165d1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Landscape Photography Show : Beyond the Typical Photo With Joshua Snow</title><description>&lt;p class=""&gt;Joshua Snow joins The Landscape Photography Show to discuss how he creates photographs and composites in landscape photography.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>davidjohnstonphoto@gmail.com (The Landscape Photography Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">87fcfd9bb3d943078a243f352a6d1281</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/87fcfd9bb3d943078a243f352a6d1281/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 04:50:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Conversations About Art : Helen Molesworth</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Helen Molesworth is a Los Angeles-based writer and curator. She recently released “Recording Artists,” a podcast series in conjunction with the Getty and she is the curator-in-residence at the Anderson Ranch Arts Center. We talked about why it’s a great thing when works of art make you cry, personal and institutional legacy, and where the divine or faith shows up in art.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts38+f5e7e78@anchor.fm (Conversations About Art)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">918c755811b44cbc86b13aeab363bb1f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/918c755811b44cbc86b13aeab363bb1f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bow Down: Women in Art : Zoe Whitley on Kathleen Collins</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hayward Gallery curator, and co-curator of the blockbuster touring exhibition ‘Soul of a Nation’ discusses the life and work of Kathleen Collins, the first African-American woman to write and direct a feature film. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>editorial@frieze.com (Bow Down: Women in Art)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5e41e12fa2bf473e8aa648e1c1c455a2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5e41e12fa2bf473e8aa648e1c1c455a2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 06:47:11 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sporkful : 1 | Live: Notes From A Young Black Chef</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Kwame Onwuachi learns to cook in the middle of the ocean... In the past year, Kwame Onwuachi has become one of the fastest rising star chefs in America. His DC restaurant, Kith and Kin, is widely considered one of the best in the country. But he went through countless twists and turns to get there. His story is so wild that he wrote a memoir, Notes From A Young Black Chef, that's now being made into a movie starring Lakeith Stanfield. This week Kwame shares the first half of that story live on stage, in conversation with Dan, at the Miracle Theatre in Washington, DC.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>dan@sporkful.com (The Sporkful)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">37eda11a030542eb8a935674e48e09be</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/37eda11a030542eb8a935674e48e09be/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>This is Joy &amp; Claire : 3: Dietary Pedestals</title><description>&lt;br /&gt;
Identifying and getting past diet rules, loving bread and pop tarts, Joy&amp;#8217;s Peloton treadmill updates, down with Jillian Michaels, and Lizzo love!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Sponsors: &lt;a rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label=" (opens in a new tab)" href="http://www.blublox.com" target="_blank"&gt;BLUBLOX&lt;/a&gt; discount code GGW&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Please leave us a review! We love hearing your feedback and want to make this show the best it can be for YOU, amazing listeners. Share with a friend while you&amp;#8217;re at it!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="GGW Instagram (opens in a new tab)" href="https://www.instagram.com/joyandclaire_/?hl=en" target="_blank"&gt;Joy &amp;amp; Claire Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Support the podcast! Subcribe and REVIEW wherever you listen to the podcasts. &lt;br /&gt;</description><author>thisisjoyandclaire@gmail.com (This is Joy &amp; Claire)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">dccc3a18e7474f9bb6ecedcf4e83e1f0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/dccc3a18e7474f9bb6ecedcf4e83e1f0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 23:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Cliff Dorfman Show : Laz Alonso Pt 2.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Laz Alonso can not be contained to one episode! Laz continues to share his journey. From being written out of a UPN and an NBC pilot and persevering only to end up in some of the biggest movies and franchises of all time.  &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>starburnsaudio@starburnsind.com (The Cliff Dorfman Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b06ddf619b454a29b621b774011458f4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b06ddf619b454a29b621b774011458f4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Alice | Interior Design : Builder Grade to Custom | Ways to Make your Home Unique</title><description>In this episode of Dear Alice, we give some advice on making a &lt;br /&gt;builder-grade home feel more custom. If you are looking to upgrade, update or just freshen up your existing home, join us as we walk through multiple ways to achieve that. From simple changes like changing out your kitchen hardware or adding window coverings to updating your builder-grade lighting to something a little more interesting, there are so many ways to give your home a little more personality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lighting 3:31&lt;br /&gt;Hardware 11:03&lt;br /&gt;Window Coverings/Stair Runners 15:57&lt;br /&gt;Large Scale 23:08&lt;br /&gt;Fireplace/Mantle &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Everything that’s affordable is going to be small and that’s gonna make you play small and it’s going to make your house look really cheap.” 23:19&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/alicelaneinteriors/" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/alicelaneinteriors/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/alicelanehome/" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/alicelanehome/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://alicelanehome.com/" rel="noopener"&gt;https://alicelanehome.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/AliceLaneHome" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/AliceLaneHome&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pinterest.com/alicelanehome/" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.pinterest.com/alicelanehome/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/alicelanehomecollectionsaltlakecity" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/alicelanehomecollectionsaltlakecity&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>contact@launchpod.media (Dear Alice | Interior Design)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">38a7c56e2aba4dd6a087410a7ea90718</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/38a7c56e2aba4dd6a087410a7ea90718/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 03:00:18 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Photography Insights - important industry interviews by Phlogger : Interview with Bellamy from Japan Camera Hunter</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For episode 74 we bring you the man behind Japan Camera Hunter, yes its Bellamy Hunt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bellamy is at the forefront for those in search of their dream cameras. &amp;nbsp;In fact, his business works around this idea of sourcing cameras in high-end condition. &amp;nbsp;But this isn’t all that Bellamy is know for. &amp;nbsp;Of course, there is his own 35mm film too! Called JCH Streetpan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He’s been around the analogue photography scene a long time as a blogger too, with reviews and articles on current news. &amp;nbsp;In fact, you might know him from his writing skills and honesty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this episode we talk about:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;The industry of sourcing camera&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Japanese customs&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Blogging&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Amazon&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Confidentiality&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Trends &amp;amp; travelling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Of course a hint of a few rare cameras&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the random questions, we discuss horse riding and the UK. &amp;nbsp;As usual, check out the website for links and sign up for the newsletter, that way you will always know about the latest work and podcast episodes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LINKS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website - &lt;a href="https://www.japancamerahunter.com/"&gt;https://www.japancamerahunter.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram - &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/japancamerahunter/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/japancamerahunter/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PAY IT FORWARD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bellamy wants to recommend - &lt;a href="http://www.tamarkin.com/blog"&gt;http://www.tamarkin.com/blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/photography-insights/message</description><author>podcasts6+3417154@anchor.fm (Photography Insights - important industry interviews by Phlogger)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">368f2bdc9d1247048de3f99d4df3ceed</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/368f2bdc9d1247048de3f99d4df3ceed/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 13:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mixed Podcast : Season 1 Trailer: What is Mixed Podcast? - Mixed Podcast</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Get a taste of what Mixed Podcast will be like, from chefs and home cooks, to eaters industry leaders who are often forgotten in the food we enjoy. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@mixedpodcast.com (Mixed Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7b96c5a69ba3456b90f1d932c7cb53b6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7b96c5a69ba3456b90f1d932c7cb53b6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:59:38 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Baron of Botox : Origin Story | Chapter 2</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A peek behind the curtain and into Fredric Sheldon Brandt's challenging and formative years in post-World-War-II Newark, where his parents run a candy shop. Young Fred is exceptionally bright, but...different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BetterHelp: &lt;/strong&gt;Get 10% off your first month at &lt;a href="https://www.betterhelp.com/start/?go=true&amp;amp;transaction_id=102ff4dcbf10519e9fb78331432dea&amp;amp;utm_source=podcast&amp;amp;utm_campaign=1705&amp;amp;utm_medium=Desktop&amp;amp;utm_content=&amp;amp;utm_term=baron&amp;amp;not_found=1&amp;amp;gor=start"&gt;BetterHelp.com/baron&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@imperativeentertainment.com (The Baron of Botox)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0c49fa83606a480ea9a8d081939fd9ac</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0c49fa83606a480ea9a8d081939fd9ac/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Couple Things with Shawn and Andrew : Embarrassing</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Episode 3 of Couple Things with Shawn and Andrew is a fun one. Today we walk you guys through some of our most embarrassing moments together that we've never shared before. &amp;nbsp;Though it all, we've learned that nobody is perfect and at the end of the day, we're all human :) We'd love to hear your thoughts on this episode &amp;amp; if you've ever been embarrassed in front of your significant other.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you haven't yet, please rate and subscribe to the show to hear more! And if you have suggestions/recommendations for the show, send us your ideas in a video format - we might just choose yours! Email us at couplethingspod@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts44+415382c@anchor.fm (Couple Things with Shawn and Andrew)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">47e9a90812f548598b9b9a57a30b2660</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/47e9a90812f548598b9b9a57a30b2660/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 07:17:43 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Unlocking Us with Brené Brown : Introducing: Unlocking Us</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Join researcher and #1 &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; best-selling author Brené Brown as she unpacks and explores the ideas, stories, experiences, books, films, and music that reflect the universal experiences of being human, from the bravest moments to the most brokenhearted.  Subscribe now for updates.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@cadence13.com (Unlocking Us with Brené Brown)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cc1fdde05fdd4c0bbd9a88e18eb2cbee</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cc1fdde05fdd4c0bbd9a88e18eb2cbee/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 09:26:52 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Blood Ties Podcast : 2: S05E02: The White House Farm Murders</title><description>Jeremy Bamber is one of few prisoners in the UK facing a whole life term. He was found guilty in October 1986 of the murders of his parents, his sister and her six-year-old twin sons. The shooting of the family in August 1985, in the parents' farmhouse in Essex, England, came to be known as the White House Farm murders. 
BOOK: Three Hours by Rosamund Lupton. CREDITS: Produced by Poppy Damon. CONTACT: Twitter: @BloodTies_Pod Instagram: bloodties_pod Email: bloodties.podcast@gmail.com</description><author>poppydamon@gmail.com (Blood Ties Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e492fcf8f0564c1db1e9748fa3989be9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e492fcf8f0564c1db1e9748fa3989be9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 21:40:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Susan Nethercote Studio Insider Art Podcast : Let's Talk About Self-Sabotage.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to episode 9 of the Studio Insider Art Podcast. This week’s conversation examines self-sabotage and it’s attempts to derail our art practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We dive in to how it presents and how you can set up your creative space with the ambiance to nurture creative flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Leaning on your support network, including professional help when you’re feeling all the feelings&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Having compassion for yourself when the going gets tough&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Laura’s strategy for managing negative self-talk&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Identifying where you’re self-sabotaging your art practice.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Using self-care practices to create structure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you enjoy the episode,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;X Suze&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LINKS FOR THIS EPISODE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Laura’s artwork discussed in this episode:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B3q9dTOhFLZ/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; https://www.instagram.com/p/B3q9dTOhFLZ/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Susan Nethercote:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/susan.nethercote/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.instagram.com/susan.nethercote/&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/susannethercoteart/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.facebook.com/susannethercoteart/&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laura Day:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/laurajaneday/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.instagram.com/laurajaneday/&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/laura.day.73594"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.facebook.com/laura.day.73594&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Susan's free education resources: &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.susannethercotestudio.com/free"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.susannethercotestudio.com/free&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Susan's art website: &lt;a href="https://www.susannethercote.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.susannethercote.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts24+fa59f10@anchor.fm (Susan Nethercote Studio Insider Art Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7adc47a31ee343c5969cf1a0ecec98f9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7adc47a31ee343c5969cf1a0ecec98f9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 20:32:18 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Here &amp; Now : Trump's Impeachment Legal Team; Bloomberg Outspends Rivals</title><description>Ken Starr and Alan Dershowitz are set to join Trump's impeachment legal team. Barbara McQuade, former U.S. attorney for the Eastern District of Michigan, joins us to discuss what this means for Trump's legal team. Former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg has spent more on ads in his campaign for president than any of his rivals for the Democratic nomination. Ken Goldstein, a professor at the University of San Francisco, joins us to discuss.</description><author>webmaster@wbur.org (Here &amp; Now)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">067f01878623457695b106149c2d84fb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/067f01878623457695b106149c2d84fb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 11:06:16 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Eat Live Love Indulge with Kathy Wakile : Eat Pray Love</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Kathy gets together with artisan handbag designer and style expert Jen Mascali. A native New Yorker, Jen shares the journey that led her to craft her passion and dreams in Italy after losing her father on 9/11.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't forget to follow me on Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook - &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/kathywakile/"&gt;@kathywakile&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter - &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/KathyWakile"&gt;@KathyWakile&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram - &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/kathywakile/?hl=en"&gt;@kathywakile&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/indulgebykathywakile/"&gt;@indulgebykathywakile&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>digitalservices@entercom.com (Eat Live Love Indulge with Kathy Wakile)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5f9cab02df9a4273acb77992fcdb8fc8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5f9cab02df9a4273acb77992fcdb8fc8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The KLN Podcast : 8: Triple D</title><description>&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img src="https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-1024x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1183" srcset="https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-1024x1024.png 1024w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-300x300.png 300w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-150x150.png 150w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-768x768.png 768w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-500x500.png 500w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-200x200.png 200w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-1536x1536.png 1536w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Discipline isn&amp;#8217;t supposed to be enjoyable so why must it even be something we want to achieve? Listen to some ways I&amp;#8217;ve learned to embrace this in my life and where I&amp;#8217;m confident the discipline will lead me.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-audio"&gt;&lt;audio controls src="https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Episode-8.mp3"&gt;&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description><author>info@karalewisnewton.com (The KLN Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bf6558443240451da1263feb2b91c25c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bf6558443240451da1263feb2b91c25c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 03:05:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>TRAINED : Shaquem Griffin | How to Maintain Your Confidence in the Face of “No”</title><description>&lt;p&gt;When Shaquem Griffin was 4, he had his left hand amputated. Growing up, that didn’t hold him back from much, including playing football—even though most of his coaches, players, and friends didn’t think he’d ever be able to make more than a hobby of it. Shaquem, now a linebacker for the Seattle Seahawks, holds some of his sport’s top awards and has certainly proved his doubters wrong. In addition to training and practicing relentlessly, Shaquem has spent his entire life honing an unbreakable never-give-up mindset. It’s what has allowed him to defy expectations and develop unwavering self-confidence that has taken him all the way to the top. In this episode, Shaquem breaks down how his approach to self-talk, recovery, nutrition, and more helped him achieve what seemed like an impossible dream.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TRAINED is produced by Nike Training Club Pro. The best of Nike. Exclusively for Trainers. To apply, go to &lt;a href="https://www.nike.com/us/en_us/e/training/nike-training-club-pro"&gt;nike.com/ntcpro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inspired by TRAINED? Then you’ll love Nike Training Club app. The Nike Training Club app provides expertly designed workouts from Nike trainers for everyone at all fitness levels. It’s the ultimate training source from the leading minds at Nike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With holistic tips on movement, recovery, nutrition, mindset and sleep from experts on Nike’s Performance Council, NTC delivers on all five facets of fitness and puts our best at your fingertips. No matter how you train, NTC will help you discover your personal greatness. Click the link below to get the app for iOS or Android.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://smart.link/5b59e1c79378b"&gt;Download Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>max@pineapple.fm (TRAINED)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d4569bbd8ae941acba9b482fce9b33c3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d4569bbd8ae941acba9b482fce9b33c3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 02:00:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Adulting Like A Mother Father : Evanna Lynch (Harry Potter films, Kinder Beauty) joins the show to talk on-set romances, co-founding Kinder Beauty, and the importance of self care.</title><description>Accomplished actor, activist entrepreneur Evanna Lynch plays a candid round of 30 in 30 with our hosts, exposing some on-set flirtations and explaining her journey with self care and confidence both personally and professionally.</description><author>info@podcastone.com (Adulting Like A Mother Father)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">be86cdab345647b5906f02c302705ce1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/be86cdab345647b5906f02c302705ce1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Magnus Archives : ANNOUNCEMENT - RQ Streams!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It's time for a new video project - RQ Streams - with Mike LeBeau (Head of Video; Tim Stoker) and Anil Godigamuwe (Community Manager) as your guides &amp;amp; fellow explorers through the worlds of gaming! And thank you so much to everyone for your support to make things like this possible!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join us weekly on &lt;strong&gt;Saturdays, at 3pm GMT - starting 25th January 2020 - at www.twitch.tv/rusty_quill&lt;/strong&gt; !&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Music&lt;/strong&gt;: "The Messenger" by Silent Partner via the Youtube Audio Library&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join our community:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WEBSITE: &lt;a href="http://rustyquill.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;rustyquill.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FACEBOOK: &lt;a href="https://facebook.com/therustyquill" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;facebook.com/therustyquill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TWITTER: @therustyquill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;REDDIT: &lt;a href="https://reddit.com/r/RustyQuill" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;reddit.com/r/RustyQuill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DISCORD: &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/KckTv8y" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;https://discord.gg/KckTv8y&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMAIL: &lt;a href="mailto:mail@rustyquill.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;mail@rustyquill.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>alexander.j.newall@gmail.com (The Magnus Archives)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e4e11fa011714500a3d598fb57482002</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e4e11fa011714500a3d598fb57482002/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 14:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Get Your Shoot Together Photography Podcast : Episode 033 - Must Love In Person Education</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Dogs may be man's best friend, but they certainly aren't Kira's. This week, Kira tells about facing her fears for the sake of a good project while Mary tries to relate. The girls also discuss the pros and cons of online VS in person learning as they both get ready to go to Texas School. Have a listen hopefully while you are on your way to Imaging USA!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>girl@getyourshoottogether.com (Get Your Shoot Together Photography Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">27dbec71715a4c769e73c2f656e0edd2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/27dbec71715a4c769e73c2f656e0edd2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Booty and the Beast Podcast : Kiara Mia talks dating, love and intimacy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Booty and the beast podcast with your hosts @sammysamla and @hoeassariel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guest @theonlykiaramia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by @innoutmanager www.aikoplus.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episode sponsors @hollowtipscalifornia @448gofficial @shopatfamily and AV Justice Law Firm.&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/d705500/podcast/sponsor/acugj9/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts14+d705500@anchor.fm (Booty and the Beast Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">027e5c3712c64b2f93632bb4c294f5dc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/027e5c3712c64b2f93632bb4c294f5dc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Date Night with Raven &amp; Adam : 8: 2020 Resolutions</title><description>&lt;div&gt;What are your goals for 2020? Lose weight? Increase your income? Decrease debt? Travel more? Curse less? Raven and Adam read your resolutions and share theirs for the new year. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Have a question for Raven or Adam? Slip into their DMs: &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/ravennicolegates/?hl=en"&gt;@ravennicolegates&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/adam_gottschalk/?hl=en"&gt;@adam_gottschalk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This episode is sponsored by: &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://withjoy.com/"&gt;Joy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.scentbird.com/"&gt;Scentbird&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Music by &lt;a href="https://freemusicarchive.org/music/Jahzzar"&gt;Jahzzar&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;Licensed under &lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/"&gt;Creative Commons: By Attribution 4.0 License&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>rss@audioboom.com (Date Night with Raven &amp; Adam)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a34a58cff37c43a1b2eddff9e22ea2d5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a34a58cff37c43a1b2eddff9e22ea2d5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Stitch Please : Cirque de SEWING--A chat with SewMuchAerial</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Mentioned in this episode&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/sewmuchaerial/" target="_blank"&gt;SewMuchAerial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.etsy.com/shop/rissewn/" target="_blank"&gt;Marissa's etsy page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aerialympics.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Aerialympics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://patterns.bootstrapfashion.com/diy-dress-form-sewing-pattern.html" target="_blank"&gt;Custom Dressform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.etsy.com/listing/698609304/swatch-set-9?ref=shop_home_active_9&amp;sca=1" target="_blank"&gt;Sheer Performance Fabrics with Melanin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support the Stitch Please podcast and Black Women Stitch. You can get an adorable enamel pin by sending $15 to Paypal or Cash App.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/blackwomenstitch" target="_blank"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.paypal.me/lisalovestosew"&gt;Paypal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/blackwomenstitch" target="_blank"&gt;Ko-Fi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://cash.app/$LisaWoolfork" target="_blank"&gt;Cash App&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>woolfork@gmail.com (Stitch Please)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">88685cb65d3b4d1d9436cb4b8c766cef</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/88685cb65d3b4d1d9436cb4b8c766cef/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 04:00:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Jungle Prince : Chapter 3: A House in Yorkshire</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In a ruined palace in the woods, rummaging through discarded papers, our reporter finds a clue.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (Jungle Prince)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6aed018c09d6440a8a0d8647281b5714</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6aed018c09d6440a8a0d8647281b5714/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:23:16 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Poetry Unbound : Welcome to Poetry Unbound</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Poetry Unbound&lt;/i&gt; features an immersive exploration of a single poem, guided by Pádraig Ó Tuama. Short and unhurried; contemplative and energizing. Proudly produced by On Being Studios.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This season features poetry from a diverse cast of poets: current and former poets laureate Joy Harjo and Tracy K. Smith; T.S. Eliot Prize winner Ocean Vuong; classic poets like Emily Dickinson and Patrick Kavanagh; spoken-word artists like Raymond Antrobus; and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anchor your week with new episodes on Monday and Friday, beginning January 27. Subscribe today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About the host: Pádraig Ó Tuama is a poet, theologian, conflict mediator — and the host of our new podcast, Poetry Unbound. His books include a prayer book, Daily Prayer with the Corrymeela Community, a book of poetry, &lt;i&gt;Sorry for Your Troubles&lt;/i&gt;, and a memoir, &lt;i&gt;In the Shelter: Finding a Home in the World&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>studio@onbeing.org (Poetry Unbound)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d47917405999405f8d0c2b912d30d652</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d47917405999405f8d0c2b912d30d652/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 09:30:29 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>LA PLATICA : YOU ARE WHO YOU HANG OUT WITH</title><description>&lt;p&gt;MI GENTE! WE FINALLY HAVE NEW MERCH!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;LAPLATICAPODCAST.COM&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;cant wait to see it on you guys im so excited! &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;also thank you to my special guest @be.lechendary for coming and speaking nothing but facts!!!!! love you bro!! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;follow me on insta! &amp;nbsp;@ayyysebas&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts33+1187cd58@anchor.fm (LA PLATICA)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">34cbc10898514741ac9f46c17df1e6dc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/34cbc10898514741ac9f46c17df1e6dc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 10:15:45 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>