<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Cultural feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My cultural episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My Cultural feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 17:17:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>Another Kingdom : Ep. 15: The Battle for the Skies - TEASER</title><description>The fate of Aona hangs in the balance.

Episode Available Monday DATE</description><author>anotherkingdom@dailywire.com (Another Kingdom)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">53bf24761cb54557913e1fd8727f2b5d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/53bf24761cb54557913e1fd8727f2b5d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Landscape Photography Show : Space for Mental Health in Landscape Photography</title><description>&lt;p class=""&gt;An honest discussion on mental health and how it can impact creative outlets like landscape photography.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>davidjohnstonphoto@gmail.com (The Landscape Photography Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">364085bf2b7f4f8cbf0055661b45db34</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/364085bf2b7f4f8cbf0055661b45db34/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 05:19:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Manifest with Tori DeSimone : How my Parents Let me Dropout of College | why college wasn't for me &amp; making a plan</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi guys, happy #ManifestMonday! Today we talk about one of my most asked questions, HOW I DROPPED OUT! College is not for everybody and this is how I did it. I am not encouraging you to drop out because honestly it's not everybody's path, but I knew it was mine &amp;amp; here's how.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FaceBook group: Manifest with Tori DeSimone&lt;br&gt;IG: @toristerling_&lt;br&gt;YouTube: www.youtube.com/toridesimone&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tsdsterling@gmail.com (Manifest with Tori DeSimone)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8ef28fd0a90b4d1f8bd9804d2b21705a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8ef28fd0a90b4d1f8bd9804d2b21705a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Artist/Mother Podcast : 50: Building tangible community in your neighborhood with Amy Soczka, Megan Woodard Johnson and Mindy Wittock</title><description>In today&amp;#8217;s episode, I talk with three amazing women from outside of Milwaukee, Wisconsin, about the power of Instagram to connect like-minded artist/mothers, opening yourself to community, and claiming space and time for your art even in the clutter and compromise of family life.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;



While these women came together through social media, they bonded through making work that stood out from that of their peers. Amy, Mindy, and Megan discuss the value of finding mutual understanding among other artist/mothers. Being both an artist and a mother can be isolating, so finding supportive community is crucial to making sure both parts of your life &amp;#8212; in tandem &amp;#8212; are sustainable and healthy.&amp;nbsp;



If Artist/Mother has taught me one thing, it&amp;#8217;s that if you can&amp;#8217;t find a suitable platform for your community, build it! Amy, Mindy, and Megan have done the same through sharing experience, motivation, and space together while forging new opportunities to grow as both an artist and a person. They discuss navigating local and larger art scenes, fighting self doubt, and encouraging each other to go out to gallery shows (or validating the choice to stay in!), They also talk about the value of committing to take the time to do studio visits, co-work, or sometimes even just get coffee and catching up.



Amy, Mindy, and Megan&amp;#8217;s advice for crafting community? Take the plunge to reach out to people you admire or whose work resonates with yours in pursuit of continuing to create collective, collaborative knowledge about artist-mothering! Show up for others and hope they&amp;#8217;ll return the favor &amp;#8212; get involved! Lastly, be true to yourself, your work, and your goals, and seek the same out in your creative connections.&amp;nbsp;Please check out more from these amazing women on their websites and IG pages! Megan Woodard Johnson   @meganwoodardjohnsonartAmy Soczka  @amysoczkaMindy Wittock   @mindymaker



The Artist/Mother podcast is created and hosted by Kaylan Buteyn. You can see more of Kaylan’s work on her&amp;nbsp;website&amp;nbsp;or connect with her on Instagram&amp;nbsp;@kaylanbuteyn



Mindy, Amy and Megan working at a local coffee shop



Painting by Amy Soczka 



Amy in her studio



 Sacred Textile by Mindy Wittock: New Kids on the Block Sleeping Bag, Hand Cut Felt Dots, Thread Year: 2018



Mindy in studio with her children 



Megan working in her studio 



Painting by Megan-&amp;nbsp;Right Where You Left It: mixed media on panel, completed January 2020</description><author>kaylan@kaylancreates.com (Artist/Mother Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">df2e2cba0344466ab2b9d8575d60c0f5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/df2e2cba0344466ab2b9d8575d60c0f5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 04:09:46 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Eat This Podcast : Why a spurtle makes a superior porridge stirrer</title><description>&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Here, for the New Year, is a confession and apology.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I was completely wrong about porridge-stirring implements and I am here to make things right.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In the episode about &lt;a href="https://www.eatthispodcast.com/porridge/"&gt;Porridge&lt;/a&gt;, I mocked the idea that the traditional Scottish spurtle, which to all intents and purposes is just a stick, might be better for stirring than a spoon. My (faulty) reasoning was that a spoon offered a greater surface area to break up lumps. In fact, as I now know, the stirrer does not break up the lumps directly.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I noted in &lt;a href="https://buttondown.email/jeremycherfas/archive/eat-this-newsletter-110-porridge-and-other-news/"&gt;Eat This Newsletter 110&lt;/a&gt; that a friend of a friend, who is a specialist in fluid dynamics, said that he had &amp;#8220;a working, testable hypothesis&amp;#8221;, which required only some worthy porridge in order to test it. So, I packed a bag of my favourite oats ready to meet up at Georgetown University in Washington DC.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I should explain that Dr David A. Gagnon, the physicist in question, is the son-in-law of one of my dearest friends, who happened to be visiting when I was editing the episode. That was how David came to know of my puzzlement &amp;#8211; and he has access to wonderful machines that can make very accurate rheological measurements. Rheology is the study of flow, and David&amp;#8217;s idea was that the faster the stirrer moved through the porridge, the lower the viscosity of the porridge would be. Shear stress in a material like porridge would be greater at higher flow speeds, and it is the shear stress that gets rid of lumps.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
You can think of shear stress as being a difference in the speed of flow of the liquid across a small distance, multiplied by its resistance to flow. That resistance to flow is what we think of as viscosity. In a viscous liquid, like honey, the stirrer produces a lot more shear stress than it would moving through water at the same speed. But there&amp;#8217;s a crucial difference between honey and water.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In water, the viscosity is the same no matter how fast the stirrer moves. Honey is different; the viscosity decreases the faster the stirrer moves. And that means that the stirrer produces more shear stress when it is moving quickly through the honey than when it is moving more slowly. David&amp;#8217;s idea was that fast stirring would result in lower viscosity, and lower viscosity would result in greater shear stress.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
To get back to porridge, and to lumps, consider a lump as the stirrer moves past it. Relatively speaking, the part of the lump in the slower flow near the edge of the stirrer is being held fast, while the part in the faster flow is being pulled away, and that&amp;#8217;s what destroys the lump, pulling it apart.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The rheometer measures all that. It has two circular plates, one above the other, and the bottom plate can be rotated very accurately through a known distance at a known speed. David carefully loaded a little bit of porridge onto the bottom plate and then lowered the top plate to make contact with the porridge. The layer of porridge mechanically connects the bottom plate to the top plate, which in turn is connected to sensors that accurately measure how fast and how far it rotates. Meanwhile, David had programmed the machine to oscillate the bottom plate over a wide range of frequencies. The faster the oscillation, the greater the stress on the porridge. The machine then takes all those measurements and creates a set of graphs that describe the rheological properties of the porridge.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.eatthispodcast.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/porridge-graph.jpeg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The viscosity graph, photographed directly from the screen.The graph appeared and I confess it was really exciting to watch the points appear. A straight line down from top left to bottom right over a h...</description><author>jcherfas@mac.com (Eat This Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">26ec791633f441d489b02718f567f4e3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/26ec791633f441d489b02718f567f4e3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 04:00:17 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Off Panel: A Comics Interview Podcast : Off Panel #239: It's Comics Town with Patrick Brower</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this week's episode of Off Panel, the co-owner of Chicago's Challengers Comics + Conversation comic shops, Patrick Brower, joins to chat about 2019 in comics retail. Brower discusses their opening of a second shop, what goes into opening a store, the state of comics retail relative to when Challengers first opened, the rise of the mini-series, what's working for them, differentiating titles today, how the year was for them, risk aversion, figuring out what customers want, second issues, how BOOM! Studios is handling things, whether he'd like more experimentation from comic publishers, the in-store comics conversation, whether he still loves comics, and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>david@sktchd.com (Off Panel: A Comics Interview Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6bdcae11ad29407b910c8a7441d3c416</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6bdcae11ad29407b910c8a7441d3c416/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The KLN Podcast : 9: What is Beautiful?</title><description>&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img src="https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-1024x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1183" srcset="https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-1024x1024.png 1024w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-300x300.png 300w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-150x150.png 150w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-768x768.png 768w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-500x500.png 500w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-200x200.png 200w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038-1536x1536.png 1536w, https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/IMG_3038.png 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;No one ever said, &amp;#8220;I am who I am because she was so skinny.&amp;#8221; Why do we look for beauty in places that leave no impact? Let&amp;#8217;s desire something that changes others for the better. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-audio"&gt;&lt;audio controls src="https://karalewisnewton.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Episode-9.mp3"&gt;&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description><author>info@karalewisnewton.com (The KLN Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">eb7d3aee293342bcb6ed811d4cd88b85</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/eb7d3aee293342bcb6ed811d4cd88b85/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 03:06:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bokeh - The Photography Podcast : #333: Fix Your Website Terms &amp; Privacy Statement! - Paige Griffith</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you protecting yourself and your business with a privacy policy or terms and conditions on your website?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In episode 333 of the Bokeh Podcast, Paige Griffith explains what these documents can do in covering all the bases when it comes to your business, as well as collecting data from potential customers through your website. Listen in as she shares the important components that you, as a photographer, need to have within your privacy policy and terms and conditions!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Bokeh Podcast is brought to you by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.photographersedit.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Photographer’s Edit&lt;/a&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Custom Editing for the Wedding and Portrait Photographer.&amp;nbsp;You can also subscribe to the Bokeh podcast on the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://bit.do/bokehpodcast" target="_blank"&gt;Apple podcast app&lt;/a&gt;, follow on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/1Qwpw3ieYGfHuUFkbZvfmq?si=_Hp5_yWBQnOICVIfX-fvcA" target="_blank"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, add to your playlist on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.stitcher.com/podcast/nathan-holritz/bokeh" target="_blank"&gt;Stitcher,&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or listen on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1140118526/bokeh" target="_blank"&gt;Overcast&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catch up with Paige:&lt;/strong&gt; (1:47)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Legal Paige - &lt;a href="https://thelegalpaige.com/" target="_blank"&gt;thelegalpaige.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Griffith Law&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brand Position:&lt;/strong&gt; Virtual legal resource that helps educate online small business owners how to protect themselves. (6:31)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Book/Content Recommendations:&lt;/strong&gt; (11:14)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everything is Figureoutable by Marie Forleo - &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/bp-figureoutable" target="_blank"&gt;bit.ly/bp-figureoutable&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Stacking Your Team Podcast by Biz Chix - &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/bp-stackingyourteam" target="_blank"&gt;bit.ly/bp-stackingyourteam&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Gear Bag:&lt;/strong&gt; KUVRD Stretchy Lens Caps - &lt;a href="https://kuvrdcamera.com/" target="_blank"&gt;kuvrdcamera.com&lt;/a&gt; (14:57)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Considering Your Privacy Policy and Terms &amp;amp; Conditions&lt;/strong&gt; (17:06)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Policy Regulations &amp;amp; Laws&lt;/strong&gt; (17:06)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;California Consumer Privacy Act&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Child Online Protection Act&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal Consumer Protection Act&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Components of Terms &amp;amp; Conditions for Photographers:&lt;/strong&gt; (24:49)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Intellectual Property Notice - Evidence that we put the public on notice of copyright.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Refund Policy (Specifically for e-commerce sites)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3. Age Requirements (COPA - 13 years or older)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Website Placement Recommendation from Paige:&lt;/strong&gt; Secondary footer that includes the Privacy Policy, Terms &amp;amp; Conditions, and Disclaimer (26:40)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Components of the Privacy Policy&lt;/strong&gt; (28:57)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Who you collect the information from.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Why you’re tracking the data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3. How you’re going to use the information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;4. Explain things regarding minors in using their information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;5. The use of information and their rights to change their consent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://thelegalpaige.com/" target="_blank"&gt;thelegalpaige.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Legal Paige Podcast - &lt;a href="https://thelegalpaige.com/podcast/" target="_blank"&gt;thelegalpaige.com/podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/thelegalpaige/" target="_blank"&gt;instagram.com/thelegalpaige&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Legal Paige Community on Facebook - &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/bp-legalpaigecommunity" target="_blank"&gt;bit.ly/bp-legalpaigecommunity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BP Episode 130 with Paige Griffith - &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/bp-131" target="_blank"&gt;bit.ly/bp-131&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evolve Conference - &lt;a href="https://www.evolveworkshops.org/" target="_blank"&gt;evolveworkshops.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info+5afb1cee126b604f03904d38@mg.pippa.io (Bokeh - The Photography Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1b89bebe15da4890b93d1875e36c29d4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1b89bebe15da4890b93d1875e36c29d4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 03:00:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dateline NBC : Nightfall</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this Dateline classic, investigators scramble to find a killer after a young mother is found dead 40 miles from Knoxville, Tennessee on the side of a country road. Andrea Canning reports. Originally aired on NBC on April 14, 2017.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>dateline.contactus@nbcuni.com (Dateline NBC)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bc16bfbdf462402c856efbc9dcb6ddd8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bc16bfbdf462402c856efbc9dcb6ddd8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Food In Five : Thai coconut curry soup in 30 minutes or less</title><description>This soup is a little sweet, a little spicy, a little acidic, and a lot flavourful. If you are looking for something a little different to have for dinner tonight, this is it.

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/foodinfive/message</description><author>podcasts4+8152@anchor.fm (Food In Five)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5111b55c2ff24c09a7d46be107a62b0d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5111b55c2ff24c09a7d46be107a62b0d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 02:14:58 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Slowdown : 301: Confession</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;#39;s poem is Confession by Leila Chatti.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>slowdown@americanpublicmedia.org (The Slowdown)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">502e1114f19949bdb2e81637813cc549</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/502e1114f19949bdb2e81637813cc549/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 02:04:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dark Side Of : Dating: Internet Dating</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Methods for finding your "perfect match" have become far more efficient in the 21st century with the invention of internet dating. While the rise of online matchmaking and app culture has opened up numerous doors for singles, it's also unleashed a minefield of unexpected pitfalls.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>support@parcast.com (The Dark Side Of)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5b671398f0374cceae3f2c705523b3fc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5b671398f0374cceae3f2c705523b3fc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Pencil Pusher's Podcast : Tara Donovan</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome folks to The Pencil Pushers Podcast and episode 21 (we’re officially legal) and our VERY first for what we’re calling the tip top year of creativity and growth, 2020! I, of course, am still your humble host, Mike Rosado. And today, we’re very thrilled to be sharing our interview with Tara Donovan - one of the few artists who has successfully broken into both traditional and CG animation, working on hand-drawn animated classics like The Thief and the Cobbler and Asterix Conquers the World to CG animation for blockbusters like Justice League, Aquaman and the upcoming King Kong vs Godzilla. We dive into how to break into the animation world, how being insatiably curious will help with growth and employment and things you can do to remain healthy in an incredibly stressful and sometimes unpredictable industry. Find and follow her online @taranimator and just add a .com to check out her site. And now, without further ado, do yourself a favor - ease your seat back, relax and enjoy our chat with Tara.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;****** &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The Pencil Pushers Podcast is a celebration of the hand-drawn arts. I’ll be interviewing friends and idols in illustration, animation, comic-art, and more.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Mike Rosado &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/ekimodasor/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/ekimodasor/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Produced and edited by &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/trujillo.media/"&gt;Trujillo Media&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>pencilpusherspodcast@gmail.com (The Pencil Pusher's Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9decaa91d7bd42be874f9a6939358965</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9decaa91d7bd42be874f9a6939358965/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>THE UPSIDE with Callie and Jeff Dauler : EPISODE 151:  HACKING RESOLUTIONS AND FAT DOGS</title><description>&lt;p&gt;episode 151 / January 20, 2020&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jdauler@gmail.com (THE UPSIDE with Callie and Jeff Dauler)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0a30967f174241cfb3354f397dbfe551</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0a30967f174241cfb3354f397dbfe551/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Get Real -w- Caroline Hobby : Allison Moorer: Grammy and Oscar nominated singer for “Soft Place to Fall” talks about her musical life and family, and why it was finally time for her to write the very personal book “Blood” and companion album about the murder/suicide of her parents.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Allison Moorer has a depth to her that feels like the ocean, and you feel it immediately when you’re in her presence. She’s feels classic like Nicole Kidman meets Kate Winslet and throw in a touch of Joni Mitchell. There’s a confident quietness to her until she is engaged in conversation... then she speaks and all you want to do is listen. I met her at an eclectic dinner party hosted by a fabulous interior Photographer, Alyssa Rosenheck. I was moved by everything Allison spoke about; from how she just published a book and album called “Blood” on the murder-suicide of her parents, and how she and her sister, Grammy winner Shelby Lynne, became each other’s rock and “nightlights,” as one of the tracks on her new album sings about. She also talked about the trials and triumphs of raising a non-verbal ten year old with autism. Allison says God gives us the child we need. She is so tuned into her spiritual being. We talk about what it felt like to be nominated for an Oscar and a Grammy and playing the Oscars. This interview hits every nerve. Allison is so transparent and honest. I love this conversation, and I feel honored to know Allison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Get Real -w- Caroline Hobby)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6c8557b57dae43aa9a71c70b5c8385a1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6c8557b57dae43aa9a71c70b5c8385a1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Happiness Lab with Dr. Laurie Santos : 2020 BONUS: Think Yourself Happy (LIVE from Yale)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Really concentrating on the emotions and physical sensations you are experiencing right now can make you happier. Join Yale mindfulness expert Dr Hedy Kober as she introduces a live audience to guided meditation. She shares her tips on being mindful with Dr Laurie Santos and explains the new scientific research that shows the benefits of this ancient practice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For an even deeper dive into the research we talk about in the show visit &lt;a href="https://www.happinesslab.fm/"&gt;happinesslab.fm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sean@dgitalmedia.com (The Happiness Lab with Dr. Laurie Santos)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7959cc6f22d2412a8f44c9b21a7e6722</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7959cc6f22d2412a8f44c9b21a7e6722/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 21:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>How Men Think with Brooks Laich &amp; Gavin DeGraw : Gavin a Good Time</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Gavin, Brooks and the Men are back together for a revealing thought provoking game of COME TO THINK OF IT. After extensive research, we have compiled a wide range of questions that women NEED answers to and the Men are doing just that. The rules...100% honesty and transparency and The Men must answer every question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (How Men Think with Brooks Laich &amp; Gavin DeGraw)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7c699b87974048cca4989f3eae1bcede</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7c699b87974048cca4989f3eae1bcede/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Seattle Kitchen : Seattle Kitchen</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today on the Show: We review all the hottest food gadgets to see if they are worth the hype // Our trusty chefs go on a world tour of different countries&amp;rsquo; takes on the turnover // We challenge ourselves with a game of &amp;ldquo;Guess the Recipe&amp;rdquo; // Angela Buck-Hatter, Assistant Manager at Cantina Le&amp;ntilde;a&amp;nbsp;drops by to chat Mocktails&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@bonneville.com (Seattle Kitchen)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b2d143efdf0d48d2a5d58c009bab45a3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b2d143efdf0d48d2a5d58c009bab45a3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 18:48:18 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Chatty AF : Chatty AF 107 - Panels Podcast</title><description>Caitlin talks hosting panels at anime conventions with special guests Megan, Zack, and Rinnie!
 
0:00:00 Intros
0:02:49 The con experience
0:06:54 Our panels
0:17:49 Feminist critique
0:24:21 Planning styles
0:34:53 Inspirations for topics
0:39:13 Panel dynamics
0:49:29 Success stories
0:54:30 Horror stories
1:04:01 Final thoughts
1:07:08 Outro
 
Caitlin: twitter.com/alltsun_nodere
Megan: twitter.com/brainchild129
Zack: twitter.com/shinyzack
Rinnie: twitter.com/idolrinny
 
AniFem Patreon: www.patreon.com/animefeminist
AniFem Twitter: twitter.com/AnimeFeminist
AniFem Facebook: www.facebook.com/animefem/
 
Recorded Saturday 27th April 2019
 
Music: Open Those Bright Eyes by Kevin MacLeod (incompetech.com)
Licensed under Creative Commons: By Attribution 3.0 License
creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/</description><author>feeds@soundcloud.com (Chatty AF)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ef7ddc25106b4c00b1e2e16c96a2757d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ef7ddc25106b4c00b1e2e16c96a2757d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 18:00:10 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Living Proof: Conversations for Bartenders : #37 | Firkin good Whisky with Mike Collings</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Mike Collings is one of the most experienced Marketing Directors in the Whisky industry, having worked with some of the biggest brands in the world during his time at Diageo (which was then known as United Distillers). He played a major hand in launching Johnnie Walker Blue Label, Green Label, as well as helping to reinvent Jack Daniels and Southern Comfort among others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, Mike is producing his own range of whiskys, including the luxury, handcrafted and personalised 'Imperial Tribute' and most recently, his range of 'Firkin Whisky Co' bottlings.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nicole@themessagebureau.com.au (Living Proof: Conversations for Bartenders)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0c1612f9ebd44e8aa9dc94bef4a2b818</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0c1612f9ebd44e8aa9dc94bef4a2b818/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 17:23:25 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Sunday Sitdown with Willie Geist : Aidy Bryant</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Aidy Bryant grew up in Arizona watching women like Molly Shannon, Cheri Oteri and Ana Gasteyer on &lt;em&gt;Saturday Night Live&lt;/em&gt;. Today, she is a member of that exclusive comedy club herself. In this week’s “Sunday Sitdown,” Willie Geist talks to the actress and comedian about her eight season run on &lt;em&gt;SNL&lt;/em&gt;, as well as her latest role as executive producer, writer and star of the acclaimed Hulu series &lt;em&gt;Shrill&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (Sunday Sitdown with Willie Geist)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4f8349a2056b4865b80ede4b7053253e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4f8349a2056b4865b80ede4b7053253e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 05:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Cliff Dorfman Show : Laz Alonso Pt 2.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Laz Alonso can not be contained to one episode! Laz continues to share his journey. From being written out of a UPN and an NBC pilot and persevering only to end up in some of the biggest movies and franchises of all time.  &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>starburnsaudio@starburnsind.com (The Cliff Dorfman Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b06ddf619b454a29b621b774011458f4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b06ddf619b454a29b621b774011458f4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>@ToyPhotoCast : Episode 18 - @Jish_Toy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Flavortown. This episode we sit down with a great Toy Photographer and friend of the community: @Jish_Toy! We discuss a wide range of topics and also why Josh has Guy Fieri as his profile. We discuss his inspiration and motivation as a Toy Photographer too! - @Dagobah_Days&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/jish_toy/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/jish_toy/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/e0fe700/podcast/sponsor/acugkf/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/toyphot/message
Support this podcast: &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/toyphot/support" rel="payment"&gt;https://anchor.fm/toyphot/support&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts16+e0fe700@anchor.fm (@ToyPhotoCast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cfe379f97f4c41539e69166bca2604d4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cfe379f97f4c41539e69166bca2604d4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 18:35:49 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Naked on Cashmere : I’ve Had The Slow Murmur of a Paris Thought</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Oh no,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve had the slow murmur of a Paris thought,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the kind that won’t leave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;until well after&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;a month-long-week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;of rosé,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;cafés,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;and sunsets on the Seine.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;xx Atticus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/atticuspoetry/?hl=en" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;@atticuspoetry &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.atticuspoetry.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;www.atticuspoetry.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nakedoncashmere@podcastnation.org (Naked on Cashmere)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8ebef38bc0974726aff7fa1b44e6541e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8ebef38bc0974726aff7fa1b44e6541e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 17:00:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Image Doctors Talk Photography : The Image Doctors #29</title><description>&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Our Favorite Photo Locations&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
We all have favorite places for photography. Whether it&amp;#8217;s in a national park, or exploring a city or country, here are some of our favorite places to shoot, and reasons why some of the better locations might not be what you expect.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Follow Us on Facebook&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/ImageDoctors" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="www.facebook.com/ImageDoctors (opens in a new tab)"&gt;www.facebook.com/ImageDoctors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Support The Image Doctors Podcast&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Keep The Image Doctors on the air by donating to our &lt;a href="https://luminescentphoto.com/blog/support-the-image-doctors-photography-podcast/"&gt;bandwidth fund&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><author>jason@luminescentphoto.com (The Image Doctors Talk Photography)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3b78862df31542d7afb038ecb3422e48</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3b78862df31542d7afb038ecb3422e48/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 03:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Parklandia : Bonus Episode! Boondocking With Brad: The Essentials</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For our second installment of Boondocking with Brad, we'll go over the nuts and bolts of what you need to know about operating and maintaining an RV, from how to power it all the way down to what kind of toilet paper you need for the very different lifestyle on the road.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Got more questions? We'd love to talk! Join the conversation in the Parklandia Rangers &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/ParklandiaRangers/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and Like our &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/parklandiapod/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;! Also be sure to follow Parklandia on Instagram &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/parklandiapod/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;@parklandiapod&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Parklandia)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">dd6b99394eb54ab49b6f955004480ca6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/dd6b99394eb54ab49b6f955004480ca6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Fresh Air : Best Of: Martin Scorsese / 'Boys &amp; Sex'</title><description>Martin Scorsese's latest film, 'The Irishman,' is up for 10 Academy Awards, including Best Picture and Best Director. He spoke with Terry Gross about childhood, redemption and getting kicked out of seminary school.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Jazz critic Kevin Whitehead reviews, 'Ow!,' a newly resurfaced live recording of saxophonists Eddie "Lockjaw" Davis and Johnny Griffin.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Peggy Orenstein's new book, 'Boys &amp; Sex,' is based on extensive interviews with more than 100 college and college-bound boys between the ages of 16 and 22. "When I was doing ['Girls &amp; Sex'] the kind of core issue with girls was that they were being cut off from their bodies and not understanding their bodies' response and their needs and their limits and their desires," she says. "With boys, it felt like they were being cut off from their hearts."</description><guid isPermaLink="false">b3351f297a5a4375a1a86aa13bf43712</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b3351f297a5a4375a1a86aa13bf43712/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 21:01:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Beer Guys Radio Craft Beer Podcast : Atlanta Cask Ale Tasting and Georgia's Next Breweries</title><description>Despite Mother Nature's best efforts, the 16th Annual Atlanta Cask Ale Tasting was a huge success &lt;p&gt;It was an unusually warm day for the 16th Annual &lt;a href= "https://www.classiccitybrew.com/acat.html" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;Atlanta Cask Ale Tasting&lt;/a&gt; and this brought with it some crazy weather.  As attendees filled &lt;a href= "https://boldmonkbrewingco.com/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;Bold Monk Brewing&lt;/a&gt; to sample the cask ales the rain started coming down strong and with about an hour left the hammer dropped.  The parking lot flooded and the very well-covered patio was drenched, and finally, the power went out.  Fortunately, we had completed our show taping but it did cause some chaos for the Bold Monk and cut a few festival-goers off from their cask ales a bit early.  Even with the craziness, I think everyone had a great time.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is our 4th year partnering with Brewtopia Events for ACAT and we kept our tradition going by speaking with festival organizer Owen Ogletree about the event and the ever-changing world of cask ales.  We also spoke to a few of the breweries currently under construction in Georgia that we hope to see debut in 2020.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;The team from Social Fox Brewing is ready to bring some brews to Norcross.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; A few of Georgia's Next Breweries &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.outrunbrewingco.com/#/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Outrun Brewing&lt;/a&gt; | Founders Josh Miller and Ryan Silva (formerly of Decatur, GA's Three Taverns) join us to discuss the plans for their retro 80s-themed brewery coming to Stone Mountain.  We did confirm there will be an Outrun arcade machine at the brewery.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/sabbathbrewing/" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Sabbath Brewing&lt;/a&gt; | Founder Jeff Oparnica joins us to talk about his struggles fighting through zoning laws with the City of Atlanta, his plan to ferment 100% in oak vessels, and brewing raw ales.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.socialfoxbrewing.com/"&gt;Social Fox Brewing&lt;/a&gt; &amp; &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/Storey-Time-Construction-107630693369361/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Storey Time Construction&lt;/a&gt; | We didn't have enough mics to get the whole team on with us but they all came out to support the cause.  Mike Greene joined us to represent Team Social Fox to talk about their brewery coming to Norcross.  Anthony Storey joins us from Storey Time Construction as well to discuss building out their brewery and some others that are in the works. (Storey Time is one of BGR's super awesome sponsors.)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; The Beer List &lt;p&gt;A few favorites from the festival:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Best End Hawker Hornet ESB&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The Eighth State Arcus | Sour Ale with blueberry, lemon, cinnamon, and marshmallow&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Rainy Day Brewery Double O Buzzin' | Coffee and vanilla Milk Stout with lactose&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;StillFire Brewing Olde Chief Inspector '19 | Traditional English Barleywine&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;The 16th Atlanta Cask Ale Tasting offered up over 50 casks including ESBs, Emglish Milds, Barleywines, and plenty of pastry stouts.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; ICYMI: Previous ACAT episodes &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href= "https://beerguysradio.com/2019/02/02/acat-2019-georgia-breweries-halfway-crooks-bold-monk-schoolhouse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;15th Annual Atlanta Cask Ale Tasting with Bold Monk Brewing, Halfway Crooks, and Schoolhouse Brewing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href= "https://beerguysradio.com/2018/01/27/episode-109-atlanta-cask-ale-tasting/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;14th Annual Atlanta Cask Ale Tasting with Banyan Roots (now Best End Brewing), Line Creek Brewing, and Split Batch Brewery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href= "https://beerguysradio.com/2017/01/28/atlanta-cask-ale-tasting-episode-57/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;13th Annual Atlanta Cask Ale Tasting with Good Word Brewing, New Realm Brewing, and Variant Brewing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>beerguys@beerguysradio.com (Beer Guys Radio Craft Beer Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9bb67545b17544de862883bc99be5f2e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9bb67545b17544de862883bc99be5f2e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>A Justin Salem Meyer Photography Podcast : Hot Topics: Finding Fulfillment in Photography</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Austin and I continue our conversation about finding fulfillment in photography, serving your clients vs. shooting for yourself. Photo by Austin Hyler (Day) &lt;a href="http://www.austinhyler.com"&gt;www.austinhyler.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>justin@justinsalemmeyer.com (A Justin Salem Meyer Photography Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3849c5b72f254a8d988a43c90c2ef03e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3849c5b72f254a8d988a43c90c2ef03e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 19:31:10 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>StarTalk Radio : Cheating in Sports</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Lance Armstrong, the New England Patriots, steroids in baseball &amp;ndash; Neil deGrasse Tyson investigates cheating in sports alongside co-hosts Chuck Nice and Gary O&amp;rsquo;Reilly, Dr. Lee Igel, PhD from the Tisch Institute of Global Sport, and behavioral scientist Lisa Shu, PhD.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jeff@startalkradio.net (StarTalk Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">96c90b6b75b3446eb972b8573cf4aa0c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/96c90b6b75b3446eb972b8573cf4aa0c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>SOMM TV : SOMM TV Podcast Episode 13:  Natural Wine</title><description>&lt;img src="https://assets.podomatic.net/ts/09/d0/15/jason22461/3000x3000_14552556.jpg" alt="itunes pic" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason Wise and Brian McClintic sit down to discuss what's involved with natural wine and what Brian is up to now. Also, an update on The Delicacy film and SOMM 4.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">85ea5c291d31484d98f1e4981e5ff101</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/85ea5c291d31484d98f1e4981e5ff101/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:58:17 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Here &amp; Now : Trump's Impeachment Legal Team; Bloomberg Outspends Rivals</title><description>Ken Starr and Alan Dershowitz are set to join Trump's impeachment legal team. Barbara McQuade, former U.S. attorney for the Eastern District of Michigan, joins us to discuss what this means for Trump's legal team. Former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg has spent more on ads in his campaign for president than any of his rivals for the Democratic nomination. Ken Goldstein, a professor at the University of San Francisco, joins us to discuss.</description><author>webmaster@wbur.org (Here &amp; Now)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">067f01878623457695b106149c2d84fb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/067f01878623457695b106149c2d84fb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 11:06:16 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Velvet’s Edge with Kelly Henderson : Act Casual: Parlez Voux Ingles’</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Kelly and Chip recap Chip’s recent trip to Paris, discussing all of the Act Casual situations that can come about from a language barrier. They each list off commonly misused words that can mean some pretty awkward things in different languages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>info@velvetsedge.com (Velvet’s Edge with Kelly Henderson)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0c705094657844469c5713cb343d7cb2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0c705094657844469c5713cb343d7cb2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 08:26:31 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Bite Goes On – Radio Misfits : The Bite Goes On – Mexico City Recap</title><description>Follow along the conversation while looking at photographs from Sondra&amp;#8217;s recent trip to Mexico City (&lt;a href="https://www.thebitegoeson.com/copy-of-gallery" target="_blank"&gt;www.thebitegoeson.com/copy-of-gallery&lt;/a&gt;). Get ready to book your trip to Mexico City just from hearing about the food. Sondra talks about her taco tour, neighborhood markets including the Jamiaca Mercado and Pujol (the #12 of the 50 Best Restaurants in the world), a special meal with a friend from Mexico City, mezcal and more. [EP63]&lt;br /&gt;</description><author>itunes@radiomisfits.com (The Bite Goes On – Radio Misfits)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3d02e6cef8c1490faec2597d483d9f6a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3d02e6cef8c1490faec2597d483d9f6a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 07:55:31 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The olive magazine podcast : ep 183 - Learn all about Singaporean food and drink with chef Elizabeth Haigh</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week Ellie chats to Elizabeth Haigh, a Singaporean-born chef who has just opened Mei Mei, a coffee house in Borough Market specializing in the food and drink of Singapore. They chat about why she pursued a career in food after completing a degree in architecture, how she travels across London to source key ingredients and the best places for kopi in Singapore.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>laura.rowe@immediate.co.uk (The olive magazine podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">99483c4a7677426692ea38d6079a4c2f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/99483c4a7677426692ea38d6079a4c2f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 07:39:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Photography Radio : Magnum's Take on Pantone, Manfrotto Memory Cards, Instagram Blocks Fake Images, No Photos In Vogue</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;"Take's Take" with Take Kayo.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Every Friday Take dives into everything what's new and interesting in the world of photography - including digital, analogue, mobile, and everything in between. &lt;br&gt;Enjoy!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Today's Show Links&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.magnumphotos.com/arts-culture/design/classic-blue-magnum-archive-design-fashion-pantone/"&gt;Magnum's Take on Pantone's Classic Blue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.manfrotto.com/us-en/products/memory-cards/"&gt;Manfrotto Memory Cards&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://instagram-press.com/blog/2019/12/16/combatting-misinformation-on-instagram/"&gt;Instagram Blocking "Fake" Images&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vogue.it/moda/article/vogue-italia-gennaio-editoriale-direttore"&gt;Italian Vogue Without Images&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Featured photographer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;Xyza Cruz Bacani (&lt;a href="http://www.xyzacruzbacani.com"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href="https://instagram.com/xyzacruzbacani"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head over to &lt;a href="http://www.photographyradio.com"&gt;www.photographyradio.com&lt;/a&gt; and scroll to the bottom of the page to send in your comment on today's show. We would absolutely love to hear from you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have a great light!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tomash@photographyradio.com (Photography Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">aceb75611f154d269fe471efed29a61f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/aceb75611f154d269fe471efed29a61f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>I Like Your Work: Conversations with Artists, Curators &amp; Collectors : Painter Mark Milroy: Stories of Discovery, Overcoming Failure &amp; the Psychology of Portrait Painting</title><description>I am thrilled to share the work of Mark Milroy! I've followed Mark's work for a few years which is why I am so excited to have him on the show! It was so much fun to record this interview in his Brooklyn studio where Mark share's hilarious stories of his background growing up in Canada, how he came to art, painting adults with mental illness and developmental disabilities, and how this lead to his interest in portrait painting and pursuing art as his career. We also discuss health setbacks and dealing with that as a human being and artist.       Mark is hilarious and I loved his stories and passion for painting. If you guys get a chance to do a studio visit to hang out and talk about art with Mark, I would highly suggest it! If you can’t make it to Brooklyn, follow him on Instagram @mark_milroy where he shares work and behind the scenes of people sitting for him which I love seeing.       Mark received a BFA from the School of the Art Institute of Chicago and has exhibited in galleries in New York City, Brooklyn, Chicago, LA, Sag Harbor, and Canada. His work has been featured in Columbia: A Journal of Art &amp; Literature and New York Metropolis, and in the Absolut Vodka advertising campaign. Milroy’s work has been written about in CityArts Magazine, Domino Magazine, The East Hampton Star, New York Arts Magazine, The New York Sun, The New York Times, Tokion Magazine, The Washington Post, and Dan’s Papers, among others.       RESOURCES:   &lt;a class= "_2qJYG blog-link-hashtag-color _1cJeG" href= "https://www.ilikeyourworkpodcast.com/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;I Like Your Work Podcast&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;a class= "_2qJYG blog-link-hashtag-color _1cJeG" href= "https://www.ilikeyourworkpodcast.com/studio-planner" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Studio Planner&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;a class= "_2qJYG blog-link-hashtag-color _1cJeG" href= "https://www.instagram.com/ilikeyourworkpodcast/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;a class= "_2qJYG blog-link-hashtag-color _1cJeG" href= "https://www.ilikeyourworkpodcast.com/submitwork" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Submit Work&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;a class= "_2qJYG blog-link-hashtag-color _1cJeG" href= "https://www.sunlighttax.com/moneybootcamp" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;Money Bootcamp&lt;/a&gt;- Use code ILIKEYOURWORK20 for $20 offG   &lt;a class= "_2qJYG blog-link-hashtag-color _1cJeG" href= "https://gamblincolors.com/gamblin/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;Gamblin Artist Oil&lt;/a&gt;       &lt;a class= "_2qJYG blog-link-hashtag-color _1cJeG" href= "https://www.markmilroy.com/" target="_self" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.markmilroy.com/&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;a class= "_2qJYG blog-link-hashtag-color _1cJeG" href= "https://www.instagram.com/mark_milroy/" target="_self" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/mark_milroy/&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>ilikeyourworkpodcast@gmail.com (I Like Your Work: Conversations with Artists, Curators &amp; Collectors)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b886d7852669467dbc3ae2ee55c5ff00</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b886d7852669467dbc3ae2ee55c5ff00/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ask An Artist : Ask an Artist Interviews Nick Bentley - Gallery Relationships from the Gallerist's Point of View</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Most artists want to get their work on the walls of a gallery, at least until someone buys it!&amp;nbsp; How do you get your work into a gallery?&amp;nbsp; What should the relationship be between you and your gallery?&amp;nbsp; Are there tings that you must never do when dealing with a gallery - and are there things that the gallery should not be doing?&amp;nbsp; In our second podcast interviewing Nick Bentley owner of Bils and Rye Gallery in Kirkbymoorside in North Yorkshire, Peter and Laura talk about how the relationship should work, how you might approach a gallery and gives some frank advice on things you should avoid.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@thetalentedmrb.co.uk (Ask An Artist)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9ab80c4836654240a61b991dbf909efb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9ab80c4836654240a61b991dbf909efb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Con Artists  : Con Artists Bites: Psychological Manipulation</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In addition to new episodes of &lt;em&gt;Con Artists&lt;/em&gt; each week, you’ll now also hear &lt;em&gt;Crime Bites&lt;/em&gt; every Friday. Each &lt;em&gt;Crime Bites&lt;/em&gt; episode gives you a deeper, yet brief look into true-crime topics covered at Parcast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today we explore the idea of Psychological Manipulation—the tactics criminals use to deceive, coerce, and exert control over their victims. We'll dive into clips from shows across the Parcast Network, and discuss how these methods work, and most importantly, their dangerous consequences.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>support@parcast.com (Con Artists )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d21d67caabec4d86a21437b627b11a3f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d21d67caabec4d86a21437b627b11a3f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Splendid Table : 675: The Food of Thailand</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Explore the regional flavors of Thailand and learn why there are so many Thai restaurants in the U.S. Plus, lessons on curry paste and coconut milk.&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>contact@splendidtable.org (The Splendid Table)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c3c433e52e23449789ac38cd108c704f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c3c433e52e23449789ac38cd108c704f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>But That's Another Story : Introducing: Storybound</title><description>&lt;p&gt;If you're enjoying But That's Another Story, there's another storytelling podcast we think you'll really like. The following is an episode of &lt;em&gt;Storybound&lt;/em&gt;, a new podcast from Lit Hub and The Podglomerate. In it, Mitch Albom reads an excerpt from his new book Finding Chika. Musical compositions by Maiah Wynne &amp;amp; Aliephant. To hear more episodes of &lt;em&gt;Storybound &lt;/em&gt;today, open Apple Podcasts, Spotify, Stitcher, or your app of choice today, search for Storybound and hit subscribe. We'll see you next week for a new episode of But That's Another Story with a very special guest. Keep up to date on the latest at Macmillan plus behind-the-scenes details by subscribing to our newsletter &lt;a href="%20https://us.macmillan.com/podcasts/join-our-newsletter/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>anotherstory@macmillan.com (But That's Another Story)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">966c24360f4a4c9ababa0adf84cbdcb0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/966c24360f4a4c9ababa0adf84cbdcb0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Rogue Theory: A New Rockstars Podcast : Morbius Spiderman SINISTER SIX Theory! | RT</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Morbius Trailer Spider-Man Easter Eggs hint at a future Sinister Six team-up in Spider-Man 3! Who will be the members of the MCU Sinister Six in the next Spider-Man film in 2021, and could Morbius introduce half of the new team? In this episode of #RogueTheory, join Filup Molina, Erik Voss, Marina Mastros, and Tommy Bechtold as they react to the new #Morbius trailer by drafting their perfect lineups of the #SinisterSix, and how new versions of Doc Ock, Green Goblin, Kraven the Hunter, and Hobgoblin could be revealed. And stick around for theories about how Avengers Endgame could have set the stage for Marvel's Eternals... and New Rockstars' first-ever awarding of the mythical GOLDEN ROGUEY!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>scottporch@gmail.com (Rogue Theory: A New Rockstars Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f291d93d67ab4dd9a0b111e25cab3467</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f291d93d67ab4dd9a0b111e25cab3467/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 18:33:50 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Fred Minnick Show Podcast : Lindsay Ell, a Banana Fan, Finds Her Perfect Whiskey. She Also Talks About Stalkers, Losing Equipment and Her Fans</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Lindsay Ell is a dynamic musician with a bright future ahead of her. Shortly after owning the stage at the Hometown Rising Country Music and Whiskey Festival, she sat down with Fred and opened up about many personal details. What&amp;rsquo;s it like to be on the road? What does she drink? What are the challenges of being a famous musician? And most importantly, as Lindsay&amp;rsquo;s eyes gazed upon the sea of bourbon in Fred&amp;rsquo;s trailer, the whiskey critic started asking a series of questions that made her mouth water and get her excited to taste a bourbon she found quite tasty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this first episode, there&amp;rsquo;s also a little whiskey trivia and more about Fred than he intended to share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sponsors: &lt;a href="https://www.sfspiritscomp.com/"&gt;The San Francisco World Spirits Competition&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://michters.com/"&gt;Michter&amp;rsquo;s American Whiskey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;WHISKEY TRIVIA answer below the show notes....&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KEEP UP WITH FRED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Free Drinks Newsletter: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.fredminnick.com&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://www.fredminnick.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bourbon Plus: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2FBourbonPlus.com&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://BourbonPlus.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spirits Network: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fexplore.spiritsnetwork.com%2Ffr&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://explore.spiritsnetwork.com/fr&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bourbon Pursuit: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2FBourbonPursuit.com&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://BourbonPursuit.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Ffredminnick%2F&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/fredminnick/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Ffred.minnick%2F&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/fred.minnick/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2FFredMinnick&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://twitter.com/FredMinnick&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Books: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=iI0WQgqpyXmoA1-x_tzGh2j5Rsd8MTU3OTI5MzU2OEAxNTc5MjA3MTY4&amp;amp;q=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fs%3Fk%3Dfred%2Bminni&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=y8_AFH9xlbQ"&gt;https://www.amazon.com/s?k=fred+minni&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOLLOW LINDSAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.lindsayell.com/"&gt;https://www.lindsayell.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/lindsayell"&gt;https://twitter.com/lindsayell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/lindsayell/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/lindsayell/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/officiallindsayell/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/officiallindsayell/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BMG granted a license to use Lindsay Ell&amp;rsquo;s music on this podcast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRIVIA Answer: President William Howard Taft&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When President William Howard Taft took office in 1909, there was mass confusion as to what whiskey was. The Pure Food &amp;amp; Drug Act had placed some limitations on medicinal marketing and given consumers an added layer of protection, but it really didn&amp;rsquo;t define whiskey types. So many distillers were adding food coloring to distilled molasses and calling it bourbon. In what became known as the Taft Decision, the president gave whiskey its first federal definitions. In his lengthy writings, he specifically called out the quality, noting:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Some time during the Civil War it was discovered that if raw whiskey as it came from the still, unrectified and without distillation, and thus containing one-half to one-sixth of 1 percent of fusel oil, was kept in oak barrels, the inside of the staves of which were charred, the tannic acid of the charred oak which found its way from the wood into the distilled spirits would color the raw white whiskey to the conventional color of American whiskey, and after some years would eliminate altogether the raw taste and the bad odor given the liquor by the fusel oil and would leave a smooth, delicate aroma, making the whiskey exceedingly palatable without the use of any additional flavoring or coloring. The whiskey thus made by one distillation and by the aging in charred oak barrels came to be known as &amp;ldquo;straight whiskey,&amp;rdquo; and to those who were good judges came to be regarded as the best and purest whiskey&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this decision, Taft is in the Kentucky Bourbon Hall of Fame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>assistant@fredminnick.com (The Fred Minnick Show Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3c40d2e4156047d381b532735bc62b7f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3c40d2e4156047d381b532735bc62b7f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 16:03:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Talk Art : Lawrence Abu Hamdan</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Russell &amp;amp; Robert speak with Lawrence Abu Hamdan, an artist, audio investigator and recent Turner Prize joint-winner. Lawrence's work explores ‘the politics of listening’ and the role of sound and voice within the law and human rights. He creates audiovisual installations, lecture performances, audio archives, photography and text, translating in-depth research and investigative work into affective, spatial experiences. Abu Hamdan works with human rights organisations, such as Amnesty International and Defense for Children International, and with international prosecutors to help obtain aural testimonies for legal and historical investigations. He is a member of Forensic Architecture at Goldsmiths London where he received his PhD in 2017. We discuss making art that's accessible, the experience of being nominated for the Turner Prize (2019), why he created the work 'Earwitness Inventory' (2018) for Chisenhale, the influence of experimental DIY music in Leeds, his admiration for the sound installations of Alvin Lucier, and what it was like growing up between Yorkshire and Jordan. Visit @TalkArt on Instagram for images of all artworks discussed in this episode, and follow @LawrenceAbuHamdan. If you've enjoyed this episode, be sure to leave us a review on Apple Podcasts or email talkartpodcast@gmail.com as we love hearing your feedback!&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>talkartpodcast@gmail.com (Talk Art)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">884ac3f66a174bd78e96fead3a9d3d5e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/884ac3f66a174bd78e96fead3a9d3d5e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ö1 Kulinarium : Moment - Kulinarium (17.01.2020)</title><description>Von der Karibik in die ganze Welt. Zuckerrohrbrand mit vielen Facetten. Die Renaissance des Rums. Gestaltung: Jana Wiese</description><author>oe1.service@orf.at (Ö1 Kulinarium)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d8000497673b4841b765d8aa51cdac40</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d8000497673b4841b765d8aa51cdac40/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Cold War: What We Saw : The Cold War: What We Saw</title><description>&lt;p&gt;November 9, 2019, is the 30th anniversary of the day the Berlin Wall came crashing down, freeing East Germany from communism, and marking the beginning of the end of the Soviet Union. But when did the Cold War start? Why does it matter 30 years later? Find out in this ten-part series, transport back in time, feel what it was like to live through the end of the Cold War, and understand why that struggle was a battle for civilization itself. Bill Whittle narrates this compelling series about two competing ideologies battling for global supremacy in the ashes of World War 2. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coming January 2020.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>whatwesaw@kastmedia.com (The Cold War: What We Saw)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a66eeca59b314759aecc435c7b982b13</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a66eeca59b314759aecc435c7b982b13/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 13:45:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>This Is Uncomfortable : I have class anxiety (rerun)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A listener struggles to navigate all the unspoken rules of middle-class life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is our last rerun before we return with new episodes later this month. To stay on top of when we&amp;#8217;re coming back, subscribe to our emails at &lt;a href="http://www.marketplace.org/comfort"&gt;marketplace.org/comfort&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>uncomfortable@marketplace.org (This Is Uncomfortable)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c28e99b9e543407ba654fbd20ab1424c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c28e99b9e543407ba654fbd20ab1424c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 13:22:37 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Studio 360 with Kurt Andersen : Images of New York: ‘West Side Story’ and Garry Winogrand’s ‘Central Park Zoo’</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Six decades after it premiered on Broadway, “West Side Story” is everywhere again, with a revival on Broadway and a movie in the works. But many still are troubled by the way Puerto Ricans are depicted. Plus, the story behind Garry Winogrand’s 1967 photo, "Central Park Zoo," which featured a white woman and a black man holding chimpanzees dressed in human clothes, and is one of his most widely exhibited — and controversial — images.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>techsupport@pri.org (Studio 360 with Kurt Andersen)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d062e3ca400841e8b3501f550890374a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d062e3ca400841e8b3501f550890374a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 13:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Endless Thread : 'I Was Abducted'</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Monique has always known she was abducted as a child, but specific details about what happened, and why, have been elusive. It wasn’t until she posted to Reddit that she found real leads and painful memories started flooding back.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@wbur.org (Endless Thread)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1ce553a97ad544c68faa515b23c8995b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1ce553a97ad544c68faa515b23c8995b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 12:36:10 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Focus On Photography (MP3) : FOP 11: Position in the Pit</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Ant is back from CES and the panel takes a moment to discuss some of the bigger photo news coming out of the convention such as the Canon 1DX Mark III as well as Nikon's new 70-200mm z-mount lens. Alan Hess and Steve Brazill join Michael Woolsey and Ant Pruitt to share insight on shooting concert photography whether you're in the photography pit or the audio booth.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hosts:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://twit.tv/people/ant-pruitt"&gt;Ant Pruitt&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://twit.tv/people/michael-woolsey"&gt;Michael Woolsey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guests:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://alanhessphotography.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Alan Hess&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://stevebrazill.com" target="_blank"&gt;Steve Brazill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Be sure to subscribe to Focus On Photography in your favorite podcatcher or at &lt;a href="https://twit.tv/shows/focus-on-photography"&gt;https://twit.tv/shows/focus-on-photography&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Join our online community at &lt;a href="https://twit.community/" target="_blank"&gt;https://twit.community/&lt;/a&gt; and be a part of the discussions.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Follow Ant on Instagram: &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/ant_pruitt/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/ant_pruitt/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Follow Wools on Instagram: &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/heywools/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/heywools/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Follow Alan on Instagram: &lt;a href="https://instagram.com/alanhess" target="_blank"&gt;https://instagram.com/alanhess&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Follow Steve on Instagram: &lt;a href="https://instagram.com/stevebrazill" target="_blank"&gt;https://instagram.com/stevebrazill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>distro@twit.tv (Focus On Photography (MP3))</author><guid isPermaLink="false">083bd84e09fb486dadfd333dfc9231f5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/083bd84e09fb486dadfd333dfc9231f5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 12:32:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Booty and the Beast Podcast : Kiara Mia talks dating, love and intimacy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Booty and the beast podcast with your hosts @sammysamla and @hoeassariel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guest @theonlykiaramia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Produced by @innoutmanager www.aikoplus.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episode sponsors @hollowtipscalifornia @448gofficial @shopatfamily and AV Justice Law Firm.&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

This episode is sponsored by 
· Anchor: The easiest way to make a podcast.  &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/s/d705500/podcast/sponsor/acugj9/url/https%3A%2F%2Fanchor.fm%2Fapp"&gt;https://anchor.fm/app&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts14+d705500@anchor.fm (Booty and the Beast Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">027e5c3712c64b2f93632bb4c294f5dc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/027e5c3712c64b2f93632bb4c294f5dc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Happy Hour with Gretchen Geraghty : How I Knew My Last Relationship Was Wrong + My Current One Is Right</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today I talk about my previous serious relationship and my current relationship. I talk all about being independent in a relationship, loving yourself first, and signs of a healthy relationship. As I always say I truly feel like you have to truly love yourself before you can love someone else! I hope this is helpful for you guys :) Be sure to check out my YouTube channel http://bit.ly/33z6gnM (Gretchen Geraghty) and my Instagram http://bit.ly/2VE0U7S (@gretchengeraghty) For business inquiries email contact@tablerockmanagement.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>gretchengeraghtypodcast@gmail.com (Happy Hour with Gretchen Geraghty)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">352af7f1534a498587ba58f6ca1e67e3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/352af7f1534a498587ba58f6ca1e67e3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 11:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>It Never Gets Old : Industry Lingo &amp; Listener Letters</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode Meredith gives a quick primer on all the lingo in secondhand - from resale to vintage to pre-loved. Then Meredith and Sarah respond to some listener letters: from Gucci loafers to first-time Poshmark haggling.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>hello@ingopodcast.com (It Never Gets Old)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b6575df6314148d4aac6513ddb7e647c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b6575df6314148d4aac6513ddb7e647c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 07:51:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Alice | Interior Design : Builder Grade to Custom | Ways to Make your Home Unique</title><description>In this episode of Dear Alice, we give some advice on making a &lt;br /&gt;builder-grade home feel more custom. If you are looking to upgrade, update or just freshen up your existing home, join us as we walk through multiple ways to achieve that. From simple changes like changing out your kitchen hardware or adding window coverings to updating your builder-grade lighting to something a little more interesting, there are so many ways to give your home a little more personality.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lighting 3:31&lt;br /&gt;Hardware 11:03&lt;br /&gt;Window Coverings/Stair Runners 15:57&lt;br /&gt;Large Scale 23:08&lt;br /&gt;Fireplace/Mantle &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Everything that’s affordable is going to be small and that’s gonna make you play small and it’s going to make your house look really cheap.” 23:19&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/alicelaneinteriors/" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/alicelaneinteriors/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/alicelanehome/" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/alicelanehome/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://alicelanehome.com/" rel="noopener"&gt;https://alicelanehome.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/AliceLaneHome" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/AliceLaneHome&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pinterest.com/alicelanehome/" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.pinterest.com/alicelanehome/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/alicelanehomecollectionsaltlakecity" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/alicelanehomecollectionsaltlakecity&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>contact@launchpod.media (Dear Alice | Interior Design)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">38a7c56e2aba4dd6a087410a7ea90718</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/38a7c56e2aba4dd6a087410a7ea90718/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 03:00:18 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Accession : Welcome to Connecticut</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Description and Notes:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Ana and Ponders start their road trip. It's going to be incredible.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The song in this episode &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/track/3MaWINEqiC8ZWpGEWz1thc"&gt;Along for the Ride&lt;/a&gt; from the album &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/album/0vlZBEIPJyCkGTJbEw53bT"&gt;Belvidere&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href="http://www.mikedunbar.com/"&gt;Mike Dunbar&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://accession.fm/episodes/welcometoconnecticut"&gt;The transcript for this episode can be found on our website here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Support:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../../../content/patreon.com/accessionfm"&gt;Pledge to Accession on Patreon for exclusive essays, bonus mini-sodes, and behind the scenes extras.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Newsletter:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://mailchi.mp/2b23f52e3baa/accessionnewsletter"&gt;Get the latest on all the Accession episodes, articles, interviews, and more.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Social:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Give us a shout out! Use #accession #accessionhomeward and #aroundtheframe!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "../../../content/twitter.com/accessionfm"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href="../../../content/instagram.com/accessionfm"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href="../../../content/facebook.com/accessionfm"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.accession.fm/"&gt;www.accession.fm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>accessionfm@gmail.com (Accession)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5220dd96cbe54c448a4fde8a6666d9e4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5220dd96cbe54c448a4fde8a6666d9e4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>TRAINED : Shaquem Griffin | How to Maintain Your Confidence in the Face of “No”</title><description>&lt;p&gt;When Shaquem Griffin was 4, he had his left hand amputated. Growing up, that didn’t hold him back from much, including playing football—even though most of his coaches, players, and friends didn’t think he’d ever be able to make more than a hobby of it. Shaquem, now a linebacker for the Seattle Seahawks, holds some of his sport’s top awards and has certainly proved his doubters wrong. In addition to training and practicing relentlessly, Shaquem has spent his entire life honing an unbreakable never-give-up mindset. It’s what has allowed him to defy expectations and develop unwavering self-confidence that has taken him all the way to the top. In this episode, Shaquem breaks down how his approach to self-talk, recovery, nutrition, and more helped him achieve what seemed like an impossible dream.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;TRAINED is produced by Nike Training Club Pro. The best of Nike. Exclusively for Trainers. To apply, go to &lt;a href="https://www.nike.com/us/en_us/e/training/nike-training-club-pro"&gt;nike.com/ntcpro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inspired by TRAINED? Then you’ll love Nike Training Club app. The Nike Training Club app provides expertly designed workouts from Nike trainers for everyone at all fitness levels. It’s the ultimate training source from the leading minds at Nike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With holistic tips on movement, recovery, nutrition, mindset and sleep from experts on Nike’s Performance Council, NTC delivers on all five facets of fitness and puts our best at your fingertips. No matter how you train, NTC will help you discover your personal greatness. Click the link below to get the app for iOS or Android.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://smart.link/5b59e1c79378b"&gt;Download Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>max@pineapple.fm (TRAINED)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d4569bbd8ae941acba9b482fce9b33c3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d4569bbd8ae941acba9b482fce9b33c3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 02:00:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>BFF with the Chef : Bay Leaves are Important - Chef Ed Harris</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today I'm interviewing Chef Ed Harris, winner of Food Network's Chopped Turbo Powered season four and Iron Chef International. He's also appeared as a chef on 24-hour Restaurant Battle, which his team won. Chef Ed began his culinary education at the Art Institute of New York City. For more than 20 years, he's been heavily involved in several aspects of the food industry from Saucier all the way up to Executive Chef. This eclectic background has allowed him to currently work as a consultant chef where he plays an active role in the planning, supervision, and creative aspects involved in the food industry.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Find Chef Ed:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://chefedharris.com/"&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://chefedharris.com/collections/all"&gt;Chef Ed’s Spices – Faye’s Flavor Enhancers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/Chef-Ed-Harris-157210770985751/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/ChefEdHarris?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor"&gt; Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/chefedharris/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Recipes Mentioned in the Show&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.thingsguyana.com/metemgee-a-delicious-and-flavorsome-dish-cooked-in-guyana/"&gt; Metem (Metemgee – Guyanese Stew)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href= "https://metemgee.com/2017/07/28/duff-guyanese-steamed-dumplings/"&gt;Duff (Guyanese Steamed Dumplings)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>bffwiththechef@gmail.com (BFF with the Chef)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3ebcddce6752487a8554a1834fd958d0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3ebcddce6752487a8554a1834fd958d0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Start Today Morning Show : 85: Our Kids Want Braces More Than Toys</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Come hang out with us weekdays LIVE at 9AM CST on Facebook and Instagram, and catch up on episodes you missed here!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Y'all. We are still pinching ourselves about the latest news out of our podcast network - Trent freakin' Shelton is launching a brand new show with the Hollis Company! That's right, Straight Up with Trent Shelton debuts on December 4th and will drop new episodes EVERY WEDNESDAY! Trent is going to bring honest, raw, life-changing wisdom straight from his heart to your ears on a weekly basis. His style is so unique, his message so powerful, we just KNOW this is going to be your new must-listen podcast. Subscribe to Straight Up with Trent Shelton on iTunes, Google, Spotify, Stitcher, or wherever you listen to podcasts by &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/trentpod"&gt;clicking this link&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@cadence13.com (Start Today Morning Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">df7c07d02e364dad98e42e3d7157f878</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/df7c07d02e364dad98e42e3d7157f878/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Art School Podcast : Ep #62: How to Harness Your Imagination</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Join me on the podcast this week to discover how to fully engage your mind, body, spirit, and soul so you can approach every aspect of your life with the confidence that, even if you didn’t get it right this time, that you are more than capable of finding a way through.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Get full show notes and more information here: &lt;a href= "https://www.leahcb.com/62" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.leahcb.com/62&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>leah@leahcb.com (The Art School Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0104ff9685754dceb3d8ebd202c3e224</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0104ff9685754dceb3d8ebd202c3e224/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>This is Joy &amp; Claire : 3: Dietary Pedestals</title><description>&lt;br /&gt;
Identifying and getting past diet rules, loving bread and pop tarts, Joy&amp;#8217;s Peloton treadmill updates, down with Jillian Michaels, and Lizzo love!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Sponsors: &lt;a rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label=" (opens in a new tab)" href="http://www.blublox.com" target="_blank"&gt;BLUBLOX&lt;/a&gt; discount code GGW&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Please leave us a review! We love hearing your feedback and want to make this show the best it can be for YOU, amazing listeners. Share with a friend while you&amp;#8217;re at it!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a rel="noreferrer noopener" aria-label="GGW Instagram (opens in a new tab)" href="https://www.instagram.com/joyandclaire_/?hl=en" target="_blank"&gt;Joy &amp;amp; Claire Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Support the podcast! Subcribe and REVIEW wherever you listen to the podcasts. &lt;br /&gt;</description><author>thisisjoyandclaire@gmail.com (This is Joy &amp; Claire)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">dccc3a18e7474f9bb6ecedcf4e83e1f0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/dccc3a18e7474f9bb6ecedcf4e83e1f0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 23:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Get Your Shoot Together Photography Podcast : Episode 033 - Must Love In Person Education</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Dogs may be man's best friend, but they certainly aren't Kira's. This week, Kira tells about facing her fears for the sake of a good project while Mary tries to relate. The girls also discuss the pros and cons of online VS in person learning as they both get ready to go to Texas School. Have a listen hopefully while you are on your way to Imaging USA!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>girl@getyourshoottogether.com (Get Your Shoot Together Photography Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">27dbec71715a4c769e73c2f656e0edd2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/27dbec71715a4c769e73c2f656e0edd2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Savor : Savor Classics: Graham Crackers</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Graham crackers today are sweet, airy, and often a component in desserts, but they originated as a bland health food peddled by a temperance preacher. In this classic episode, Anney and Lauren explore the long, weird journey of graham crackers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Savor)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8b87596752004dd2a47b919b2ef1a235</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8b87596752004dd2a47b919b2ef1a235/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 18:41:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>SOMM TV : SOMM TV Podcast Episode 14: Enter the Delicacy</title><description>&lt;img src="https://assets.podomatic.net/ts/09/d0/15/jason22461/3000x3000_14555988.jpg" alt="itunes pic" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason Wise and Stephanie Mutz discuss the strange and wonderful food, sea urchin, and the upcoming film.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">c252dfa8e9ff441db434072b4ad60ddd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c252dfa8e9ff441db434072b4ad60ddd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 11:58:36 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Natch Beaut : 2019 Year in Review with Bree Essrig Part 2</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Skincare brings people together! This is part 2 of the 2019 Product year in review. This time, Jackie is up, who shares with guest Bree Essrig all of her favorite products in every category. For a list of everything discussed on this episode, visit www.natchbeaut.com. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>starburnsaudio@starburnsind.com (Natch Beaut)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fab8780b7f9c41499509f817f88aff08</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fab8780b7f9c41499509f817f88aff08/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:26:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Major Crush : Season Two Trailer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It's time for another season of Major Crush, and we're excited to be back! This season we're letting the experiences take us where we need to go, so we hope you'll join us! CONTACT US: If you have questions or comments for Meredith and Lou, and you're listening on the Anchor App, you can send them to us directly. If you're listening to this podcast on any other platform, and you want to reach out, you can email us at majorcrushpodcast@gmail.com &amp;nbsp;// Follow us on Instagram: @majorcrushwinecast. // Be sure to check out the entire first season of Major Crush on Spotify, or wherever you access your favorite podcasts! Episodes of Season Two drop every Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts11+b19dad8@anchor.fm (Major Crush)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7daec5120ca94c77a518c41d4c87ed04</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7daec5120ca94c77a518c41d4c87ed04/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 13:40:48 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Photography Insights - important industry interviews by Phlogger : Interview with Bellamy from Japan Camera Hunter</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For episode 74 we bring you the man behind Japan Camera Hunter, yes its Bellamy Hunt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bellamy is at the forefront for those in search of their dream cameras. &amp;nbsp;In fact, his business works around this idea of sourcing cameras in high-end condition. &amp;nbsp;But this isn’t all that Bellamy is know for. &amp;nbsp;Of course, there is his own 35mm film too! Called JCH Streetpan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He’s been around the analogue photography scene a long time as a blogger too, with reviews and articles on current news. &amp;nbsp;In fact, you might know him from his writing skills and honesty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this episode we talk about:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;The industry of sourcing camera&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Japanese customs&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Blogging&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Amazon&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Confidentiality&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Trends &amp;amp; travelling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Of course a hint of a few rare cameras&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the random questions, we discuss horse riding and the UK. &amp;nbsp;As usual, check out the website for links and sign up for the newsletter, that way you will always know about the latest work and podcast episodes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LINKS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website - &lt;a href="https://www.japancamerahunter.com/"&gt;https://www.japancamerahunter.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram - &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/japancamerahunter/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/japancamerahunter/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PAY IT FORWARD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bellamy wants to recommend - &lt;a href="http://www.tamarkin.com/blog"&gt;http://www.tamarkin.com/blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/photography-insights/message</description><author>podcasts6+3417154@anchor.fm (Photography Insights - important industry interviews by Phlogger)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">368f2bdc9d1247048de3f99d4df3ceed</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/368f2bdc9d1247048de3f99d4df3ceed/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 13:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Marvel by the Month : November 1964 - 1st appearance of Dormammu, Immortus, Unus the Untouchable</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It's Robb and Bryan's birthday, but you get the present of this fancy new episode! Doctor Strange faces the Dread Dormammu for the first time (but definitely not the last)! Unus the Untouchable does not get touched by the X-Men! And Immortus... shows up and does some stuff, all of which is undone by the end of the issue! Plus, Spider-Man goes a whole issue without punching anyone, the Fantastic Four solve the mystery of the Invincible Man, and much, much more!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts11+33d0808@anchor.fm (Marvel by the Month)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">13fec255d9fe4a91a59c332c4e483394</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/13fec255d9fe4a91a59c332c4e483394/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 10:53:17 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Couple Things with Shawn and Andrew : Embarrassing</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Episode 3 of Couple Things with Shawn and Andrew is a fun one. Today we walk you guys through some of our most embarrassing moments together that we've never shared before. &amp;nbsp;Though it all, we've learned that nobody is perfect and at the end of the day, we're all human :) We'd love to hear your thoughts on this episode &amp;amp; if you've ever been embarrassed in front of your significant other.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you haven't yet, please rate and subscribe to the show to hear more! And if you have suggestions/recommendations for the show, send us your ideas in a video format - we might just choose yours! Email us at couplethingspod@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts44+415382c@anchor.fm (Couple Things with Shawn and Andrew)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">47e9a90812f548598b9b9a57a30b2660</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/47e9a90812f548598b9b9a57a30b2660/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 07:17:43 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MOOD with Lauren Elizabeth : 12: MOOD: Boss Bitches Spilling Tea with Cassie Randolph &amp; Michelle Randolph!</title><description>&lt;div&gt;On this week's episode of MOOD we discuss our current mood's before jumping right into this week's episode of The Bachelor with veteran Cassie Randolph and her sister Michelle Randolph. Listen to our recap and in-depth Q&amp;amp;A on all things reality TV and Los Angeles life!&lt;br&gt;Follow me on Instagram: &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/laurenelizabeth/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/laurenelizabeth/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;And for the next #MyMOOD segment make sure to send in your mood and what you need advice on to MoodWithLaurenElizabeth@gmail.com&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>rss@audioboom.com (MOOD with Lauren Elizabeth)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b2bb590a687842629ff38a72fe2757af</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b2bb590a687842629ff38a72fe2757af/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Popcast With Knox and Jamie : Captain In/Of Pop Culture</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, we talked about captains in and of pop culture. What makes a captain? Who makes you want to be First Mate and who makes you want to abandon ship? There are so many captains and a vast sea of opportunities to go overboard with our nautical references.&amp;nbsp;See what we did there?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MENTIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Join as a Friend of the Show at &lt;a href="http://knoxandjamie.com/patreon" target="_blank"&gt;knoxandjamie.com/patreon&lt;/a&gt; to get our EXCLUSIVE Bachelor recaps!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://imgix.ranker.com/user_node_img/50018/1000341934/original/zodiac-symbol-photo-u3?w=650&amp;amp;q=60&amp;amp;fm=pjpg&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;crop=faces%22" target="_blank"&gt;Chris Evans’ Taurus Tattoo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Don Cheadle &lt;em&gt;Funny or Die&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TwJaELXadKo" target="_blank"&gt;Short&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Oh Captain, my Captain” &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j64SctPKmqk" target="_blank"&gt;Scene&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ariana Grande &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/popculture/ariana-grande-apologizes-doughnut-lick-i-hate-america-t31006" target="_blank"&gt;Donut-gate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2017/02/27/entertainment/academy-awards-mistake-what-happened/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Oscar Blunder 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://knoxandjamie.com/254" target="_blank"&gt;Episode 254&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE BACHELORETTE EPISODE RECAPS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We recap each episode of &lt;em&gt;The Bachelorette&lt;/em&gt; for our Friends of the Show at Patreon. Support at either Friend level gets you our weekly recaps dropped into your podcast app every Tuesday. Go to &lt;a href="http://www.knoxandjamie.com/patreon" target="_blank"&gt;www.knoxandjamie.com/patreon&lt;/a&gt; to support the show. And thank you!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GREEN LIGHTS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jamie – Television: &lt;a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/81039393" target="_blank"&gt;Cheer&lt;/a&gt; | Movie: &lt;a href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt4916630/" target="_blank"&gt;Just Mercy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knox – Television: &lt;a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80211991" target="_blank"&gt;You&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BONUS SEGMENT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our Patreon supporters can get full access to this week’s The More You Know news segment. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.patreon.com/popcast" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Become a partner.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The More You Know&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vanityfair.com/style/2020/01/meghan-and-harrys-royal-exit-biggest-and-wildest-rumors" target="_blank"&gt;Harry and Megan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/music/story/2020-01-09/selena-gomez-rare-new-album-review" target="_blank"&gt;Selena Gomez New Album&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/10/entertainment/justin-chambers-leaving-greys-anatomy/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Justin Chambers Leaves Grey’s Anatomy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.boxofficemojo.com/article/ed3614442500/?ref_=bo_hm_hp" target="_blank"&gt;Box Office Recap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2020/01/13/oscars-nominations-2020-full-list-of-nominees-announced-live/" target="_blank"&gt;Oscar Nominations (Monday Morning)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SHOW SPONSORS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rothys&lt;/strong&gt;: Go to &lt;a href="http://rothys.com/pop" target="_blank"&gt;rothys.com/pop&lt;/a&gt; to get your new favorite flats.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Postmates&lt;/strong&gt;: Get $100 of free delivery credit for your first SEVEN days. To start your free deliveries, download the app and use code “[POPCAST]”.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ZipRecruiter&lt;/strong&gt;: Popcast listeners can try ZipRecruiter FOR FREE at &lt;a href="http://ziprecruiter.com/popcast" target="_blank"&gt;ziprecruiter.com/popcast&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noom&lt;/strong&gt;: Small steps make big progress. Sign up for your trial today at &lt;a href="http://noom.com/pop" target="_blank"&gt;noom.com/pop&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscribe to Episodes:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/popcast-pop-culture-commentary/id712316884?mt=2" target="_blank"&gt;iTunes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;|&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.stitcher.com/podcast/the-popcast-2" target="_blank"&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.knoxandjamie.com/newsletter" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.knoxandjamie.com/newsletter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow Us:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.instagram.com/thepopcast" target="_blank"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/popcastpod" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/thepopcast" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support Us:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.patreon.com/popcast" target="_blank"&gt;Monthly Donation&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_donations&amp;amp;business=JTT8988U8SZSU&amp;amp;lc=US&amp;amp;item_name=The%20Popcast&amp;amp;currency_code=USD&amp;amp;bn=PP%2dDonationsBF%3abtn_donateCC_LG%2egif%3aNonHosted" target="_blank"&gt;One-Time Donation&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="http://www.zazzle.com/thepopcast" target="_blank"&gt;Swag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>rkmccoy@gmail.com (The Popcast With Knox and Jamie)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2954ef77290b48408f8a36a6788d05a5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2954ef77290b48408f8a36a6788d05a5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 06:11:23 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Historic Royal Palaces Podcast : Royal women and power dressing</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Throughout history the clothing of British royalty has influenced fashion tastes and trends.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This series complied from our archive explores contemporary royal fashion and its influence on what we wear today.         &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This talk explores the wardrobes of seven royal women who have used, and continue to use, clothing and fashion as a tool for diplomacy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This talk was recorded live at Kensington Palace in 2016.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To find out more about the history and stories of our palaces visit &lt;a href= "http://www.hrp.org.uk/history-and-stories"&gt;www.hrp.org.uk/history-and-stories&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>claudia.strange@hrp.org.uk (Historic Royal Palaces Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6b378c1475d540aba1258865716cc226</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6b378c1475d540aba1258865716cc226/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Stay Focused Podcast : #49 The #1 Thing to AVOID When Learning Photography</title><description>&lt;p&gt; Learning photography can be incredibly overwhelming.  I get it. And there are many , many other photographers that are feeling the pain too.  You are not alone. On today’s episode I talk with long time &lt;a href= "https://cozy-clicks-education.teachable.com/"&gt;Cozy Clicks student&lt;/a&gt;, Jennifer Corbin.  As a hobbyist photographer (with a goal to go pro!) she shares with you want she has found to be some of the most helpful things to do to learn photography and beat the overwhelm, plus has incredibly wonderful insight on the things you should be avoiding if you want to see progress in your work! Listen here cozyclicks.com/fortynine&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>emily@cozyclicks.com (The Stay Focused Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">21b4a05aaa9a47eb95c2dd9d23182021</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/21b4a05aaa9a47eb95c2dd9d23182021/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 04:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Stitch Please : Cirque de SEWING--A chat with SewMuchAerial</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Mentioned in this episode&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/sewmuchaerial/" target="_blank"&gt;SewMuchAerial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.etsy.com/shop/rissewn/" target="_blank"&gt;Marissa's etsy page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aerialympics.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Aerialympics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://patterns.bootstrapfashion.com/diy-dress-form-sewing-pattern.html" target="_blank"&gt;Custom Dressform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.etsy.com/listing/698609304/swatch-set-9?ref=shop_home_active_9&amp;sca=1" target="_blank"&gt;Sheer Performance Fabrics with Melanin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support the Stitch Please podcast and Black Women Stitch. You can get an adorable enamel pin by sending $15 to Paypal or Cash App.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/blackwomenstitch" target="_blank"&gt;Patreon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.paypal.me/lisalovestosew"&gt;Paypal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/blackwomenstitch" target="_blank"&gt;Ko-Fi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://cash.app/$LisaWoolfork" target="_blank"&gt;Cash App&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>woolfork@gmail.com (Stitch Please)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">88685cb65d3b4d1d9436cb4b8c766cef</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/88685cb65d3b4d1d9436cb4b8c766cef/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 04:00:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Local Mouthful: A podcast about food and home cooking : Episode 302: Loaded Baked Potatoes, Mushroom Steaks, and Weight</title><description>&lt;figure class="wp-block-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.localmouthful.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/lars-blankers-B0s3Xndk6tw-unsplash-1024x683.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1428" srcset="http://www.localmouthful.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/lars-blankers-B0s3Xndk6tw-unsplash-1024x683.jpg 1024w, http://www.localmouthful.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/lars-blankers-B0s3Xndk6tw-unsplash-300x200.jpg 300w, http://www.localmouthful.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/lars-blankers-B0s3Xndk6tw-unsplash-768x512.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;These potatoes are hoping to get loaded.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In our food news segment this week, we were talking about Melissa Clark&amp;#8217;s recent &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/31/dining/flexitarian-eating-less-meat.html"&gt;Meat Lover&amp;#8217;s Guide to Eating Less Meat&lt;/a&gt; in the New York Times. (Great recipes at the link!)&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In our What&amp;#8217;s for Dinner segment, it&amp;#8217;s all about the loaded baked potato.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In How&amp;#8217;d You Make That? Joy talks about her recent maitake mushroom &amp;#8220;steaks.&amp;#8221; (Joy didn&amp;#8217;t follow &lt;a href="https://www.bonappetit.com/recipe/seared-maitake-mushrooms"&gt;this recipe&lt;/a&gt; exactly but it gave her enough inspiration for quick-and-dirty lunchtime version.)&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;We are wondering if it&amp;#8217;s even possible to write or talk about food and eating as it relates to body weight without somehow inadvertently contributing to weight stigma. Share your thoughts. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And in What We&amp;#8217;re Loving: It&amp;#8217;s remodeled Aldi stores!&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;
If you like what you hear,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/local-mouthful/id1027658451?mt=2"&gt;make sure to subscribe&lt;/a&gt;! Bonus points if you rate us or leave a review. Follow us on Instagram and twitter&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/localmouthful"&gt;@localmouthful&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and help us spread the word about the show.



&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.localmouthful.com/2020/01/15/episode-302-loaded-baked-potatoes-mushroom-steaks-and-weight/"&gt;Episode 302: Loaded Baked Potatoes, Mushroom Steaks, and Weight&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="http://www.localmouthful.com"&gt;Local Mouthful&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marisa@localmouthful.com (Local Mouthful: A podcast about food and home cooking)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7fc625ab1085443a9f7fff69a3d5e408</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7fc625ab1085443a9f7fff69a3d5e408/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 03:05:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dream Big Podcast : Bob Goff -- Season 2: Dreaming Big in 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Season 2 is now live, with more friends, deep conversations, and practical tools to guide you to discover, declare, and chase your big ambitions!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This month, in honor of the new year and the new decade, we have a &lt;a href="https://mailchi.mp/bobgoff.com/2020clarity"&gt;free PDF workbook for you to download&lt;/a&gt;. It’s a user-friendly guide to defining your core values and fundamental beliefs- the essential building blocks to discovering which dreams you should invest in this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the episode:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Producers :&lt;a href="https://bobgoff.com/team"&gt; Tatave Abeshyan and Haley King&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engineer :&lt;a href="https://jackcarpproductions.com/"&gt; Jackson Carpenter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Producer &amp; Co-host :&lt;a href="http://theyouschool.com/the-team"&gt; Scott Schimmel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@pushplaypodcasts.com (Dream Big Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d015598e1bb9447d949d5218da6d1f28</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d015598e1bb9447d949d5218da6d1f28/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 03:00:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Left Brain Artist : #136 Lara Cornell: Art, Flowers, and Travel Adventures</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Artist Lara Cornell is a lifelong traveler who hosts creative retreats all over the world. She also has a space called Anahata Collaborative, where she holds creative seminars and events. Lara also facilitates entrepreneur meetup groups in her home town of Minneapolis. I met Lara in Morocco when we attended an art retreat. We talk about that and her upcoming retreats, including one in 2020 to Scotland. The Show Notes and links for all my episodes can be found at &lt;a href= "https://suzanneredmond.com/my-podcast/list-of-artists/"&gt;https://suzanneredmond.com/my-podcast/list-of-artists/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sredmond75@comcast.net (The Left Brain Artist)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f6d9690074dd4b40b625514fb0fa8945</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f6d9690074dd4b40b625514fb0fa8945/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Moment : Introducing Deadly Misadventures</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Exclusively on Wondery+, each episode of Deadly Misadventures will bring you some of the most terrifying, real-life stories of those who came face to face with death. Some who lived to tell the tale while others succumbed to their&amp;nbsp;Deadly&amp;nbsp;Misadventures. You know the odds. The stakes are high. If you dare to take a chance with Lady Luck, visit &lt;a href="http://wondery.fm/deadly" target="_blank"&gt;wondery.fm/deadly&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>iwonder@wondery.com (The Moment)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9b00ac2b7c3f4f2791f6b60a90105543</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9b00ac2b7c3f4f2791f6b60a90105543/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The History of Egypt Podcast : Mini Episode: An Intact Tomb</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Kha and Merit, an Intact Tomb. In 1906, a remarkable discovery came to light: the tomb of a middle-class couple, who lived in the town of Deir el-Medina. Here, amid the craftsmen and specialists who made tombs, a man named Kha and a woman named Merit enjoyed an affluent lifestyle. When they died, they were interred with all their worldly possessions and slept undisturbed for 3300 years. Then, a wonderful discovery occurred and an ancient story came to life... The History of Egypt Podcast is supported by Patrons, get early access and ad-free listening at &lt;a href="https://create.acast.com/episodes/c8530076-4db3-4326-b377-6a676931ff74/www.patreon.com/egyptpodcast" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.patreon.com/egyptpodcast&lt;/a&gt;... Images and Bibliography at &lt;a href="https://create.acast.com/episodes/c8530076-4db3-4326-b377-6a676931ff74/www.egyptianhistorypodcast.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.egyptianhistorypodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;... Music by Keith Zizza &lt;a href="https://create.acast.com/episodes/c8530076-4db3-4326-b377-6a676931ff74/www.keithzizza.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.keithzizza.com&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>egyptpodcast@gmail.com (The History of Egypt Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">be7991cdc62b4028a5a4fee23a03ef4c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/be7991cdc62b4028a5a4fee23a03ef4c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:45:30 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Last Day : 15: A Parenting Nightmare</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;A few years ago, Laurie McTeague noticed her teenage son, Ian, was uncharacteristically depressed. So she went snooping around on his phone and discovered that he’d been widely experimenting with nearly every drug under the sun. What followed was years of relentless searching for effective adolescent treatment while her son continued to relapse again and again. As a parent, how do you navigate this?  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please note, Last Day contains strong language, mature themes, and may not be appropriate for all listeners. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Everything-Horrible-Wonderful-Tragicomic-Memoir/dp/1492664103"&gt;Everything Is Horrible and Wonderful: A Tragicomic Memoir of Genius, Heroin, Love and Loss&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lemonadamedia.com/lastdaysurvey"&gt;www.lemonadamedia.com/lastdaysurvey&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://rothys.com/lastday"&gt;rothys.com/lastday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.lemonadamedia.com/shop"&gt;www.lemonadamedia.com/shop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Transcriptions available shortly after air date at&lt;a href="https://www.lemonadamedia.com/show/last-day/"&gt; https://www.lemonadamedia.com/show/last-day/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>WWOPodcasts@westwoodone.com (Last Day)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4f5663b442804e609f667a1a62ce8a6b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4f5663b442804e609f667a1a62ce8a6b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Beauty Closet : How to Be A (Very) Hot 74</title><description>&lt;p&gt;World-famous fashion designer Norma Kamali is glowy, brilliant, sexy, life-loving, and more successful than ever. She talks to us about her new clean beauty line (the self-tanner is out of this world); the magic of acupuncture facials; her no-fail secret for great sex, incredible skin, shiny hair, and digestion (hint: you can ingest it); and why aging isn’t a bad thing—&lt;em&gt;at all&lt;/em&gt;. (For more, see &lt;a href="https://goop.com/beauty-closet-podcast/"&gt;The Beauty Closet hub&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@goop.com (The Beauty Closet)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7a3666c5ee4b488ba69e695eac82774b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7a3666c5ee4b488ba69e695eac82774b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Fail With Elizabeth Day : S7, Ep3 How to Fail: Mabel</title><description>&lt;p&gt;My guest today has the middle name Alabama-Pearl, which is pretty cool but NOT QUITE AS COOL as the fact that she's a chart-topping pop-star who has racked up three top-10 hits and recently wrote one of the best Christmas songs of all time, &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hVzjR6hBArE'&gt;Loneliest Time of the Year&lt;/a&gt; (and I say that as a die-hard Mariah fan). Plus, my guest is still only 23 years old. Revolting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, that's right, it's &lt;a href='https://www.mabelofficial.com/'&gt;Mabel&lt;/a&gt;, a double Brit nominee and the creative brains behind the hit song &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9TQKyDD9Yig'&gt;Don’t Call Me Up&lt;/a&gt;, which was in the top 40 for four months. She was born in Malaga, went to school in Stockholm and now lives in London. Her creative lineage is quite something: Mabel's mother is &lt;a href='https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Neneh_Cherry'&gt;Neneh Cherry&lt;/a&gt;, her dad &lt;a href='https://www.instagram.com/theboogabear/?hl=en'&gt;Cameron McVey&lt;/a&gt; is a producer who has worked with Massive Attack, Portishead, All Saints and Sugababes, her uncle is &lt;a href='https://www.eagleeyecherry.com/'&gt;Eagle-Eye Cherry&lt;/a&gt; and her  step-grandfather is the legendary jazz musician &lt;a href='https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Don_Cherry_(trumpeter)'&gt;Don Cherry&lt;/a&gt;. But her talent and self-possession is all her own. Mabel joins me to talk about her failure to remember lyrics, her failure to stay vegan (which is hilarious) and her failure to sleep, which is a first on the podcast and I'm so glad she decided to broach the subject of insomnia as I know it effects so many of us and is such a debilitating thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Mabel, for coming on the podcast and doing your research so well that you actually read my book first. I heart you hard for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Talking of that book...the Sunday Times Top 5 bestselling book of the podcast, How To Fail: Everything I've Ever Learned From Things Going Wrong is out now in paperback and available to buy &lt;a href='https://www.amazon.co.uk/How-Fail-Everything-Learned-Things/dp/0008327327/ref=asap_bc?ie=UTF8'&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;* &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;This episode is sponsored by &lt;a href='https://welcometomeya.com/'&gt;MEYA&lt;/a&gt;, a new meditation app that uses the power of music to switch you into a meditative state. Download the app &lt;a href='https://welcometomeya.com/'&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to experience the power of MEYA mind journeys and a new way to fit meditation into your daily routine this January. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;How To Fail With Elizabeth Day is hosted by Elizabeth Day, produced by Naomi Mantin and Chris Sharp. We love hearing from you! To contact us, email &lt;a href='mailto:email:%20howtofail@gmail.com'&gt;howtofailpod@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p2"&gt;* &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Social Media:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Elizabeth Day &lt;a href='https://twitter.com/elizabday'&gt;@elizabday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Mabel &lt;a href='https://twitter.com/Mabel?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor'&gt;@Mabel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;MEYA &lt;a href='https://twitter.com/meya_app'&gt;@meya_app&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p2"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p2"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p2"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>elizabethdayjournalist@gmail.com (How To Fail With Elizabeth Day)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8c932efbc77247309d2c8a2a136e03cf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8c932efbc77247309d2c8a2a136e03cf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>What I Know Now with Amelia Liana : Cleaning Up, Clearing Out &amp; Moving On</title><description>Ever heard of a post-breakup concierge? Well we hadn’t until we came across Onward, a company that does exactly that; and doesn’t it sound like a dream. Imagine all the horrible admin that occurs after a heartache/traumatic cycle change disappeared! Amelia grabbed Lindsay Meck, co-founder of Onward, to talk about what sparked her to build the company and how it actually helps people move from a state of extreme distress to a positive place of rebuilding and recovery. What we’ve all been missing no? Please rate, review &amp; subscribe to What I Know Now. Shop the Heartbreak Manual 20% off now! &lt;a href="https://amelialiana.com/heartbreakmanual/" rel="noopener"&gt;https://amelialiana.com/heartbreakmanual/&lt;/a&gt;  Visit Onward here: &lt;a href="https://www.move-onward.com" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.move-onward.com&lt;/a&gt;  Follow Amelia on Instagram: &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/amelialiana/" rel="noopener"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/amelialiana/&lt;/a&gt; #WhatIKnowNowPodcast</description><author>feeds@spreaker.com (What I Know Now with Amelia Liana)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b47efbc08bc94a8f90a031807eeafeea</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b47efbc08bc94a8f90a031807eeafeea/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:00:17 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Creative Chats podcast : 17. Creative Chat with Megan Carty: The Windy Road of the Creative</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Megan Carty is a contemporary painter residing with her family in the beautiful countryside of Massachusetts. Her colorful art has been featured by Anthropologie, Minted, Homegoods, Maine Home &amp; Design magazine, Maine Cottage, the Improper Bostonian, Glitter Guide, The English Room, Loom &amp; Kiln, Sloan Kettering Memorial Hospital and The Boston Daybook. When she's not joyfully slinging the paint you can find her listening to records, hiding from her three young kiddos, indulging in bad reality television (that MAY involve “real housewives”) while savoring a delicious hot chocolate. Her awesome husband Chris always adds just the right amount of marshmallow!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Megan is passionate about sharing her journey living most of her life with chronic depression and anxiety...she wants to show it's possible to use art as active therapy for yourself while bringing hope to others.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.megancartyart.com/"&gt;https://www.megancartyart.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mike@mikebrennan.me (Creative Chats podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f42fc62b6d9a41a2b1143d0f83554ead</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f42fc62b6d9a41a2b1143d0f83554ead/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Craft Will Never Die (Woodworking Podcast) : Episode 2.1: Beware the Butt Spector!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;To get the Aftershow... Join us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/cwndpodcast&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our NEW MAKER is Andrew Szeto! Instagram: @szetoszeto &amp;nbsp;YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCEyBnGE6eAu_Dr4lN0bK6pg&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All three of us are on Instagram and Youtube as:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blake: "The Weber Woodshop" https://www.youtube.com/c/BlakeWeber&amp;nbsp; https://www.instagram.com/weberwoodshop&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nick: "Key Woodworks" https://www.youtube.com/c/KeyWoodworks&amp;nbsp; https://www.instagram.com/keywoodworks&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jason: "Bourbon Moth Woodworking" https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCQ_bmgSrYsQS0LboA_tZpEw/featured&amp;nbsp; https://www.instagram.com/bourbonmoth&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for listening everyone! Please give us feedback or ask questions on our podcast instagram account: @craftwillneverdie See ya later!&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/craftwillneverdie/message</description><author>podcasts10+6e91848@anchor.fm (Craft Will Never Die (Woodworking Podcast))</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fec85027839c4031bb21c41623f6b3c7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fec85027839c4031bb21c41623f6b3c7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 21:33:34 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>You're Welcome with Hilary Rushford : Ep 41: How We Make Change Happen (Part 2): Fear of Failure + Being a Good Friend</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In part 2 of this convo... when my dear friend Brian lost 140 pounds in one year I was fascinated! Not by the weight loss methods, but by what prompted the change. Why do we finally change something that’s been making us unhappy? How do we start and stick with it? What makes the difference from all the times we’ve tried before?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If Brian’s story resonated with you today, you can follow his journey on Instagram &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/brianbrister/?hl=en"&gt;@brianbrister&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is the year for change for many of us. Take advantage of the special promo for &lt;a href= "https://elegantexcellencejournal.com/"&gt;Elegant Excellence Goals Journal&lt;/a&gt; to help you gain clarity on the change you'd like to see this year.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What change are you seeking in your life this year? Let’s chat over on Instagram &lt;a href= "http://instagram.com/hilaryrushford"&gt;@HilaryRushford&lt;/a&gt;. Leave me a voice memo at &lt;a href= "http://hilaryrushford.com/podvip"&gt;HilaryRushford.com/podvip&lt;/a&gt; to suggest podcast topics or Q’s for 2020!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@hilaryrushford.com (You're Welcome with Hilary Rushford)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2afe162027234ce7b8467fd5b1f0bd3f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2afe162027234ce7b8467fd5b1f0bd3f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 21:09:46 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Young Rocker : E2: BASS PLAYER</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Young Chelsea brings us back to the strange landscape of middle school and recounts how she discovered and fell in love with her favorite band and playing bass. Old Chelsea provides some much-needed advice about making and keeping friends.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>cursin@gmail.com (Dear Young Rocker)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c3cacb3af7f24d038530bf0033e6162b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c3cacb3af7f24d038530bf0033e6162b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 21:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bad On Paper : The Veronica(s) Beard talk to us about building their brand!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We’re thrilled to have sister-in-law duo Veronica Swanson Beard + Veronica Miele Beard with us today! Besides being two of the most stylish women we know, they have built an incredible brand. Both women have incredible backgrounds (and stories) to share - it was fun learning how they got their start and went into business together. With backgrounds in design, entrepreneurship, finance, and a mutual love for fashion, they created  a brand that it smart, stylish, and inclusive. We talk about extending their size range, their best-selling Dickie jackets, their 10 year anniversary, favorite fashion trends, and personal style icons. We also talk about the importance of family and life outside of work.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;More about Veronica Beard:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://veronicabeard.com/"&gt;Veronicabeard.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/veronicabeard/?hl=en"&gt;@veronicabeard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Products Mentioned:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://shopstyle.it/l/bcCMe"&gt;Vintner’s Daughter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://shopstyle.it/l/bcCKo"&gt;Nars Laguna bronzer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://shopstyle.it/l/bcCKB"&gt;Charlotte Tilbury&lt;/a&gt; eyeshadow palettes &amp; IG tutorials&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.shophq.com/a/boutique/activated-argan-oils?icid=DB-_-AAOils-_-020419"&gt; Active Argan Oils &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Obsessions:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://amzn.to/3858ahQ"&gt;Conair Fabric Defuzzer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://shopstyle.it/l/bcCMx"&gt;Zalto Wine Glasses&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Instagram Obsessions:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/veryrealfantasy/?hl=en"&gt;@veryrealfantasy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/cobblerscovehotel/?hl=en"&gt;@cobblerscovehotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.pictame.com/user/baoace/1942622974"&gt;@baoace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Books Mentioned:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://amzn.to/37mUHSm"&gt;A Court of Thorns and Roses By Sarah J Maas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://amzn.to/2sV2Tuz"&gt;Big Magic by Elizabeth Gilbert&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://amzn.to/2tRfe2Z"&gt;Long Bright River by Liz Moore&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;January Book Club Pick:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://amzn.to/2MLr8C3"&gt;Good Girls Lie By JT Ellison&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Sponsors: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;Kassatex: Take 20% off your first order when you shop at &lt;a href="https://kassatex.com/"&gt;kassatex.com&lt;/a&gt; and enter code BOP20 at checkout&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;HelloFresh: Get 10 free meals at &lt;a href="https://www.hellofresh.com/"&gt;hellofresh.com/BOP10&lt;/a&gt; and use code BOP10.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;LOLA: Take 30% off your first month subscription - &lt;a href= "https://www.mylola.com/"&gt;mylola.com&lt;/a&gt; and enter code BOP30 at checkout.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Join our &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/badonpaperpodcast/"&gt;FB group&lt;/a&gt; for amazing book recs &amp; more!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on Instagram &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/badonpaperpodcast/?hl=en"&gt;@badonpaperpodcast&lt;/a&gt;. Follow Grace on Instagram &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/graceatwood/?hl=en"&gt;@graceatwood&lt;/a&gt; and her blog TheStripe.com and Becca &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/beccamfreeman/"&gt;@beccamfreeman&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>badonpaperpodcast@gmail.com (Bad On Paper)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b043c7eb5f994764a30c4094ea07bba0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b043c7eb5f994764a30c4094ea07bba0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Fighting In The War Room: A Movies And Pop Culture Podcast : 284 – Catching-Up, Adding a Critic’s Branch to the Academy, 1917 Reviewed</title><description>&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
	This week, all four hosts are back in the war room! After a lengthy first segment catching up with the stuff we watched over the break, David and Katey square off over if there should be a Critic&amp;#39;s Branch to the Academy of Motion Picture Sciences before all four hosts dive into Best Picture hopeful 1917.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
	Take a listen, embed and/or download below; for more from all of us on Twitter: follow the show (&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/FITWR" style="line-height: 1.5em;" target="_blank"&gt;@FITWR&lt;/a&gt;), Katey (&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/kateyrich"&gt;@kateyrich&lt;/a&gt;), Da7e (&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/da7e" target="_blank"&gt;@da7e&lt;/a&gt;)&amp;nbsp; Patches (&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/misterpatches" style="line-height: 1.5em;" target="_blank"&gt;@misterpatches&lt;/a&gt;),&amp;nbsp;and &amp;nbsp;David (&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/davidehrlich" target="_blank"&gt;@davidehrlich&lt;/a&gt;) .&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
	Please s&lt;a href="http://fightinginthewarroom.com/subscribefollow/" target="_blank"&gt;ubscribe on iTunes and KICK US A REVIEW&lt;/a&gt; if you like what you hear! &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
	FORMAT&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
	00:00 &amp;#8211; Lightning Round: P.Diddy Songs&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
	02:19&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8211; Intro &amp;#8211; Welcome to Episode 284! Reviews!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
	13:19&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8211; Tidbit &amp;#8211; &amp;quot;What we watched on our Christmas vacations that wasn&amp;#39;t 1917&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
	38:32&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8211; Mini-Segment &amp;#8211; Should The Academy Add A Critic&amp;#39;s Branch?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
	47:09&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8211; Segment 3 &amp;#8211; 1917 Review&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
	01:13:43&amp;nbsp; &amp;#8211; Outro&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;</description><author>dave.m.gonzales@gmail.com (Fighting In The War Room: A Movies And Pop Culture Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">29a6297f33824367ae3e3a20c782049f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/29a6297f33824367ae3e3a20c782049f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 19:32:18 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Magnus Archives : ANNOUNCEMENT - RQ Streams!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It's time for a new video project - RQ Streams - with Mike LeBeau (Head of Video; Tim Stoker) and Anil Godigamuwe (Community Manager) as your guides &amp;amp; fellow explorers through the worlds of gaming! And thank you so much to everyone for your support to make things like this possible!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join us weekly on &lt;strong&gt;Saturdays, at 3pm GMT - starting 25th January 2020 - at www.twitch.tv/rusty_quill&lt;/strong&gt; !&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Music&lt;/strong&gt;: "The Messenger" by Silent Partner via the Youtube Audio Library&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join our community:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WEBSITE: &lt;a href="http://rustyquill.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;rustyquill.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FACEBOOK: &lt;a href="https://facebook.com/therustyquill" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;facebook.com/therustyquill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TWITTER: @therustyquill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;REDDIT: &lt;a href="https://reddit.com/r/RustyQuill" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;reddit.com/r/RustyQuill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DISCORD: &lt;a href="https://discord.gg/KckTv8y" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;https://discord.gg/KckTv8y&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMAIL: &lt;a href="mailto:mail@rustyquill.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;mail@rustyquill.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>alexander.j.newall@gmail.com (The Magnus Archives)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e4e11fa011714500a3d598fb57482002</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e4e11fa011714500a3d598fb57482002/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 14:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Artist Next Level with Sergio Gomez : 7 Things You Need to Sell More Art in 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, I share important sales strategies tested in 2019 as well as important shifts for 2020 that you need to keep in mind if you are planning to make bigger and better sales this year. these strategies will help you look ahead as you realize what things you may need to prepare for.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>yes@takethenextlevel.com (The Artist Next Level with Sergio Gomez)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fd4918bd0ad64bb4b8150981ea1ff285</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fd4918bd0ad64bb4b8150981ea1ff285/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 13:04:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Illustration Department Podcast : Kelly Delaney</title><description>&lt;p class=""&gt;Vice President of Learning Experience Design at McGraw-Hill Education, Kelly Delaney, talks to Giuseppe Castellano about her role within an educational publisher; why she doesn’t love the word, “textbook”; and why McGraw-Hill—who published Paul Galdone, Robert Barry, and a teenage Maurice Sendak—isn’t part of “The Big 6”. . . &lt;em&gt;yet&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>giuseppe@illustrationdept.com (The Illustration Department Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">edcb534aead14422bd905c30326df51e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/edcb534aead14422bd905c30326df51e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 07:50:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Golden Hour : Ep. 44: Greg Farnum (Commercial Cinematographer &amp; YouTube Host)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Recording live from CES 2020 in Las Vegas, Dave sits down with Greg Farnum- the host and face of LensProTogo and Lens Rentals. This YouTube channel covers all things photography and video related, from camera and lens tests to tutorials and how-to's. Greg shares his journey post-film school and offers advice on how to succeed as a creator in both the freelance and YouTube spaces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>support@polarprofilters.com (Golden Hour)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2109fe95d8b74f0ea9442a5268961884</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2109fe95d8b74f0ea9442a5268961884/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Creative Pep Talk : 260 - Why You Should Quit Worrying About Being a Jack of All Trades with Temi Coker</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Temi Coker&lt;br /&gt;https://www.temicoker.co/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/temi.coker"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/temi.coker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/cokerstudio/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/cokerstudio/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Temi’s Skillshare Class -&lt;strong&gt;Digital Poster Design: Combining Images &amp; Type for Powerful Visuals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.skillshare.com/classes/Digital-Poster-Design-Combining-Images-Type-for-Powerful-Visuals/2122421041"&gt;https://www.skillshare.com/classes/Digital-Poster-Design-Combining-Images-Type-for-Powerful-Visuals/2122421041&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;.....................................&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPONSORS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SKILLSHARE X CREATIVE PEP TALK&lt;br /&gt;Our first ever online video course is out now on SKILLSHARE!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you looking for your next big break? Whether you’ve NEVER had a big break in your creative career OR you’re a veteran creative who needs a new big break to reinvent yourself: this class is for you!!! Go to &lt;a href="https://skl.sh/creativepeptalk"&gt;https://skl.sh/creativepeptalk&lt;/a&gt; to get started!!!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freshbooks&lt;br /&gt;Freshbooks is accounting software specifically designed for small businesses. They make invoicing, expenses, payments, accounting, estimates, proposals extremely easy. Do yourself a favor, streamline the admin side of your creative business today and go to Freshbooks.com/creativepep to get a 30 day free trial and don’t forget to enter Creative Pep Talk in the “how did you hear about us section”&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>andy@andy-j-miller.com (Creative Pep Talk)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c1c84784d30a4565b096b5742521c498</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c1c84784d30a4565b096b5742521c498/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 03:42:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bad Batch : Introducing American Jihadi</title><description>&lt;p&gt;American Jihadi is the incredible story of a secret friendship between journalist Christof Putzel and Omar Hammami, the American-born Christian who became one of the FBI’s most wanted Islamic extremists. Follow the evolution of their risky relationship, dodging government surveillance to confide in one other—until it all came to an abrupt end. American Jihadi is hosted and Executive Produced by Christof Putzel in partnership with Endeavor Audio. Executive Produced by Adam Levine, Josh Gummersall, and Adam Harrison at 222 Productions. Subscribe now:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://bit.ly/americanjihadi_bb" target="_blank"&gt;bit.ly/americanjihadi_bb&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>iwonder@wondery.com (Bad Batch)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2536e5d4ff584c9a99752d8a3b929671</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2536e5d4ff584c9a99752d8a3b929671/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Strange Fruit : The Magical Queer Love Interest Of Color In Fiction</title><description>This week on the show: Ashia Monet on queer love Interests of color and the white gaze (https://medium.com/@ashiamonetb/queer-love-interests-of-color-and-the-white-gaze-8928b7b5e6ad), and Sydney Balloue on what the "realness" ballroom category means now that passing isn't the goal for most LGBTQ people (https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/22/opinion/ball-culture.html).</description><author>support@louisvillepublicmedia.org (Strange Fruit)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">542023eca89f4649a883c8cba9bf13b3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/542023eca89f4649a883c8cba9bf13b3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Adulting Like A Mother Father : Evanna Lynch (Harry Potter films, Kinder Beauty) joins the show to talk on-set romances, co-founding Kinder Beauty, and the importance of self care.</title><description>Accomplished actor, activist entrepreneur Evanna Lynch plays a candid round of 30 in 30 with our hosts, exposing some on-set flirtations and explaining her journey with self care and confidence both personally and professionally.</description><author>info@podcastone.com (Adulting Like A Mother Father)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">be86cdab345647b5906f02c302705ce1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/be86cdab345647b5906f02c302705ce1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Boomtown : A Thin Line | Chapter 6</title><description>&lt;p&gt;During booms, the Permian Basin sees a rise in prostitution charges. But misperceptions and stereotypes about sex work have led to policies that may actually harm the women involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SimpliSafe: &lt;/strong&gt;Get free shipping plus a 60-day money-back guarantee at &lt;a href="SimpliSafe.com/boomtown"&gt;SimpliSafe.com/boomtown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@imperativeentertainment.com (Boomtown)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a68920e9854647999ad1f92c0dec60fd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a68920e9854647999ad1f92c0dec60fd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:20:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Sleepwalkers : AI &amp; Us</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this special episode, Oz and Karah examine our evolving relationship with the technology we create. Karah meets Jason Cohen, CEO of Analytical Flavor Systems, to see if his team can hack her taste preferences, and use AI to create a new flavor of beverage that she will love. Oz and Karah also look ahead to Season 2, previewing stories they are excited to report, including algorithms that promise to optimize end-of-life conversations. And they share highlights from conversations with guests from Season 1 who shaped their thinking about AI: Yuval Noah Harari, Siddhartha Mukherjee, and Regina Barzilay of MIT.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Sleepwalkers)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9c192305a6b34b7781b3344287b3d2d0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9c192305a6b34b7781b3344287b3d2d0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Beginner Photography Podcast : BPP 182: Martin Moore - Following Your Passion and Landing Your Dream Job</title><description>&lt;p class="" data-pm-slice="1 1 []"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="" data-pm-slice="1 1 []"&gt;Martin Moore is a commercial product photographer for KOSS Headphones from Milwaukee Wisconsin who after 20 years as a mechanic left his job to become a full-time staff photographer. Today we’re going to chat about leaving your job and following your passion.&lt;/p&gt;   In This Episode You'll Learn: &lt;ul data-rte-list="default"&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;The unconventional start Martin got in photography&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;What it was about photography that got Martin so excited while working as a mechanic&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;Where Martin learned photography&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;How Martin booked and shot his first wedding&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;What about the technical side of photography is most challenging&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;How a commercial product photographer gets ready for a shoot&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;What its like working and shooting for a large company&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;How much gear Martin uses and his most used piece of equipment during a shoot&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;What Matin heard being taught as gospel to beginners but in practice is’’t as important&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; Premium Members Also Learn: &lt;ul data-rte-list="default"&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;What you need to be valuable in today’s workforce as a photographer&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;The pros and cons of being a staff photographer vs a freelance photographer&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;How to get the attention of a company you want to work for&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;Why building a personal brand is so important even when working as an employee&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; Resources: &lt;ul data-rte-list="default"&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.martinmoorephotography.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Martin Moore Photography&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/martinmoorejr" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Martin Moore on Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/martinmoorejr" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Martin Moore on Youtube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.twitter.com/martinmoorejr" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Martin Moore on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>beginnerphotographypodcast@gmail.com (The Beginner Photography Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1a76e771f69e45b997de68e014a36282</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1a76e771f69e45b997de68e014a36282/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Art Juice: A podcast for artists, creatives and art lovers : What to Do When You feel Like Giving Up [51]</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At one time or another, most of us have considered giving up making our art. In this episode, we share our own experiences and discuss why this feeling arises. Perhaps we have ambitions that exceed our current skill level and this leads to disappointment with the results. Sometimes, we are not creating what we really want to create, leading to boredom and burn-out. It is also common for people to become discouraged when they lack a support system and even when they have a spouse or partner who actively discourages their art-making. The conversation leads us to conclude that all these issues can be addressed - we can find support elsewhere, we can improve our skills through education and practice, and we can start to make art that we really love instead of just doing the same old thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week we also tackle the topic of returning after a break and offer our different perspectives on how to get back into your work after the holidays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mentioned&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Find out about Alice's Connected Artist Club and join the interest list here:&lt;a href="https://alicesheridan.com/artists/"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;https://alicesheridan.com/artists/&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link to louise’s Flickr album of self portraits &lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/63799511@N05/albums/72157663186899771"&gt;&lt;u&gt;https://www.flickr.com/photos/63799511@N05/albums/72157663186899771&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Link to studio tidy post &lt;a href="https://alicesheridan.com/how-to-kon-mari-your-studio/"&gt;How to Kon Mari Your Studio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See Alice's sketchbook progress page &lt;a href="https://alicesheridan.com/artjuice51"&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nourkarim-eddin.co.uk"&gt;Nour the artist/Ocado delivery driver!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sign up for our newsletters at:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.alicesheridan.com/podcast"&gt;www.alicesheridan.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.louisefletcherart.com/for-artists/podcast/"&gt;www.louisefletcherart.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submit a question at &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/artjuicepodcast"&gt;bit.ly/artjuicepodcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buy us a coffee at: &lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/artjuice"&gt;https://ko-fi.com/artjuice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow us on Instagram:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow Alice on Instagram &lt;a href="http://www.instagram.com@alicesheridanstudio/"&gt;@alicesheridanstudio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;or Louise &lt;a href="http://www.instagram.com/louisefletcher_art"&gt;@louisefletcher_art&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Credits&lt;br&gt;
"Monkeys Spinning Monkeys" Kevin MacLeod (incompetech.com) Licensed under Creative Commons: By Attribution 3.0 License&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts23+8a082e8@anchor.fm (Art Juice: A podcast for artists, creatives and art lovers)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e1f2cbba7b8b48d0ad58596944c782c7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e1f2cbba7b8b48d0ad58596944c782c7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>888-Barbara : 09: Divorce Your Husband Tomorrow</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We all have that friend who’s divorcing her husband “tomorrow,” but my first caller this week really is! With finances to worry about, how will her divorce play out? And later, I speak with a mom who’s going through the same heartbreak I've faced: the empty nest. Together, we come up with a plan to fill the void. Listen in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Got a problem? Call me at 888-Barbara. Nothing’s off limits, so what are you waiting for?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>lila@barbaracorcoran.com (888-Barbara)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">04d98a5f87ac4963856a0942defa4ace</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/04d98a5f87ac4963856a0942defa4ace/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Server Life Podcast : Episode 6 - Why do YOU serve?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Pres and Connor share some of your responses as to why you currently serve. Some of the reasons range from simply getting money to overcoming anxiety.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts33+11e2cd0c@anchor.fm (The Server Life Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">714682065b5c43f6bbc029e67218bed0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/714682065b5c43f6bbc029e67218bed0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 12:52:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hashtag Authentic - for small businesses, bloggers and online creatives : Life Lessons for Freelancers, with Anna Codrea-Rado</title><description>&lt;h2&gt;Things we talk about in this episode:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;What journalists and content creators can learn from one another&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The power of engagement of numbers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The content creator/journalist/freelancer as a brand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Managing your public versus private self&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The positives of being more 'reachable' in today's media/content realm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anna's newsletter, how she developed and grew it, and how it now pays her revenue&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The freelance mindset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Why having a key message and consistency is essential for freelancers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Why you haven't missed the boat if you want to set out as a content creator&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anna's Fair Pay for Freelancers campaign&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Links mentioned in this episode:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://theprofessionalfreelancer.substack.com/"&gt;The Professional Freelancer&lt;/a&gt; - Anna's newsletter&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anna's Twitter - &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/annacod"&gt;@annacod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anna's Instagram - &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/annacod/"&gt;@annacod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anna's &lt;a href="https://www.annacodrearado.com/about"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pressgazette.co.uk/freelance-journalists-demand-end-to-payment-on-publication-and-respect-for-late-fees-in-open-letter-to-publishers/"&gt;#FairPayForFreelancers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anna's podcast - &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/is-this-working/id1473508626"&gt;Is This Working?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://dollyalderton.com/about/"&gt;Dolly Alderton&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://tiffanyphilippou.com/"&gt;Tiffany Philippou&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://substack.com/about?utm_source=menu"&gt;Substack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/sianysianysiany?lang=en"&gt;Sian Meades-Williams&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.katmolesworth.com/"&gt;Kat Molesworth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Letters From a Hopeful Creative &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/letters-from-a-hopeful-creative/id1408102079"&gt;podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/me_and_orla/" target="_blank"&gt;My Instagram&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/meandorla" target="_blank"&gt; Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://meandorla.co.uk/the-insta-retreat-2-0/" target="_blank"&gt;My Insta Retreat class,&lt;/a&gt; enrolling soon!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://me-orla.ck.page/ccde566713"&gt;Sign up to join my new free community, The Flock&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>admin@meandorla.co.uk (Hashtag Authentic - for small businesses, bloggers and online creatives)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cdf49ed5739c4b65b05ef79de1a7f015</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cdf49ed5739c4b65b05ef79de1a7f015/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 12:37:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Meditative Story : Through friendship, a better version of myself, by Reid Hoffman</title><description>&lt;p&gt;How do you find joy in your life? For entrepreneur, venture capitalist, and author Reid Hoffman, it’s through the act of genuine, honest, and intimate conversations with friends. Once a self-described misfit, in college, Reid finds his place. He connects with people who share not necessarily his interests but his curiosity, and his dedication to asking big questions. It is in asking the big questions, in discussing the answers, that Reid learns and grows – and begins to discover the meaning of his life. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@waitwhat.com (Meditative Story)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0b6476d5d36d4fa6ac2e48abe3c59ac9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0b6476d5d36d4fa6ac2e48abe3c59ac9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 12:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Artful Painter : Anne Blair Brown - Inspired by Light (19)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Anne Blair Brown describes herself as a contemporary impressionist. She is drawn to impressionism because it is an interpretation of a moment in time. Light is the subject of her paintings. The light that imbues her paintings radiates a feeling of warmth. Light glows in an open doorway, shadows accentuate warm afternoon sunlight, and, dapples of light dance upon a picnic table in the summer shade of an old oak tree. Anne's play of light is found in her rural and urban landscapes, her figurative work, and her intimate interior spaces. As you peer into Anne’s paintings, you begin to sense it as if it were your own memory. Her broken brushstrokes begin a story that only you as the viewer can complete. The sense of place and memory Anne suggests in her beautiful paintings becomes your story.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this edition of the &lt;em&gt;Artful Painter&lt;/em&gt;, Anne freely shares her thoughts on her process of creating light-filled, impressionistic paintings. She talks about her joy of teaching and how we as students can most benefit from artist workshops and training. Anne discusses, too, her experiences with showing her work in galleries.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Get out your pen and notebook and prepare to take notes! Other artists have told me that I need to talk to Anne Blair Brown. I’m glad I took their advice! I’m happy to share this conversation with artist Anne Blair Brown with you in this episode.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Mentioned in this episode:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Anne Blair Brown's website: &lt;a href= "http://anneblairbrown.com/"&gt;http://anneblairbrown.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A Painter's Journey: &lt;a href= "http://apaintersjourney.com/"&gt;http://apaintersjourney.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Trey Finney: &lt;a href= "http://treyfinney.com"&gt;http://treyfinney.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dawn Whitelaw: &lt;a href= "http://www.dawnwhitelaw.com"&gt;http://www.dawnwhitelaw.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;David Boyd, Jr.: &lt;a href= "https://davidboydjr.com"&gt;https://davidboydjr.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Charles Movalli: &lt;a href= "https://charlesmovalli.org/home"&gt;https://charlesmovalli.org/home&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Kim English: &lt;a href= "http://anglinsmith.com/artists/kim-english/"&gt;http://anglinsmith.com/artists/kim-english/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Colin Page: &lt;a href= "https://www.colinpagepaintings.com"&gt;https://www.colinpagepaintings.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;About the Artful Painter:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Send me an email: &lt;a href= "https://carlolson.tv/contact"&gt;https://carlolson.tv/contact&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe to my YouTube channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCIo1YmQXnMm21b-Slkr69Tg &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;My Artful Painter Sketchbooks: &lt;a href= "https://carlolson.tv/artful-painter-sketchbooks"&gt;https://carlolson.tv/artful-painter-sketchbooks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Carl Olson on Instagram: &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/artful.creative/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/artful.creative/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As an Amazon Associate, I earn from qualifying purchases.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>carl@theartfulpainter.com (Artful Painter)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4050afd8354042d98891df7ccff06f95</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4050afd8354042d98891df7ccff06f95/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 11:38:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Industry Seating : Ep 3: STL to Anaheim 2</title><description>STL was another burner, we get into it here and look on to Anaheim 2.</description><author>swizcore@me.com (Industry Seating)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">971d4c40a75942a3862f9a10b77d1779</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/971d4c40a75942a3862f9a10b77d1779/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 10:08:38 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Beyond the Studio - A Podcast for Artists : BTS x AWC - Amy Whitaker talks Using Business as a Tool, Building Equity in the Arts, and Re-Inventing the Art Market</title><description>Hear more from Amy on finding common language between art and business, what artists need to know about economics, how new technologies like blockchain could be used to help artists retain equity in their work, and embracing doubt as a process of invention. &lt;p class=""&gt;Links to resources mentioned throughout the episode: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://artworldconference.com/"&gt;Art World Conference&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://cciarts.org/"&gt;CCI Arts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sunlighttax.com/"&gt;Money Bootcamp 2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.amazon.com/Art-Thinking-Creative-Schedules-Budgets/dp/0062358278"&gt; “Art Thinking: How to Carve Out Creative Space in a World of Schedules, Budgets, and Bosses” by Amy Whitaker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/slade/"&gt;Slade School of Fine Art&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yale.edu/"&gt;Yale University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.amazon.com/Making-Being-Embodiment-Collaboration-Circulation/dp/1945711078"&gt; “Making and Being: Embodiment, Collaboration, and Circulation in the Visual Arts” by Caroline Woolard and Susan Jahoda&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href= "https://artivate.org/artivate/article/view/94"&gt;“Art and Blockchain” by Amy Whitaker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.amazon.com/Work-Art-Creative-Careers-Economic/dp/1503603822"&gt; “The Work of Art: Value in Creative Careers (Culture and Economic Life)” by Alison Gerber&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.amazon.com/Winners-Take-All-Charade-Changing/dp/0451493249"&gt; “Winners Take All: The Elite Charade of Changing the World” by Anand Giridharadas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/artnome?lang=en"&gt;Jason Bailey @artnome&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="http://monegraph.com/"&gt;Monegraph&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.artory.com/"&gt;Artory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://verisart.com/"&gt;Verisart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href= "https://blog.maecenas.co/blockchain-art-auction-andy-warhol/"&gt;Maecenas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://withotis.com/"&gt;With Otis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://opensea.io/"&gt;OpenSea&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href= "https://hyperallergic.com/312390/why-teach-business-to-artists/"&gt;“Why Teach Business to Artists?” by Amy Whitaker in Hyperallergic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2FqVY6WR8nM"&gt;“A new way to pay artists” TEDx talk by Amy Whitaker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class=""&gt;Follow more of Amy’s work on Twitter at &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/theamywhit?lang=en"&gt;@theamywhit&lt;/a&gt;, and keep an eye out for her upcoming book “Economics of Visual Art” (2020)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.beyondthe.studio/"&gt;www.beyondthe.studio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Intro and Ad Music by: &lt;a href= "http://www.suahnmusic.com/"&gt;Suahn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Album Artwork by: &lt;a href= "http://davidjamescolson.com/"&gt;David Colson&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>beyondthestudiopodcast@gmail.com (Beyond the Studio - A Podcast for Artists)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">55fb337ddbb44f82a7b314b917b5e170</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/55fb337ddbb44f82a7b314b917b5e170/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 09:45:45 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Art Producer : 040: Milagros DeLaRosa, Senior Producer, Leo Burnett</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Milagros has been in the industry for 30 years and she comes on the show to share her advice on the importance of relationships, what we should see on your website, and team synergy, as well as her best tips on the estimating process.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[:32] Heather introduces Milagros and asks her to share the story of how she made her way into the advertising industry from a political major as well as the people that shaped her path and propelled her forward.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[4:04] Heather shares her own start as an account person when everything was so brand new and Milagros touches on the industry’s hay day — but come to terms with it ’cause it’s gone!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[9:45] Getting Milagros’ attention goes primarily through email, but she does enjoy the moments at Leo Burnett when the reps come in and share the recent work they have on their roster. She shares her e-classification system!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[12:25] Milagros touches on how her team finds photographers for specific projects, it usually starts with six to seven photographers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[13:40] Websites are so very important and everybody has more than enough things to do in a day so ease of navigation is paramount! Milagros also enjoys seeing the more personal side of a photographer — showcase some of your personal work too! She also touches on the importance of reps.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[18:08] The creative teams also play a role in the types of photographers they look for; personalities have to agree! So pay attention to the conversations you have with the prospective teams, they are more important than you know.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[20:45] Milagros will still consider a photographer who has no motion on their site, and in any case, it sometimes needs to be two separate people. She speaks to how much education she still has to impart to clients surrounding motion.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[23:50] Leo Burnet’s firm bid structure provides a lot of positive aspects, Milagros touches on the flexibility that is still required once you arrive on set.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[27:25] Heather asks Milagros to break down the estimating process on her side — from initial reviews to cost consulting to client meetings — and though there may sometimes be a front-runner, Milagros’ team always presents three candidates they would be happy working with.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[30:30] Milagros’ tips for the estimating process are simple but important: be clear, take notes, and speak up if something seems off to you.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[31:35] Treatments are more important for projects that include motion and about 60% of the projects she bids require them, but when they are in play, it’s critical to give it all you’ve got and make a mark for yourself.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[37:20] The worst part of Milagros’ job is letting people know they didn’t get the job. Heather and her guest discuss the importance of having that conversation after the fact, all the while keeping in mind that everyone is just so crazy busy!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[41:59] Who am I bidding against is a question best answered after the fact.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[45:03] Would you have guessed that Milagros is shy, focused, and kind — maybe the last two!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[47:50] If she wasn’t an art producer, Milagros would be a location photographer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;[48:50] Heather thanks Milagros for coming on the podcast!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thanks for listening.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In an industry where the rules are always changing, it’s helpful to hear from those on the front line. Heather Elder is the visionary behind &lt;a href= "https://notesfromarepsjournal.com/"&gt;NotesFromARep’sJournal.com&lt;/a&gt;; visit her &lt;a href= "https://www.heatherelder.com/"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; for industry updates, stunning photography and video, and the artists behind the work.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Mentioned in this episode&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://leoburnett.com/"&gt;Leo Burnett&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;More about your host&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Heather Elder’s &lt;a href= "https://www.heatherelder.com/CONNECT-&amp;-RESOURCES/thumbs"&gt; Bio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Heather Elder’s &lt;a href= "https://notesfromarepsjournal.com/"&gt;Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Heather Elder on &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/heatherelderrepresents/?hl=en"&gt; Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Heather Elder on &lt;a href= "https://mobile.twitter.com/heathereldersf?lang=en"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Heather Elder on &lt;a href= "https://ca.linkedin.com/company/heather-elder-represents"&gt; LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Heather Elder on &lt;a href= "https://m.facebook.com/HeatherElderRepresents"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;More about today’s guest&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Milagros DeLaRosa on &lt;a href= "https://www.linkedin.com/in/milagros-delarosa-35352512/"&gt; LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>office@heatherelder.com (Dear Art Producer)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b8580965f811483d90959e9f8856febb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b8580965f811483d90959e9f8856febb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 06:44:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Vision Slightly Blurred : In (Partial) Defense of Flickr</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On December 19, 2019, Flickr (and Smugmug) CEO Don MacAskill &lt;a href="https://blog.flickr.net/en/2019/12/19/the-worlds-most-beloved-money-losing-business-needs-your-help/"&gt;posted a letter&lt;/a&gt; entitled “The world’s most-beloved, money-losing business needs your help.” MacAskill described how Smugmug saved Flickr from an imminent demise at the hands of Verizon, and how the company needed the photo community to step up to staunch the money-losing operation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Was the plea an honest and transparent message, or an admission that MacAskill made a critical mistake in acquiring the company. Online reaction was swift, but not necessarily fair. In this episode of Vision Slightly Blurred, PhotoShelter co-founder Allen Murabayashi shares his thoughts from his experience as an entrepreneur within the photo space, and his hopes for Flickr moving forward.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>caitlyn@photoshelter.com (Vision Slightly Blurred)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c1564ddf1bc44404b38f40fc943e592a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c1564ddf1bc44404b38f40fc943e592a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dish Food Travel Show : 48 Piri Piri Chicken</title><description>IN THIS EPISODE:

&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The story of piri piri chicken, what is piri piri sauce and where did it come from?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plus, a short history of Nandos, the international piri piri chicken chain restaurant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partial Transcript at &lt;a href='https://foodfuntravel.com/history-of-piri-piri-chicken/'&gt;https://foodfuntravel.com/history-of-piri-piri-chicken/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The history of piri piri chicken, one of the world's most popular spicy grilled chicken dishes. From its origins, to modern chain restaurant success as part of the Nando's restaurant chain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who invented the original piri piri sauce? And how did that become piri piri chicken and part of an international craze. Plus, the best piri piri chicken is certainly not at Nandos... We explore the local chicken scene in a European country where it has almost become a national dish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>megsy@foodfuntravel.com (The Dish Food Travel Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bdac9d32026142b3821d3ad07c3bd926</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bdac9d32026142b3821d3ad07c3bd926/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 02:13:01 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Not Guilty : Listen First! SECRET SOCIETIES, A Parcast Original Series!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;They’ve been around for thousands of years…orchestrating some of history’s most controversial events. And if not for their radical actions, you may never have even known they existed. Every Thursday, take a journey through hidden passageways and become a member of Parcast’s diabolical series, &lt;em&gt;SECRET SOCIETIES. &lt;/em&gt;Each society is explored in 2 episodes—exposing the people and context responsible for its founding, and analyzing the psychology behind their beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enjoy this exclusive clip from the first episode on Yale’s mysterious “Skull and Bones” fraternity. To finish this episode, subscribe to &lt;em&gt;SECRET SOCIETIES&lt;/em&gt; free on Spotify, or wherever you listen to podcasts!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>support@parcast.com (Not Guilty)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8329384cb8734a1987340f336382dfae</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8329384cb8734a1987340f336382dfae/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Kick in The Creative's Podcast : Ep 52 The Power of Continuous Practice for Your Art</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today we are talking about the power of continuous practice… And I think that most of the people who joined KITC at the start and have been joining in with the challenges ever since will be able to see how much they have improved by adopting a creative habit. So if you haven’t joined us yet and you want to improve your skills, then now is a good time to start. Our Facebook Group is a great place to share your work, get encouraged by other artists and hold yourself accountable.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>howdy@kickinthecreatives.com (Kick in The Creative's Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">14a4dbeda6ea4130a37d10a11099280c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/14a4dbeda6ea4130a37d10a11099280c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 23:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Toasted Sister Podcast : E60: Bruce Savage — Spirit Lake Native Farms</title><description>In this episode, I visit Spirit Lake Native Farms in Minnesota and one of its owners, Bruce Savage (Fond du Lac Band of Ojibwe), for a tour through the wild rice processing plant. Included in this episode is a short ASMR session that’ll make you tingle.  

Tour photos are at ToastedSisterPodcast.com

Mentioned: 
Bruce’s email address spiritlakesugar@yahoo.com 
Natives on a Budget Podcast: http://nativesonabudget.com/</description><author>andimurphy13@gmail.com (Toasted Sister Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ddc29f0d329b43a28ba6f095c39bcf13</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ddc29f0d329b43a28ba6f095c39bcf13/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 22:14:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Learn to Paint Podcast : Episode 7: Joan Fullerton</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, Fullerton discusses how she learned to distinguish the voice inside of her, how she teaches materials in her workshops&amp;nbsp; and why learning to critique your own work- the right way- is so important as a painter. Plus a whole lot more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>learntopaintpodcast@gmail.com (Learn to Paint Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f35d27c1191e4c00af35f11007b2cc15</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f35d27c1191e4c00af35f11007b2cc15/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 18:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Kermode on Film : #66: MK3D Live! with Dexter Fletcher and Maxine Peake</title><description>&lt;p&gt;MK3D Live! Mark talks to Dexter Fletcher on his hit musical biopic of Elton John - Rocketman and to actress Maxine Peake on her acting career and the film that changed her life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Want to come to a recording of a Mark Kermode Live in 3D show at the BFI Southbank in London?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can book tickets to next month’s MK3D here:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://whatson.bfi.org.uk/Online/default.asp?doWork::WScontent::loadArticle=Load&amp;amp;BOparam::WScontent::loadArticle::article_id=9FD162DC-3C10-43AB-ADCC-31364C1822AE&amp;amp;BOparam::WScontent::loadArticle::context_id=9F31E26A-0485-48B9-B9CB-4BA957BE7942&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it says it's sold out - don’t despair, there are often returns so check again nearer the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Mark @KermodeMovie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;www.markkermode.co.uk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kermode On Film is produced by HLA Agency and Hidden Flack&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Producers Hedda Archbold, Nick Freand Jones and Tom Whalley&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>nickfreand@mac.com (Kermode on Film)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a752cc0fa17c4d2b92b306afa6288fb9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a752cc0fa17c4d2b92b306afa6288fb9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 16:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Eating Matters : Episode 153: Kid Food</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Author Bettina Elias Siegel joins host Jenna Liut to talk about her first book, "Kid Food: The Challenge of Feeding Children," which was recently published this past November.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Eating Matters&lt;/i&gt; is powered by &lt;a href="https://simplecast.com/"&gt;Simplecast&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@HeritageRadioNetwork.org (Eating Matters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cfa4e5d753d141d79d73916ec687c47b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cfa4e5d753d141d79d73916ec687c47b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>u+1f60c : the doors that exist (feat. julia furlan)</title><description>&lt;p class=""&gt;“if you have it, you just waltz effortlessly in the rooms you want to be in”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;~ thanks to &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/juliastmi?lang=en" target=""&gt;julia furlan&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://alexlaughs.com/"&gt;alex laughlin&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://elenafernandezcollins.com/"&gt;elena fernandez collins&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/sandhyadirks"&gt;sandhya dirks&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.thisisparker.com/"&gt;b.a. parker&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://mollywoodstock.com/about"&gt;molly woodstock&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="http://www.arianamartinezstudio.com/"&gt;ariana martinez&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@jamestgreen.com (u+1f60c)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ebf5b3f56e2946ee9406286f1d0c4a60</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ebf5b3f56e2946ee9406286f1d0c4a60/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 07:55:48 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>ASMP Experts &amp; Masters : Ep 26: Robert Seale</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Robert Seale is a commercial photographer and long-time ASMP member based out of Houston. Throughout his career, he has been able to stay versatile and prolific, while providing his services to advertising agencies, corporate reports, and a host of editorial publications. Robert has made a name for himself with his exceptional technical ability, graphic eye, lighting skills, and his execution speed as a visual problem solver. From his start as a college newspaper photographer, Robert has spent years establishing himself as one of the premier names in the commercial photography industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this episode, Tom Kennedy, ASMP’s Executive Director, and Robert Seale talk about…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Getting into photography and influences that Robert had&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Transitioning from newspaper to sports magazines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Preparation for photographing an athlete without the athlete&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deciding to go out on his own as a commercial photographer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Looking into the creative process that goes into getting a great shot&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Educating clients about the photography that they are looking for&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How Robert finds people that he really likes to work with&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advising young photographers on which skills to hone in on&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The evolution from film to digital and how it has changed photography&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Importance of Instagram for displaying your portfolio to the new world&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Changes going on now that are creating more avenues for photography services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The two factors that go into charging appropriately&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Things to know if entering the photography industry right now&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Staying critical and re-evaluating your process as time goes on&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Links to resources:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robert Seale's website: &lt;a href="https://www.robertseale.com/"&gt;https://www.robertseale.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robert Seale's Instagram: &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/robertsealephoto/?hl=en"&gt;@robertsealephoto&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Send us your comments and suggestions: &lt;a href="mailto:communications@ASMP.org"&gt;communications@ASMP.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To donate to the ASMP archives go to:&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href="https://www.asmp.org/asmp-foundation/"&gt;https://www.asmp.org/asmp-foundation/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="https://www.asmp.org/asmp-foundation-donations/"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tierney@asmp.org (ASMP Experts &amp; Masters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0042e6d12b23410c83a2916d5da2a1ab</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0042e6d12b23410c83a2916d5da2a1ab/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>LA PLATICA : YOU ARE WHO YOU HANG OUT WITH</title><description>&lt;p&gt;MI GENTE! WE FINALLY HAVE NEW MERCH!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;LAPLATICAPODCAST.COM&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;cant wait to see it on you guys im so excited! &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;also thank you to my special guest @be.lechendary for coming and speaking nothing but facts!!!!! love you bro!! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;follow me on insta! &amp;nbsp;@ayyysebas&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts33+1187cd58@anchor.fm (LA PLATICA)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">34cbc10898514741ac9f46c17df1e6dc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/34cbc10898514741ac9f46c17df1e6dc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 10:15:45 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>For All Mankind - A Super Friends Podcast : For All Mankind #2</title><description>FOR ALL MANKIND #2 - SUPER FRIENDS #2

Rob and returning guest Shawn Myers review "Trapped by the Super-Foes!" by E. Nelson Bridwell and Ric Estrada, SUPER FRIENDS #2!

&lt;a href="http://fireandwaterpodcast.com/podcast/FAM2gallery" target="_blank"&gt;Check out images from this comic by clicking here!&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;E-MAIL: &lt;a href="mailto:firewaterpodcast@comcast.net" target="_blank"&gt;firewaterpodcast@comcast.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Follow FOR ALL MANKIND on Twitter: &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/ForAllMankindSF" target="_blank"&gt;@ForAllMankindSF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Subscribe to FOR ALL MANKIND on Apple Podcasts: &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/for-all-mankind-a-super-friends-podcast/id1481080710" target="_blank"&gt;https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/for-all-mankind-a-super-friends-podcast/id1481080710&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
Opening and closing themes by Hanna Barbera.

This podcast is a proud member of the FIRE AND WATER PODCAST NETWORK:
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Visit the Fire &amp;amp; Water WEBSITE: &lt;a href="http://fireandwaterpodcast.com/"&gt;http://fireandwaterpodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Follow Fire &amp;amp; Water on TWITTER – &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/FWPodcasts"&gt;https://twitter.com/FWPodcasts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Like our Fire &amp;amp; Water FACEBOOK page – &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/FWPodcastNetwork"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/FWPodcastNetwork&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Support The Fire &amp;amp; Water Podcast Network on Patreon: &lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/fwpodcasts" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.patreon.com/fwpodcasts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Use our HASHTAG online: #FWPodcasts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
Thanks for listening!</description><author>firewaterpodcast@comcast.net (For All Mankind - A Super Friends Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ce5d0d8a29e640f798c648d391934cc1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ce5d0d8a29e640f798c648d391934cc1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 09:05:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Plein Air Art Podcast : Chuck Waldman on Art Materials and More</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Listen as Chuck Waldman shares: His physical experience with certain art materials, why he shied away from them, and what's changed since then; How he went from being a family practitioner for 20 years and then left the medical field, unsure of what he would do; The art materials he uses now and his thoughts on toning canvases, as well as painting lights, darks, and mid-tones; And more!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href= "https://www.outdoorpainter.com/original-podcast-episodes/"&gt; https://www.outdoorpainter.com/original-podcast-episodes/&lt;/a&gt; to listen to all of our episodes, including interviews with Joseph Zbukvic, Anne Blair Brown, Joe Pacquet, Nancie King Mertz, Alvaro Castagnet, Albert Handell, and many more!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@streamlinepublishing.com (Plein Air Art Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">eee06687ec644454ad571c3a6fd847d9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/eee06687ec644454ad571c3a6fd847d9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 12:44:27 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind The Icing  : Gettin’ Social With It</title><description>In this episode we chat with Malek from Frosted By Malek and Ashley from Crumbs about social media and your business.</description><author>podcasts26+fb14450@anchor.fm (Behind The Icing )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">94ed501e0b4646da8c358e0c93d5bfa4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/94ed501e0b4646da8c358e0c93d5bfa4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 07:31:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Comic Book Noise : Comic Book Noise 863: A Quick Catch-up</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Host Derek Coward catches up with what has been going on since the last episode and talks briefly about the Watchmen TV show and the new Legion of Superheroes series.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img src="https://i0.wp.com/www.comicbooknoise.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/SmartSelect_20200110-093058_Instagram.jpg?resize=474%2C487" alt="" class="wp-image-8429" srcset="https://i0.wp.com/www.comicbooknoise.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/SmartSelect_20200110-093058_Instagram.jpg?resize=996%2C1024 996w, https://i0.wp.com/www.comicbooknoise.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/SmartSelect_20200110-093058_Instagram.jpg?resize=292%2C300 292w, https://i0.wp.com/www.comicbooknoise.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/SmartSelect_20200110-093058_Instagram.jpg?resize=768%2C789 768w, https://i0.wp.com/www.comicbooknoise.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/SmartSelect_20200110-093058_Instagram.jpg?w=1046 1046w" sizes="(max-width: 474px) 100vw, 474px" data-recalc-dims="1" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/ComicBookNoise/~4/EEeX7iauIDc" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>derek@comicbooknoise.com (Comic Book Noise)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8e2536b9d53c484eb0e5a5712441e49e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8e2536b9d53c484eb0e5a5712441e49e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 06:35:22 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Love of Jewelers: A Jewelry Journey Podcast : 03: Tim McCreight, Books from the Bench</title><description>&lt;p&gt;While working on his iconic volume, &lt;em&gt;The Complete Metalsmith&lt;/em&gt;, Tim McCreight imagined, “What if silver was writing this?” In 1985 he started Brynmorgen Press to provide practical, bench-tested textbooks on metalsmithing and design. Decades later his experiential approach to research led him to co-found the Toolbox Initiative, which delivers new and gently-used tools and silver to jewelers in Africa.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join Tim and Courtney as they discuss what makes a great jewelry book, the generosity of the jewelry community, and “partnering with metal.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(P.S.: You’ll also get a sneak preview of an upcoming book by Toolbox Initiative co-founder Matthieu Cheminée!)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>avantcreative@gmail.com (For the Love of Jewelers: A Jewelry Journey Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">83920c2de7f54c89b3828074c82f3647</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/83920c2de7f54c89b3828074c82f3647/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Chewing : Episode 72: Uncle Remus, Chinatown Museum, jook recipes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Louisa Chu talks to 93 year old Uncle Remus Saucy Fried Chicken founder Gus Rickette and daughter / CEO Charmaine Rickette. Monica Eng talks to 85 year old namesake of Chinese-American Museum of Chicago Raymond Lee, and great aunts about jook / congee recipes. Plus Monica dares Louisa to eat German currywurst chips, but Will She Eat It?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>chewing@chewing.xyz (Chewing)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8ed871a028474192b093cdffa1d9bd96</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8ed871a028474192b093cdffa1d9bd96/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Start With This : Outlining</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Outlining your story is like a puzzle for plot. In this episode, we talk about how mapping out what will happen before you start writing gives your story shape, and makes it much easier to write. This way, you can land a satisfying ending and give focus to your process to free your brain up for new discoveries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consume: Listen to &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/ca/podcast/the-shadows/id1420121326?mt=2" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;The Shadows&lt;/a&gt;, a six-episode podcast series by Kaitlin Prest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Create: Write a six section outline with a max word count of 60 words for each section. Give your project a beginning, middle, and end. Have the character’s growth matches the plot, and that the ending is set up by the structure. The goal is to figure out what happens within each section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join the SWT Membership community to share your work, give feedback, and connect with other artists:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.patreon.com/startwiththis" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.patreon.com/startwiththis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Help spread the word about our show by wearing our logo: &lt;a href="https://topatoco.com/collections/startwiththis" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;https://topatoco.com/collections/startwiththis&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;Follow us on &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/startwiththis/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/startthispod" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Credits: Jeffrey Cranor (host) &amp;amp; Joseph Fink (host), Julia Melfi (producer), Grant Stewart (editor), Vincent Cacchione (mixer). Rob Wilson (logo).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Theme written and performed by Joseph Fink. If you'd like your own cover of the theme song featured on this show, email us at &lt;a href="http://mailto:startwiththis@nightvalepresents.com" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;startwiththis@nightvalepresents.com&lt;/a&gt; or share it in our membership community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Produced by Night Vale Presents. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.startwiththispodcast.com/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.startwiththispodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.nightvalepresents.com/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.nightvalepresents.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>startwiththis@nightvalepresents.com (Start With This)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">93b62785cdc5476094f37598a8701146</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/93b62785cdc5476094f37598a8701146/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Southern Glazers What Am I Drinking Podcast : Southern Glazers What Am I Drinking Podcast Episode 2 Jessica to Brian</title><description>The What Am I Drinking Podcast brings you highly credentialed experts from within the beverage industry to share what they love! What makes them and their brands unique? Find out here!  Our Instagram and Facebook @SGWSAcademy  Our email- NVBevAllies@sgws.com  &lt;span style="font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size: large;"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;audio controls=""&gt;&lt;source src="https://www.crntalk.com/podcast/Glazers/2019/Southern%20Glazers%20What%20Am%20I%20Drinking%20Podcast%20Episode%202%20Jessica%20to%20Brian.mp3"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;If you cannot see the audio controls, &lt;a href="https://www.crntalk.com/podcast/Glazers/2019/Southern%20Glazers%20What%20Am%20I%20Drinking%20Podcast%20Episode%202%20Jessica%20to%20Brian.mp3"&gt;listen/download the audio file here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/audio&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><author>noreply@blogger.com (Southern Glazers What Am I Drinking Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9218e62a4de04828a5a8c3148f9e840e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9218e62a4de04828a5a8c3148f9e840e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 15:10:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Artrepreneur Creative Careers Podcast : Turning Your Creative Career Goals into Action</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Frantz Alcindor is the Director of Career and Internship Services at the Fashion Institute of Technology where he serves the career development needs of over 9,000 students.&lt;span class="Apple-converted-space"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this podcast, Frantz discusses what it takes to find work and succeed in the creative industry. Matching your skillset to job opportunities, viewing yourself as an entrepreneur, and guiding your career path through the lens of problem-solving, are just a few of the topics you’ll hear in this extremely informative podcast. &lt;span class="Apple-converted-space"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regardless of where you are in your creative career, Frantz has advice for you. &lt;span class="Apple-converted-space"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>rob@artrepreneur.com (Artrepreneur Creative Careers Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9d94ff306f7a44a78b2bad3c7ac4053e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9d94ff306f7a44a78b2bad3c7ac4053e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 12:18:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Unlocking Us with Brené Brown : Introducing: Unlocking Us</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Join researcher and #1 &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; best-selling author Brené Brown as she unpacks and explores the ideas, stories, experiences, books, films, and music that reflect the universal experiences of being human, from the bravest moments to the most brokenhearted.  Subscribe now for updates.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@cadence13.com (Unlocking Us with Brené Brown)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cc1fdde05fdd4c0bbd9a88e18eb2cbee</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cc1fdde05fdd4c0bbd9a88e18eb2cbee/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 09:26:52 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hatchling : The Influencer's Dilemma (Part 1)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This is chapter one of a new mini-series about my relationship with the internet. It begins with my very first smartphone, then follows my path to success on social media, and ends with a philosophical crisis. Join me as I investigate how technology affects artists, and work toward a healthier and more balanced life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email me your questions and responses: &lt;a href="mailto:augustbryanlamm@gmail.com"&gt;augustbryanlamm@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow Hatchling on &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/hatchlingpod/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hosted by &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/augustlamm/"&gt;August Lamm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts10+9af6244@anchor.fm (Hatchling)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6f2678efa47d4982b035eb3106c9d2d0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6f2678efa47d4982b035eb3106c9d2d0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 09:08:11 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hunt, Gather, Talk with Hank Shaw : Bobwhite Quail</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode of Hunt Gather Talk, we are delving deep into Gentleman Bob, the bobwhite quail. we are paying special attention to why this iconic game bird is disappearing from part of its habitat.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>scrbblr@hotmail.com (Hunt, Gather, Talk with Hank Shaw)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ad324bfd3e5c4f88b97970d2a03d289d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ad324bfd3e5c4f88b97970d2a03d289d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 05:25:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Savvy Painter Podcast with Antrese Wood : Defeating Overwhelm and Finding Clarity</title><description>&lt;p&gt;If you are anything like me, you find yourself fighting back the feeling of overwhelm from time to time. What do you usually do when you start to feel overwhelmed? How do you cut through the usual complexity that life brings and find clarity? As we start the New Year, I wanted to take some time to go over some helpful tools and insights that I've gained over the years through experience and learning from my peers. I hope that artists like you will find something of value as I share some useful practices and lessons that I've gathered over the years. &lt;/p&gt; Beginning with the end in mind  &lt;p&gt;If you want to start finding clarity in your life, it can be helpful to begin with, the end in mind. Too often, people get overwhelmed with the idea of significant change that they give up before they get started. To make big change more manageable, try breaking it down. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Author Annie Dillard once wrote, "How we spend our days is, of course, how we spend our lives. What we do with this hour, and that one is what we are doing. A schedule defends from chaos and whim. It is a net for catching days."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;How do you want your year to look? Why not set some goals and start to work your way backward from there? If you're going to make a trip to another country, start planning out what you need to do each day, week, and month leading up to the trip. What works for trips can work for your art projects as well! &lt;/p&gt; Say no to the right things &lt;p&gt;One of the hardest lessons that I've had to learn over the years is to disappoint the right people and to say "No" to the right things. Let's face it, you can't make everyone happy, and you can't do all of the things! Part of ordering your life and your career is learning how to prioritize your time, energy, and relationships. You may want to take every opportunity that comes your way, but the truth is, that is not sustainable. If you're going to keep a healthy work-life balance, you need to decide on your priorities and stick to them. &lt;/p&gt; Take action!  &lt;p&gt;One of the worst aspects of getting overwhelmed can be finding yourself frozen with inaction. How do you react when you feel overwhelmed? If you want to make some positive changes in your life, you need to start somewhere. Even if you need to make a small step toward change, take it! I challenge you to write down the one thing that you will do today that will make you feel accomplished. Here are a few examples that you can use: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Knock out a small painting like an 8x10 or even a 3x5. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Set your studio up for tomorrow, so you are ready to go. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Open your sketchbook up and sketch for just 15 minutes. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Prepare canvases for the weekend, so you are ready to paint. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Choose one small section of that large painting that you will resolve today. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Write that email that you've been avoiding. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Make that decision that you've been agonizing over. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;These examples are just intended to get you started. Pick an action step that makes sense for you - but don't put it off!&lt;/p&gt; Outline of This Episode &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;[2:30] I give a shoutout to a few listeners. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[6:40] Why you need to figure out your life design. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[9:00] Where are your priorities? &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[11:30] I describe my ideal day. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[19:20] Finding clarity and focus. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[22:00] Saying “No” to the right things. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[24:00] Action steps you can take today!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[26:00] Closing thoughts.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; Resources Mentioned on this episode &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.savvypainter.com/faso" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;www.savvypainter.com/faso&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; Connect With Antrese &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/savvypainter/" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;On Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pinterest.com/savvypainter/" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;On Pinterest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/antresewood/" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;On Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/SavvyPainter" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;On Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>podcast@savvypainter.com (Savvy Painter Podcast with Antrese Wood)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9fa11125542543cea20ac93053314259</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9fa11125542543cea20ac93053314259/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Flipping the Table : S2 -  Ep#1 - Peter Hoffman, NYC’s most thoughtful activist chef</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Chef Hoffman shares his unique culinary journey, including how he catalyzed farm to table in the Big Apple.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mail@rootsofchange.org (Flipping the Table)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4cb5cbec89d1474ab3afd943333b370a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4cb5cbec89d1474ab3afd943333b370a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Twenty Thousand Hertz : #85 | Seinfeld</title><description>&lt;p&gt;No bass for you!! In 1987, TV composer &lt;a href="https://seinfeldmusicguy.com/"&gt;Jonathan Wolff&lt;/a&gt; was still trying to make a name for himself in Hollywood. Then one day, he got a call from Jerry Seinfeld, who needed music for his new sitcom. This is the story behind the unforgettable music of Seinfeld, and how Jonathan Wolff’s unique approach helped make Seinfeld a TV classic."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://20k.org/"&gt;Twenty Thousand Hertz&lt;/a&gt; is produced out of the studios of &lt;a href="http://defactosound.com/"&gt;Defacto Sound&lt;/a&gt;, and hosted by &lt;a href="http://dallastaylor.com/"&gt;Dallas Taylor&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow the show on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/20korg"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href="http://facebook.com/20korg"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Become a monthly contributor at &lt;a href="http://20k.org/donate"&gt;20k.org/donate&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you know what this week's mystery sound is, tell us at &lt;a href="http://mystery.20k.org/"&gt;mystery.20k.org&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out SONOS at &lt;a href="http://sonos.com/"&gt;sonos.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Find Jonathan on &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/SeinfeldMusicGuy/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; and on &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/seinfeldmusic"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can reach Steve at &lt;a href="stevelack.com"&gt;stevelack.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href="https://www.armandalegshow.com/"&gt;An Arm and a Leg&lt;/a&gt; wherever you get your podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Episode transcript, music, and credits can be found here: &lt;a href="https://www.20k.org/episodes/seinfeld"&gt;https://www.20k.org/episodes/seinfeld&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>dallas@20k.org (Twenty Thousand Hertz)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f8094a5750524639b60eee2c228d3d3e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f8094a5750524639b60eee2c228d3d3e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Radiolab : 60 Words</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This hour we pull apart one sentence, written in the hours after September 11th, 2001, that has led to the longest war in U.S. history. We examine how just 60 words of legal language have blurred the line between war and peace.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (Radiolab)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">64a3d753dd9549458d25f395096c34de</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/64a3d753dd9549458d25f395096c34de/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Backcountry Gallery's Wildlife Photography Podcast : Keep Shootin’, Mirrorless Future, Box Talk, VR And Tripods</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, we&amp;#8217;ll talk about the importance of knowing when to stop shooting and when to keep going. From there, we&amp;#8217;ll talk about when it&amp;#8217;s time to upgrade to mirrorless, if you should keep your boxes (yeah, it&amp;#8217;s weird), and if you should use VR / Stabilization when using a tripod.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Lots of great stuff this time, so grab a warm drink, your favorite earbuds, and take a listen.  &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://backcountrygallery.com/keep-shootin-mirrorless-future-box-talk-vr-and-tripods/"&gt;Keep Shootin&amp;#8217;, Mirrorless Future, Box Talk, VR And Tripods&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://backcountrygallery.com"&gt;Backcountry Gallery&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>steve@bcgphotos.com (Backcountry Gallery's Wildlife Photography Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">da45debbc41e4a1e928e4b081de94a0b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/da45debbc41e4a1e928e4b081de94a0b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 05:53:01 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Full of Joy : Ep #11 My 2020 Mindset &amp; How I'm Hitting My Goals</title><description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;In today's episode were talking about my 2020 mindset! The new year, resolutions, goals, vision boards, the law of attraction! I hope this episode inspires hope for the new days to come!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>fullofjoypodcast@gmail.com (Full of Joy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">739995b44d85456a99fa63b3706409a6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/739995b44d85456a99fa63b3706409a6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 05:06:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Photog Adventures Podcast: A Landscape Photography and Astrophotography Podcast : Untold Stories 2019 Part 1 | Instagrammers at Mesa Arch, Barn Owls &amp; Scared of a Juvenile | Ep 142</title><description>Joined by Kirk Keyes and Rob Ryan we share untold stories from 2019. 

Between Kirk's National Media name snub, Rob's fear of Owls but not Snakes and my own new juvenile arch-nemesis out at Escalante we share some funny success stories &amp; annoying situations from 2019!

Rhonda's recommended snake protection - Turtleskin Snake Gaitors: https://amzn.to/2Foku0C</description><author>photogadventures@gmail.com (Photog Adventures Podcast: A Landscape Photography and Astrophotography Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d92de417577f448d91542b143c487133</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d92de417577f448d91542b143c487133/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 05:00:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Feast : Feast &amp; Fast: How Clean Eating Came to Early Modern Europe</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Feast is back! Just in time for the month of healthy New Year’s resolutions, our season premiere features a rich discussion on the history of feasting and fasting in Europe. We talk to Dr. Victoria Avery and Dr. Melissa Calaresu, co-curators of the exhibition “Feast &amp;amp; Fast: The Art of Food in Europe 1500–1800” at the &lt;a href="https://feast-and-fast.fitzmuseum.cam.ac.uk/"&gt;Fitzwilliam Museum&lt;/a&gt; in Cambridge, England, to learn some of the questions early modern Europeans were asking about what to eat and where their food came from: How can I eat clean? What is a moderate diet? Should I adopt a plant-based lifestyle?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such questions might sound very 21st century, but these topics wouldn’t have been out of place in the 17th or 18th centuries as Europeans wrestled with the idea of how to adopt a moderate and nutritious diet. We’ll also look at some of the most epic feasting traditions of early modern Europe, from architectural sugar sculptures to ten-foot tall pineapples, but we’ll also uncover the questionable and often dark histories that lay at their root. Join us for a feast and fast of epic proportions on the Season 4 premiere of The Feast. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more: &lt;a href="https://www.thefeastpodcast.org"&gt;www.thefeastpodcast.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cover Photo by James Berrill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jumbro@thepodglomerate.com (The Feast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d3f0f01c9fe54fadb73249ba46ed21cd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d3f0f01c9fe54fadb73249ba46ed21cd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mixed Podcast : Season 1 Trailer: What is Mixed Podcast? - Mixed Podcast</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Get a taste of what Mixed Podcast will be like, from chefs and home cooks, to eaters industry leaders who are often forgotten in the food we enjoy. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@mixedpodcast.com (Mixed Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7b96c5a69ba3456b90f1d932c7cb53b6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7b96c5a69ba3456b90f1d932c7cb53b6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:59:38 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Noble Blood : The Swan King Went Mad</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Only days after he was deposed, King Ludwig II of Bavaria died in an apparent suicide. But was it murder? Or was it just the final act of a king who had gone mad with love and with passion, born into the wrong century?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Noble Blood)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cc2efddbf165428aa4308a191108fdde</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cc2efddbf165428aa4308a191108fdde/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Conversations About Art : Helen Molesworth</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Helen Molesworth is a Los Angeles-based writer and curator. She recently released “Recording Artists,” a podcast series in conjunction with the Getty and she is the curator-in-residence at the Anderson Ranch Arts Center. We talked about why it’s a great thing when works of art make you cry, personal and institutional legacy, and where the divine or faith shows up in art.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts38+f5e7e78@anchor.fm (Conversations About Art)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">918c755811b44cbc86b13aeab363bb1f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/918c755811b44cbc86b13aeab363bb1f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Oath with Chuck Rosenberg : BONUS: Chuck Rosenberg on Article II</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Every President of the United States must swear to a 35-word oath, promising to preserve, protect and defend the Constitution. Special guest and MSNBC Contributor Chuck Rosenberg joins Steve Kornacki to discuss the founders’ intent behind that oath&amp;nbsp;and what happens&amp;nbsp;when it's put&amp;nbsp;to the test.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chuck Rosenberg served as a career federal prosecutor and later as United States Attorney for the Eastern District of Virginia. He has also served in senior positions at the Department of Justice for two Attorneys General, in the Federal Bureau of Investigation under two directors, and as the head of the Drug Enforcement Administration. Chuck is also the host of an MSNBC podcast, The Oath with Chuck Rosenberg.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>theoathpodcast@gmail.com (The Oath with Chuck Rosenberg)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">84425c8cb43849179c2c778ed760eede</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/84425c8cb43849179c2c778ed760eede/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 10:49:45 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Date Night with Raven &amp; Adam : 8: 2020 Resolutions</title><description>&lt;div&gt;What are your goals for 2020? Lose weight? Increase your income? Decrease debt? Travel more? Curse less? Raven and Adam read your resolutions and share theirs for the new year. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Have a question for Raven or Adam? Slip into their DMs: &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/ravennicolegates/?hl=en"&gt;@ravennicolegates&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/adam_gottschalk/?hl=en"&gt;@adam_gottschalk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This episode is sponsored by: &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://withjoy.com/"&gt;Joy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.scentbird.com/"&gt;Scentbird&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Music by &lt;a href="https://freemusicarchive.org/music/Jahzzar"&gt;Jahzzar&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;Licensed under &lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/"&gt;Creative Commons: By Attribution 4.0 License&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>rss@audioboom.com (Date Night with Raven &amp; Adam)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a34a58cff37c43a1b2eddff9e22ea2d5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a34a58cff37c43a1b2eddff9e22ea2d5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Green Eggs and Dan : Introducing Food, We Need to Talk</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Food, We Need to Talk is a new podcast from WBUR about one woman's quest to end her war with food. Hosts Juna Gjata and Dr. Eddie Phillips wield solid science, medical knowledge, common sense and an endless supply of dad jokes to teach us how to eat better and feel better about it. Hint: It’s not dieting. They discuss exercise, body image, food addiction, genetics, weight loss and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen and subscribe today on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/food-we-need-to-talk/id1490621476"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; or wherever you listen to podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>listen@thepodglomerate.com (Green Eggs and Dan)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3ee9bcc77d964506bcc98ea254b0c32c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3ee9bcc77d964506bcc98ea254b0c32c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Eat It, Virginia! : Keeping the River City rolling</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It was not so long ago that River City Roll owner and Richmond native Rob Long was an investment banker who hated his job. So, he got out of the office and did something about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Corporate America wasn't really for me," Long told Scott and Robey on the CBS 6 food podcast Eat It, Virginia! "I lived in three other cities across the country and they all had concepts similar to River City Roll. I saw them and spent a lot of money at them when I lived there. So when I moved back to Richmond, I actually moved into the Cookie Factory Lofts. And the acreage that [River City Roll] is on now was kind of a dilapidated old parking lot. And I was like, somebody is going to do this in Richmond. I don't particularly care for corporate America or my current job. So I'm going to take the leap of faith."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And it was quite a leap. With neither restaurant experience nor an impressive bowling average, Long opened River City Roll on Myers Street, off Arthur Ashe Boulevard, in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The concept combines an upscale bowling environment (think leather seats and playful lighting) with elevated dining options not typically expected at a bowling alley.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since this is a food podcast, it's that menu which drew our interest. The man behind the menu is Chef Brad Slemaker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I couldn't do it without Brad Slemaker our chef," Long said. "He's just so talented. I mean he's trained under the best. So he was Walter Bundy sous chef at Lemaire. So, you know, Walter, I would say is, you know, one of the people I respect the most in the city. Shagbark [Bundy's current restaurant] is where I eat for my birthday every year. And for us to get Brad and give him kind of his own kitchen, he's really doing a great job."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While wood-fired pizzas remain River City Roll's number one seller, Long highlighted other menu items such as Chef Brad's pork belly steamed buns and the truffle fries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"[Chef Brad has] tried to take the truffle fries off the menu the last three times and it's just the only time I give him a firm 'no.' They're probably also the biggest culprit for why I've gained 15 pounds since we've opened," Long laughed. "The ginger glazed chicken bowl is something I eat four to five times a week. I've convinced myself that it's somewhat healthy, which it is. But that that's my go-to. The new tuna dish which he's going to do on the next menu is incredible. Sesame crusted tuna, which I'm a big fan of. Our burger is underrated. I think his take on the Mexican shrimp cocktail is really cool and different."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to food, drink, and bowling, River City Roll bring music to Scott's Addition. The venue hosted a dozen concerts both inside the alley and out in the expansive parking lot. Long hopes to bring even more acts to town in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We had over 1,200 people here for Robert Randolph on our outdoor stage," he said. "We have had other acts like Andy Frasco who played at Lockn and Chris Jacobs played outside. The Wailers played inside."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;River City Roll made local headlines in 2019 when Long and his team opened Tommie's patio - a space dedicated with a Richmond's dog whose abusive death captured the community's hearts. When guests order a TOMMIETAIL cocktail, a portion of the proceeds goes to Richmond Animal Care and Control (RACC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We wanted to think of a way that we could honor Tommie, but as well continue to support RACC in an ongoing fashion. So, the original debut of Tommie's patio, I think we raised close to $7,000," Long said. "But you know, sales on Tommie's patio get donated to RACC every month. So it's not just a one time thing. It's a kind of a constant thing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long hopes River City Roll remains a constant choice for Richmonders looking to have fun in the city. Email EatItVirginia@gmail.com to provide podcast feedback and suggest guests for future shows.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>eatitvirginia@gmail.com (Eat It, Virginia!)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c2f93b3368dd4545bcbc6ec5780d8cd3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c2f93b3368dd4545bcbc6ec5780d8cd3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Big Schmear Podcast : Stirring the Pot</title><description>&lt;div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_0 et_section_regular"&gt;
				
				
				
				
					&lt;div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_0 et_pb_equal_columns"&gt;
				&lt;div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_1_3 et_pb_column_0  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough"&gt;
				
				
				&lt;div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_0  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_dark"&gt;
				
				
				&lt;div class="et_pb_text_inner"&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;Episode 46&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .et_pb_text --&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .et_pb_column --&gt;&lt;div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_1_3 et_pb_column_1  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough"&gt;
				
				
				&lt;div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_1  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_dark"&gt;
				
				
				&lt;div class="et_pb_text_inner"&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;Guest:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;Chef Laura Frankel&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p style="font-weight: 400;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .et_pb_text --&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .et_pb_column --&gt;&lt;div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_1_3 et_pb_column_2  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child"&gt;
				
				
				&lt;div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_2  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_dark"&gt;
				
				
				&lt;div class="et_pb_text_inner"&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Stirring the Pot &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .et_pb_text --&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .et_pb_column --&gt;
				
				
			&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .et_pb_row --&gt;&lt;div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_1"&gt;
				&lt;div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_3  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child"&gt;
				
				
				&lt;div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_3  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light"&gt;
				
				
				&lt;div class="et_pb_text_inner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="wp-image-2039 alignnone size-full" src="https://secureservercdn.net/198.71.233.254/597.223.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/image1-1-e1570376245359.jpeg" alt="" width="358" height="510" srcset="https://secureservercdn.net/198.71.233.254/597.223.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/image1-1-e1570376245359.jpeg 358w, https://secureservercdn.net/198.71.233.254/597.223.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/image1-1-e1570376245359-211x300.jpeg 211w" sizes="(max-width: 358px) 100vw, 358px" /&gt;​&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I couldn&amp;#8217;t think of a better way to begin 2020 on &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Big Schmear&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; than with the topic of Marijuana and Jewish food. So many states have now legalized recreational pot that it seemed a timely topic.  I went to my go-to expert on all things kosher in the kitchen, Chef Laura Frankel and she even provided two recipes for this episode. In honor of &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Big Schmear &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;we now have a recipe for &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mixed Green Olive-Cannabis Schmear AND Chicken Soup with Potza Balls. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;So have a listen to the episode and then, if marijuana is legal where you live, try one of these edible cannabis recipes and let me know what you think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .et_pb_text --&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .et_pb_column --&gt;
				
				
			&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .et_pb_row --&gt;
				
				
			&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!-- .et_pb_section --&gt;</description><author>beth@thebigschmear.com (The Big Schmear Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">16cb69f3fe7b4e1dab7dad43241a8fea</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/16cb69f3fe7b4e1dab7dad43241a8fea/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 17:54:34 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Extremities : St Helena's Decisive Decade</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On January 1st, 2020, St Helena enters what will potentially be the most important and consequential decade in its history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extremities is made possible by Curiosity Stream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sign up for a &amp;nbsp;Curiosity Stream subscription at &lt;a href="http://CuriosityStream.com/ext"&gt;http://CuriosityStream.com/ext&lt;/a&gt; and get a free subscription to Nebula--the streaming video site that Wendover Productions helped found. On Nebula, find The World's Most Useful Airport--the documentary we produced about St Helena's airport.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sam@wendover.productions (Extremities)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1f264a6627bd48c89a255b94ca017e62</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1f264a6627bd48c89a255b94ca017e62/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 09:47:25 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Cooler : We Need A Resolution</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On this month&amp;#8217;s episode of &lt;em&gt;The Cooler&lt;/em&gt;, we&amp;#8217;re making resolutions to upgrade ourselves in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-113277" src="https://ww2.kqed.org/app/uploads/sites/12/2019/12/upgrade-beyonce.gif" alt="" width="500" height="281" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#8217;re discussing how some of our favorite shows and films have retconned plots to cover their asses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-113278" src="https://ww2.kqed.org/app/uploads/sites/12/2019/12/comeback-changes.gif" alt="" width="325" height="225" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And we&amp;#8217;re making a pilgrimage to visit one of Jennifer Aniston&amp;#8217;s exes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-113276" src="https://ww2.kqed.org/app/uploads/sites/12/2019/12/closure-rachel.gif" alt="" width="371" height="209" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember: if you want to be featured in a future episode, call our hotline at 415.553.2850 with a question and we might answer it on the show!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-113211" src="https://ww2.kqed.org/pop/wp-content/uploads/sites/12/2019/10/barney-phone.gif" alt="" width="325" height="252" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Listen to hear all about it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--[if lt IE 9]&gt;&lt;script&gt;document.createElement('audio');&lt;/script&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;
&lt;audio  class="wp-audio-shortcode" id="audio-113275-1" preload="none" style="width: 100%; visibility: hidden;" controls="controls" data-permanlink="" data-id3TagWidget="1"  data-audioPodcastTitle="The Cooler"  data-audioEpisodeTitle="We Need A Resolution" data-siteName="KQED Pop" data-audioAirdate="" data-audioPoster="https://ww2.kqed.org/app/uploads/sites/12/2019/12/Screen-Shot-2019-12-17-at-1.46.03-AM.png" data-audioComments="" data-postDate="January 1, 2020"  data-perspectivesAuthor="" title="KQED The Cooler / We Need A Resolution "&gt;&lt;source type="audio/mpeg" src="https://www.kqed.org/.stream/anon/radio/thecooler/2019/12/WeNeedAResolution.mp3?_=1" /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kqed.org/.stream/anon/radio/thecooler/2019/12/WeNeedAResolution.mp3"&gt;https://www.kqed.org/.stream/anon/radio/thecooler/2019/12/WeNeedAResolution.mp3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/audio&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until next time! &lt;a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1041117499" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Subscribe and rate us five stars in iTunes&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ondemand@kqed.org (The Cooler)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1771ae8fd9354ba4813b4498e8568603</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1771ae8fd9354ba4813b4498e8568603/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 03:00:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Sierra Unfiltered : What We're Leaving Behind for 2020 (new years resolutions)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Looking back on the decade, we're talking about what we're leaving behind in 2019 and our goals and new years resolutions for 2020. In this episode of Sierra Unfiltered, we're talking about the best and worst parts of the year and what we're looking forward to for the new year!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts11+c61f880@anchor.fm (Sierra Unfiltered)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fbadb6ec0237454fa688472dca7c48ff</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fbadb6ec0237454fa688472dca7c48ff/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 10:36:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>1865 : Bonus: In Their Own Words | 17</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s New Year’s Eve, 2019, and the entire team behind &lt;em&gt;1865&lt;/em&gt; wants to wish you a happy new year, with health, prosperity and good listening in 2020. We have high hopes for the coming year, including more from 1865. But today, we’re presenting an episode that’s previously only been available to our subscribers at 1865podcast.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s a bonus series called “In Their Own Words,” wherein we explore the journals, letters and speeches of some of the major characters in our series, performed by our incredibly talented cast. You’ll hear these historical figures’ unfiltered, unmistakable, often uncomfortable emotions and opinions as they witness and participate in this tumultuous period of history.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hope you enjoy it. If you do, consider becoming a subscriber yourself at 1865podcast.com, to gain access to all these bonus episodes and more, plus early access to what’s coming next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1865 is an Airship production. You can support this show at &lt;a href="https://1865podcast.com/" target="_blank"&gt;1865podcast.com&lt;/a&gt; to get early, ad-free access to episodes and more, or find us on &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/1865podcast" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook &lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/1865podcast" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>1865@airship.fm (1865)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">22596d38fd5348a799c36d9f8e87fc09</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/22596d38fd5348a799c36d9f8e87fc09/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Sake On Air : Aroma &amp; Sake</title><description>What exactly is the scent of sake? For our final episode of 2019, Chris Hughes, Rebekah Wilson-Lye, and Sebastie Lemoine gather to discuss the nature and role of aroma in sake. Seeing as how the smells that we experience impart so much influence on our perception of taste and our associated memories, this is a […]</description><author>jpotts0011@yahoo.co.jp (Sake On Air)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a04c7cc6f4714ae781310c862b2722c1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a04c7cc6f4714ae781310c862b2722c1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 01:23:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Art Party : Art Party -- Episode 18 -- 2019: A Vague Recap</title><description>Art Party -- Episode 18 -- 2019: A Vague Recap by Art Party</description><author>feeds@soundcloud.com (Art Party)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c2bcac48c27a490eb02fdc5dc8ab78e4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c2bcac48c27a490eb02fdc5dc8ab78e4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 17:21:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Photographer Life Podcast : Episode 22 – The Delicate Balance of Work and Family Life</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this recording of Photographer Life Podcast, Ellie and Cori discuss family life, work-life, and the delicate balance that it is to maintain health in both. They share some tips, failings, successes, and favorite ways to do both well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Resources&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Book: &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Feeding-Mouth-That-Bites-You/dp/1514762374/ref=sr_1_1?crid=3HH2PT1DB82YQ&amp;amp;keywords=feeding+the+mouth+that+bites+you+book&amp;amp;qid=1576272531&amp;amp;sprefix=feeding+the+mouth+%2Caps%2C201&amp;amp;sr=8-1"&gt;Feeding the Mouth that Bites You&lt;/a&gt; by Ken Wilgus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://calendar.google.com/"&gt;Google Calendar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rate our podcast and leave us a review in the iTunes store!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>hello@photographerlifepodcast.com (Photographer Life Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6f43bd4f9bb8452da6ba52b5fb404b68</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6f43bd4f9bb8452da6ba52b5fb404b68/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 05:00:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Georgia Foodcast : The Plate Sale</title><author>atlfoodcast@gmail.com (The Georgia Foodcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5e5fb5091c1b47f690688c1529563a45</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5e5fb5091c1b47f690688c1529563a45/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 17:27:27 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Cask Club Radio : Cask Club Radio Episode 116</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In today's show, Justin, Lydia, and Maura discuss a study that says wine can kill germs that cause bad breath and sore throats, scientists who determined whether tapping a beer actually prevents it from foaming over, and Bud Light picking up the tab for an NFL player's fine. Then, we take a look at New Year's resolutions and who is best at keeping them by state and Danielle Kartes of &lt;em&gt;'Joyful Rustic Food'&lt;/em&gt; joins us to talk about holiday baking and cocktails pairings. Plus, we leave you with a perfect cocktail to ring in the new year!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@bonneville.com (Cask Club Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d0c110b0253d430a8eae80af873d4090</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d0c110b0253d430a8eae80af873d4090/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dialogues | A podcast from David Zwirner about art, artists, and the creative process : Marcel Dzama and Will Butler (Re-run)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We're taking a quick break from new episodes but please enjoy this episode from the first season of 'Dialogues' with the artist Marcel Dzama and the musician Will Butler of the band Arcade Fire. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@davidzwirner.com (Dialogues | A podcast from David Zwirner about art, artists, and the creative process)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c4e9f8c1ec11490f8f85411fbba315ff</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c4e9f8c1ec11490f8f85411fbba315ff/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 21:44:39 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Anthropocene Reviewed : Auld Lang Syne</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;John Green reviews Auld Lang Syn&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;e in this podcast's first ever one-review episode.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (The Anthropocene Reviewed)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e5eed9540e6c4eef877d05c13b891825</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e5eed9540e6c4eef877d05c13b891825/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Artcast : Episode 4: Dora Maar at the Tate Modern</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Episode 4: Dora Maar at the Tate Modern discussed by Vikki Kosmalska and Caz Murray.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For our final episode of series 4 we delve into the world of photographer, painter and poet Dora Maar. History has remembered Maar primarily for being the muse and lover of Picasso and the full breath of her artistic output has only been recognised since her death in 1997.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This exhibition is re-writing her back into the artistic canon, shining a light on her innovative and varied photographic practice, her influential role in the Surrealist movement and how she collaborated (and influenced) her better know peers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Art News, we cover the recent decision to award The Turner Prize to 4 artists. Wider opinion on this is mixed and we discuss what means in the current climate and implications for The Turner Prize in future.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you so much to everyone who has tuned in this season (and this year!) If you like what you hear please rate, review and subscribe.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you want to email us, we would love to hear from you: helloartcast@gmail.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And you can follow us on instagram: @theartcast&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our wonderful editor Jonny Lennard has also launched his own podcast The Old Boys Book Club. It's not about art, but we highly recommend you give it a listen. Available on all major podcast platforms and you can find them on insta here: @theoldboysbookclub.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last but not least - thank you to the incredible Nat Witts for our jazzy jingle and Jonny for his amazing editing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merry Christmas from The Artcast and see you in the New Year (and new decade) for more chats about art!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>helloartcast@gmail.com (The Artcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">69f29c35ddca46be8b66b80472fe6d03</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/69f29c35ddca46be8b66b80472fe6d03/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Solvable : The Mental Health Crisis is Solvable</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Jacob Weisberg talks to Dixon Chibanda about giving access to mental health care in non-Western nations.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marketing@pushkin.fm (Solvable)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bc37e7bc8d8741aaaf2a5146c4bf04b1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bc37e7bc8d8741aaaf2a5146c4bf04b1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 21:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Art Movements : Hyperallergic Picks Their Favorite Holiday Movie Classics</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s the holidays and you can’t get away from them. Some classic films have come to represent the season in the popular imagination, and we all have our favorites. I invited film editor Dan Schindel to talk about this unique genre of cinema, while discussing our favorite films about Christmas and more. I also invited a number of Hyperallergic staff to share their favorites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have a feeling this episode will get you into the holiday mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;** Sponsor **&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ovid.tv/"&gt;OVID.tv&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you’re into art films, documentaries on artists, or simply want visual inspiration, consider subscribing to our favorite streaming service, OVID.tv. To make this easy, they’re offering a special year-end discount on monthly plans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From now until January 1st, you can save 25% off your first four months of OVID. This means you’ll get access to OVID—the best streaming service for critically acclaimed independent films—for just $5.25 per month instead of $6.99. Simply head over to &lt;a href="https://ovid.tv/"&gt;www.OVID.tv&lt;/a&gt; and use the code "HYPER" at check-out. Then, start watching films on art, dance, photography and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;****&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A special thanks to &lt;a href="https://www.patrickthomasmusic.com/"&gt;Patrick Thomas&lt;/a&gt; for providing the music to this episode and getting us into the holiday spirit. You can find &lt;a href="https://music.apple.com/us/album/christmas-with-patrick-thomas/1490001290"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Christmas with Patrick Thomas&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on iTunes, and follow him on &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/apatrickthomas/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/APatrickThomas"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This and more in the current episode of Hyperallergic’s &lt;a href="https://hyperallergic.com/tag/art-movements-podcast/"&gt;Art Movements&lt;/a&gt; podcast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Subscribe to Hyperallergic’s Art Movements on &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/hyperallergic/id1112233641?mt=2"&gt;&lt;i&gt;iTunes&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;, and &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://hyperallergic.simplecast.com/"&gt;&lt;i&gt;anywhere else&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; you listen to podcasts.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>veken@hyperallergic.com (Art Movements)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cf2d06245e54475d868782f12ec69ba6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cf2d06245e54475d868782f12ec69ba6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 19:52:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Art Side of Life : Ep.210: Interview with community members - Donovan, Visi and Keshna (YouTube 20k subs giveaway)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey, guys! This is another special episode with the winners of the Art Side of Life YouTube 20k giveaway. I chat with Donovan (Fantasy &amp; Mythology illustrator from Texas), Visi (Freelance illustrator from Colorado) and Keshna (Illustrator from New Jersey) about their artistic journey and tips for the artistic community. Enjoy!!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show notes: &lt;a href= "https://artsideoflife.com/community-donovan-visi-keshna" target= "_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://artsideoflife.com/community-donovan-visi-keshna&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Special offer for Art Side of Life listeners&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;💲&lt;a href="https://artsideoflife.com/make-money-pod" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;How to Make Money as an Artist Course&lt;/a&gt; - Proven ways to a creative career you will love!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;🎓&lt;a href="https://artsideoflife.com/evolve-pod" target= "_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Evolve Artist Program&lt;/a&gt; -  better than an art college education and only at a fraction of the cost - World’s Simplest Art Training Method*&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;🎨&lt;a href="https://artsideoflife.com/color-pod" target= "_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Storytelling with Color and Light Course&lt;/a&gt; - make your artworks more believable and appealing&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;📚🎧&lt;a href= "https://artsideoflife.com/audible-pod"&gt;Audible&lt;/a&gt; - 2 audiobooks FREE - learn by listening to hundreds of books&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Please note: I am Evolve's affiliate partner, meaning I get paid a small commission (at no extra cost to you) if you use my link to make a purchase. Thank you for supporting Art Side of Life!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe to Art Side of Life Podcast to get notified when I post new episodes!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://artsideoflife.com/itunes"&gt;https://artsideoflife.com/itunes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://artsideoflife.com/spotify"&gt;https://artsideoflife.com/spotify&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow me on Instagram&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/art_side_of_life/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/art_side_of_life/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/ivkam/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/ivkam/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Subscribe to Art Side of Life&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://artsideoflife.com/subscribe"&gt;https://artsideoflife.com/subscribe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thanks for listening!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Special thanks to Donovan, Visi and Keshna for joining me today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you enjoyed this interview please let me know with a review, hopefully, 5 stars because I would like to reach many artists like you!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;See you in the next episode :) Bye!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@artsideoflife.com (Art Side of Life)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">81b3c4b8a9b5472391b95e9cf4c165d1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/81b3c4b8a9b5472391b95e9cf4c165d1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Studio C-41: 1 Hour Photo Podcast : The Last Episode of the Decade!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Merry Christmas Everybody! We record the last episode of the year (and the decade)! Bill gives Jordana and Steven some Christmas gifts. They briefly go over the photo news. Lastly, they discuss where they were 10 years ago and what their goals are for 2020.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thank you, listeners, for making 2019 a fantastic year and we can't wait to get started in 2020.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Photo News:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ektachrome in 120 and 4x5&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Fujifilm Acros 100 II&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Kodak Alaris Increases Film Prices&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;OneInstant Pack Film&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;FILM Ferrania P30&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>contact@studioc41.net (Studio C-41: 1 Hour Photo Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2636de476ac74aa5be37fd136424b44f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2636de476ac74aa5be37fd136424b44f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 20:53:15 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Susan Nethercote Studio Insider Art Podcast : Let's Talk About Self-Sabotage.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to episode 9 of the Studio Insider Art Podcast. This week’s conversation examines self-sabotage and it’s attempts to derail our art practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We dive in to how it presents and how you can set up your creative space with the ambiance to nurture creative flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Leaning on your support network, including professional help when you’re feeling all the feelings&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Having compassion for yourself when the going gets tough&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Laura’s strategy for managing negative self-talk&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Identifying where you’re self-sabotaging your art practice.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;Using self-care practices to create structure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you enjoy the episode,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;X Suze&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LINKS FOR THIS EPISODE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Laura’s artwork discussed in this episode:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B3q9dTOhFLZ/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; https://www.instagram.com/p/B3q9dTOhFLZ/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Susan Nethercote:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/susan.nethercote/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.instagram.com/susan.nethercote/&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/susannethercoteart/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.facebook.com/susannethercoteart/&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laura Day:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/laurajaneday/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.instagram.com/laurajaneday/&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/laura.day.73594"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.facebook.com/laura.day.73594&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Susan's free education resources: &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.susannethercotestudio.com/free"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.susannethercotestudio.com/free&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Susan's art website: &lt;a href="https://www.susannethercote.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://www.susannethercote.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts24+fa59f10@anchor.fm (Susan Nethercote Studio Insider Art Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7adc47a31ee343c5969cf1a0ecec98f9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7adc47a31ee343c5969cf1a0ecec98f9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 20:32:18 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Jungle Prince : Chapter 3: A House in Yorkshire</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In a ruined palace in the woods, rummaging through discarded papers, our reporter finds a clue.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (Jungle Prince)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6aed018c09d6440a8a0d8647281b5714</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6aed018c09d6440a8a0d8647281b5714/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:23:16 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Perceived Value : Grad School Was My Version Of YOLO: Adriane Dalton</title><description>&lt;p class=""&gt;Adriane Dalton is an artist, writer, and educator based in Richmond, Virginia. She is the Editor of &lt;a href="https://www.snagmetalsmith.org/metalsmith-magazine/about-metalsmith/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Metalsmith&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Metalsmith Tech&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt;magazines, and the annual &lt;a href="https://www.snagmetalsmith.org/resources-opportunities/jams/" target="_blank"&gt;Jewelry and Metals Survey (JaMS) &lt;/a&gt;published by the &lt;a href="https://www.snagmetalsmith.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Society of North American Goldsmiths (SNAG)&lt;/a&gt;. She received her MA in History of Decorative Arts and Design (now the History of Design and Curatorial Studies) from Parsons The New School for Design in partnership with the Cooper Hewitt, Smithsonian Design Museum, and her BFA in Craft &amp;amp; Material Studies from The University of the Arts in Philadelphia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;She was formerly the Assistant Curator and Exhibitions Manager at the Nora Eccles Harrison Museum of Art (NEHMA) in Logan, Utah where she co-curated &lt;em&gt;ARTsySTEM: The Changing Climate of the Arts and Sciences &lt;/em&gt;and&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;taught History of American Studio Craft, among many other curatorial and educational projects. She is a past contributor to &lt;a href="https://artjewelryforum.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Art Jewelry Forum&lt;/a&gt; and the Cooper Hewitt, Smithsonian Design Museum &lt;a href="https://www.cooperhewitt.org/category/object-of-the-day/" target="_blank"&gt;Object of the Day &lt;/a&gt;blog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;Over the past fifteen years, her &lt;a href="http://spitandwishes.com/" target="_blank"&gt;studio practice &lt;/a&gt;has evolved from traditional metalsmithing and enameling techniques to incorporate alternative and recycled materials. Lately, she is using disused and discarded materials to engage with intersections of labor, class, gender, and consumption. She brings her appreciation for creative reuse into her role as lead instructor for &lt;a href="https://www.vmfa.museum/teens/teen-stylin/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Teen Stylin’&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;—a twelve-week wearable arts program at the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts. She also teaches recycled materials jewelry and enameling at the &lt;a href="https://www.visarts.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Visual Arts Center of Richmond,&lt;/a&gt; and is a past Program Leader at &lt;a href="https://www.art180.org/" target="_blank"&gt;ART 180&lt;/a&gt;, a non-profit providing art-related programming for young people in Richmond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;APPLY TO THE NEW VOICES WRITING CONTEST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In celebration of its 40th year of publication, &lt;em&gt;Metalsmith&lt;/em&gt; magazine invites new and aspiring writers to submit proposals to the New Voices Writing Contest. Do you have a research topic that feels congruent with the varieties of content featured in &lt;em&gt;Metalsmith&lt;/em&gt;? Are you interested in broadening the discourse within the fields of jewelry, metalworking, adornment, design, and craft? Do you have a fresh perspective, unique voice, or a radical idea? We want to hear about it!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;New Voices: &lt;a href="https://www.snagmetalsmith.org/metalsmith-magazine/new-voices-writing-contest/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.snagmetalsmith.org/metalsmith-magazine/new-voices-writing-contest/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;Application: &lt;a href="https://www.snagmetalsmith.org/metalsmith-magazine/new-voices-writing-contest/" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.snagmetalsmith.org/metalsmith-magazine/new-voices-writing-contest/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>perceivedvaluepodcast@gmail.com (Perceived Value)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">252d36a76b0d401b9ffb6346f5bc000b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/252d36a76b0d401b9ffb6346f5bc000b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:12:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Poetry Unbound : Welcome to Poetry Unbound</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Poetry Unbound&lt;/i&gt; features an immersive exploration of a single poem, guided by Pádraig Ó Tuama. Short and unhurried; contemplative and energizing. Proudly produced by On Being Studios.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This season features poetry from a diverse cast of poets: current and former poets laureate Joy Harjo and Tracy K. Smith; T.S. Eliot Prize winner Ocean Vuong; classic poets like Emily Dickinson and Patrick Kavanagh; spoken-word artists like Raymond Antrobus; and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anchor your week with new episodes on Monday and Friday, beginning January 27. Subscribe today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About the host: Pádraig Ó Tuama is a poet, theologian, conflict mediator — and the host of our new podcast, Poetry Unbound. His books include a prayer book, Daily Prayer with the Corrymeela Community, a book of poetry, &lt;i&gt;Sorry for Your Troubles&lt;/i&gt;, and a memoir, &lt;i&gt;In the Shelter: Finding a Home in the World&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>studio@onbeing.org (Poetry Unbound)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d47917405999405f8d0c2b912d30d652</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d47917405999405f8d0c2b912d30d652/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 09:30:29 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>ArtTactic : Judd Tully reviews the art market in 2019</title><description>In our end of year 2019 episode, Judd Tully, veteran art market reporter and frequent contributor to ARTnews, joins us to recap the art market in 2019. First, Judd identifies some of the top storylines of 2019 for the art market. Then, he reveals who were some of the biggest winners of the year when we think about artists and their markets. Also, he shares what trends in art defined the year. Additionally, Judd tells us his favorite exhibition of 2019. And lastly, Judd gives us a few bold predictions of the art market in 2020.</description><author>adam@arttactic.com (ArtTactic)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8087948454a34d98b8f4b03fa60e6814</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8087948454a34d98b8f4b03fa60e6814/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 07:29:10 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bow Down: Women in Art : Zoe Whitley on Kathleen Collins</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Hayward Gallery curator, and co-curator of the blockbuster touring exhibition ‘Soul of a Nation’ discusses the life and work of Kathleen Collins, the first African-American woman to write and direct a feature film. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>editorial@frieze.com (Bow Down: Women in Art)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5e41e12fa2bf473e8aa648e1c1c455a2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5e41e12fa2bf473e8aa648e1c1c455a2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 06:47:11 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Calligraphy Podcast : Ep. 20: Year in Review</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We started from the bottom, now we're here. Less than a year ago, Christen and Ajab decided to venture into the podcast world with The Calligraphy Podcast. In this final episode of Season 1, we talk through each episode and share some of our favorite moments from the show.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more episodes coming in 2020. In the meantime, follow us on Instagram @thecalligraphypodcast.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thecalligraphypodcast@gmail.com (The Calligraphy Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e38833aed87e43179f159cf9173bfd5d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e38833aed87e43179f159cf9173bfd5d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 22:02:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Workbook Radio : Episode 035- Creative Buyers talk Social Media</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Gain valuable insight about social media from Creative Producer Ron Beinner, Visual Lead Anna Dickson, Sr. Art Producer Brian Gibson, Art Producer Jen Lamping. Moderated by Workbook rep Heidi Goverman.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jacqueline.lopez@workbook.com (Workbook Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5f380385d6d54b40a7394e163d4d5d8e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5f380385d6d54b40a7394e163d4d5d8e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 17:09:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Audio Mullet : Audio Mullet #35: How To Forgive The Man Who Shot Your Daughter</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Doug TenNapel and Ethan Nicolle welcome special guest McGill Alexander from South Africa, who was in an intense hostage situation many years ago while living in Taiwan. A notorious murderer and rapist held his family hostage for 26 hours, shooting McGill and his daughter - both survived. McGill and his wife later brought a Bible to the man who held them hostage and led him to Christ, forgiving him for what he put them through. This interview is all about that act - loving those who are your enemies, praying for those who persecute you. Why are we called to do it and what does it mean?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The episode of Locked Up Abroad must be purchased to be viewed. &lt;a href= "https://www.amazon.com/gp/video/detail/B0053WTE16/ref=stream_est_hd_ep?autoplay=1&amp;t=0"&gt; Click here&lt;/a&gt; and make sure you are getting Season 1, Ep. 10: "Taiwan"&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Read McGill's book &lt;a href= "https://www.amazon.com/Hostage-Taipei-True-Story-Forgiveness/dp/0967038626"&gt; Hostage In Taipei&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Watch this episode on video &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PV_Za-sH09I"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@audiomullet.com (Audio Mullet)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e6d6aa8e9a6b4b749497eedfa949dcdb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e6d6aa8e9a6b4b749497eedfa949dcdb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>AA Cafe Podcast : Christmas 2019 Bonus</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a bonus episode of AA Cafe. Mark and Brian always read their top ten lists during the last episode of the year. It's usually things they're thankful for, but this year Mark decided it would be 10 things they hate. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>brian@doubleshotcoffee.com (AA Cafe Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">613e63e2374a47cf924f58daf6c83abe</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/613e63e2374a47cf924f58daf6c83abe/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 11:10:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Crumb - Bake from Scratch : Great British Baking with Edd Kimber</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The bakers bring on Edd Kimber, a British baking icon who won the first series of &lt;em&gt;Great British Bake Off&lt;/em&gt;. We get his insight on UK baking idiosyncrasies, from the catchall term “pudding” to the holiday baking traditions that have endured over the years. Then we get his formula for making some of the very best chocolate chip cookies. Plus, Brian shares the holiday pie he can’t stop serving, and Kyle Grace offers a Dutch oven bread recipe that’ll be the perfect addition to the dinner table.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A special thank-you to our sponsor, Red Star, our official test kitchen partner and trusted source for all things yeast. Check out their products here: &lt;a href="https://redstaryeast.com/products/"&gt;https://redstaryeast.com/products/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Recipes mentioned in this episode:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bakefromscratch.com/cheddar-sage-dutch-oven-bread/"&gt;Cheddar Sage Dutch Oven Bread&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bakefromscratch.com/custard-tart/"&gt;Edd Kimber’s Custard Tart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bakefromscratch.com/marmalade-pudding/"&gt;Marmalade Pudding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Special links from this episode:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bake from Scratch : &lt;a href="https://www.bakefromscratch.com/product/holiday-cookies-2019/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Holiday Cookies&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Special Issue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Follow &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bake from Scratch&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/thebakefeed/"&gt;@thebakefeed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Website: &lt;a href="https://www.bakefromscratch.com/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;bakefromscratch.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Brian on Instagram: &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/brianharthoffman/"&gt;@brianharthoffman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow Edd on Instagram: &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/theboywhobakes/?hl=en"&gt;@theboywhobakes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>bakefromscratch@mailer.hoffmanmedia.com (The Crumb - Bake from Scratch)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5138335318a949358675b091d7572841</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5138335318a949358675b091d7572841/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>