<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My News feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My news episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My News feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 03:25:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>NPR News Now : NPR News: 02-15-2020 9PM ET</title><description>NPR News: 02-15-2020 9PM ET</description><author>PodCasts@npr.org (NPR News Now)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7a02d046fefe42ff90578983342f4b24</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7a02d046fefe42ff90578983342f4b24/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 18:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC Nightly News with Lester Holt : Saturday, February 15, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;U.S. to evacuate Americans trapped on quarantined cruise ship off Japan, Mississippi braces for widespread flooding after days of heavy rain, and 14-year-old arrested in stabbing death of Barnard student Tessa Majors.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (NBC Nightly News with Lester Holt)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cec509aa56d24e8eb8b00d5eaacdfac4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cec509aa56d24e8eb8b00d5eaacdfac4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 17:35:15 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FOX News Radio Newscast : 8PM EDT 02/15/2020 Newscast</title><description>Latest FOX News hourly newscast.&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=4dbYPXxUBp0:XbbbWcZp41Q:yIl2AUoC8zA"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=yIl2AUoC8zA" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=4dbYPXxUBp0:XbbbWcZp41Q:qj6IDK7rITs"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=qj6IDK7rITs" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=4dbYPXxUBp0:XbbbWcZp41Q:O3QAOHgViy4"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=O3QAOHgViy4" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=4dbYPXxUBp0:XbbbWcZp41Q:I9og5sOYxJI"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=I9og5sOYxJI" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/FoxNewsRadio/~4/4dbYPXxUBp0" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>podcast@foxnewsradio.com (FOX News Radio Newscast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b034aa5cf8004d219ed7280b89a768e3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b034aa5cf8004d219ed7280b89a768e3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 17:08:01 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Freedomizer Radio : Keys of the Kingdom</title><description>Keys to The Kingdom of God are the keys to liberty under God.

Brother Gregory hosts Straight talk about the Keys Of The Kingdom.

Offering a unique perspective to the ancient texts, hidden histories, and natural law.

The Bible is the book for the government of, for and by the people.

 His Holy Church was instituted so that you might be free. Thedaily ministration is key to that freedom.

How were people able to escape the bondage of Egypt, Rome and the "World"?

The secrets of liberty under God have been hiding for centuries right before us!

Broadcasts and videos at: http://www.preparingyou.com/wiki/Audio-Video</description><author>Proof@freedomizerradio.com (Freedomizer Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1276052ec9f04f3a9bf2871f21d8b37d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1276052ec9f04f3a9bf2871f21d8b37d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hold These Truths with Dan Crenshaw : How Millennials Think, with Kristen Soltis Anderson</title><description>&lt;p&gt;How have smart phones and social media shaped the political views of Millennials? What tricks do socialists like AOC and Bernie use to emotionally engage them into supporting programs like Medicare-for-All and the Green New Deal? Kristen Soltis Anderson joined me to delve into these topics and much more, including tips on how to bring young people into the conservative movement with honesty, not talking points.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Kristen is a pollster, speaker, commentator, and author of The Selfie Vote: Where Millennials Are Leading America (And How Republicans Can Keep Up). She is co-founder of Echelon Insights, an opinion research and analytics firm that serves brands, trade associations, nonprofits, and political clients.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>danny.walden@mail.house.gov (Hold These Truths with Dan Crenshaw)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">50567f47b9114850835d9def14c6b4cb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/50567f47b9114850835d9def14c6b4cb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 12:42:24 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Tim Pool Daily Show : Donald Trump Is WINNING His Fight With "The Swamp" And Putting DC Elites In Full On Panic Mode</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump Is WINNING His Fight With "The Swamp" And Putting DC Elites In Full On Panic Mode. Even before he was elected Trump was facing "swamp" opposition as dubious investigations jammed up his campaign.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But somehow Trump was able to win and since then has faced intense opposition from DC elites and the Democratic establishment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now with impeachment finally over and all the investigations done Trump and Bill Barr are moving to clean house and "drain the swamp." Whatever your view is on Trump it is clear that he is winning. None of the scandals have stuck, none of the investigations bore fruit, and now Bill Barr is making heavy moves at the DOJ for Mike Flynn and Roger Stone, Republicans are investigating the Biden's, and Trump has purged 70+ staff from the National Security Council.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is winning, "The Swamp" is being drained, and the Democrats are in the middle of a massive conflict with no clear winner in sight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="http://timcast.com/donate"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (http://timcast.com/donate)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tim@timcast.com (Tim Pool Daily Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">704b250e30d04a95a5f5daf502bfec3b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/704b250e30d04a95a5f5daf502bfec3b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>AM Joy : Legal experts question Barr’s independence from Trump</title><description>&lt;p&gt;William Barr’s possible impact on the Department of Justice, and the behavior of GOP senators who have supported Donald Trump, are analyzed by Joy Reid’s panel, including former GOP Congressman David Jolly who asserts, ‘There is no post-Trump Republican party for a generation.’ And: William Barr’s independence from Donald Trump is questioned by legal experts. Do some federal prosecutors fear reprisals under Barr’s Department of Justice related to cases with political implications? Joy Reid and her panel discuss. Then: William Barr’s role in the Trump administration is discussed by former federal prosecutor Cynthia Alksne who tells Joy Reid that in her view, ‘Barr has destroyed his reputation.’ Plus: Stop-and-frisk and its impact on young men of color when Michael Bloomberg was the mayor of New York City is discussed by Bloomberg 2020 co-chair Rep. Bobby Rush who tells Joy Reid that the 2020 Democratic presidential candidate seeks ‘atonement,’ adding, ‘I believe he's the only one right now who can defeat Donald Trump and that has to be our number one priority.’ All this and more in this Saturday edition of AM JOY on MSNBC.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (AM Joy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c11f072979ba4058a09bfc5007138991</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c11f072979ba4058a09bfc5007138991/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 11:13:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>KRDO Newsradio 105.5 FM • 1240 AM • 92.5 FM : The Agent with Antonio Briceno - February 15, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;-----------------------------------------------&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The health and life, insurance world is big &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; confusing.  Everybody needs insurance, but, it's hard to get unless you gotta guy and that guy is Antonio Briceno, "The Agent"!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Antonio's an independent licensed insurance agent.  He's contracted with "HealthMarkets" Insurance Agency.  The information he gives you on "The Agent" is general in nature, it's educational, it's not legal advice but it will help get you covered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://healthmarketsabriceno.fullslate.com/'&gt;Click and Book Your Appointment with "The Agent&lt;/a&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The Agent" with Antonio Briceno airs Saturdays at 11:30 a.m. only on KRDO Newsradio.  Listen live at KRDO.com and on-demand.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ted.robertson@krdo.com (KRDO Newsradio 105.5 FM • 1240 AM • 92.5 FM)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4fb15fb9a5ec4f369c7cbcdd8c29e0e3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4fb15fb9a5ec4f369c7cbcdd8c29e0e3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 11:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Lawfare Podcast : Patrick Radden Keefe on 'Say Nothing: A True Story of Murder and Memory in Northern Ireland'</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In 2013, Patrick Radden Keefe, a staff writer for the New Yorker, came across the &lt;a href= "https://www.nytimes.com/2013/01/26/world/europe/dolours-price-defiant-ira-bomber-dies-at-61.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;obituary&lt;/a&gt; of a woman named Dolours Price, a former member of the Irish Republican Army (IRA). Keefe's interest in Price led to sprawling research about an appalling crime that took place over the course of the three-decade Troubles in Northern Ireland: The disappearance of Jean McConville, a widowed young mother of ten children. His research led to his 2019 &lt;a href= "https://www.amazon.com/Say-Nothing-Murder-Northern-Ireland/dp/0385521316" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;book&lt;/a&gt;, “Say Nothing: A True Story of Murder and Memory in Northern Ireland.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Mikhaila Fogel sat down with Keefe to discuss his book, the shocking history of McConville’s disappearance, the broader context of the terrorism and counterterrorism campaigns in Northern Ireland over the course of the Troubles, and what happened to the perpetrators and the victims of this crime.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>benjamin.wittes@lawfareblog.com (The Lawfare Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">239ad8fd5a954caeb1d95e322b432de5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/239ad8fd5a954caeb1d95e322b432de5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>CNN News Briefing : Morning news briefing from CNN</title><description>https://www.cnn.com/videos/us/2020/02/15/daily-news-briefing-02152020-1.cnn &lt;a href="http://knit.audio/podcast-advertising"&gt;via Knit&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcast@turner.com (CNN News Briefing)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">641eff601bf74bf58403e24d8f454af9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/641eff601bf74bf58403e24d8f454af9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 06:29:37 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Up First : Saturday, February 15, 2020</title><description>Quarantined Americans to be evacuated from cruise ship in Japan, meanwhile a large number of health care workers in China test positive for coronavirus. Tension between President Trump and Attorney General Barr increases questions about independence of the Department of Justice.  U.S. officials at Munich Security Conference mostly quiet on US/Taliban Peace Agreement.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (Up First)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">230b2141e3ca457f9a0b26bd4453275b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/230b2141e3ca457f9a0b26bd4453275b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 04:49:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Rick &amp; Bubba University Podcast : Ep 19 | Behind the Scenes of College Football GameDay | Guest: Rece Davis</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, Rick &amp;amp; Bubba visit with ESPN College GameDay host Rece Davis and talk about his path from his childhood in Alabama to becoming the host of the most popular college football show. They discuss the dynamic of the College GameDay team and what it's like to host a show on location with the most passionate sports fans on the planet. Rick, Bubba, and Rece also break down the state of college football, including Rece's thoughts on the transfer portal, paying student-athletes, and the hirings of Mike Leach and Lane Kiffin into the SEC. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@theblaze.com (Rick &amp; Bubba University Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bd007b89cf8e4897930b08093468fd73</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bd007b89cf8e4897930b08093468fd73/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best of Coast to Coast AM : Coronavirus - Best of Coast to Coast AM - 2/14/20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Guest host Richard Syrett and an open lines caller explore some conspiracy theories linked to the coronavirus that originated in China and has spread across the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts@rsvmedia.com (The Best of Coast to Coast AM)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e67b11e8bfd44243b97e517fc246443d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e67b11e8bfd44243b97e517fc246443d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 02:58:48 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The FOX News Rundown : Fox News Rundown Extra: How Daytona 500 Pole-Sitter Driver Ricky Stenhouse Jr. Is Driven By 'Talladega Nights'</title><description>&lt;p&gt;When President Donald Trump appears at Sunday's, Ricky Stenhouse Jr. will be starting in the pole position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stenhouse Jr. has been racing in the NASCAR Cup Series for nine years and this weekend he'll be driving the number 47 Chevrolet Camaro.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this week, Fox News Rundown host Dave Anthony sat down with Stenhouse Jr. to discuss his career and how he was preparing for NASCAR's first and biggest race of the 2020 season. The superspeedway ace describes what it is like to drive 205 mph when you're just 'Inches' away from your competitors and how he's been practicing for this weekend's Daytona since he's been six-years-old.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the first time, you will hear our conversation Ricky Stenhouse Jr. on The Fox News Rundown Extra.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/FoxNewsRundown/~4/095E4zq7n3U" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>podcasts@foxnewsradio.com (The FOX News Rundown)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">695433aaac1c4f73ba002e9fec4a61be</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/695433aaac1c4f73ba002e9fec4a61be/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Glenn Beck Program : Ep 67 | I’m Not Sober, I’ve Just Learned to Deal with It | Mat Best | The Glenn Beck Podcast</title><description>&lt;p&gt;American war hero, CIA contractor, serial entrepreneur, and the face of the most freedom-filled coffee America has ever brewed. Black Rifle Coffee Company executive vice president Mat Best wasn’t always the bearded, gun-toting, whiskey-drinking war veteran YouTube has grown to love. In high school, he was a scrawny kid in the botany club! Glenn and Mat dive into his untold history, his years as an Army Ranger in Iraq and Afghanistan, and his mission to serve our veterans and help them overcome PTSD through comedy and community — not to mention plenty of caffeinated insight into coffee, filmmaking, and, of course, America, the Constitution, and being a patriot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This Week’s Sponsor:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ashford University gives you the convenience and flexibility to earn your master’s degree at your own pace!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Study wherever and whenever you’re the most comfortable learning, on a schedule that works for you. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enroll now at&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://ashford.edu/BECK"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;http://Ashford.edu/BECK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ccardon@blazemedia.com (The Glenn Beck Program)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ea6c4b91c93b4b68b0b2b3b3dafa756d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ea6c4b91c93b4b68b0b2b3b3dafa756d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>All In with Chris Hayes : BONUS: Protecting Trans Rights with Chase Strangio</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a bonus for All In listeners, Chris is sharing some of his favorite episodes of his original podcast, Why Is This Happening?, right here over the next few weekends. In this episode, he talks with Chase Strangio, a trans man and lawyer at the ACLU, about many of the complex factors at play in the fight for transgender rights.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Trump administration wants to legalize transgender discrimination in the workplace. This conversation breaks down how we reached this point. From the ways our social system constructs and uses gender, to the law and its limitations, to the political struggles within the LGBTQ community, Chase Strangio discusses many of the complex factors at play in the fight for transgender rights. A lawyer at the ACLU and a trans man himself, Strangio has been at the epicenter of the extremely high stakes battle for transgender people to receive equality and recognition. Right now, he is part of the legal team preparing to challenge the Trump administration before the Supreme Court, representing a woman fired for being trans.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Subscribe to Why Is This Happening? with Chris Hayes now:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.chtbl.com/cNMwXv_A?sid=partners" target="_blank"&gt;https://link.chtbl.com/cNMwXv_A?sid=partners&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (All In with Chris Hayes)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1068abe70cbe42319b63c96a048ee185</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1068abe70cbe42319b63c96a048ee185/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Amicus With Dahlia Lithwick | Law, Justice, and the Courts : Election Meltdown, Part 4</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In the fourth part of this special five-part series of Amicus, Dahlia Lithwick is joined by election law professor Rick Hasen and Professor Carol Anderson, Charles Howard Candler Professor of African American Studies at Emory University and author of &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/1635571391/?tag=slatmaga-20"&gt;&lt;em&gt;One Person, No Vote: How Voter Suppression is Destroying Our Democracy.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Together, they try to sort through the rhetoric and the reality of “stolen” elections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rick Hasen’s new book &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/0300248199/?tag=slatmaga-20"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Election Meltdown&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;forms the basis for this special series of Amicus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join Slate for the &lt;a href="https://slate.com/live/amicus-live-w-dahlia-lithwick-andrew-gillum-and-more.html"&gt;Election Meltdown live show&lt;/a&gt; on Feb. 19 in Washington. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Podcast production by Sara Burningham.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>amicus@slate.com (Amicus With Dahlia Lithwick | Law, Justice, and the Courts)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">959d5a9b2ed140629dc37a51030aecab</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/959d5a9b2ed140629dc37a51030aecab/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The 11th Hour with Brian Williams : Day 1,121: Trump's DOJ drops McCabe case, will have Flynn case investigated</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With Trump's influence in question, the department of Justice is having the case against Flynn investigated &amp;amp; the case against McCabe dropped. Plus Democrats continue to try to drum up support in Nevada and South Carolina ahead of the next round of voting. Joining us is Susan Page, Philip Rucker, Josh Gerstein, Frank Figliuzzi, Jonathan Allen, Errin Haines, Fred Kaplan, and Doris Kearns Goodwin.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (The 11th Hour with Brian Williams)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a07fc63b8b01487d931bc1946bd3b43d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a07fc63b8b01487d931bc1946bd3b43d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 21:29:35 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Last Word with Lawrence O’Donnell : Federal judge fears Trump involvement in DOJ cases could make U.S. a 'banana republic'</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Tonight on the Last Word: Accusations grow that Attorney General Bill Barr is using the Department of Justice to help Trump in criminal cases. Also, Fmr. Gov. Bill Weld joins Ali to discuss the growing crisis at the Justice Department and the current state of the GOP primary race. Plus, Michael Moore returns to discuss how strong Trump’s re-election chances are.&amp;nbsp;And Democratic voters share their thoughts on the state of the race in Nevada.&amp;nbsp;Neal Katyal, Zerlina Maxwell and Cristina Beltran also join Ali Velshi.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (The Last Word with Lawrence O’Donnell)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3e812a3ff12742d59beb3432fb84111b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3e812a3ff12742d59beb3432fb84111b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 21:18:50 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rachel Maddow Show : Rule of law is not threatened but broken where it involves Trump</title><description>&lt;p&gt;February 14, 2020&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (The Rachel Maddow Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bae2932dfce24519a772b567bc25899c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bae2932dfce24519a772b567bc25899c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 20:14:27 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mark Levin Podcast : Mark Levin Audio Rewind - 2/14/20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On Friday's Mark Levin Show, FDR sought the death penalty for several Germans before they were even tried. President Trump has merely questioned the length of a prison sentence of Roger Stone, by way of a tweet and the media fails to realize that Trump's right to ask a question is a constitutional matter of fact called a unitary executive power. This is what FDR employed when he assembled secret tribunals to execute German spies in 1942. Then, some things have been said about Rush Limbaugh that are despicable. The left is mad that Rush got the medal of Freedom so they've reverted to what they do best — destruction. They're going after him for a comment about Pete Buttigieg and a potential public display of affection with his husband. Later, Bernie Sanders and the Democrats continue to harp on racism, sexism and other types of Marxist ism's. Plus, disgraced FBI Deputy Director Andrew McCabe is walking free after his soft coup attempt, despite his lies and all the public information the government felt they didn't have a solid case. This doesn't even come close to what Roger Stone is accused of, yet they want to give him 7-9 years. Afterward, the media’s favorite lawyer Michael Avenatti was found guilty of extorting Nike and several clients including Stormy Daniels.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wwopodcasts@westwoodone.com (Mark Levin Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">45fd4d4b11ba4bd09b93151d749c2934</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/45fd4d4b11ba4bd09b93151d749c2934/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 18:24:31 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Gist : Why Iran-Contra Hardly Rings a Bell</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On the Gist, the Houston Astros cheating scandal is like the US Democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mike and former host of Slow Burn, and current host of Luminary Podcast network's &lt;a href="https://luminarypodcasts.com/listen/leon-neyfakh/fiasco-luminary-premium/8607a31a-cab7-4c9f-9df8-b6110ba93b52"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fiasco&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; Leon Neyfakh get into the details of the Iran-Contra Affair. They discuss the key players in the saga, why this story was such a fiasco and the new Slow Burn TV-show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the spiel, let's just go with Caucus debacle avoidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thegist@slate.com (The Gist)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f3c76af068634dbebf9a92c7b8bf614e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f3c76af068634dbebf9a92c7b8bf614e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 17:50:49 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Stu Does America : Ep 5 | Stu Does Woke Racism | Guest: Pat Gray</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Stu does… woke racism! The Left is constantly bragging about how woke and against racism they are… while simultaneously being extremely unwoke and racist at the same time. Liberals. Go figure. And Pat Gray makes his grand — and first — appearance on the program to talk about the return of his acclaimed series, "Leakages."&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ccardon@blazemedia.com (Stu Does America)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">95274e9ec4f84c6e9bba661bc1efb762</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/95274e9ec4f84c6e9bba661bc1efb762/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Left, Right &amp; Center : From impeachment acquittal to taking revenge</title><description>&lt;p&gt;President Trump is on a revenge tour, firing administration officials who cooperated with the impeachment probe, using Twitter to rail against the prosecutions of his allies, and demanding to know why the Justice Department doesn't prosecute more of his enemies. Attorney General William Barr says he wants the president to back off and stop tweeting, but Barr has also been taking extraordinary interventions in criminal cases of interest to the president.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then: Bernie Sanders won the New Hampshire primary but with the smallest vote share ever for a New Hampshire winner. Will the Democratic field ever winnow? Is there a real possibility of a contested convention? Is it Mike Bloomberg's fault? Are all the candidates being too nice to each other? Speaking of Bloomberg, he's soaring in the national polls on the back of an enormous television campaign, and speaking of being too nice, should we be seeing more attack ads? Erika Franklin Fowler of the Wesleyan Media Project talks about the power of those ads and whether they make a difference for voters.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@kcrw.org (Left, Right &amp; Center)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d0d3835d259d487eafcff9c733fb3b5c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d0d3835d259d487eafcff9c733fb3b5c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 16:24:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Deadline: White House : "We start staring at the trees and we lose the forest"</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Nicolle Wallace discusses attorney general Bill Barr reopening the investigation intro Trump's former national security adviser Michael Flynn. Plus, the DOJ drops its case against former FBI deputy director Andrew McCabe, Trump using the Justice Department for his political gain, and Bernie Sanders sets his sights on Super Tuesday.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joined by: Washington Post reporter Matt Zapotosky, NBC News correspondent Carol Lee, former U.S. attorney Joyce Vance, former chief spokesman for the Department of Justice Matt Miller, GOP strategist Rick Wilson, politics editor for The Daily Beast Sam Stein, NBC News' Shaquille Brewster, politics editor for The Root Jason Johnson, and national editor for The Cook Political Report Amy Walter &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (Deadline: White House)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6dd2c58443eb48a89e890dd53501f2d2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6dd2c58443eb48a89e890dd53501f2d2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 15:10:43 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Savage Nation Podcast : San Francisco Public Library's Most Commonly Stolen Book: Liberalism is a Mental Disorder by Savage</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Savage's book &lt;em&gt;Liberalism is a Mental Disorder&lt;/em&gt; is the most commonly stolen book in San Francisco's public library.  Other news of the day; Michael Avenatti found guilty in his Nike extortion case; Bernie Sanders wants to legalize sex workers and create a federal jobs program, more reasons he cannot become President; Savage reads from his book and considers an updated version.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/most-commonly-stolen-book-library-Michael-Savage-15045259.php"&gt;https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/most-commonly-stolen-book-library-Michael-Savage-15045259.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wwopodcasts@westwoodone.com (The Savage Nation Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b760d5b32eea43338bc909e123796997</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b760d5b32eea43338bc909e123796997/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 14:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WSJ What’s News : States Reject Massive Opioid Settlement Offer</title><description>P.M. Edition for February 14th: State attorneys general reject drug distributors' $18 billion opioid-addiction settlement plan. The Wall Street Journal's Jared S. Hopkins discusses why. Plus, the WSJ's Natalie Andrews on how Democrats plan to defend their control of the House of Representatives. Charlie Turner hosts.&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@dowjones.com (WSJ What’s News)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4a992238c6fa4fb9a73355802206eaf4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4a992238c6fa4fb9a73355802206eaf4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 14:23:52 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ricochet Podcast : 483. Everybody Must Get Stone</title><description>Yeah, it another really busy week in the Ricochet Podcast Extended Universe (or as we like to call it, RIPEU, or repoo): we had a primary, some candidates drop out the race, we had a former Trump campaign advisor sentencing blow up into a fight between the President and his Attorney General. But we decided [&amp;#8230;]</description><author>support@ricochet.com (Ricochet Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f06a503975814ee3a2701b13d2a8c77f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f06a503975814ee3a2701b13d2a8c77f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 13:42:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Skimm This : I’m Not Gonna Write You A Love Song: The US and Iran...and Switzerland?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As the coronavirus continues to spread, one of the affected groups has been healthcare workers on the frontlines in China. We’ll dive into how a vaccine could be on the horizon, but still has a long way to go. Then: the Senate votes to rein in President Trump’s power to conduct military strikes in Iran. As tensions increase between the US and Iran, an unlikely middleman is helping the two countries work out their issues and bring much needed humanitarian aid to the Iranian people. Also on the show: why the US government wants to remind you on Valentine’s Day … to take things slow. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>skimmthis@theskimm.com (Skimm This)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7fa993e026a04612a4292f2ee0707498</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7fa993e026a04612a4292f2ee0707498/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 13:38:23 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Get 2 the Point : Tim Hanna:  What next for Appleton Mayor</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On April 7, voters in the city of Appleton will elect a new mayor, the first new one in 24 years.  When the mayor-elect is sworn in on April 21, current mayor Tim Hanna will find himself out of that job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our Get 2 the Point podcast conversation with Mayor Hanna continues this week, as Hanna looks back at his career in government. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tmiller@wbay.com (Get 2 the Point)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">affa21481963468ab459d63cbd7a7fb5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/affa21481963468ab459d63cbd7a7fb5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 13:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The News &amp; Why It Matters : Ep 470 | Safe, Legal, and WHERE’D the Abortion Limits Go?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The days of safe, legal, and rare abortions are fading, and not in the good way. A Colorado House panel just killed a bill that would mandate that babies born alive after failed abortions receive medical care. And the 2020 Democrats have made it clear that there’s no room in the party for pro-lifers. Bernie Sanders now leads the pack after a Morning Consult poll ranked him ten points ahead of Joe Biden. And while Michael Bloomberg looks promising, could he last as a front-runner with all the problems on his hands?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today's Sponsors:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PARLER is the news and free speech app that won’t silence your opinion or violate your privacy for financial gain. Go to https://parler.com/auth/access or check it out in the app store.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The FBI calls home title theft one of the fastest-growing white-collar crimes. Go to https://www.hometitlelock.com/ and register your address to see if you’re already a victim and don’t know it. Then sign up to help protect the legal title to your home with 60-day risk-free protection.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tcardon@glennbeck.com (The News &amp; Why It Matters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e121c32ad0ae4e8fac7fdc699a69bab9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e121c32ad0ae4e8fac7fdc699a69bab9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 13:05:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WSJ Opinion: Potomac Watch : Barr Takes on Trump's Roger Stone Tweets</title><description>Barr takes on Trump's Roger Stone tweets&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@dowjones.com (WSJ Opinion: Potomac Watch)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">28e47c695a5f4b26bead2543e4046025</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/28e47c695a5f4b26bead2543e4046025/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 13:00:49 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Yorker Radio Hour : Bernie Sanders Ascends, and a High School Simulates the Election</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bernie Sanders’s win in New Hampshire has established him as the Democratic Presidential front-runner. Centrist Democrats regard him not as a challenge but more like an existential threat: they assume that only a moderate—and certainly not a democratic socialist—can sway critical swing voters and win in November. Are they right? David Remnick speaks with Keith Ellison, the Minnesota Attorney General who served as co-chair of the Democratic National Committee after that organization infamously tried to spike Sanders’s candidacy in 2016. Ellison says that the clarity of Sanders’s mission and his appeal to economic problems can win over struggling voters in both parties. Then Nathaniel Rakich, a pollster for FiveThirtyEight, presents what the data indicates about Sanders’s chances. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Plus, a civics project goes off the rails when high-school students run a simulation of the 2020 primaries. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (The New Yorker Radio Hour)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7fcf1b5ad9754c01b41fa9aad32a4cf8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7fcf1b5ad9754c01b41fa9aad32a4cf8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 13:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Daily Detroit : Michael Zadoorian On His New Book, "The Narcissism Of Small Differences"</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Ferndale Author Michael Zadoorian joins us to talk about his new book "The Narcissism of Small Differences," that beyond being a good book also has lots of little nods to Metro Detroit. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Pre-order here: &lt;a href= "https://www.amazon.com/Narcissism-Small-Differences-Michael-Zadoorian/dp/1617758175"&gt; https://www.amazon.com/Narcissism-Small-Differences-Michael-Zadoorian/dp/1617758175&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"For anyone who's ever asked themselves, 'Am I weird?' Michael Zadoorian has the answer: 'Of course you are. That's the whole idea.' While everyone is trying so hard to act normal, The Narcissism of Small Differences revels in its own weirdness." --Ben Folds, New York Times best-selling author/singer-songwriter&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>dailydetroit@gmail.com (Daily Detroit)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0b51721a277b4476a5dddcc3b33d5f09</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0b51721a277b4476a5dddcc3b33d5f09/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 12:29:45 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>What Next | Daily News and Analysis : Introducing: The United States of Anxiety</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Every so often, the What Next team wants to share another great podcast with our listeners. This time, it's The United States of Anxiety from WNYC. In its fourth season, host Kai Wright is figuring out how the intense debates happening during the 2020 election can be traced back to a key point in American history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To listen to the rest of the episodes, subscribe wherever you get your podcasts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tj.raphael@slate.com (What Next | Daily News and Analysis)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5629c3ac686e42d4a5486ffe3120f38a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5629c3ac686e42d4a5486ffe3120f38a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Buck Sexton Show : Deep State McCabe Gets Off</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Season 4, Episode 32.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AG Barr wants Trump to Tweet less, continued fallout of the Roger Stone sentencing, Dems want to impeach the AG, Bernie's lead, and no punishment for McCabe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>teambuck@iheartmedia.com (The Buck Sexton Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">14c8961dd0ec483d9381b74914a51abe</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/14c8961dd0ec483d9381b74914a51abe/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 11:38:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Matt Walsh Show : Ep. 426 - The Absurdity Of The Equal Rights Amendment</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Democrats in Congress are trying to revive the Equal Rights Amendment, which supposedly will guarantee equal rights for women in America. The problem is that women already have equal rights, so what will this amendment really do? We'll talk about it. Also, are people who recline their seats on airplanes sociopaths? We discuss. And I answer emails from some listeners who think I'm a bad Christian for saying that we should teach our children to fight back against bullies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out The Cold War: What We Saw, a new podcast written and presented by Bill Whittle at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar&lt;/a&gt;. In Part 1 we peel back the layers of mystery cloaking the Terror state run by the Kremlin, and watch as America takes its first small steps onto the stage of world leadership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like The Matt Walsh Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: WALSH and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/Walsh"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/Walsh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mattwalshshow@dailywire.com (The Matt Walsh Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">baf97e42c46448e495aecae2c4eb63ec</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/baf97e42c46448e495aecae2c4eb63ec/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 10:27:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bannon's War Room : Special Ep 17- War Room: Pandemic, Alex Azar Won't Rule Out Coronavirus Link to Bio-Weapon (w/ Senator Tom Cotton)</title><description>Steve Bannon, Jack Maxey and Dr. Steven Hatfill discuss the validity of China's reporting on the coronavirus outbreak. Calling in is Senator Tom Cotton who also questions China's relationship with the facts.</description><author>admin@citizensoftheamericanrepublic.org (Bannon's War Room)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">933259f7b8ba4f1c97badf350731de28</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/933259f7b8ba4f1c97badf350731de28/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 10:11:34 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Two-Minute Briefing : The Evening Briefing: Friday February 14</title><description>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Heathrow scare: Passenger falls ill on flight from San Francisco - live updates http://bit.ly/2u24jUG |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Two MPs self-isolate: Pair cancel public engagements after attending conference with virus sufferer http://bit.ly/2Sps6al |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cruise ship joy: Jubilant passengers finally depart after two weeks stuck at sea&amp;nbsp;http://bit.ly/2vxR4eG |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;'Transphobic' tweets: Judge rules police interfered with ex-officer's freedom of speech http://bit.ly/3bIKS4n |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solskjaer under fire: Manager 'not fit to lead' Man Utd, says woman at centre of Norway rape case involving ex-player http://bit.ly/2Hovegr |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rape case: Questions we put to Man Utd that they did not answer http://bit.ly/2OUcfyt |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Storm Dennis: Hundreds of homes at risk as flooding to hit Britain http://bit.ly/2uCCkLH |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prince Andrew at 60: How did Queen's 'favourite' son fall so spectacularly from grace? http://bit.ly/2UTHfTc |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read all these articles with a digital Telegraph subscription - from £2 per week. Sign up here: http://bit.ly/2WRuvh9. If you're enjoying my audio briefings, please consider encouraging others to sign up for FREE here: http://bit.ly/2XxhVAI.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@telegraph.co.uk (The Two-Minute Briefing)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0cf67fd1d7724aaa9e49fbbcaaded378</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0cf67fd1d7724aaa9e49fbbcaaded378/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 10:01:22 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ticket: Politics from The Atlantic : A Historic Vote on Equal Rights, and Hopes for Gun Control</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, Congresswoman Jennifer Wexton presided over debate on a bill to advance the Equal Rights Amendment. After the bill passed, she sat down in her office with Isaac Dovere to discuss the historic ERA vote and how she thinks Congress can take action on gun violence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also on the show: thoughts on New Hampshire and an exclusive exchange with Andrew Yang, recorded as he prepared to announce the end of his candidacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcastproduct@theatlantic.com (The Ticket: Politics from The Atlantic)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ec00ea53e3c441fda14f1c2a9e2dabdb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ec00ea53e3c441fda14f1c2a9e2dabdb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 09:38:23 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ben Shapiro Show : Ep. 954 - Donald, Barr The Door</title><description>Attorney General Barr speaks out against Trump’s twitter logorrhea, Trump goes after former chief of staff John Kelly, and Biden turns on Bloomberg.

Check out The Cold War: What We Saw, a new podcast written and presented by Bill Whittle at  https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar. In Part 1 we peel back the layers of mystery cloaking the Terror state run by the Kremlin, and watch as America takes its first small steps onto the stage of world leadership.

If you like The Ben Shapiro Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: SHAPIRO and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at https://www.dailywire.com/Shapiro</description><author>benshapiroshow@dailywire.com (The Ben Shapiro Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">51319c16206d4b14847189910e3f23d9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/51319c16206d4b14847189910e3f23d9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 09:28:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Erick Erickson Show : #EERS S9 Ep28: Bill Barr’s Valentine to Trump</title><description>Today on the show Valentine's day is awful, AG Barr speaks out, Bernie is burning down the party, a star might blow up any day, Mayor Pete apparently isn't gay enough, Stars and Stripes gets cut and a coronavirus update.</description><author>erick@theresurgent.com (The Erick Erickson Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a76f1d04f36b4666945455f27c7b81a4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a76f1d04f36b4666945455f27c7b81a4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 09:19:30 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dan Bongino Show : The Media Fell Right Into the Trap (Ep 1181)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, I address the bombshell Spygate article dropped by The NY Times and the subsequent head-fake interview given by Attorney General Barr. Don&amp;rsquo;t fall for the nonsense, Barr knew exactly what he was doing. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;News Picks:Breaking: &lt;a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/durham-reportedly-investigating-whether-cia-withheld-information-from-fbi-in-russia-probe_3237947.html"&gt;John Durham is investigating&lt;/a&gt; whether John Brennan&amp;rsquo;s CIA misled the FBI in the Russia probe.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attorney General Barr says &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/impossible-for-me-to-do-my-job-barr-wishes-trump-would-stop-tweeting-about-doj"&gt;he wishes Trump would stop tweeting&lt;/a&gt; about DOJ cases.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Democrat shows up at a Trump rally and is &lt;a href="https://medium.com/@karlyn/ive-been-a-democrat-for-20-years-here-s-what-i-experienced-at-trump-s-rally-in-new-hampshire-c69ddaaf6d07"&gt;stunned at what she finds&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bongino.com/as-sanders-rises-democrats-panic-about-losing-house-majority/"&gt;The rise of Bernie Sanders&lt;/a&gt; has the Democrats in a panic.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://dailycaller.com/2020/02/13/roger-stone-jury-selection/"&gt;More devastating information&lt;/a&gt; about the lead juror in the Roger Stone case.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/analysis-hope-hicks-return-part-of-trump-embrace-of-loyalists-as-he-rebuilds-post-impeachment"&gt;Hope Hicks&lt;/a&gt; returns to the White House.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Copyright Dan Bongino All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@bongino.com (The Dan Bongino Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7799f370713e4c63a6c7f8e41e753d66</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7799f370713e4c63a6c7f8e41e753d66/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 09:17:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>On the Media : Norm!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Attorney General Bill Barr appeared to spar with Donald Trump in the latest chapter of the Roger Stone case. On this week’s On the Media, why the apparent interference in the Justice Department’s work should cause concern. Plus, Customs and Border Patrol builds a new bulwark against disclosure and transparency. And, a family migration story three decades in the making. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/author/dahlia-lithwick"&gt;Dahlia Lithwick&lt;/a&gt;, writer for Slate, on what the latest Dept. of Justice news tells us about the fragility of American justice. &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/otm/segments/role-stone-on-the-media"&gt;Listen.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Susan Hennessey [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Susan_Hennessey"&gt;@Susan_Hennessey&lt;/a&gt;], executive editor at Lawfare, on the latest threats to "prosecutorial independence." &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/otm/segments/goodbye-sweet-norms"&gt;Listen.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Ken Klippenstein [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/kenklippenstein"&gt;@kenklippenstein&lt;/a&gt;], DC correspondent at &lt;em&gt;The Nation&lt;/em&gt;, on Customs and Border Patrol (CBP)'s re-designation as a "security agency." &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/otm/segments/cbps-new-secrecy-protections"&gt;Listen.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. Jason DeParle [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/JasonDeParle"&gt;@JasonDeParle&lt;/a&gt;], author of &lt;em&gt;A Good Provider Is One Who Leaves&lt;/em&gt;, on the 32-year process of reporting one family's migration story. &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/otm/segments/family-migration-on-the-media"&gt;Listen.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Music from this week's show:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In The Bath — Randy Newman&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Artifact &amp;amp; Living — Michael Andrews&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;String Quartet No. 5 — Philip Glass, performed by Kronos Quartet&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Glass House - Marjanes's Inspiration — David Bergeaud&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Frail as a Breeze, Pt. 2 — Erik Friedlander&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Thompson Fields — Maria Schneider &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (On the Media)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7555a352a34e41dfb651b18c5a671175</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7555a352a34e41dfb651b18c5a671175/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill O’Reilly’s No Spin News and Analysis : The O'Reilly Update, February 14, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With Iowa and New Hampshire in the rearview and 55 more contests to go, the search for the Democratic nominee remains mostly &lt;em&gt;unclear&lt;/em&gt;… &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@www.billoreilly.com (Bill O’Reilly’s No Spin News and Analysis)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">45f769df7b464b809d8e2239553bf84e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/45f769df7b464b809d8e2239553bf84e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 08:45:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Checks and Balance : Checks and Balance: The Trump pay bump</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amid the drama of impeachment and the Democrats' first primaries, President Trump expanded the list of mostly Muslim nationalities restricted from travel to the US. A hard line on immigration will be a big part of his reelection pitch. He’ll make the link between stronger borders and a booming economy. It turns orthodox economics on its head, but recent data on rising wages will help the president make his case. Might the wall be good economics after all? Callum Williams, senior economics writer, joins Checks and Balance host John Prideaux. Charlotte Howard and Jon Fasman also join to examine the electoral power of Trump’s record on immigration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pete Buttigieg speaks to Economist Asks&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/21/which-democrats-can-challenge-donald-trump" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/21/which-democrats-can-challenge-donald-trump&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.economist.com/pod2020" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.economist.com/pod2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>radio@economist.com (Checks and Balance)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">be1d40b99d0e4cc2a14eaa7f9705313d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/be1d40b99d0e4cc2a14eaa7f9705313d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 08:21:46 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Marketplace Morning Report : Millennials’ Hallmark moment</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The U.S. charges Huawei with racketeering, accusing it of stealing trade secrets. But how can a law meant to target gangsters work against the Chinese tech giant? Plus, young people are making greeting cards cool again.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>MorningReportComments@marketplace.org (Marketplace Morning Report)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fc129d6087db4caaa2e50f73d7016be3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fc129d6087db4caaa2e50f73d7016be3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 08:00:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>CBS This Morning - News on the Go : 2/14: Attorney General Barr says Mr. Trump’s Twitter habits make his job “impossible.” CDC says 15 people in the U.S. have contracted coronavirus.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In an extraordinary critique of the President's Twitter habits, the Attorney General William Barr&amp;nbsp;says Mr. Trump is making it impossible for him to do his job. Democratic presidential hopeful Mike Bloomberg is facing new attacks from rivals on what they see as one of his biggest vulnerabilities. A major cleanup is underway after a train partially derailed in Kentucky following a rockslide. The coronavirus outbreak in China is growing by thousands of cases a day, while the CDC says 15 people in the U.S. have now contracted the illness. We have a tragic update to a story we've been following about a six-year-old girl who disappeared in South Carolina. Newly-released police video raises disturbing new questions about why school officials held a six-year-old girl in a mental health facility for two days.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>CBSNetworkRadioNewsWeb@cbsnews.com (CBS This Morning - News on the Go)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">80469a738f4f4faf940661244ffcd399</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/80469a738f4f4faf940661244ffcd399/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 07:51:17 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Benjamin Dixon Show : Episode 811 | Welcome to the Roughnecks. Bernie's Roughnecks.</title><description>nothing to say but, "let's go."</description><author>thebpdshow@gmail.com (The Benjamin Dixon Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">deb8874f1b1d4b3ca9ccad9e52642da6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/deb8874f1b1d4b3ca9ccad9e52642da6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 05:33:01 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Morning Joe : Morning Joe 2/14/20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The president on Thursday tweeted that the forewoman of the federal jury that heard the case against Roger Stone had 'significant bias.' The panel discusses Trump's weighing in on the Stone case.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (Morning Joe)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5cd30d749d4e458492b3f5de72543a9b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5cd30d749d4e458492b3f5de72543a9b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 05:12:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Election 2020: Updates from The Washington Post : Trump allies are starting to focus attention on Pete Buttigieg’s sexual orientation</title><description>From "The Daily 202" podcast: Rush Limbaugh, a week after receiving the Presidential Medal of Freedom during the State of the Union, questioned on his show whether Americans are ready for a gay presidential candidate who kisses his husband onstage.</description><author>jessica.stahl@washpost.com (Election 2020: Updates from The Washington Post)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">03e16c7c6e5f44f5ae6970c492dcf70a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/03e16c7c6e5f44f5ae6970c492dcf70a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 05:04:21 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Daily 202's Big Idea : Why Bill Barr really rebuked President Trump</title><description>Attorney General Bill Barr pushed back last night against Trump’s attacks on the Justice Department. The remarkable public rebuke of the president by a sitting member of the cabinet arose from a crisis of confidence at the Justice Department.</description><author>jessica.stahl@washpost.com (The Daily 202's Big Idea)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f2ad0755dafb4773ae3b381b0bcbe103</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f2ad0755dafb4773ae3b381b0bcbe103/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 04:59:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>RTÉ - Today with Sean O'Rourke : The Gathering</title><description>Colette Browne, Irish Independent Columnist, Anne Rabbitte, Fianna Fail TD Galway East, Brian Hayes, CEO of the Banking and Payments Federation, Matt Carthy, New Sinn Fein TD for Cavan Monaghan</description><author>radio.player@rte.ie (RTÉ - Today with Sean O'Rourke)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">99c13e3f9133488eabc1a5992942ea92</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/99c13e3f9133488eabc1a5992942ea92/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Sky News Daily : Is China's response to COVID-19 too little too late? | 14 February 2020</title><description>On this edition of the Sky News Daily podcast with Dermot Murnaghan we examine the Chinese response to the coronavirus outbreak and look at the story of a doctor who tried to warn the world about it last year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dr Li Wenliang later died after contracting the virus himself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also speak to a journalist from Beijing about her own personal experience of being a Chinese national in the UK.</description><author>radio@sky.uk (Sky News Daily)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">966f47457caa4ac9b13f7fbf7c9bbd15</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/966f47457caa4ac9b13f7fbf7c9bbd15/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 03:58:50 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Baltimore Sun : Baltimore Sun - Feb. 13</title><description>Good morning. The forecast today in Baltimore is mostly sunny with a high of about 36 and a low tonight around 19. I'm Sam Scholl and here are the top headlines from the Baltimore Sun for Friday, February 14th. Federal prosecutors are seeking to send former Baltimore Mayor Catherine Pugh to prison for almost five years when she is sentenced later this month for conspiracy and tax evasion.</description><author>distribution@spokenlayer.com (Baltimore Sun)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7c3ad91519b14a9a88532aabbe8cd76d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7c3ad91519b14a9a88532aabbe8cd76d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 03:03:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Houston Matters : Friday’s Show: Compensation For Reservoir Damages, And Your Worst Date (Feb. 14, 2020)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On Friday's Houston Matters: A judge says the federal government is to blame for houses and businesses that flooded upstream of the Addicks and Barker Reservoirs. So how much should homeowners be compensated? Also this hour: In celebration of Valentine's Day, Houstonians share stories of their worst dating experiences. Then, we break down The Good, The Bad, and The Ugly of the week's news. And we broadcast live from Interfaith Ministries' Meals on Wheels deliveries.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@houstonpublicmedia.org (Houston Matters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e01e5285586147dd83918b3da1216ab2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e01e5285586147dd83918b3da1216ab2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 03:00:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Intelligence : Another man’s Treasury: Britain’s cabinet upheaval</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The dramatic departure of the head of the Treasury reveals Prime Minister Boris Johnson’s desire—and that of his wily chief aide—to take firm hold of the country’s purse strings. A new book finds that a landmark study in psychiatry was not at all what it seemed. And the thumping changes going on in Berlin’s club scene.&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For full access to print, digital and audio editions of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;, subscribe here &lt;a href="http://www.economist.com/radiooffer" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.economist.com/radiooffer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Additional audio “Dustbin Acid (Super Rhythm Trax)” courtesy Jerome Hill&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>radio@economist.com (The Intelligence)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d14ba9e4bf5a4c4496b7071874f2e20d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d14ba9e4bf5a4c4496b7071874f2e20d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 03:00:15 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Relatable with Allie Beth Stuckey : Ep 213 | Pop Culture Sans Propaganda</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Alex Clark, host of Turning Point USA's "POPlitics" on IGTV, talks about her journey from being the lone conservative voice on a morning radio program to occupying a unique space in the conservative movement: commenting on popular culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BOLSTER SLEEP&lt;/strong&gt;: Visit https://bolstersleep.com/ - use promo code 'ALLIE' to save 15% off your entire purchase. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ccardon@glennbeck.com (Relatable with Allie Beth Stuckey)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7a5fcac614aa442da1c04a5f41cb5b53</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7a5fcac614aa442da1c04a5f41cb5b53/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Daily : The Post-Acquittal Presidency</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Since his acquittal in the Senate, President Trump has undertaken a campaign of retribution against those who crossed him during the impeachment inquiry — while extending favors to those who have tried to protect him. Today, we explore what has happened so far in this new phase of his presidency. Guest: &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker?smid=pc-thedaily?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt;Peter Baker&lt;/a&gt;, the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times. For more information on today’s episode, visit nytimes.com/thedaily.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background reading:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mr. Trump called those who testified against him in the impeachment&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/06/us/politics/trump-impeachment.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; “evil,” “corrupt” and “crooked.”&lt;/a&gt; After he was acquitted, he &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/07/us/politics/alexander-vindman-gordon-sondland-fired.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt;began firing witnesses&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A handful of senators reached out to the White House to warn the president not to dismiss Gordon D. Sondland, the ambassador to the European Union who testified in the House hearings.&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/08/us/politics/trump-vindman-sondland-fired.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; Mr. Trump removed him anyway&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (The Daily)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">062255e8450e4e5ba8ec8964dcae097c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/062255e8450e4e5ba8ec8964dcae097c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 02:51:14 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Start Here : Does This Clear the Barr?</title><description>In an exclusive interview with ABC News, Attorney General William Barr criticizes the president for inserting himself in the Roger Stone case. A judge halts a massive Pentagon technology project over concerns that Amazon lost the bid because of a Trump beef. And after a year of widespread wildfires, a tribe in the Amazon goes to war -- literally -- with the illegal logging industry.
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt; Like the show? Leave a review: http://bit.ly/ReviewStartHere &lt;p&gt; Follow @StartHereABC for exclusive content, show updates and more:&lt;br&gt; - Twitter: https://www.twitter.com/starthereabc&lt;br&gt; - Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/starthereabc&lt;br&gt; - Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/starthereabc &lt;p&gt; Discover more ABC News podcasts: http://www.abcnewspodcasts.com &lt;p&gt; Start Here is produced by ABC Audio. For more information: http://www.abcnewspodcasts.com</description><author>abc.podcast.support@abc.com (Start Here)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">171a5f8598f140c4b79e71438ee8c5b7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/171a5f8598f140c4b79e71438ee8c5b7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 02:30:16 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>the NewsWorthy : AG Pushback, Pentagon Contract &amp; Uber’s Phone Number - Friday, February 14th, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The news to know for Friday, February 14th, 2020! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What to know today about some unexpected comments from the U.S. attorney general, and why the Pentagon, Microsoft and Amazon are all going to court.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Plus: why Uber has a new 1-800 number, the planned tribute at this weekend's all-star game, and Happy Valentine's Day!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Those stories and more in less than 10 minutes!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Award-winning broadcast journalist and former TV news reporter Erica Mandy breaks it all down for you. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Head to &lt;a href= "http://www.thenewsworthy.com/"&gt;www.theNewsWorthy.com&lt;/a&gt; or see sources below to read more about any of the stories mentioned today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This episode is brought to you by &lt;a href= "http://www.Rothys.com/newsworthy"&gt;www.Rothys.com/newsworthy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em style= "font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;"&gt; Become a NewsWorthy INSIDER! Learn more here: &lt;a href= "http://www.TheNewsWorthy.com/insider"&gt;www.TheNewsWorthy.com/insider&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sources:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="margin: 0in; margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;em&gt; Attorney General’s Frustrations: &lt;a href= "https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/barr-blasts-trumps-tweets-stone-case-impossible-job/story?id=68963276"&gt;   ABC News&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.wsj.com/articles/attorney-general-says-tweets-make-it-impossible-for-me-to-do-my-job-11581628588?mod=hp_lead_pos3"&gt;   WSJ&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.foxnews.com/politics/bill-barr-trump-tweets-roger-stone"&gt;   FOX News&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/13/us/politics/william-barr-trump.html?action=click&amp;module=Top%20Stories&amp;pgtype=Homepage"&gt;   NYT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="margin: 0in; margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;em&gt; War Powers Resolution: &lt;a href= "https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/13/politics/war-powers-resolution-vote-senate-iran/index.html"&gt;   CNN&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/senate-poised-pass-resolution-curb-trumps-war-authority/story?id=68943735&amp;cid=clicksource_4380645_2_heads_hero_live_hero_hed"&gt;   ABC News&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://apnews.com/6286252716f16d09c23451cf95443c6f"&gt;  AP&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.npr.org/2020/02/13/805594383/senate-approves-legislation-to-limit-presidents-war-powers-against-iran"&gt;   NPR&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="margin: 0in; margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;em&gt; Hope Hicks Returns: &lt;a href= "https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/hope-hicks-returning-trump-s-white-house-n1136331"&gt;   NBC News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="margin: 0in; margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;em&gt; US vs. Huawei: &lt;a href= "https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-02-13/u-s-adds-racketeering-conspiracy-charge-against-huawei"&gt;   Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinas-huawei-charged-with-racketeering-11581618336"&gt;   WSJ&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/newsbeat-47041341"&gt;  BBC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="margin: 0in; margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;em&gt; Pentagon, Microsoft &amp; Amazon in Court: &lt;a href= "https://www.wsj.com/articles/federal-court-orders-pentagon-to-halt-controversial-jedi-cloud-contract-11581622049"&gt;   WSJ&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.reuters.com/article/us-amazon-com-pentagon/judge-grants-amazon-bid-to-pause-microsofts-pentagon-contract-work-idUSKBN2072P6"&gt;   Reuters&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.axios.com/pentagon-microsoft-judge-blocks-amazon-e4624833-45c9-4613-a59e-fe3211f8faac.html"&gt;   Axios&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="margin: 0in; margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;em&gt; Hottest January on Record: &lt;a href= "https://www.nbcnews.com/science/environment/earth-just-had-its-hottest-january-recorded-history-n1136426"&gt;   NBC News&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://weather.com/news/climate/news/2020-02-13-january-global-temperatures-warmest-on-record-noaa-climate-report"&gt;   Weather Channel&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://apnews.com/bcba86be0c35b42bc65d2205db1aa6e2"&gt;  AP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="margin: 0in; margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;em&gt; Zillow Fights Homelessness: &lt;a href= "https://www.engadget.com/2020/02/13/zillow-search-tool-housing-need-homeless-housing-connector/"&gt;   Engadget&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.geekwire.com/2020/zillow-launches-tool-help-seattleites-exiting-homelessness-find-affordable-housing/"&gt;   Geekwire&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="margin: 0in; margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;em&gt; Uber’s 1-800 Number: &lt;a href= "https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/13/tech/uber-1-800-number-arizona/index.html"&gt;   CNN&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://techcrunch.com/2020/02/13/dial-an-uber-lets-users-talk-to-an-actual-human-to-hail-a-ride/"&gt;   TechCrunch&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.theverge.com/2020/2/13/21136090/uber-1800-phone-number-no-apps-smartphone"&gt;   The Verge&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="margin: 0in; margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;em&gt; NBA All-Star Game: &lt;a href= "https://www.si.com/nba/2020/02/12/nba-all-star-game-jerseys-honor-kobe-bryant-gianna-david-stern"&gt;   Sports Illustrated&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.nba.com/article/2020/02/13/commercial-free-fourth-quarter-all-star-game"&gt;   NBA.com&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://fansided.com/2020/02/02/super-bowl-54-prop-bets-smart-money/"&gt;   Fanside&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="margin: 0in; margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;em&gt; Sonic the Hedgehog Controversy: &lt;a href= "https://variety.com/2020/film/news/sonic-box-office-opening-weekend-birds-of-prey-1203501227/"&gt;   Variety&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/box-office-preview-sonic-hedgehog-boom-past-competition-1279187"&gt;   The Hollywood Reporter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="margin: 0in; margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;em&gt; Happy Valentine’s Day: &lt;a href= "https://nrf.com/media-center/press-releases/confident-consumers-and-broader-buying-lead-record-valentines-day"&gt;   NRF&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/13/how-much-americans-plan-to-spend-on-valentines-day.html"&gt;   CNBC&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2020/02/13/valentines-day-flower-deal-whole-foods-market-roses-prime-members/4738592002/"&gt;   USA Today&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.history.com/topics/valentines-day/history-of-valentines-day-2"&gt;   History&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://martechseries.com/analytics/data-management-platforms/valentines-day-millennials-give-gift-experience-new-bigresearch-report-uncovers/"&gt;   MarTechSeries&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style="margin: 0in; margin-bottom: .0001pt;"&gt;&lt;em&gt; Feel Good Friday -  Boy Pays off Lunch Debt: &lt;a href= "https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/04/us/boy-pays-off-lunch-debt-trnd/index.html"&gt;   CNN&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>staff@theNewsWorthy.com (the NewsWorthy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1cfd9a3e8e474b06ad9899e489e1f14c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1cfd9a3e8e474b06ad9899e489e1f14c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 01:10:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Wars Daily : Saucony Reduces Carbon Footprint with Biodegradable Shoe</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today is Friday, February 14, and we’re looking at Saucony vs. Adidas.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>iwonder@wondery.com (Business Wars Daily)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">83f88807456a47e0872666f6d125b5be</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/83f88807456a47e0872666f6d125b5be/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ao Ponto (podcast do jornal O Globo) : Míriam Leitão: 'ministro da Economia não fala sobre câmbio'</title><description>Nos últimos dias, o coronavírus e seus reflexos pressionaram o câmbio. Fatores internos, como a recuperação mais hesitante da economia aqui no Brasil, com números abaixo da expetativa na indústria e no comércio, impulsionaram ainda mais o dólar, que atingiu, na quarta-feira, o que era marca histórica de R$ 4,35. Isso antes do ministro da Economia, Paulo Guedes, falar sobre o assunto e provocar polêmica durante um evento em Brasília. Na quinta-feira, o mercado abriu agitado a reboque da repercussão da fala de Guedes. O dólar atingir R$ 4,38 e obrigou o Banco Central a intervir. Até o presidente Jair Bolsonaro se esquivou de opinar sobre as declarações do homem forte da economia. No Ao Ponto desta sexta-feira, a colunista Míriam Leitão analisa o peso da palavra do ministro da Economia, quando fala sobre a taxa de câmbio ou outros temas sensíveis ao setor. Ela também explica para quem o dólar alto é bom e para quem é ruim.</description><author>maggi@oglobo.com.br (Ao Ponto (podcast do jornal O Globo))</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f6ca097be3144054a3aafb3832657353</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f6ca097be3144054a3aafb3832657353/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 23:55:16 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Statesman Podcast : Reshuffle Special!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On this week's New Statesman Podcast, Stephen Bush and Anoosh Chakelian are joined by Ailbhe Rea and Patrick Maguire to look at Boris Johnson's reshuffle and the shock departures of Julian Smith and Sajid Javid. Then, in You Ask Us, they tackle your questions on what a Labour party led by Keir Starmer might look like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;New Statesman&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;digital subscriber you can get advert free access to this podcast by visiting&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.newstatesman.com/nssubscribers" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;newstatesman.com/nssubscribers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you haven't signed up yet, visit&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.newstatesman.com/subscribe" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;newstatesman.com/subscribe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to purchase your subscription.&amp;nbsp;Send us your questions for future episodes via Twitter&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.twitter.com/ns_podcasts" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;@ns_podcasts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>helen@newstatesman.co.uk (The New Statesman Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a3d41d6228374987a0ba691d3b3acdae</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a3d41d6228374987a0ba691d3b3acdae/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The News : Friday, February 14</title><description>Turnover in China's political leadership continues with the coronavirus outbreak, Attorney General Barr complains about President Trump's tweets, and Divest Princeton leads a march to Nassau Hall.</description><author>managingeditor@dailyprincetonian.com (The News)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ade498f67fa94759ae14e51745b421d6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ade498f67fa94759ae14e51745b421d6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:35:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Federalist Radio Hour : Where 2020 Candidates Stand Post-New Hampshire, Going Into Super Tuesday</title><description>David Marcus, New York Correspondent at The Federalist, joins Ben Domenech to discuss the Trump rally in New Hampshire he attended, as well as the viability of a Bloomberg nominee. Plus, where Bernie Sanders and Pete Buttigieg stand going into Nevada and South Carolina.</description><author>info@podcastone.com (The Federalist Radio Hour)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">107d8eca02af4bb78be1075fcb6a713f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/107d8eca02af4bb78be1075fcb6a713f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>RUMBLE with MICHAEL MOORE : Ep. 37: If The System Doesn’t Want You, Invent Your Own System (feat. John Sayles)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;John Sayles is a writer, director and indie film legend behind such films as &lt;em&gt;Return of the Secaucus Seven&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Brother from Another Planet&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Passion Fish&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Lone Star&lt;/em&gt;, Matewan and &lt;em&gt;8 Men Out&lt;/em&gt;. He joins Michael to discuss how movies get made, race, class and gender in the film industry and Sayles' new novel, &lt;em&gt;Yellow Earth&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;********************&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buy John Sayles’ new novel, “Yellow Earth” here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.haymarketbooks.org/books/1380-yellow-earth"&gt;https://www.haymarketbooks.org/books/1380-yellow-earth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See where John is touring here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.haymarketbooks.org/blogs/101-john-sayles-national-tour"&gt;https://www.haymarketbooks.org/blogs/101-john-sayles-national-tour&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Sayles IMDB page:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.imdb.com/name/nm0000626/"&gt;https://www.imdb.com/name/nm0000626/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;********************&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Subscribe to “RUMBLE with Michael Moore” on:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apple&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://apple.co/rumble"&gt;https://apple.co/rumble&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spotify&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/5KubucWBfyJr14bD7xWBvS"&gt;https://open.spotify.com/show/5KubucWBfyJr14bD7xWBvS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9hbmNob3IuZm0vcy8xMGZjOWEzMC9wb2RjYXN0L3Jzcw=="&gt;https://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9hbmNob3IuZm0vcy8xMGZjOWEzMC9wb2RjYXN0L3Jzcw==&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stitcher:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/michael-moore-4/rumble-with-michael-moore"&gt;https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/michael-moore-4/rumble-with-michael-moore&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anchor:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/rumble-with-michael-moore"&gt;https://anchor.fm/rumble-with-michael-moore&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow Michael on:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MMFlint"&gt;https://twitter.com/MMFlint&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/mmflint/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/mmflint/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/michaelfmoore/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/michaelfmoore/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;********************&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/rumble-with-michael-moore/message</description><author>podcasts39+10fc9a30@anchor.fm (RUMBLE with MICHAEL MOORE)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">eb99b0e8cc7942d0a68e27f10dfc0124</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/eb99b0e8cc7942d0a68e27f10dfc0124/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 21:53:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Commercial Awareness Podcast : Episode 40: Season Finale</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Contact: &lt;a href="mailto:commawarepod@gmail.com"&gt;commawarepod@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram: @&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/commawarepod/?hl=en"&gt;commawarepod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Links for the headlines:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HS2 Green Light&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/live/business-51418693"&gt;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/live/business-51418693&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BP Net Zero Pledge&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e1ee8ab4-4d89-11ea-95a0-43d18ec715f5"&gt;https://www.ft.com/content/e1ee8ab4-4d89-11ea-95a0-43d18ec715f5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Injunction Granted&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/13/technology/amazon-jedi-pentagon-contract-microsoft.html"&gt;https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/13/technology/amazon-jedi-pentagon-contract-microsoft.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deal News&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.lw.com/news/latham-advises-casper-sleep-inc-in-ipo"&gt;https://www.lw.com/news/latham-advises-casper-sleep-inc-in-ipo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelawyer.com/us-and-french-firms-lead-on-billion-dollar-payments-deal/"&gt;https://www.thelawyer.com/us-and-french-firms-lead-on-billion-dollar-payments-deal/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Govt Considers Flybe Stake&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-51453196"&gt;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-51453196&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Novartis Panel Rules&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelawyer.com/novartis-panel-review-2020/"&gt;https://www.thelawyer.com/novartis-panel-review-2020/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nissan Loss&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cityam.com/nissan-records-losses-amid-backdrop-of-carlos-ghosn-scandal/"&gt;https://www.cityam.com/nissan-records-losses-amid-backdrop-of-carlos-ghosn-scandal/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FTC Investigates Big Tech&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cityam.com/ftc-demands-data-on-startup-purchases-by-tech-giants/"&gt;https://www.cityam.com/ftc-demands-data-on-startup-purchases-by-tech-giants/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Firm Paternity Leave Increase&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelawyer.com/ao-matches-linklaters-with-12-weeks-paternity-leave/"&gt;https://www.thelawyer.com/ao-matches-linklaters-with-12-weeks-paternity-leave/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UK Allows Huawei Involvement&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2020/01/28/huawei-will-allowed-build-parts-britains-5g-network/"&gt;https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2020/01/28/huawei-will-allowed-build-parts-britains-5g-network/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Created and Hosted by: Tapiwa Museba&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Season 3 Begins on 28 February&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts8+75b7794@anchor.fm (The Commercial Awareness Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">069a0fd9c14d45f4b3e51850fc1f63f9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/069a0fd9c14d45f4b3e51850fc1f63f9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 21:47:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FT News Briefing : Friday, February 14</title><description>&lt;p&gt;US attorney-general William Barr publicly rebuked Donald Trump, saying the president’s tweets about ongoing criminal cases had made it “impossible” to do his job, while the US Senate voted to limit Mr Trump’s military authority in Iran. Plus, US prosecutors accuse Huawei of stealing technology from several American companies and Amazon wins its request to temporarily block a $10bn US defence contract awarded to Microsoft. Plus, Sajid Javid abruptly quit as UK chancellor on Thursday after a brutal power struggle with prime minister Boris Johnson. The FT’s Robert Shrimsley explains what happened.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>newsbriefing@ft.com (FT News Briefing)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ab603271ed2a4c7aa9b2c20a4d65b8f4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ab603271ed2a4c7aa9b2c20a4d65b8f4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Townhall Review | Conservative Commentary On Today's News : Biden Takes a Hit in New Hampshire; Leader McConnell Keeps a Keen Eye on the Courts</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Townhall Review &amp;ndash; February 15, 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hughhewitt.com/"&gt;Hugh Hewitt&lt;/a&gt; talks with &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone"&gt;Michael Barone&lt;/a&gt; of the &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/"&gt;Washington Examiner&lt;/a&gt; and fellow with the &lt;a href="https://www.aei.org/"&gt;American Enterprise Institute&lt;/a&gt; about the Democratic primaries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hughhewitt.com/"&gt;Hugh Hewitt&lt;/a&gt; and Senate Majority Leader &lt;a href="https://www.mcconnell.senate.gov/public/"&gt;Mitch McConnell&lt;/a&gt; talk about Federal judge confirmations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://am970theanswer.com/radioshow/578"&gt;Kevin McCullough&lt;/a&gt; talks with former Arkansas Governor &lt;a href="https://www.mikehuckabee.com/"&gt;Mike Huckabee&lt;/a&gt; talk about President Trump&amp;rsquo;s actions against terrorists and terrorism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sebgorka.com/"&gt;Sebastian Gorka&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.heritage.org/staff/james-carafano"&gt;James Carafano&lt;/a&gt; of the &lt;a href="https://www.heritage.org/"&gt;Heritage Foundation&lt;/a&gt; discuss China&amp;rsquo;s efforts to combat the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/index.html"&gt;Coronavirus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hughhewitt.com/"&gt;Hugh Hewitt&lt;/a&gt; talks with Nebraska Senator &lt;a href="https://www.sasse.senate.gov/public/"&gt;Ben Sasse&lt;/a&gt; about his proposed &amp;ldquo;Born Alive Protection Act.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://am970theanswer.com/radioshow/578"&gt;Keven McCullough&lt;/a&gt; talks with former NYPD Commissioner &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bernard_Kerik"&gt;Bernard Kerik&lt;/a&gt; about the recent attempted assassination of New York City police officers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dennisprager.com/"&gt;Dennis Prager&lt;/a&gt; talks with &lt;a href="https://amgreatness.com/author/karin-mcquinlan/"&gt;Karen McQuillan&lt;/a&gt; about her recent column, &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href="https://amgreatness.com/author/karin-mcquinlan/"&gt;American Greatness&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mikeonline.com/"&gt;Mike Gallagher&lt;/a&gt; looks at a recent segment from &lt;a href="https://abc.com/shows/the-view"&gt;The View&lt;/a&gt; where &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meghan_McCain"&gt;Meghan McCain&lt;/a&gt; asked some hard question of Mayor &lt;a href="https://peteforamerica.com/"&gt;Pete Buttigieg&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thr@salemmedia.com (Townhall Review | Conservative Commentary On Today's News)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fac0a496219e4a6a82662e8fd767d3c6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fac0a496219e4a6a82662e8fd767d3c6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Trending Stories Taking Over podcast | T.S.T.O. : 020 | Superbowl, Rogan responds, Bezos security, DirecTV, Russia, and TINDER</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Watch the full episode: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hWMwxV2W9Ps&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be"&gt;https://bit.ly/2wbpows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is HAPPENING people of the interwebs?!?! &amp;nbsp;In this episode of the Trending Stories Taking Over show we peek in on the Superbowl, Rogan responds, Bezos security, DirecTV, Russia, and TINDER. &amp;nbsp;ENJOY!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't forget about the giveaway: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2RJDrBM"&gt;https://bit.ly/2RJDrBM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Todd + Jake&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/tsto/message</description><author>tstoshow@gmail.com (The Trending Stories Taking Over podcast | T.S.T.O.)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">deba77b90d424fea83f3b05675f16284</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/deba77b90d424fea83f3b05675f16284/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 20:47:46 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>ESPN Chicago GameNight : 2-13 9 PM: Gordon Monson and TBT</title><description>"Make Sure You Bring Your Wallet": Throwback Thursday featuring the best non-Jordan and Wilkins dunkers. Also, Gordon Monson from the Salt Lake Tribune and 1280 AM The Zone joins the show to talk about Jim Boylen's time at Utah.</description><author>feedback@goodkarmabrands.com (ESPN Chicago GameNight)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">efc87001023a48b1b7ff1ce005a75b52</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/efc87001023a48b1b7ff1ce005a75b52/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 20:04:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Today in Focus : Who killed Swedish prime minister Olof Palme?</title><description>After a night at the cinema in 1986, Olof Palme was assassinated on Stockholm’s busiest street. The killer has never been found. Jan Stocklassa discusses whether novelist Stieg Larsson’s theory can provide any answers. And: the first same-sex couple to get married in Northern Ireland. Help support our independent journalism at &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://www.theguardian.com/infocus&amp;quot;&amp;gt;theguardian.com/infocus&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;</description><author>userhelp@theguardian.com (Today in Focus)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">818e5ddb37474a31b8bb3560505de8d4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/818e5ddb37474a31b8bb3560505de8d4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 19:00:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MarketBuzz : 435: Sensex, Nifty likely to open in green; Vodafone Idea, Avenue Supermarts, BPCL in focus</title><description>The Indian market is likely to open in the green on Friday over global markets stabilizing as China is set to halve tariff rates on certain US products with effect later during the day. However, increasing coronavirus death toll and cases could put pressure on the market. At 7:20 am, the SGX Nifty was trading 27.50 points or 0.23 percent higher at 12,178, indicating a positive opening for the Sensex and Nifty50.</description><author>sunep.imchen@nw18.com (MarketBuzz)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b668806006fd453eb8499764da1c5ca4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b668806006fd453eb8499764da1c5ca4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 18:33:21 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hot Zone with Chuck Holton : Episode 287 - Living 40 Feet Below the Las Vegas Strip</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Follow one of the 1000 homeless people living below the streets of Las Vegas, NV.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>holtocw@gmail.com (The Hot Zone with Chuck Holton)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ac266bcd1c8e467d9ff53d067b250b72</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ac266bcd1c8e467d9ff53d067b250b72/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 18:17:10 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Beat with Ari Melber : Under fire, Barr stands by helping convicted Trump aide while criticizing tweets</title><description>&lt;p&gt;MSNBC Chief Legal Correspondent Ari Melber host "The Beat" Attorney General Bill Barr admits Trump makes his job harder by tweeting, but still stands by helping convicted Trump aide, Roger Stone.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ari@msnbc.com (The Beat with Ari Melber)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3fba874ece70463f80ca1c14af97d45e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3fba874ece70463f80ca1c14af97d45e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 17:06:21 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The KrisAnne Hall Show : Episode 1043 Roger Stone &amp; Govt Science Experiments</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://youtu.be/HOOXFYRh5M4"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch The KrisAnne Hall Show on YouTube&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn from someone who has actually spent a lot of time in the courtroom about the new Roger Stone discussion. Then YOU can discern the truth from the MSM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also an in depth discussion about how your tax dollars are being used to develop mind control and manipulation techniques and drugs... Who is our source for this information? Videos directly from The US Army! We MUST start talking about this or the general public will never know.&lt;br&gt;
#LibertyFirst&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ensure this Excellent Constitution Training Continues! Partner with The KrisAnne Hall Daily Journal and be a part of the force that will restore Americans with their Constitutional Principles! To JOIN with us just simple text- impact2020 to 33777&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Support this podcast: &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/the-krisanne-hall-show/support" rel="payment"&gt;https://anchor.fm/the-krisanne-hall-show/support&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts44+f0b3c04@anchor.fm (The KrisAnne Hall Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a45e30a16fca487cb560e297159e8e2f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a45e30a16fca487cb560e297159e8e2f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 17:05:18 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>We the People : How Can We Be Our Best “We the People”?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In these polarized times and in the wake of impeachment – how can we be a better “We the People”? Host Jeffrey Rosen is joined by Margaret Taylor of Lawfare and Adam White of AEI to discuss the values that our founders thought were necessary to uphold American government, and whether or not the American people and our representatives are living up to them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The episode centers around the idea of civic virtue: a political philosophy term which describes personal qualities associated with the effective functioning of the civil and political order, or the preservation of its values and principles (per Encyclopedia Britannica.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Margaret Taylor and Adam White are authors of pieces for The Battle for the Constitution – a partnership between The National Constitution Center and The Atlantic which features essays exploring the constitutional issues at the center of American life. Check out the page here: &lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/projects/battle-constitution/"&gt;https://www.theatlantic.com/projects/battle-constitution/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Questions or comments about the podcast? Email us at podcast@constitutioncenter.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jmcdermott@constitutioncenter.org (We the People)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a1c763fe233a4a30943334ddd370b5a5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a1c763fe233a4a30943334ddd370b5a5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 16:26:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Advisory Opinions : Voir Dire</title><description>&lt;p&gt;David and Sarah take on the whirlwind of news surrounding the Roger Stone case, go behind the scenes of opposition research, and share their thoughts on the Netflix docuseries "Cheer."&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>caleb@thedispatch.com (Advisory Opinions)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3f880c7391c34735aae920ffeb543bf6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3f880c7391c34735aae920ffeb543bf6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>TJ Trout : Legislation session winds down, and election security</title><description>TJ chats with NM State Sen. Mimi Stewart on legislative issues and Sec. of State Maggie Toulouse Oliver talks about what NM is doing for election security for 2020 on News Radio KKOB</description><guid isPermaLink="false">544608de306b43b8878b47659d94bb62</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/544608de306b43b8878b47659d94bb62/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 15:53:58 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>This Is America with Rich Valdes Podcast : Ep. 101 Racism, Radicals, and Roger Stone</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, Rich discusses the racism abounding on college campuses. Then, Rep Ayanna Pressley says that the American Constitution is sexist. Plus, an update on Roger Stones sentencing from Michael Caputo, sharing the latest push for a presidential pardon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comment and follow on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/richvaldes"&gt;Twitter&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://facebook.com/RichValdesCompany"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or visit us at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://richvaldes.com/"&gt;RichValdes.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Portions of today's program are brought to you by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://justfacts.com/rich"&gt;JustFacts.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://paypal.me/RichValdes" rel="payment"&gt;Support the show.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>rsementa@gmail.com (This Is America with Rich Valdes Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">326e29261aca40eb9675bd3741a4a582</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/326e29261aca40eb9675bd3741a4a582/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 14:42:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Campaign HQ with David Plouffe : Heavyweight Battle in Nevada</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Jon Ralston has covered politics in Nevada for more than 30 years and will be one of the moderators of Wednesday’s Democratic Debate. Jon shares his deep knowledge of Nevada politics, and what he hopes to get from the candidates on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@cadence13.com (Campaign HQ with David Plouffe)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5e23a7af07d84d3282e6a7dfe75faac9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5e23a7af07d84d3282e6a7dfe75faac9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 14:21:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Can He Do That? : Trump’s view of a unilaterally powerful president goes unchallenged</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Since President Trump was &lt;a href="https://link.chtbl.com/acquitted"&gt;acquitted by the Senate&lt;/a&gt; in his impeachment trial, there has been a lot of action out of the White House. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;From firing people in his administration who testified against him in the House Inquiry to compromising the Justice Department’s independence, Trump's actions seem to paint a picture of a president who feels emboldened by the resolution of his months-long impeachment battle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;So does this post-acquittal moment reflect a president more emboldened than before? White House reporter Ashley Parker offers insight into President Trump’s perception of power and what we can expect to see from him in an election year.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Related episodes&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.chtbl.com/acquitted"&gt;A president acquitted. The balance of power tested.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.chtbl.com/reelection"&gt;If a president is impeached, can they run for reelection&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.chtbl.com/framers"&gt;'The Framers would not recognize the modern presidency.’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>jessica.stahl@washpost.com (Can He Do That?)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">650e480f7869446d9b0217db0e135907</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/650e480f7869446d9b0217db0e135907/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 14:07:46 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Newscast : Get Rishi Quick</title><description>Newscast ushers in Sajid Javid's replacement the way Newscast does best... with the world’s first Rishi Sunak quiz! The Saj's former special advisor Salma Shah joins us to unpick the cabinet reshuffle. And Rory Stewart wants a sleepover.

Producers: Emma Close and Ione Wells
Editor: Dino Sofos</description><author>RadioMusic.Support@bbc.co.uk (Newscast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0d467527320345a197b4a5ec0787fafc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0d467527320345a197b4a5ec0787fafc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 13:42:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Rome Daily Sentinel - Cinema Podcast : February 13, 2020 - &amp;quot;Birds of Prey&amp;quot;</title><description>After getting no predictions right at the Oscars, Sentinel movie reviewer Sean Ian Mills checks out the year's first superhero movie with "Birds of Prey" and has fun news about Rick Moranis!</description><author>podcasts@rnymedia.com (Rome Daily Sentinel - Cinema Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c0ffa3e87a0647a2ba44cc0d6019a5fb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c0ffa3e87a0647a2ba44cc0d6019a5fb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 13:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>John Solomon Reports : Inside Trump's Counter-Terrorism Effort</title><description>&lt;p&gt;National Security Council Senior Director Kash Patel on the greatest threats to U.S. security.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>media@justthenews.com (John Solomon Reports)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">51266b19943e4242817799b17a86be27</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/51266b19943e4242817799b17a86be27/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 12:50:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The McCarthy Report : Episode 72: The Absurd Roger Stone Controversy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today on &lt;i data-stringify-type="italic"&gt;The McCarthy Report&lt;/i&gt;, Andy and Rich dissect the legal ruckus surrounding Roger Stone’s sentencing, and discuss Bill Barr’s impending House Judiciary Committee testimony.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>studio@nationalreview.com (The McCarthy Report)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c25efbc646f94140ba252ae0d17264fb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c25efbc646f94140ba252ae0d17264fb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 12:02:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Andrew Klavan Show : Ep. 845 - Stepping on the Rake of Socialism</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Democrats get run over by their own policies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out The Cold War: What We Saw, a new podcast written and presented by Bill Whittle at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar&lt;/a&gt;. In Part 1 we peel back the layers of mystery cloaking the Terror state run by the Kremlin, and watch as America takes its first small steps onto the stage of world leadership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like The Andrew Klavan Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: KLAVAN and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/Klavan"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/Klavan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>andrewklavanshow@dailywire.com (The Andrew Klavan Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8366f0251a7f46d68aa8fa9dc4a26442</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8366f0251a7f46d68aa8fa9dc4a26442/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 11:44:45 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sara Carter Show : Parkland father Andrew Pollack describes the last moments of Meadow's life: 'It was heroic'</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Sara A. Carter interviewed Andrew Pollack, a father who tragically lost his daughter Meadow when a shooter opened fire at Marjorie Stoneman Douglas High School in Parkland, Florida two years ago. Pollack described the last moment's of Meadow's life. It was heroic.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>support@thesaracartershow.com (The Sara Carter Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0030f3929ff34490ab77aaeddadb53ea</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0030f3929ff34490ab77aaeddadb53ea/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 11:01:12 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Honey Badger Radio : Start Here: Honey Badger Weekly Digest 12</title><description>Enjoy a bite sized version of a week in badger.&lt;br /&gt;For 3rd-7th Feb</description><author>feeds@spreaker.com (Honey Badger Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">dd73ed4661a44b50bac7defe56418237</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/dd73ed4661a44b50bac7defe56418237/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 10:55:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Carnegie Council Audio Podcast : Who Controls the Global Thermostat? with C2G's Janos Pasztor</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With record-breaking winter warmth in Europe, catastrophic fires in Australia, and deadly flooding in Indonesia, we are deep into a climate crisis. In this wide-ranging talk, Janos Paztor, executive director of the Carnegie Climate Governance Initiative (C2G), talks about his organization's work on the governance of emerging technologies that intentionally seek to change the Earth's climate system, including carbon dioxide removal and solar radiation modification.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>carnegieitunes@cceia.org (Carnegie Council Audio Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">79ec83819a694f2da5a9aa57bb200e11</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/79ec83819a694f2da5a9aa57bb200e11/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 09:47:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Commentary Magazine Podcast : Getting Stoned with Progressive Prosecutors</title><description>Today's podcast features special guest star Andy McCarthy, who tells us about his important new COMMENTARY article "The Progressive Prosecutor Project" and schools us on what's really going on when it comes to the sentencing of Trump intimate Roger Stone. Give a listen.</description><author>feeds@soundcloud.com (Commentary Magazine Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">df86c36fdecf43f68237f09bf3f68333</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/df86c36fdecf43f68237f09bf3f68333/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 09:14:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Yorker: Politics and More : After Two Primary Contests, What’s Ahead for the Democratic Race?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;On Tuesday, voters in New Hampshire cast their ballots in the Democratic Presidential primary. Following &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/news/campaign-chronicles/pretty-much-a-big-mess-one-iowa-caucus-precincts-drama-filled-night"&gt;the debacle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;surrounding the Iowa caucuses, many Democrats hoped that the results from New Hampshire would bring clarity to the race. Bernie Sanders&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/news/our-columnists/bernie-sanders-leads-a-jumbled-new-hampshire-primary"&gt;won&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, arguably making him the front-runner. But close behind him was Pete Buttigieg, who also narrowly won the Iowa caucuses, and Amy Klobuchar, whose third-place finish gave her campaign renewed energy. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/benjamin-wallace-wells"&gt;Benjamin Wallace-Wells&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; joins&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/eric-lach"&gt;Eric Lach&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;to discuss the New Hampshire primaries and how a clear picture of the future of the Democratic contest remains elusive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (The New Yorker: Politics and More)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">00ac241677a1484ab2218ca37a8e9ea7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/00ac241677a1484ab2218ca37a8e9ea7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Michael Knowles Show : Ep. 495 - Toxic Effeminacy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;AOC’s boyfriend goes viral for castigating his fellow white people as hopelessly racist. We will examine the dangers of toxic effeminacy. Then, Squad Member Ayanna Pressley whines on the floor of the House, Elizabeth Warren takes money from a broke student, and President Trump teaches us all a lesson when the media ask him what lessons he learned from impeachment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out The Cold War: What We Saw, a new podcast written and presented by Bill Whittle at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar&lt;/a&gt;. In Part 1 we peel back the layers of mystery cloaking the Terror state run by the Kremlin, and watch as America takes its first small steps onto the stage of world leadership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like The Michael Knowles Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: KNOWLES and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/Knowles"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/Knowles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>michaelknowlesshow@dailywire.com (The Michael Knowles Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a98fef20566742dfb7b40404cd494e60</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a98fef20566742dfb7b40404cd494e60/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 08:32:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Gettysburg Connection Podcast : Gettysburg College Women’s Hoopsters Rewrite Conference Record Book [Episode 22]</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;To say the Gettysburg College Woman&amp;#8217;s Basketball team is on a roll is to understate things.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/021320_1351_GettysburgC1.png" alt=""&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coach Davis and the team&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;Although the team lost to Haverford College on Saturday, until then it was on an eighteen game winning streak, the longest-ever for the team and the longest-ever in the Centennial conference.  And the team has broken into the national Division III rankings.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;In this interview I talk with the team&amp;#8217;s coach, Nate Davis, now in his fifth season with the Bullets&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;Davis talks about his approach to coaching, the role of athletics at the college, and his take on the amazing winning streak.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;And if you like basketball, please come out to see the team as it finishes off its season.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mail@gettysburgconnection.org (Gettysburg Connection Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3e73860cf9144cb98c17699304e5a766</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3e73860cf9144cb98c17699304e5a766/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 05:51:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Deconstructed with Mehdi Hasan : Live from L.A. with John Legend and Patrisse Cullors</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The United States has the biggest prison population of any country on the planet. The crime rate is down, but the incarceration rate continues to soar. With the 2020 presidential election around the corner, what hope is there for fixing the system? Mehdi Hasan sits down with John Legend and Patrisse Cullors in Los Angeles for a live conversation about criminal justice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deconstructed interviews a variety of guests who share their views in order to educate and inform our listeners on the most pressing issues of the day and on the democratic process. Our guests’ views on the issues and on elected officials’ and candidates’ approaches to them are their own, and do not reflect of the views of First Look Media Works.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@theintercept.com (Deconstructed with Mehdi Hasan)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1fe24fca10e64fed83f5a21ab8804b3a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1fe24fca10e64fed83f5a21ab8804b3a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Throughline : Becoming America</title><description>When the United States of America was founded, it was only a union of a small number of states. By the beginning of the 20th century, the United States had become an empire; with states and territories and colonies that spanned the globe. As a result, the country began to not only reconsider its place in the world, but also its very name.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (Throughline)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1d4d0bd73ffa4377b581038d61c86722</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1d4d0bd73ffa4377b581038d61c86722/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 21:01:41 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Argument : Are We Headed for a Bernie Sweep?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Is Bernie Sanders on an unstoppable path to the Democratic nomination — and if so, can he defeat President Trump in November? The columnists discuss the results of the New Hampshire primary and what they portend for the next contests in the race. Then, should Valentine's Day be canceled once and for all? For background reading on this episode, visit &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/column/the-argument" target="_blank"&gt;nytimes.com/theargument&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>argument@nytimes.com (The Argument)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">33e3ef1dc44d4ca497576a4016975284</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/33e3ef1dc44d4ca497576a4016975284/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Global Dispatches -- World News That Matters : The Link Between Healthcare and Peace in Africa | with Dr. Roseanne Nijiru</title><description>&lt;p&gt;My guest today, &lt;a href= "https://www.ssrc.org/fellows/D1310C7A-3F7E-E811-80CB-005056AB0BD9/"&gt; Dr. Roseanne Njiru&lt;/a&gt; is a sociologist at the University of Nairobi in Kenya. She has conducted cutting edge field research that finds a link between healthcare and peacebuilding. Specifically, she examines the role that community health workers play in preventing conflict in marginalized communities, or urban slums, around Nairobi. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Community health workers, or what in other contexts is sometimes called health extension workers, poor, rural or otherwise marginalized communities to a country's broader health care system. The health workers themselves are from these communities and they are given some basic level of training. Essentially, they are the eyes and ears and first point of contact between the health system and the community. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Deploying cadres of these community health workers has become increasingly popular as a public health strategy in the developing world. In my years of reporting, I've seen the key role that community health workers play in places like rural Bangladesh and Ethiopia. This strategy has been demonstrated to improve health outcomes in some of the most vulnerable communities in a society. But what I did not appreciate until I encountered Dr. Njiru's research was some of the ancillary benefits, beyond health that community health workers can confer to their community. Namely, Dr. Njiru found through her research that community health workers are also agents of peace and conflict prevention--including helping to prevent political violence. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Her research is absolutely fascinating and I am glad to bring it to you as part of a series of episodes supported in part from a grant from &lt;a href="https://www.carnegie.org/"&gt;Carnegie Corporation of New York&lt;/a&gt; to feature African perspectives on peace and security issues in Africa.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.undispatch.com/"&gt;https://www.undispatch.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.globaldispatchespodcast.com/"&gt;https://www.globaldispatchespodcast.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p1"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/UNDispatch/&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>globaldispatchespodcast@gmail.com (Global Dispatches -- World News That Matters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">92fc588b180b4f9f8c5a3e259dc99581</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/92fc588b180b4f9f8c5a3e259dc99581/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dispatch Podcast : Messy Chaotic Lanes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Sarah and the guys examine the results of the New Hampshire primary, dive into the debate over electability and the importance of ideological lanes, and discuss the impact going forward of the move to lessen a sentencing recommendation for Roger Stone.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>caleb@thedispatch.com (The Dispatch Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">163bc0f97e5949a29bf97e2eec54add8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/163bc0f97e5949a29bf97e2eec54add8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bold and Blunt : Cartels in America: Mexico's Scum Move North</title><description>&lt;p&gt;If you think border violence is something that's confined to, well, the border states -- think again. Cochise County Sheriff Mark Dannells gives some shocking, first-hand accounts of how Mexico's cartels are bringing the drugs and trafficking here -- and actually setting up residence. And sadly, the border protection comes at great cost to our own U.S. agents.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>media@washingtontimes.com (Bold and Blunt)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4b7c16e631774da18b7e6b42ca0eb4c1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4b7c16e631774da18b7e6b42ca0eb4c1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 14:45:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Editors : Episode 190: This Week in New Hampshire</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today on &lt;em&gt;The Editors&lt;/em&gt;, Rich, Charlie, Luke, Alexandra, and Jim discuss the outcomes and projections after last night’s New Hampshire caucuses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Light Items&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rich: It’s almost spring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charles: Fats Waller.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Luke: The Westminster dog show winner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alexandra: Rewatching &lt;em&gt;Parks &amp;amp; Rec&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jim: Rewatching &lt;em&gt;Stranger Things&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Editors’ Picks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rich: &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/02/national-review-webathon-whittaker-chambers-the-left/"&gt;Whitaker Chambers piece from the archives&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charles: &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/magazine/2020/02/24/has-the-presidency-become-impossible/"&gt;Rick Brookhiser’s magazine piece&lt;/a&gt; on whether the presidency is too difficult to succeed in.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Luke: KDW’s “&lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/02/democratic-socialism-problem-it-is-both/"&gt;Them the People&lt;/a&gt;”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alexandra: &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/magazine/2020/02/24/donald-trumps-pro-life-presidency/"&gt;Ramesh on Trump and pro-life movement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jim: &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/02/keep-politics-fun-save-the-iowa-caucuses/#slide-1"&gt;Charlie Szold’s case for keeping the Iowa caucuses&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Editors&lt;/em&gt; is hosted by Rich Lowry and produced by Sarah Schutte.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>studio@nationalreview.com (The Editors)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fd9a22fa0235434a80a574f8c36378f1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fd9a22fa0235434a80a574f8c36378f1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 13:50:29 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Chuck ToddCast: Meet the Press : The New Hampshire Primary and Beyond: Betsy Woodruff Swan and Carl Cannon plus McKay Coppins</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Betsy Woodruff Swan and Carl Cannon join Chuck Todd to discuss what the results from the New Hampshire primary and what they mean for the 2020 race overall. Plus, McKay Coppins talk all things Mitt Romney and the impact his impeachment vote has had on the Republican Party.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>matt.rivera@nbcuni.com (The Chuck ToddCast: Meet the Press)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c1ab31ec4dac444299b9297ed1343d9d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c1ab31ec4dac444299b9297ed1343d9d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 13:36:52 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Individual 1 podcast : The Case That Amy Klobuchar is the Last/Best Hope to Beat Trump</title><description>&lt;div&gt;John breaks down the latest example of Trump acting like King by using the DOJ for his own purposes.  He then explains why Amy Klobuchar has the best chance to beat Trump if she can win the nomination.&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>batoul.peters@globalstorynetwork.com (Individual 1 podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b6a10279ce0c435c964640221a165c46</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b6a10279ce0c435c964640221a165c46/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 11:41:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Graham Allen’s Dear America Podcast : EP 65 | Jussie Smollett INDICTED!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On this episode, we look at the remaining Democratic candidates. Bernie is taking the lead as Bloomberg pays influencers $150 to say how cool he is. Who really has a shot at beating Trump? Also, Jussie Smollett is indicted! After a year of evading justice, will he finally be held accountable?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SimpliSafe.com/DearAmerica&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PrepareWithGraham.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TacPack.com OFFER CODE: GRAHAM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RedArrowWeapons.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>dearamerica76@gmail.com (Graham Allen’s Dear America Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2a955059fa724f03b7c6bee79bc46361</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2a955059fa724f03b7c6bee79bc46361/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 11:06:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Pega'os En La Mañana con Julio Rivera Saniel : Pega'os en la Mañana - Miércoles, 12 de febrero de 2020</title><author>radioisladigital@gmail.com (Pega'os En La Mañana con Julio Rivera Saniel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9bc7b38696344714a66834d7eecc3195</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9bc7b38696344714a66834d7eecc3195/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 10:14:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>BE THE PEOPLE : 🎧 Rejecting Your Parents Faith &amp; Embracing Your Own Transformation</title><description>Young people are quick to notice contradictions between and among religious leaders, doctrines, and lifestyle choices. In this episode, I interview an amazing young woman who grew up in a multi-generational Mormon pioneer family. Carrie Sheffield once romanticized the Mormon Church’s worldwide missionary achievements, but eventually rejected her parents’ faith tradition. After living life as an agnostic, she became a follower of Jesus Christ. In this episode, we discuss her transformation. Carrie Sheffield is a millennial who has achieved enormous success as a columnist and broadcaster. The founder of Bold TV, Carrie has testified before Congress and been profiled in The Wall Street Journal, Forbes Magazine, Entrepreneur Magazine, and other major news outlets.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Carrie Sheffield Website: &lt;a href="https://carriesheffield.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://carriesheffield.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
BOLD TV: &lt;a href="https://bold.global/author/carrie-sheffield/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://bold.global/author/carrie-sheffield/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Secrets of Wealthy Women: &lt;a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/secrets-of-wealthy-women-how-carrie-sheffield-changed-her-view-of-money-11553259601" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;How Carrie Sheffield Changed Her View of Money&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><author>speakup@malcolmoutloud.com (BE THE PEOPLE)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8b76dd53274f45e9b2449d6aeaa62fa7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8b76dd53274f45e9b2449d6aeaa62fa7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 10:10:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Between The Lines Radio Newsmagazine podcast : Between The Lines - Feb. 12, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;After Trump’s Senate Impeachment Acquittal, Attention Turns to Volatile Democratic Primary Campaign; Indigenous Nations Struggle to Stop Construction of Coastal GasLink Pipeline; Landmark Pro-Worker Legislation Wins Passage in House of Representatives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit our website at &lt;a href="https://btlonline.org/"&gt;BTLonline.org&lt;/a&gt; for more information, links, transcripts and in-depth interviews. (Updates after 3 p.m. ET Wednesdays) Follow us on Facebook at BetweenTheLinesRadioNewsmagazine and on Twitter @BTLRadioNews. Join our new Patreon community at Patreon.com/BetweenTheLinesRadioNewsmagazine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="https://secure.givelively.org/donate/squeaky-wheel-productions/support-progressive-voices-to-defend-democracy-and-fight-fascism"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (https://secure.givelively.org/donate/squeaky-wheel-productions/support-progressive-voices-to-defend-democracy-and-fight-fascism)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>contact@btlonline.org (Between The Lines Radio Newsmagazine podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">34c2c479922948bbb5e636011b4e71d5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/34c2c479922948bbb5e636011b4e71d5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WFUV's Cityscape : Ending the AIDS Epidemic in NY</title><description>It’s estimated that 1.1 million people in the United States are living with HIV. New York State is aiming to be the first state in the country to end the HIV/AIDS epidemic by the end of 2020.    Doug Wirth is the President and CEO of Amida Care. Amida Care has a wide network of health care providers throughout New York City and is the largest Medicaid Special Needs Health Plan (SNP) in New York State. Doug joins us on this week's Cityscape to talk about New York’s initiative to end the HIV/AIDS epidemic, and how Amida care is contributing to that effort. Doug served on Governor Cuomo’s Ending the Epidemic Task Force, which came up with a blueprint to snuff out AIDS. Doug is our guest on this week's Cityscape.</description><author>newsroom@wfuv.org (WFUV's Cityscape)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9cff960b26964c2f9ab51e78ba0d563f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9cff960b26964c2f9ab51e78ba0d563f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Deep Background with Noah Feldman : Malcolm Gladwell and "Magical Technical Fixes"</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Malcom Gladwell and Noah Feldman discuss whether we should add more states to the union, and why Americans are always searching for "magical technical fixes." For further listening check out the "Divide and Conquer" episode of the Revisionist History podcast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marketing@pushkin.fm (Deep Background with Noah Feldman)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">751ddaf120374872a2153d8013732893</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/751ddaf120374872a2153d8013732893/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Twelve O'clock Siren : Episode - 24</title><description>&lt;p&gt;RC Kuhn, as born in Leonard as you can be, most senior member of our town at 97 years old on Feb 12, 2020, Cowboy, BBQ pit master and story telling extraordinaire.  We have been trying to get Mr. Kuhn on the podcast since we began. We really enjoyed hearing a fraction of his story, and hope to learn more soon.  &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jameshartley1@gmail.com (The Twelve O'clock Siren)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">06a1c87c37104cf59ebc364c0ac23861</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/06a1c87c37104cf59ebc364c0ac23861/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 20:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Pronoia Now Network : Secrets to Happy Healthy Living - Ep 120</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Getting enough Vit. D in the winter season? Learn all about why this is so important for your health!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mysticandwizard@gmail.com (Pronoia Now Network)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">98b448c302204ba5952860b64625d2e5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/98b448c302204ba5952860b64625d2e5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 17:51:35 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Make Me Smart with Kai and Molly : No more business as usual?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The big buzzwords among the executives and world leaders at the World Economic Forum&amp;#8217;s annual meeting this year were &amp;#8220;stakeholder capitalism,&amp;#8221; the idea that a corporation should serve a social and environmental good, not just enrich shareholders. What a concept, right? It comes after those Business Roundtable guidelines on corporate responsibility, and sustainability pledges from big players like Microsoft and BlackRock. But is this really a challenge to Milton Friedman&amp;#8217;s 50-year-old treatise on corporations&amp;#8217; purpose? Or just a savvy but cynical PR move? We put that question to Jerry Davis, the associate dean for business and impact at the University of Michigan’s business school. He says it&amp;#8217;s harder for a company to be a &amp;#8220;successful hypocrite&amp;#8221; now.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>makemesmart@marketplace.org (Make Me Smart with Kai and Molly)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">42e6fed500664ac7b62bf13be00b9d60</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/42e6fed500664ac7b62bf13be00b9d60/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 17:49:43 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Beating Around The Bush : S3E4 - Cabinet reshuffle, Water sharing woes, Will Canavan cross the floor? and Coronavirus threat</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week’s take on the news relating to rural and regional Australia with Fleur Anderson and Wade Dabinett.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Politics&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Cabinet Reshuffle:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://thenewdaily.com.au/news/politics/australian-politics/2020/02/06/nationals-cabinet-reshuffle-2020/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://thenewdaily.com.au/news/politics/australian-politics/2020/02/06/nationals-cabinet-reshuffle-2020/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Will Canavan cross the floor?:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theaustralian.com.au/nation/politics/matt-canavan-reserves-right-to-cross-floor-against-coalition/news-story/4ed6c102bb30f47832b031785fd0daed" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.theaustralian.com.au/nation/politics/matt-canavan-reserves-right-to-cross-floor-against-coalition/news-story/4ed6c102bb30f47832b031785fd0daed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agribusiness&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Water sharing woes:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theaustralian.com.au/nation/politics/nsw-victoria-anger-as-queensland-farmers-get-their-fill-of-water/news-story/66a2068eb58d2285efd091c3165852ce" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.theaustralian.com.au/nation/politics/nsw-victoria-anger-as-queensland-farmers-get-their-fill-of-water/news-story/66a2068eb58d2285efd091c3165852ce&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Community&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Coronavirus threat:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2020-02-09/coronavirus-death-toll-surpasses-sars/11947010" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;http://www.abc.net.au/news/2020-02-09/coronavirus-death-toll-surpasses-sars/11947010&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Shout-out:&lt;/b&gt; to Engage &amp;amp; Create Consulting launching their Engage Course and offering Listeners a discount!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Being a female business owner in regional Australia is amazing, right? But it also comes with its fair share of challenges… The girls at Engage &amp;amp; Create Consulting understand this all too well so they developed the ENGAGE e-course: a road map to clarity, confidence &amp;amp; connection in your business. Their next live round starts March 5th - head to engageandcreateconsulting.com.au and use code ENGAGERBC for $150 off course fees&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Follow Us:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Join the Rural Business Collective community and join the conversation over at &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/ruralbusinesscollective/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/ruralbusinesscollective/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/ruralbusinesscollective/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Beating Around the Bush is the podcast of the &lt;a href="https://www.ruralbusinesscollective.com.au/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Rural Business Collective&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.ruralbusinesscollective.com.au/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;www.ruralbusinesscollective.com.au&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This is a &lt;a href="https://www.cahootsradio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Cahoots Radio&lt;/a&gt; production edited by Skye Manson &lt;a href="https://www.cahootsradio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;www.cahootsradio.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Hosted by &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/wade-dabinett-947763167" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Wade Dabinett&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/wade-dabinett-947763167/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/in/wade-dabinett-947763167/&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/fleuranderson/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Fleur Anderson&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/fleuranderson/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/in/fleuranderson/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Let us know your favourite news stories for the week on email - &lt;a&gt;podcasts@ruralbusinesscollective.com.au&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>fleur@thecahootsgroup.com.au (Beating Around The Bush)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f74d0c2985ac46bf8882cf1dec7b4710</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f74d0c2985ac46bf8882cf1dec7b4710/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Views from Hong Kong : Toilet paper shortages amidst coronavirus panic</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to another episode of Views from Hong Kong!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our topics for today are:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The tragic death of Dr. Li Wenliang&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The Hong Kong government's dithering response to the outbreak&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The ongoing U.S. Democratic primary&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have questions/comments, please write to us at viewshk@outlook.com. We would love to hear from you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow us on twitter @viewshk. Located here: https://twitter.com/viewshk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disclaimer: The views and opinions expressed on the podcast are those of the authors only and do not necessarily reflect the views of any other person or organisation. The authors do not give advice via the podcast and do not warrant or represent the accuracy, completeness, correctness, suitability or validity of any information given on the podcast.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>viewshk@outlook.com (Views from Hong Kong)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">53f79dc8195348f6983be4ec77d75842</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/53f79dc8195348f6983be4ec77d75842/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Jay Talk : Episode 15: Danny Bohnemann Joins</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Creighton cross country runner Danny Bohnemann joins the podcast. We discuss his favorite quotes, the upcoming track season, and the bright future of Creighton XC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">0fd7bf792e7c4e9fa94bc0eda0a7c539</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0fd7bf792e7c4e9fa94bc0eda0a7c539/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 10:13:29 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Uncommon Knowledge : The World According to Thiel</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Recorded on January 17, 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peter Thiel, the cofounder of PayPal and Palantir; early investor in Facebook, LinkedIn, and SpaceX; and the founder of the Thiel Fellowship, which encourages young people to drop out of college to start their own businesses, is interviewed live on stage in front of the members of the Mont Pelerin Society. This wide-ranging conversation covers globalization, the continuing and ever-growing threat from China and what the United States can and can’t do it about, what the rise of Bernie Sanders means for the future of US capitalism, the “derangement” (Thiel’s phrase) of Silicon Valley in the last decade, the scourge of political correctness on campuses and in society at large, and why Thiel thinks we should rethink the doctrine of American exceptionalism.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>institutionhoover@gmail.com (Uncommon Knowledge)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">53c50814c0c9463084b8e380ea61cbe6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/53c50814c0c9463084b8e380ea61cbe6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 08:42:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Red Box Politics Podcast : Big fish in a small reshuffle</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Matt Chorley is joined by James Starkie, a former special adviser to Priti Patel, Dominic Raab and Michael Gove, who explains what is like inside government in reshuffle week.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plus Kieran Andrews, The Times Scottish political editor, on who might be Sturgeon's successor, and Esther Webber, Red Box reporter, on John Bercow not getting a peerage, which isn't funny at all.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>feeds@soundcloud.com (The Red Box Politics Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d5ccc1143fb940b69453b1f82c35b77d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d5ccc1143fb940b69453b1f82c35b77d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 05:30:48 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Realignment : Ep. 24: Krystal Ball and Saagar Enjeti, The Populist Guide to 2020</title><description>Hill Rising co-hosts Krystal Ball and Saagar Enjeti join The Realignment to articulate the case for the populist left and right.</description><author>phegseth@hudson.org (The Realignment)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2fbfa92ad9ff41a7ab96b96f39f401cf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2fbfa92ad9ff41a7ab96b96f39f401cf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 04:00:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Field : The Aftershocks of Iowa in New Hampshire</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Voters in New Hampshire pride themselves on helping winnow the nomination field. While many polls show Senator Bernie Sanders leading in this year’s primary, the caucus debacle in Iowa meant no single candidate left that first contest with full momentum. We flew from Iowa to New Hampshire, following the campaign trail and talking to voters about whether Democrats who don’t support Sanders are coalescing around another choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guests: &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/by/lisa-lerer?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt;Lisa Lerer&lt;/a&gt;, a reporter at The New York Times, covering campaigns, elections and political power, and Clare Toeniskoetter and Jessica Cheung, producers on “The Daily.” For more information on today’s episode, visit &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/thedaily" target="_blank"&gt;nytimes.com/thedaily&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background reading:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mr. Sanders and Mayor Pete Buttigieg, of South Bend, Ind., are hoping to make the race for the nomination &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/09/us/politics/sanders-buttigieg-new-hampshire.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt;a two-person contest&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Still, after a&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/09/us/politics/iowa-democratic-caucuses.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; voting fiasco&lt;/a&gt; in Iowa, it’s possible that&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/10/us/politics/new-hampshire-democrats.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; five leading candidates&lt;/a&gt; will&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/10/us/politics/andrew-yang-new-hampshire.html?action=click&amp;amp;module=Top%20Stories&amp;amp;pgtype=Homepage?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; survive beyond New Hampshire&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;President Trump is coming to New Hampshire, too: He’s scheduled to hold a campaign rally in Manchester tonight and will be on the Republican ballot Tuesday. Here are the&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/live/2020/new-hampshire-primary-02-10?action=click&amp;amp;module=Top%20Stories&amp;amp;pgtype=Homepage?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; latest updates from the state’s last day of primary campaigning&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (The Field)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6b2cb6f4ca4948dc9c5036ab30854dde</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6b2cb6f4ca4948dc9c5036ab30854dde/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 02:55:58 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Effective Compassion : Episode 7: Compassionate Conservatism</title><description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;style type="text/css"&gt;&lt;!--
p.p1 {margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px 'Helvetica Neue'; color: #454545}
span.s1 {text-decoration: underline ; color: #e4af0a}
--&gt;&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;In 1999, George W. Bush launched his presidential campaign as a Compassionate Conservative. Many of the policies he advocated came straight out of the playbook of 19th century poverty fighters. Soon, compassion tactics from 200 years ago were shaping national politics... and drawing criticism from all sides. This episode is about 19th century compassion versus D.C. politics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Effective Compassion is a production of WORLD. Learn more at &lt;a href="http://wng.org/"&gt;&lt;span class="s1"&gt;wng.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>feedback@worldandeverything.com (Effective Compassion)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">93ddc74512e04136aa2d6dae3296987b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/93ddc74512e04136aa2d6dae3296987b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:15:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Verdict with Ted Cruz : Ep. 13 - Two Visions Of America</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Impeachment is over. Now the real political risk begins.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>verdictcruz@gmail.com (Verdict with Ted Cruz)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3efe17189ac64bc6b00a29207b2ecfe8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3efe17189ac64bc6b00a29207b2ecfe8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Is This Happening? with Chris Hayes : The Gettable Voter with Jon Favreau</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Democrats can beat Donald Trump in the 2020 election. Another four years of a Trump White House is not a foregone conclusion. With nine months to go before the general election, there’s a tremendous amount of fear and uncertainty hanging over many of us about the future of the American republic. Amidst this fear, Democratic voters are deciding which candidate is best suited to run against the President. But a lot of the fights over who that person could be are actually fights over how to build a coalition of voters big enough to beat Donald Trump in the electoral college. In envisioning how to build that coalition, you have to look at the margins. If the solid-blue, never-Trump contingency make up the reliable core of the voting bloc, then the folks on the margins are key to solving the puzzle of 2020. Former Obama speechwriter and Crooked Media co-founder Jon Favreau spent time talking with members of this crucial group in four battleground states for the second season of his podcast, "The Wilderness". He joins to discuss what a winning coalition could look like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RELATED LINKS:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://crooked.com/podcast-series/the-wilderness/" target="_blank"&gt;The Wilderness&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.indiebound.org/book/9781982116781?aff=simonsayscom" target="_blank"&gt;Politics is for Power&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;YOU MIGHT ALSO LIKE:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/think/opinion/organizing-trump-country-george-goehl-podcast-transcript-ncna956386" target="_blank"&gt;Organizing in Trump Country with George Goehl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/think/opinion/how-build-progressive-majority-dorian-warren-podcast-transcript-ncna985136" target="_blank"&gt;Building a Progressive Majority Dorian Warren&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>think@nbcuni.com (Why Is This Happening? with Chris Hayes)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">474778e9415e4ff5872c044b1a0fb0b9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/474778e9415e4ff5872c044b1a0fb0b9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hear the Bern : 44 - Big Tents &amp; Iowa (w/ Victoria Rodriguez-Roldán, Dr. Steven Thrasher, &amp; Christine Hallquist)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Briahna explains why Bernie won Iowa despite efforts to discount predominantly minority and working-class voters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victoria Rodriguez-Roldán, a transgender and disability activist, argues that the concerns of her communities cannot be separated from universal programs like Medicare for All.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Journalist and professor Dr. Steven Thrasher explains why LGBTQIA+ communities are often the first and worst affected by scourges like HIV/AIDS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christine Hallquist, an entrepreneur and the first openly transgender major party nominee for governor in the United States, talks building a coalition with those "on the other side" without compromising your values.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victoria on Twitter: &lt;a title="https://twitter.com/yovimi" target="_blank" rel="nofollow ugc" href="https://gate.sc/?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2Fyovimi&amp;amp;token=bdfe3-1-1581397578794"&gt;twitter.com/yovimi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Thrasher on Twitter: &lt;a title="https://twitter.com/thrasherxy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow ugc" href="https://gate.sc/?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2Fthrasherxy&amp;amp;token=96f43f-1-1581397578794"&gt;twitter.com/thrasherxy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christine on Twitter: &lt;a title="https://twitter.com/christine4world" target="_blank" rel="nofollow ugc" href="https://gate.sc/?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2Fchristine4world&amp;amp;token=406d64-1-1581397578794"&gt;twitter.com/christine4world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hearthebern@berniesanders.com (Hear the Bern)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">25d0423f50e143c0b840b2f2fb5b2b24</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/25d0423f50e143c0b840b2f2fb5b2b24/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 21:10:40 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Choice : The Argument: Why Endorse Elizabeth Warren and Amy Klobuchar?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Host Katie Kingsbury visits Opinion's other podcast, "The Argument," to defend the editorial board's two endorsements for Senators Elizabeth Warren and Amy Klobuchar against her disagreeing colleagues Ross Douthat, Michelle Goldberg and David Leonhardt. They talk about the current political moment, each of the Democratic contenders, and the path to the nomination. For background reading on this episode, click here or search for &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/23/opinion/the-argument-endorsement-klobuchar-warren.html" target="_blank"&gt;nytimes.com/theargument&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>opinionpodcasts@nytimes.com (The Choice)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">79c3c9035c6a45e7b16b949c5893a9fa</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/79c3c9035c6a45e7b16b949c5893a9fa/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Left Anchor : Episode 119 - Why It Matters if Bernie Sanders Becomes President</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Just Ryan today with a quick pre-New Hampshire episode going through Reed Hundt's excellent book &lt;a href='https://www.simonandschuster.com/books/A-Crisis-Wasted/Reed-Hundt/9781948122313'&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Crisis Wasted&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; about the presidential transition in 2007-8 and Obama's consequential early decisions as president. We go through how Obama allowed Bush Treasury Secretary Hank Paulson to set the priorities for the bank bailout (thus ensuring Wall Street would not be cut down to size), how Obama allowed his Treasury Secretary Tim Geithner to turn homeowner assistance policy into a quiet backdoor bailout of the banks, and how the Obama administration definitely could have gotten a bigger stimulus but chose not to. Having the right person in the presidential chair matters a great deal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Links to the episodes and articles mentioned: &lt;a href='https://leftanchor.podbean.com/e/episode-112-the-true-history-of-fdr-and-the-new-deal-with-eric-rauchway/'&gt;Eric Rauchway on the Hoover-FDR transition&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href='https://syntheticassets.wordpress.com/2018/09/16/why-claims-that-the-2008-bailout-was-a-success-should-make-you-angry/'&gt;Carolyn Sissoko on the bailout disaster&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href='https://leftanchor.podbean.com/e/episode-97-david-dayen-on-presidential-power/?utm_source=dlvr.it&amp;utm_medium=twitter'&gt;David Dayen on what the next president could do without passing any new laws&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>catchment.basin@gmail.com (Left Anchor)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f284abce29814616a368e8f50643788d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f284abce29814616a368e8f50643788d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 20:03:31 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Full Frontal Honesty in Real Estate  : Realtor Scalp Hunters??</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Have you heard of the Realtor Scalp Hunters? Well, they DO exist! Plus, we talk about limited service listings, job openings in the PHX area, and we get some one on one with Dean Benigno... All right here on Full Frontal Honesty&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts37+b93548@anchor.fm (Full Frontal Honesty in Real Estate )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2b5a3a9e5d024bb78cff67ffc309163e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2b5a3a9e5d024bb78cff67ffc309163e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 19:15:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>UnAborted : We Are a House Divided. Again | UnAborted Ep. 33</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At the State of the Union, Congressional Democrats cheer for saving prematurely born babies who are wanted by their parents while scowling at the President’s call to ban the killing of fully viable, unwanted 3rd trimester babies. Then, appearing on “The View,” Pete Buttigieg defends 9-month abortions and infanticide. Again. 162 years after Lincoln’s speech, we are again a house divided on the question of human equality and human rights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Date: 02/10/20&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>seth@prolifetraining.com (UnAborted)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3577848af6f94d48be7ff0b5a4be288a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3577848af6f94d48be7ff0b5a4be288a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 13:52:18 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MEDIA INDIGENA : Indigenous current affairs : Ep. 196: Another paramilitary push against Wet'suwet'en camps in BC</title><description>&lt;p&gt;THIS WEEK: Wet'suwet'en Redux. It’s an ever-changing story, yet all-too-reminiscent of other Indigenous struggles—and that’s just in &lt;a href="https://declaration.gov.bc.ca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;supposedly pro-UNDRIP&lt;/a&gt; British Columbia. With &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23ShutCanadaDown" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;#ShutCanadaDown&lt;/a&gt; solidarity rallies and blockades going up in different parts of Canada and beyond, we look at how police actions &lt;a href= "https://ricochet.media/en/2924/rcmp-raid-unistoten-healing-centre-arrest-matriarchs"&gt; this time around&lt;/a&gt; compare to &lt;a href= "https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/dec/20/canada-indigenous-land-defenders-police-documents" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;last year’s RCMP raid&lt;/a&gt; of the anti-pipeline, pro-sovereignty encampments in ancestral Wet'suwet'en territory.  Joining host/producer Rick Harp this week are Candis Callison, associate professor in the School of Journalism at UBC, and Kim TallBear, associate professor in the Faculty of Native Studies at the University of Alberta.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;// Our theme is 'nesting' by birocratic.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>indigena.group@gmail.com (MEDIA INDIGENA : Indigenous current affairs)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">12947867cb4b46e2a0628b9d38ff04b5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/12947867cb4b46e2a0628b9d38ff04b5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 12:23:40 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Overwatch : E12: Iran’s Reserve of Last Resort: Uncovering the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps Order of Battle</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Qassem Soleimani’s death and the prospect of further US-Iranian military escalation raise the question of Iran’s military capacity. The Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps’ (IRGC) Ground Forces are Tehran’s reserve of last resort for both internal and external security challenges.  The Iranian regime goes to great lengths to obfuscate the IRGC’s military strength and organization of its ground forces. The Critical Threats Project (CTP) at the American Enterprise Institute (AEI) recently published the &lt;a href= "https://www.criticalthreats.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/20200121-Report-Iran%E2%80%99s-Reserve-of-Last-Resort.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;groundbreaking report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;Iran’s Reserve of Last Resort: Uncovering the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps Ground Forces Order of Battle.&lt;/em&gt; In this episode of Overwatch, AEI Resident Scholar and CTP Director Fred Kagan and CTP Iran Team Lead Nicholas Carl discuss their recent report and the crucial role that the IRGC plays in the regime’s survival and Iranian efforts to project power and export their revolution abroad.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>press@understandingwar.org (Overwatch)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5a5d2a81ab0949cc8039e92280385171</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5a5d2a81ab0949cc8039e92280385171/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 11:28:48 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Under-Told: Verbatim : The Leftover Landmines</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Rebecca Letven is the Cambodia country director for the UK based Mines Advisory Group, or MAG, a non-governmental organization that works to clear explosives and return land to communities. These deadly remnants of the Cambodian civil war were planted in the late 1960s and early 70s by both the genocidal Khmer Rouge and the Cambodian Vietnamese forces. They also include thousands of unexploded bombs dropped by the United States as part of the Vietnam war. Most of the minefields are in rural areas, where close to 80% of Cambodians live and depend on the land for farming or other natural resources.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>undertold@stthomas.edu (Under-Told: Verbatim)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8072336352aa4e0aa39a6ecff2a2e23b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8072336352aa4e0aa39a6ecff2a2e23b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 08:12:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Catchup : Ep.56: The Catchup x The Players' Take</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, Denison sits down once again with the hosts of The Players' Take Podcast to discuss the art of learning how to host a podcast, growing your brand, and a whole lot more. It's an all-new Catchup! Join the discussion!&lt;br&gt;-----------------&lt;br&gt;Follow us:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="http://facebook.com/TheCatchupCast"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="http://instagram.com/TheCatchupCast"&gt;Instragram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-players-take/id1447839963?mt=2"&gt;Players' Take Podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ThePlayersTake"&gt;Players' Take Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="https://www.facebook.com/TheCatchupCast/"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (https://www.facebook.com/TheCatchupCast/)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>stratocast24@yahoo.com (The Catchup)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">870858c7285c4bce8ed2ee7ae1e08ce2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/870858c7285c4bce8ed2ee7ae1e08ce2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>I'm Calling Bovine Scatology : More Guns Means More Violence?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The conventional wisdom on the left is that more guns means more violence, but is it true? Phil Valentine calls bovine scatology on that.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>phil@philvalentine.com (I'm Calling Bovine Scatology)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6f9ab8abf3d64b36b567773db6d40ab1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6f9ab8abf3d64b36b567773db6d40ab1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 04:35:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>So You Wanna Be President? with Chris Matthews : 4 - Play from the Back</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Maybe Iowa didn’t go as planned, but there's a still a chance for your campaign. In a crowded field, great politicians know how to play from the back. They know how to turn a loss into a win. Bill Clinton did just that when he called himself the "Comeback Kid." We break down that moment—and how it helped propel him to the White House—with Republican strategist Susan Del Percio and Beth Fouhy, senior editor of politics for NBC News.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (So You Wanna Be President? with Chris Matthews)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1ba5c9e560b04a45b296ac961d878bca</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1ba5c9e560b04a45b296ac961d878bca/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The SCNS Live Podcast : SCNS Live Season 9 Episode 3: News on Videogames, Anime, and More!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;So much news to cover this week guys.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>admin@untitledscns.com (The SCNS Live Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7cf7feee0528488eb9a8fb30bc760e9a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7cf7feee0528488eb9a8fb30bc760e9a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 20:02:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Reasons to be Cheerful with Ed Miliband and Geoff Lloyd : 125. WALK THIS WAY</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello! We’ve wrapped up warm and headed outside for a good old stroll... because this week we’re diving into the wonders of walking! We speak to neuroscientist and walking champion Shane O’Mara about why it’s so good for our body and mind. Then Joe Irvin from Living Streets and transport planner Susan Claris talk about how we can redesign our public spaces around people rather than cars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AND we chat to Grace Campbell about podcasting, feminism and why she’d never go into politics.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>reasons@cheerfulpodcast.com (Reasons to be Cheerful with Ed Miliband and Geoff Lloyd)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d43e496519e942b1bb6a95b4a93f1a0e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d43e496519e942b1bb6a95b4a93f1a0e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Australia in the World : Ep. 40: Coronavirus; Huawei in the UK; the WTO, and UK / EU trade deals</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Allan and Darren begin this episode with Australia’s response to the novel coronavirus, including the government’s efforts to evacuate Australians from Wuhan, the decision not to charge evacuees, and the decision to the bar entry into Australia of foreigners who have been in or travelled through China. Darren then wonders whether the variation across countries in the response to the virus—notably the hostility of Cambodia’s Prime Minister to wearing masks—is connected to China’s influence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next up is the UK’s decision to allow Huawei to participate in the country’s 5G network. Given Australia came to the opposite position, Allan grapples with the fact that he knows and trusts the judgments of individuals involved with both decisions. Darren asks whether there is much precedent for the inventions by four Australian MPs into the UK debate, or the recent piece by former Australian Signals Directorate senior official Simeon Gilding expressing disappointment with the UK’s decision. What’s the path forward now for Australia? Allan and Darren do not entirely agree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The discussion moves to trade. Now that the Trump administration has neutered the World Trade Organisation’s appellate body by blocking the appointment of new judges, what’s next for the WTO? One interesting possibility is the creation of parallel appellate structures that essentially replicate the WTO model and allow willing countries (including Australia) to prop up the WTO system while a more permanent set of reforms can (hopefully) be negotiated. Finally, Darren asks Allan about bilateral free trade agreements between Australia and both the UK and EU that are on the agenda for 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, we invite our listeners to email us at this address: &lt;a href='mailto:australia.world.pod@gmail.com'&gt;australia.world.pod@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; We welcome feedback, requests and suggestions. You can also contact Darren on twitter @limdarrenj&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to AIIA intern Isabel Hancock for research and audio editing, and Rory Stenning for composing our theme music. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Relevant links&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jane Norman, “Coronavirus evacuees avoid $1,000 charge for flight from China after Federal Government backs down”, ABC News, 2 February 2020: &lt;a href='https://www.abc.net.au/news/2020-02-02/government-blames-dfat-for-coronavirus-charge-mix-up/11921846'&gt;https://www.abc.net.au/news/2020-02-02/government-blames-dfat-for-coronavirus-charge-mix-up/11921846&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hannah Beach, “Quieter response to coronavirus in countries where China holds sway”. New York Times, 2 February 2020: &lt;a href='https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/02/world/asia/china-coronavirus-philippines-thailand.html'&gt;https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/02/world/asia/china-coronavirus-philippines-thailand.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Latika Bourke, “Four Australian MPs urge Britain to ban Huawei”, Sydney Morning Herald, 24 January 2020: &lt;a href='https://www.smh.com.au/world/europe/four-australian-mps-urge-britain-to-ban-huawei-20200124-p53u9x.html'&gt;https://www.smh.com.au/world/europe/four-australian-mps-urge-britain-to-ban-huawei-20200124-p53u9x.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Simeon Gilding, “5G choices: a pivotal moment in world affairs”, ASPI Strategist, 28 January: &lt;a href='https://www.aspistrategist.org.au/5g-choices-a-pivotal-moment-in-world-affairs/'&gt;https://www.aspistrategist.org.au/5g-choices-a-pivotal-moment-in-world-affairs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andrew Tillett and Hans van Leeuwen, “Australian warning over Trump’s WTO bear hug”, Australian Financial Review, 24 January 2020: &lt;a href='https://www.afr.com/politics/federal/australian-warning-over-trump-s-wto-bear-hug-20200123-p53u4h'&gt;https://www.afr.com/politics/federal/australian-warning-over-trump-s-wto-bear-hug-20200123-p53u4h&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ivan Krastev and Stephen Holmes, &lt;em&gt;The light that failed: A reckoning&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;a href='https://www.penguin.co.uk/books/308/308740/the-light-that-failed/9780241345702.html'&gt;https://www.penguin.co.uk/books/308/308740/the-light-that-failed/9780241345702.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scholar’s Stage, “Public intellectuals have short shelf lives—But why?”, 29 January 2020: &lt;a href='https://scholars-stage.blogspot.com/2020/01/why-public-intellectuals-have-short.html'&gt;https://scholars-stage.blogspot.com/2020/01/why-public-intellectuals-have-short.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tyler Cowen, “How public intellectuals can extend their shelf lives”, 6 February 2020: &lt;a href='https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2020/02/how-public-intellectuals-can-extend-their-shelf-lives.html'&gt;https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2020/02/how-public-intellectuals-can-extend-their-shelf-lives.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kristen Roupenian, “Cat person”, The New Yorker, 4 December 2017: &lt;a href='https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2017/12/11/cat-person'&gt;https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2017/12/11/cat-person&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>australia.world.pod@gmail.com (Australia in the World)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ce3f305fe13b4c9ab46b729ac0de8f6f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ce3f305fe13b4c9ab46b729ac0de8f6f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 14:49:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FOX News Sunday Audio Podcast : 2-9-2020 - FOX News Sunday Audio Podcast</title><description>&lt;p&gt;2-9-2020 - FOX News Sunday Audio Podcast&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@foxnewsradio.com (FOX News Sunday Audio Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e97fcab940744a7f9ea0516fcd13ed10</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e97fcab940744a7f9ea0516fcd13ed10/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 11:06:32 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC Meet the Press : Feb. 9 - Pete Buttigieg and Sen. Bernie Sanders</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On a special edition of Meet the Press, Chuck Todd is live in New Hampshire two days before the caucuses. Presidential candidates and front runners Pete Buttigieg and Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) discuss their momentum boost post-Iowa. Kasie Hunt, Joshua Johnson, Claire McCaskill and John E. Sununu join the panel.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>MeetThePress@nbcuni.com (NBC Meet the Press)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4520a2645a9841779a1d18d84811baaf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4520a2645a9841779a1d18d84811baaf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 08:01:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Al Franken Podcast : A Conversation with Jimmy Kimmel</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Al and Jimmy discuss his radio days, Jimmy Kimmel Live’s rough start, then success, bad guests, his emotional appearance after his son’s birth, and his passionate support of universal health care.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>paulwoodywoodhull@gmail.com (The Al Franken Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5c90906587494dcab8e633bcb915d4c3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5c90906587494dcab8e633bcb915d4c3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 07:15:40 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>HYPAT med Jennifer &amp; Julia : 2.4 Sexistiska företag &amp; massmord av kycklingar</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Veckans nyheter är bland annat Julias favoritreklam från Super Bowl, den senaste Victoria's Secret-skandalen och Frankrikes kontroversiella lag. Jennifer senaste vecka leder oss in på samtalsämnet &lt;em&gt;framtidens jobb.&lt;/em&gt; Vilka jobb kommer vi se i framtiden? Vilka jobb kommer försvinna? Och kommer våra nuvarande jobb finnas kvar om några år?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instagram: @hypatpodcast @hipsterjefe @juliahqvist&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jennifer.carp@ymail.com (HYPAT med Jennifer &amp; Julia)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4ab58d78fd88427c9230313780c55095</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4ab58d78fd88427c9230313780c55095/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Article II: Inside Impeachment : Behind the Scenes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this final episode,&amp;nbsp;Steve&amp;nbsp;Kornacki&amp;nbsp;sits&amp;nbsp;down&amp;nbsp;with&amp;nbsp;NBC&amp;nbsp;News&amp;nbsp;journalists&amp;nbsp;to&amp;nbsp;reflect on&amp;nbsp;what it was like to cover the impeachment of President Donald&amp;nbsp;Trump.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NBC News Correspondent Leigh Ann Caldwell,&amp;nbsp;NBC News producer covering the Senate&amp;nbsp;Frank Thorp, and senior White House reporter for NBC News Shannon&amp;nbsp;Pettypiece&amp;nbsp;open&amp;nbsp;up&amp;nbsp;their reporters’ notebooks to share their favorite&amp;nbsp;moments from this historic&amp;nbsp;event.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>articletwopodcast@gmail.com (Article II: Inside Impeachment)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e7bf82ba0e064c53a3148b6359645e79</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e7bf82ba0e064c53a3148b6359645e79/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 17:18:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sean Klitzner Show : The #YangGang</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Tonight gets political. We talk about the top democrats running for office. I can't promise anything we say is serious.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>SeanKlitzner@gmail.com (The Sean Klitzner Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4c849be0f5524fbc8b96efe74a78d32e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4c849be0f5524fbc8b96efe74a78d32e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 20:16:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FontCast : Summer Series - Terry Field, part two</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Terry Field, former Chief of Staff to Premier David Bartlett, is back for the second part of his Summer Series long form interview. He picks up from the high point of the Labor Party's victory in the 1998 state election. Terry also makes some bold predictions for the current government after Will Hodgman's retirement. &lt;/div&gt;</description><author>samikin@me.com (FontCast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f0bc305bbdfe4c5e8d43fd89f94d6290</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f0bc305bbdfe4c5e8d43fd89f94d6290/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 11:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Building Tomorrow : Venture Capital Built Silicon Valley</title><description>&lt;p&gt;While fans of the show&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Silicon Valley&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;might not have much regard for the role of venture capital in technological innovation, the reality is that venture capitalists do more than act as ATMs for startups. They provide crucial business, marketing, and legal expertise, all of which are necessary to actually get a product to market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;But while venture capital might seem obvious to us today, it was a radical idea in the mid-20th century. Paul interviews Spencer Ante about his biography of the founding father of venture capital, Georges Doriot, a French immigrant who revolutionized the way startups are funded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is the relationship between venture capital and start-up owners? Who was Georges Doriot and how did he change the world of venture capital? How is venture capital regulated by the SEC? What barriers do venture capitalists face?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info+5e309ca47cd7f6767ff252f3@mg.pippa.io (Building Tomorrow)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e3c510c82c254b69bc9f292ac53dd3ce</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e3c510c82c254b69bc9f292ac53dd3ce/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 06:20:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>National Review's Radio Free California Podcast : Episode 106: Here’s Wishing the Governor Didn’t Love Us So Much</title><description>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Governor Gavin Newsom introduces a record-setting state budget he says proves what “big-hearted government” can do and proposes a state takeover of private utilities, including PG&amp;amp;E. In other news: we&amp;#8217;ll discuss the case against Assemblyman Bill Brough (R., Dana Point), and school kids dousing themselves in fake oil to fight climate change in Sacramento. Intro music by Metalachi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="mailto:dbahnsen@thebahnsengroup.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;dbahnsen@thebahnsengroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="mailto:Will@calpolicycenter.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;span class="il"&gt;Will&lt;/span&gt;@calpolicycenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span id="m_4124646736231928874gmail-docs-internal-guid-cd11aa91-7fff-d013-c77c-1fd7d60df777"&gt;Show&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span id="m_4124646736231928874gmail-docs-internal-guid-cd11aa91-7fff-d013-c77c-1fd7d60df777"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ocregister.com/2020/01/13/gavin-newsoms-budget-proposal-is-big-and-irresponsible/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.ocregister.com/2020/01/13/gavin-newsoms-budget-proposal-is-big-and-irresponsible/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258086000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFsjTWKTp31Dn4yUX4IBqRkGKO7mw"&gt;Gavin Newsom’s big budget proposal is bloated and irresponsible&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article239050443.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article239050443.html&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258086000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNF5j6qL24XKmuLrVng9HwtI-Q1myg"&gt;California state budget breaks record, tops $220 billion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://californiapolicycenter.org/newsoms-2020-21-budget-a-big-pie-but-empty-calories/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://californiapolicycenter.org/newsoms-2020-21-budget-a-big-pie-but-empty-calories/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258086000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHcioqGgDcdeBYMC6hQg0CDOqSZMw"&gt;Newsom’s 2020-21 Budget – A big pie but empty calories&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.politico.com/states/california/story/2020/01/10/newsom-proposes-medicaid-benefits-for-undocumented-senior-citizens-1248937?fbclid=IwAR3l25K0Z58ey9unZF7hxycfO-r0G5bRq8xAdcZTQS_0J86J0_b6UrVfGXk" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.politico.com/states/california/story/2020/01/10/newsom-proposes-medicaid-benefits-for-undocumented-senior-citizens-1248937?fbclid%3DIwAR3l25K0Z58ey9unZF7hxycfO-r0G5bRq8xAdcZTQS_0J86J0_b6UrVfGXk&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258086000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFc9Qe8Hr1jvCHnl4gLwSPxMrBhHw"&gt;Newsom proposes Medicaid benefits for undocumented senior citizens&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/the-state-worker/article239461768.html#storylink=cpy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/the-state-worker/article239461768.html%23storylink%3Dcpy&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258087000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNF2cvy5dWZsj_1Fmou_mF2R9FJVqw"&gt;Gavin Newsom’s budget would make state government bigger. Can California sustain the spending?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://calmatters.org/commentary/budget-entitlements-as-economy-slows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://calmatters.org/commentary/budget-entitlements-as-economy-slows/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258087000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNH8HqeFQuh3bxA1q-0XLabhPUMI8g"&gt;More entitlements as economy slows?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-01-29/high-profile-california-housing-bill-to-allow-mid-rise-apartments-near-transit-falls-short?utm_source=Essential+California&amp;amp;utm_campaign=5f010e98b4-EMAIL_CAMPAIGN_2020_01_31_01_15&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_term=0_6e35f7f85b-5f010e98b4-84210865" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-01-29/high-profile-california-housing-bill-to-allow-mid-rise-apartments-near-transit-falls-short?utm_source%3DEssential%2BCalifornia%26utm_campaign%3D5f010e98b4-EMAIL_CAMPAIGN_2020_01_31_01_15%26utm_medium%3Demail%26utm_term%3D0_6e35f7f85b-5f010e98b4-84210865&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258087000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNEX6igV6rnFuqt06cPA_4-kkFwcAQ"&gt;SB50 fails again&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sacbee.com/article239806898.html?fbclid=IwAR2-GZTmiZ7aW7q26hC6CVQJQnVZa0Yje1Xgn4kW6VjuvyLWJHZflpReGQ8" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.sacbee.com/article239806898.html?fbclid%3DIwAR2-GZTmiZ7aW7q26hC6CVQJQnVZa0Yje1Xgn4kW6VjuvyLWJHZflpReGQ8&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258087000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFvoonxFinr_fNuof--WOhWO0lXww"&gt;Teens drench themselves in fake oil in climate change protest at California pension fund&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article239920693.html?fbclid=IwAR0UyG4uljsgIbTM-o5CxuIUbSgtfZ8OvzMm-x83cVpxTD2Jd3Y4sv9iyBw" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article239920693.html?fbclid%3DIwAR0UyG4uljsgIbTM-o5CxuIUbSgtfZ8OvzMm-x83cVpxTD2Jd3Y4sv9iyBw&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258087000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNF8-vzTpXd4kY7-8GMxxWV09aGFvg"&gt;Should California take over PG&amp;amp;E? San Francisco Democrat proposes a public utility&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ocregister.com/2020/02/04/the-case-against-bill-brough/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.ocregister.com/2020/02/04/the-case-against-bill-brough/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258087000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNExIIbZvD2S9uvDXNaCe6luvGJHJw"&gt;The case against Bill Brough&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>studio@nationalreview.com (National Review's Radio Free California Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d2dd12ea940146e59647ffaa89107886</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d2dd12ea940146e59647ffaa89107886/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 14:57:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump, Inc.  : An Intimate Dinner with President Trump</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Lev Parnas and Igor Fruman have attained notoriety for their parts in the Ukraine mess. They’re both Soviet-born U.S. citizens who worked closely with the president’s personal lawyer, Rudy Giuliani, serving as emissaries in the campaign to oust then-U.S. Ambassador Marie Yovanovitch and press Ukraine’s government to investigate Joe Biden’s son. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But Parnas and Fruman also exemplify the shattering of norms when it comes to the influence of big money in politics during the administration of President Donald Trump.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Parnas and Fruman are not the first people that we've seen fit this mold of someone with deep foreign connections, who's never given campaign contributions before, suddenly starts giving large amounts of political contributions and then shows up at exclusive events,” said Robert Maguire, the research director at &lt;a href="https://www.citizensforethics.org/"&gt;Citizens for Responsibility and Ethics in Washington&lt;/a&gt;, or CREW. But he says they can be a model for what to look for: political newcomers suddenly making big donations, often using an LLC to obscure their identity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parnas and Fruman now &lt;a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/pr/lev-parnas-and-igor-fruman-charged-conspiring-violate-straw-and-foreign-donor-bans"&gt;face federal criminal charges for&lt;/a&gt;, among other things, allegedly funneling foreign money into U.S. elections and trying to hide its source. (They’ve pleaded not guilty.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The law is clear on this: “At the most basic level, one is not allowed to solicit, accept, or receive any foreign money in connection with a US election at the state, federal, or local level,” said Ellen Weintraub, a member of the Federal Election Commission. In practice, though, it’s perhaps easier than ever for foreign money to enter the American political system undetected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Learn more about how you can dig into campaign finance documents yourself with &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/reporting-recipe-how-to-identify-suspicious-campaign-finance-records"&gt;our new Reporting Recipe&lt;/a&gt;. Read about &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/trump-inc-2020-how-parnas-and-frumans-dodgy-donation-was-uncovered-by-two-people-using-google-translate"&gt;how watchdogs identified Parnas and Fruman’s suspicious campaign contributions&lt;/a&gt; at ProPublica. An earlier version of this story incorrectly identified FEC vice-chair Steven Walther as a Republican; he is an independent.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (Trump, Inc. )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">33f4a865e82c4ef09d97da9e66aee062</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/33f4a865e82c4ef09d97da9e66aee062/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>More Than Enough : 4: We All Deserve An Income Floor: Why the Bold Policy of Guaranteed Income Works</title><description>&lt;div&gt;If guaranteed income is an attempt to provide people with more resources—resources that come with very few restrictions—it demands a conversation with the people who would most benefit from it. It also demands a conversation about deservedness. When we ask “How much would it be?” “Who would get it?” And “How would we pay for it?” what we are really asking is who deserves more and who doesn’t.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m not the only one who thinks Guaranteed income is a realistic option, either—it’s actually being tried out as we speak. Presidential hopeful Andrew Yang advocates for Guaranteed Income as part of his platform. Aisha Nyadoro’s project—The Magnolia Mother’s Trust, which you heard about in Episode 2 [link to episode]—is getting ready to launch their second round of a guaranteed income project in Jackson, Mississippi. The city of Stockton, California, and its mayor Michael Tubbs are also running a demonstration of Guaranteed Income right now—they are working to build an economy that grants everyone the right to have enough to get by.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Over the last two years, I’ve talked to wide-ranging audiences about guaranteed income. One of the things that consistently gets fretted about is the boldness of guaranteed income. People have said to me, What will poor people do with that money? The Right will never go for it. How will we pay for it? And I can’t help but think of the people who thought that ending slavery was too hard, to bold an idea.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Too many of us have become convinced that the rules, as written by fear, scarcity, and avarice, are the ones we must play by.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We don’t. We have to be willing to dream our most courageously when it comes to policy and systems change, because we cut ourselves off from the best possible outcomes if we start compromising our ideal before we begin. So let’s be bold, let’s be courageous, and let’s start by recognizing that this country has more than enough wealth—enough money, enough talent, enough courage—for all of us.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Show Notes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;More Than Enough was developed by Next River Productions. Created and hosted by Mia Birdsong. Audio engineering and music by Nino Moschella. Script development and production by Allison Cook. The content of this podcast was informed by the stories of hundreds of people across the country, only some of whom you heard from. Thank you to everyone who took the time to speak with me and share their story.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Support for the production of More Than Enough was provided by a few generous folks and the Economic Security Project, an organization advancing cash-based interventions in the United States and reigning in corporate monopolies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;More Than Enough is a project of The Nation Magazine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>frank@thenation.com (More Than Enough)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">62b7e1fa81f54ef493dafb2b70d7829b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/62b7e1fa81f54ef493dafb2b70d7829b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bag Man : Wondery presents WeCrashed</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Rise and Fall of WeWork is a stunning story of hope and hubris. WeWork was the poster child for a new economy. Its founders wanted to revolutionize everything about the way people lived their lives. Its charismatic founder Adam Neumann had an intoxicating vision for the company - but did it ever match the reality?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subscribe today:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__http://wondery.fm/wecrashedbagman__;!!PIZeeW5wscynRQ!4D3jTjJXKpFbK_rLRp6Bi57TG4rzoDzG8Oich4R-nFm72nyXk0fXZ1_Xbt94vpNtmXs$" target="_blank"&gt;wondery.fm/wecrashedbagman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (Bag Man)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">af0258c5fc5446318e8e7cad9c5ddedc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/af0258c5fc5446318e8e7cad9c5ddedc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Latest : What Happened in Iowa?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;After a night of chaos and confusion at the Iowa caucuses, and nearly a full day since the results were initially expected, the state’s Democratic Party has announced only partial numbers, from 62 percent of precincts. We look at what the debacle in Iowa will mean for the results — when they’re finally released.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The Latest,” from the team behind “The Daily,” brings you the most important developments on today’s biggest news stories. You can find more information about it &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/column/the-latest" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (The Latest)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6dd0d3add65341bb916ebf0e64d642ff</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6dd0d3add65341bb916ebf0e64d642ff/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 19:11:10 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Beat – CUNY Podcasts : The Rise and Fall of The Young Lords</title><description>&lt;br /&gt;
One of the most influential groups of the radical &amp;#8217;60s was the Young Lords, an organization of poor and working class Puerto Ricans that began as a street gang and rose to confront the racism of institutions from government to religion. Johanna Fernandez, a professor of history at Baruch College, traces their roots and tells the story of their rise and fall in The Young Lords: A Radical History. She talks about it with Beth Harpaz.&lt;br /&gt;</description><author>webservices@cuny.edu (Book Beat – CUNY Podcasts)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3a08a18ca5c748c798258b7d41e858af</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3a08a18ca5c748c798258b7d41e858af/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 15:38:14 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Brown Girls Guide to Politics : What Can We Expect in 2020?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;To learn more about the work of the NAACP Youth &amp; College Division, the League of Conservation Voters and the Planned Parenthood Action Fund, visit their websites:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://naacp.org/youth-college/" target="_blank"&gt;NAACP Youth &amp; College Division&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.lcv.org/" target="_blank"&gt;League of Conservation Voters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.plannedparenthoodaction.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Planned Parenthood Action Fund&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Brown Girls Guide to Politics Podcast is all about amplifying the voices of women who are too often forgotten in media coverage. Host A’shanti Gholar leads conversations with women changing the face of politics. In the BGG to Politics blog, A’shanti created a space for Women of Color to learn about the current state of women in politics, to support others breaking into the political sphere, and to celebrate incredible people changing the course of the country. A’shanti founded the blog and Wonder Media Network is thrilled to extend her platform to audio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow The BGG:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://thebgguide.com/"&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/thebgguide"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://instagram.com/thebgguide"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Wonder Media Network:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://wondermedianetwork.com/"&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/wmnmedia"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://instagram.com/wmn.media"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>pod@wondermedianetwork.com (The Brown Girls Guide to Politics)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e3258dc5b45044b29f0ca651334b0b23</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e3258dc5b45044b29f0ca651334b0b23/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 03:00:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Candace Owens Show : The Candace Owens Show: Tim Ballard</title><description>Slavery is alive and well today. Human trafficking is a booming business that is being propelled by both the powerful and our on-demand sexualized culture. Tim Ballard, former special agent and founder of Operation Underground Railroad, joins Candace to discuss how society aids this multi-billion-dollar criminal enterprise.</description><author>tylerg@prageru.com (The Candace Owens Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ff77bf7eb035405ebfe6932588ef64cc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ff77bf7eb035405ebfe6932588ef64cc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 02:00:20 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hot Take : Jan 2020: No Chill</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The first month of 2020 proves that the climate story has no chill at all. From the Australian bushfires to big important stories on everything from climate vision to radiioactive fracking, the story just keeps getting bigger and crazier. Special guest co-host Meera Subramanian joins Mary and Amy to break it all down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;About Meera: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Meera Subramanian is an award-winning freelance journalist whose work has been published around the world, and her first book is &lt;em&gt;A River Runs Again: India’s Natural World in Crisis&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;from the Barren Cliffs of Rajasthan to the Farmlands of Karnatak&lt;/em&gt;a, published in 2015 by PublicAffairs. She is currently serving as the president of the Society of Environmental Journalists and the Currie C. and Thomas A. Barron Visiting Professor in the Environment and the Humanities at Princeton University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Reading list:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;United in Change, Meera Subramanian &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://orionmagazine.org/article/united-in-change/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://orionmagazine.org/article/united-in-change/&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s Not Just Australia, Rachel Ramirez&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://t.co/xCu8Qh7LUn?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/xCu8Qh7LUn?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;‘Scarier’ Than Hurricane Maria: A Deadly Earthquake Terrifies Puerto Rico&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://t.co/Gwlecq5FhV?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/Gwlecq5FhV?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At the 7th Democratic debate, candidates took every opportunity to talk climate, Zoya Tierstein &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://grist.org/politics/at-the-7th-democratic-debate-candidates-took-every-opportunity-to-talk-climate/"&gt;https://grist.org/politics/at-the-7th-democratic-debate-candidates-took-every-opportunity-to-talk-climate/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For the first time, the Alarmed are now the largest of Global Warming’s Six Americas &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://climatecommunication.yale.edu/publications/for-the-first-time-the-alarmed-are-now-the-largest-of-global-warmings-six-americas/"&gt;https://climatecommunication.yale.edu/publications/for-the-first-time-the-alarmed-are-now-the-largest-of-global-warmings-six-americas/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Emily Townsend's Resignation Email &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/media/2020/jan/10/news-corp-employee-climate-misinformation-bushfire-coverage-email"&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/media/2020/jan/10/news-corp-employee-climate-misinformation-bushfire-coverage-email&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We, the Media, must take some of the blame as Australia Burns&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;John Birmingham&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://t.co/eIp4YB9aOO?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/eIp4YB9aOO?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It's Not Arson, You Absolute Fucking Morons, Brian Kahn &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://earther.gizmodo.com/its-not-arson-you-absolute-fucking-morons-1840862475"&gt;https://earther.gizmodo.com/its-not-arson-you-absolute-fucking-morons-1840862475&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pregnant Women are Asking for Ultrasounds in Australia, Gina Rushton&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://t.co/XUTwPTsdWp?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/XUTwPTsdWp?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Concession to Climate Change I Will Not Make in the Atlantic, Jedediah Britton-Purdy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/01/becoming-parent-age-climate-crisis/604372/?utm_source=twitter&amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;utm_campaign=share"&gt;https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/01/becoming-parent-age-climate-crisis/604372/?utm_source=twitter&amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;utm_campaign=share&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noah’s Rainbow , James Murray&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.businessgreen.com/blog-post/3084916/noahs-rainbow-raising-children-in-an-age-of-climate-crisis"&gt;https://www.businessgreen.com/blog-post/3084916/noahs-rainbow-raising-children-in-an-age-of-climate-crisis&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon’s New Rationale for Working with Big Oil: Saving the Planet, Maddie Stone&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://t.co/kf8UxXdsrJ?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/kf8UxXdsrJ?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google and Amazon Are Now in the Oil Business, Adam Cole:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/recode/2020/1/3/21030688/google-amazon-ai-oil-gas"&gt;https://www.vox.com/recode/2020/1/3/21030688/google-amazon-ai-oil-gas&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;David Roberts, The Sad Truth About Our Boldest Climate Target &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/energy-and-environment/2020/1/3/21045263/climate-change-1-5-degrees-celsius-target-ipcc"&gt;https://www.vox.com/energy-and-environment/2020/1/3/21045263/climate-change-1-5-degrees-celsius-target-ipcc&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diego Arguedas Ortiz, Is It Wrong to be Hopeful About Climate Change? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://t.co/1Heh58QNcQ?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/1Heh58QNcQ?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking to the Future: In 2030, We Ended the Climate Emergency. Here’s How, Eric Holthaus &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://thecorrespondent.com/214/in-2030-we-ended-the-climate-emergency-heres-how/28330740746-6b15af77"&gt;https://thecorrespondent.com/214/in-2030-we-ended-the-climate-emergency-heres-how/28330740746-6b15af77&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Year in Climate Conversations, Emily Raboteau&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://t.co/UDePWvCr4L?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/UDePWvCr4L?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Baby Boomers: You Can Still Be Heroes in the Story of Climate Change, Laura McGann: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2020/1/8/21055097/baby-boomers-climate-change-australia"&gt;https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2020/1/8/21055097/baby-boomers-climate-change-australia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;STAND OUT PIECES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meera: What Climate Change Tells Us about Being Human by Genevieve Gunther &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://blogs.scientificamerican.com/observations/what-climate-change-tells-us-about-being-human/"&gt;https://blogs.scientificamerican.com/observations/what-climate-change-tells-us-about-being-human/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mary: Here Comes the Sun was an Anthem of Hope, Now It’s a Reminder of Climate Change, Amy Brady: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://t.co/8uA55iCI2M?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/8uA55iCI2M?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amy: America’s Radioactive Secret, by Justin Nobel &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-features/oil-gas-fracking-radioactive-investigation-937389/"&gt;https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-features/oil-gas-fracking-radioactive-investigation-937389/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>amy@criticalfrequency.org (Hot Take)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5eb0206d09c04bdbbab3a82c19100a5b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5eb0206d09c04bdbbab3a82c19100a5b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Impeachment, Explained : The impeachment trial convicted American politics</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This episode, likely the final episode of this podcast, is a bit different: It’s a look not just at what happened this week, but at the deep lessons of impeachment, and the unresolved conflicts and contradictions we’re left with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Put simply, the Senate will acquit Donald Trump. But in refusing to even hear witnesses, they have convicted American politics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Want to contact the show? Reach out at &lt;a href="mailto:ezrakleinshow@vox.com"&gt;ezrakleinshow@vox.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ezra's book is available for pre-order! You can find it at &lt;a href="http://simonandschusterpublishing.com/why-were-polarized/"&gt;www.EzraKlein.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can subscribe to Ezra's other podcast &lt;em&gt;The Ezra Klein Show &lt;/em&gt;on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-ezra-klein-show/id1081584611"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/6NOJ6IkTb2GWMj1RpmtnxP"&gt;Spotify,&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/vox/the-ezra-klein-show"&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; or wherever you get your podcasts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Credits: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Host - Ezra Klein&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Producer/Editor - Jeff Geld&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researcher - Roge Karma&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theme Music - Jon Natchez&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EP - Liz Nelson&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Special thanks to Andrew Prokop and Matt Yglesias&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasting@voxmedia.com (Impeachment, Explained)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1cdcb868687847dfb31408013354e7ff</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1cdcb868687847dfb31408013354e7ff/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Asset : What's Next?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Max Bergmann, the host of the Asset Podcast, assesses the Impeachment Trial to date and handicaps what's ahead, as the end of Donald Trump's trial before the Senate looms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To hear the full episode, become a Patreon subscriber. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://www.patreon.com/posts/33614330&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@theassetpodcast.org (The Asset)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">52107dbf8c13443590b57ff7d8215756</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/52107dbf8c13443590b57ff7d8215756/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 08:26:43 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Brendan O'Neill Show : Gisela Stuart: Brexit and belonging</title><description>&lt;p&gt;To mark Brexit Day, former Vote Leave chair Gisela Stuart sits down with Brendan to discuss the future of an independent Britain. Support spiked by becoming a regular donor: &lt;a href='https://www.spiked-online.com/donate-to-spiked/'&gt;https://www.spiked-online.com/donate-to-spiked/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thebrendanoneillshow@spiked-online.com (The Brendan O'Neill Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3aa2ddedac124b808ab7307f1ab45989</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3aa2ddedac124b808ab7307f1ab45989/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 15:24:20 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>DriveTimes Podcast : Episode 14: Elephants, Mangos, and the Chamber of Secrets</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Come one come all to the next episode of the DriveTimes podcast where 2 dads discuss funny, interesting, and good story from throughout the week to give you some hope in life. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thedadbodsshow@gmail.com (DriveTimes Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">df9a97ebd6694825b1e210232b67ed9a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/df9a97ebd6694825b1e210232b67ed9a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 11:47:16 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Armstrong Simms Show : Coach K and Twitter Trends</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Armstrong discusses Coach K screaming at his OWN student section, and decides to comment on the day's Twitter Trends. Join me!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts44+e7b59a4@anchor.fm (The Armstrong Simms Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b2c5a240c29a4d42a54fd906f10902fc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b2c5a240c29a4d42a54fd906f10902fc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 15:02:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>bonkers.ie  : bonkers.ie Looks Closer: So you're approaching retirement age? Here's what you need to know.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A person who’s approaching retirement today, could, theoretically, spend almost as much time in retirement as they did while working. Which means retirement planning is something that needs to be taken seriously and considered carefully. So, in this episode of our Looks Closer series, we chat with Moneycube Co-Founder and Chief Financial Advisor to get the lowdown on what you need to know as you approach your golden years.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts44+e2b7d1c@anchor.fm (bonkers.ie )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4ce724d97fd646f5a216af94914b8306</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4ce724d97fd646f5a216af94914b8306/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 07:18:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Capitol J : Episode 2 - Reporting From The Center Of The EU</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Mark, Joe and Sara talk about their press visit to Brussels, Belgium to learn about the European Union and its institutions, sponsored by the EU Delegation to the United States. &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">f74215de9fa04560a9b0ac3d3a3c5588</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f74215de9fa04560a9b0ac3d3a3c5588/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 09:21:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Daily Bernie Podcast : Hillary Attacks Bernie as he Surges in the Polls</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Daily Bernie podcast is a short-form podcast to give the daily news about Bernie Sanders 2020 campaign and related news about progressive issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In today’s episode we discuss these headlines: Hillary Attacks Bernie as he Surges in the Polls; Bernie is 1st in Iowa and other states; Krystal Ball defends Bernie on CNN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related links:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/ilikebernie-trends-after-hillary-clinton-says-nobody-likes-bernie-sanders-1483273"&gt;#ILIKEBERNIE TRENDS AFTER HILLARY CLINTON SAYS 'NOBODY LIKES' BERNIE SANDERS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/sanders-reacts-to-hillary-clintons-attack-says-on-a-good-day-my-wife-likes-me?via=twitter_page"&gt;Sanders Responds to Hillary Clinton’s Attack: ‘On a Good Day, My Wife Likes Me’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/480101-poll-sanders-leads-by-13-percentage-points-in-utah"&gt;Leading by 9 in New Iowa Poll, Sanders Says His Campaign Is 'Worst Nightmare' of Trump and Billionaire Class&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/oh-my-god-sanders-can-win-democrats-grapple-bernie-surge-n1123806"&gt;'Oh my God, Sanders can win': Democrats grapple with Bernie surge in Iowa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/480101-poll-sanders-leads-by-13-percentage-points-in-utah"&gt;Poll: Sanders up 13 points in Utah&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/22/politics/cnn-poll-sanders-biden-january-national/index.html"&gt;CNN poll: Bernie Sanders surges to join Biden atop Democratic presidential pack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Support the podcast!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Support the Daily Bernie podcast on Patreon: &lt;a href="http://patreon.com/dailyberniepod"&gt;http://patreon.com/dailyberniepod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Twitter: &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/TheDailyBernie"&gt;http://twitter.com/TheDailyBernie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Facebook: &lt;a href="http://facebook.com/dailyberniepod"&gt;http://facebook.com/dailyberniepod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Instagram: &lt;a href="http://instagram.com/dailyberniepod"&gt;http://instagram.com/dailyberniepod&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Website: &lt;a href="http://www.dailyberniepod.com/"&gt;http://www.dailyberniepod.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can find our podcast on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-daily-bernie-podcast/id1493033686?uo=4"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/0kh8ZxeLAgW1y6tjWx5mlS"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, and other podcast apps! Remember to rate, review, and subscribe!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Music:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Music from https://filmmusic.io&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;"Limit 70" by Kevin MacLeod (https://incompetech.com)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;License: CC BY (&lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/"&gt;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="http://patreon.com/dailybernpod"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (http://patreon.com/dailybernpod)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>dailyberniepod@gmail.com (The Daily Bernie Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e818288dfdbc4b578d43c28618f0d316</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e818288dfdbc4b578d43c28618f0d316/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>BTS with CTV News Vancouver : Flight 752: Finding &amp; Telling the Victims' Stories</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The world was shocked when a Ukrainian Airlines flight went down near Tehran, but when officials confirmed dozens of Canadians were on board our nation was stunned -- as journalists sprang into action to tell the stories of the innocent lives taken too soon. With so many &lt;a href="https://bc.ctvnews.ca/sorry-we-lost-you-grief-stricken-canadians-react-to-cause-of-plane-crash-1.4763547"&gt;victims in the Lower Mainland&lt;/a&gt;, CTV Vancouver journalists were inundated with heart-wrenching stories as communities mourned the tragedy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bc.ctvnews.ca/bts-podcast"&gt;BTS with CTV&lt;/a&gt; Vancouver host &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/PennyDaflos"&gt;Penny Daflos&lt;/a&gt; and reporter &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ctv_shannon"&gt;Shannon Paterson&lt;/a&gt; describe the difficult steps in finding the loved ones left behind, then respectfully conveying the loss felt by their families, friends, and communities. This is, quite simply, one of the toughest jobs reporters have, but they are often a welcome conduit for grieving loved ones to express their loss.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>iheartradiopodcasts@bellmedia.ca (BTS with CTV News Vancouver)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7e4bd092725a4b1f8a5a652076878067</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7e4bd092725a4b1f8a5a652076878067/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 19:35:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Patriots Fight Media : PFM: The Bidens - Part 1</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Part 1 of the expose of the Biden family and their internationally corrupt dealings. Showcased in this episode: Hunter Biden, Devon Archer, and Bohai Harvest RST -- the joint venture deal between the Biden family and the state of China.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ford@patriotsfight.com (Patriots Fight Media)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">20d1191c9f8940b291980c52801dd003</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/20d1191c9f8940b291980c52801dd003/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Blinders Off : STL Neighborhoods: Midtown 37 of 79</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Midtown is one of St. Louis' most well - loved neighborhoods...but how well do you know the area?  Can you tell the difference between “Historic Midtown”, “Midtown”, and “midtown”? Matt &amp; Lucas explore current boundaries, historical neighborhood designations, Art Deco cop shops, as well as test their knowledge of landmarks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Check out our &lt;a href= "http://bit.ly/midtownstl" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;show notes&lt;/a&gt; for additional information.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Questions? Comments?  Email us at &lt;a href= "mailto:BlindersOffPodcast@gmail.com"&gt;BlindersOffPodcast@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;, or reach out to us on &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/blindersoffpodcast/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/blindersoffpodcast/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/blindersoffSTL"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Original photos by Russell Ward, Landmark Mashup illustration by &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/missiadair/"&gt;Missi Adair&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Find us at &lt;a href= "https://www.blindersoff.show/"&gt;blindersoff.show&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>blindersoffpodcast@gmail.com (Blinders Off)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fd1d21de679e4249ac006fcf2a0f0071</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fd1d21de679e4249ac006fcf2a0f0071/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 12:48:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Political Mind of Jerry Brown : BONUS: Jerry Brown on the 2020 Election, Education Policy, and His Next Portrait (LIVE in San Francisco)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Jerry Brown shares his thoughts on the 2020 election, his own presidential campaigns, efforts to reform his state education policies, and more with KQED&amp;#8217;s Scott Shafer. Recorded at the  Herbst Theatre in San Francisco on January 13, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ondemand@kqed.org (The Political Mind of Jerry Brown)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">62656bd1fb1344f5be5f3d366e216e4d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/62656bd1fb1344f5be5f3d366e216e4d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 17:59:25 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Women belong in the House : Bonus: Introducing Ordinary Equality</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/ordinary-equality/id1492330633"&gt;Subscribe now&lt;/a&gt; to hear Episode 1 of Ordinary Equality.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>pod@wondermedianetwork.com (Women belong in the House)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">077dd4f42a454833b9e14e9ffbebb842</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/077dd4f42a454833b9e14e9ffbebb842/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 03:00:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MORNINGS with BOB MARRONE on Radio Westchester ™ : Local Westchester Dobbs Ferry Top News Stories of the Day - January 13, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://radiowestchester.com/january-20-2020-6-am-10-am/"&gt;January 20, 2020 – 6 AM – 10 AM&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://radiowestchester.com"&gt;Radio Westchester ™ Local NYC Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>production@radiowestchester.com (MORNINGS with BOB MARRONE on Radio Westchester ™)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">73a680f6a29a404c8a9f6ff1f6ef76bf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/73a680f6a29a404c8a9f6ff1f6ef76bf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 15:09:44 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>