<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My News feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My news episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My News feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 15:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>FOX News Radio Newscast : 8AM EDT 03/07/2020 Newscast</title><description>Latest FOX News hourly newscast.&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=mt0P3pAkyJ0:gkR5hGtjDU4:yIl2AUoC8zA"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=yIl2AUoC8zA" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=mt0P3pAkyJ0:gkR5hGtjDU4:qj6IDK7rITs"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=qj6IDK7rITs" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=mt0P3pAkyJ0:gkR5hGtjDU4:O3QAOHgViy4"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=O3QAOHgViy4" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=mt0P3pAkyJ0:gkR5hGtjDU4:I9og5sOYxJI"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=I9og5sOYxJI" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/FoxNewsRadio/~4/mt0P3pAkyJ0" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>podcast@foxnewsradio.com (FOX News Radio Newscast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">209502f3d7534a4eaf5af9ab570ce3d2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/209502f3d7534a4eaf5af9ab570ce3d2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 05:08:21 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>NPR News Now : NPR News: 03-07-2020 8AM ET</title><description>NPR News: 03-07-2020 8AM ET</description><author>PodCasts@npr.org (NPR News Now)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5ced3b163a3848059b9dcd4f1cceec82</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5ced3b163a3848059b9dcd4f1cceec82/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Up First : March 7, 2020</title><description>Officials in Washington State are scrambling to identify new coronavirus infections. President Trump visited tornado victims and CDC workers. And in Europe, infections are increasing and the response to the outbreak varies country to country.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (Up First)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c289277f8bca4424b359865dd964d3be</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c289277f8bca4424b359865dd964d3be/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 04:40:37 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Rick &amp; Bubba University Podcast : Ep 22 | Good Christian Movies? Yes, They Exist! | Guest: Andy Erwin</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Rick &amp;amp; Bubba visit with Andy Erwin, half of the filmmaking duo the Erwin Brothers. Together, they strive to create excellent films — not just Christian films. Their movies have all opened in the top ten on opening weekends, including "October Baby," "Moms' Night Out," "Woodlawn," and the 2018 smash hit "I Can Only Imagine." With their upcoming film, "I Still Believe," hitting theaters March 13, 2020, the Erwin Brothers are continuing to bring the light of the gospel to the dark world of Hollywood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today's Sponsor:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CarShield: Get your vehicle covered by the ultimate in vehicle service protection before it's too late. CarShield has affordable protection plans that can save you thousands on a covered repair, including computers, GPS, electronics, and more. With CarShield, you’re behind the wheel of your plan. CarShield has customizable monthly plans with rates as low as $99 a month! CarShield has helped over one million customers! So, drive with confidence knowing you got coverage from America’s number one auto protection provider. Get covered by CarShield today. Call 800-CAR-6000 and mention code RICKBUBBA or visit &lt;a href="http://carshield.com%20with%20code%20RICKBUBBA"&gt;http://carshield.com with code RICKBUBBA&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@theblaze.com (Rick &amp; Bubba University Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">57c7a9bfd76b44d8945ce7efac1b0bf3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/57c7a9bfd76b44d8945ce7efac1b0bf3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>KRDO Newsradio 105.5 FM • 1240 AM • 92.5 FM : Help to Heat Your Home! - KRDO's Afternoon News with Ted Robertson - Kristina Iodice - March 6, 2020</title><description>&lt;p style="text-align:justify;"&gt;Do you need help paying the costs to heat your home? Do you know of anyone who does?  The El Paso County Department of Human Services' Low Income Energy Assistance Program, or, LEAP, is available through April.  Get all the details in the podcast.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Listen Now!  &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ted.robertson@krdo.com (KRDO Newsradio 105.5 FM • 1240 AM • 92.5 FM)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cba5eea97d3c4f309e12c3c02b18505f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cba5eea97d3c4f309e12c3c02b18505f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 02:49:35 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Start Here : Bonus: What You Need to Know About COVID-19</title><description>It's your user guide to the coronavirus outbreak. In a special edition of Start Here, ABC News Chief Medical Correspondent Dr. Jennifer Ashton answers listener questions about the outbreak, telling us what we should (and shouldn't) be doing to protect ourselves.
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt; Like the show? Leave a review: http://bit.ly/ReviewStartHere &lt;p&gt; Follow @StartHereABC for exclusive content, show updates and more:&lt;br&gt; - Twitter: https://www.twitter.com/starthereabc&lt;br&gt; - Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/starthereabc&lt;br&gt; - Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/starthereabc &lt;p&gt; Discover more ABC News podcasts: http://www.abcnewspodcasts.com &lt;p&gt; Start Here is produced by ABC Audio. For more information: http://www.abcnewspodcasts.com</description><author>abc.podcast.support@abc.com (Start Here)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1b6d8eef9ca84d09925fef40877e36f4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1b6d8eef9ca84d09925fef40877e36f4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 02:30:38 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The FOX News Rundown : FOX News Rundown Extra: Charles Payne on the Economic Impact of the Coronavirus</title><description>&lt;p&gt;President Trump signed an $8.3 billion bipartisan spending bill on Friday to help fight the coronavirus outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this week, Charles Payne host of "Making Money with Charles Payne" on FOX Business joined the FOX News Rundown to talk about the global economic impact of the coronavirus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Payne discusses, with host Lisa Brady, how the coronavirus is affecting businesses, the travel industry and stocks. He explains why he thinks the illness will be short term economic hit to the U.S. and what it's like reporting on the illness without causing a mass hysteria both economically and medically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Payne also talks about his book "Unstoppable Prosperity." He tells us why he wrote the book and why he thinks it is helpful for anyone who is interested in investing the stock market, but may be nervous to do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll hear all of this and more from Fox Business anchor Charles Payne on The Fox News Rundown Extra.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/FoxNewsRundown/~4/OdErYEEjvT8" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>podcasts@foxnewsradio.com (The FOX News Rundown)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1e72ad18db8d4f6daf92edca2b34e5f0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1e72ad18db8d4f6daf92edca2b34e5f0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best of Coast to Coast AM : Anunnaki - Best of Coast to Coast AM - 3/6/20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;George Noory and historian Dr. Heather Lynn discuss her research into evidence of an alien race called the Anunnaki that were viewed as gods and could have created primitive human life to use as slaves to mine gold for their planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts@rsvmedia.com (The Best of Coast to Coast AM)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">66b049ab85584dcc9ae394440c110234</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/66b049ab85584dcc9ae394440c110234/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 01:57:21 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Glenn Beck Program : Ep 70 | Don’t Feel Guilty Celebrating America’s Miracles | Michael Medved | The Glenn Beck Podcast</title><description>&lt;p&gt;America has forgotten how blessed it has been throughout its history. But Michael Medved hasn’t just studied history – he’s lived it. He worked on the Robert F. Kennedy campaign on the day he was shot. He went to Yale Law School with Bill and Hillary Clinton. He’s a former liberal activist who argues what the modern-day Left adamantly refutes: America is a kingdom of kindness, blessed by God. Film critic, best-selling author, acclaimed conservative radio host, and proud American, Michael sits down with Glenn to discuss his latest book, “God’s Hand on America: Divine Providence in the Modern Era.” From freedom to electricity, America has made the world a better place. But if we’re not grateful, we’ll only feel guilty.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ccardon@blazemedia.com (The Glenn Beck Program)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bd715636f0d4483eb2b53ca6676e775a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bd715636f0d4483eb2b53ca6676e775a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rachel Maddow Show : BONUS: Organizing in Trump Country with George Goehl</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As a bonus for our listeners, Rachel is sharing a preview of one of her favorite episodes of “Why Is This Happening? with Chris Hayes”&lt;em&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;In this episode, Chris talks with grassroots organizer and Director of People’s Action, George Goehl, about how Democrats can win in deep red America—a conversation that feels particularly relevant during 2020 primary season. Goehl, who focuses his efforts on white rural America, tells Chris how his own story of poverty and addiction helped inform how he works to build across race and place in order to lay the groundwork for radical change.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We hope you enjoy the preview. Listen to the full episode and subscribe to “Why Is This Happening? with Chris Hayes”:&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.chtbl.com/cNMwXv_A?sid=partners" target="_blank"&gt;https://link.chtbl.com/cNMwXv_A?sid=partners&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (The Rachel Maddow Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">08970fbd2dc740b2a542950e9f88bd86</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/08970fbd2dc740b2a542950e9f88bd86/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Lawfare Podcast : Joseph Nye on "Do Morals Matter?: Presidents and Foreign Policy from FDR to Trump"</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We ask a lot of questions about foreign policy on this podcast. Why do certain countries make certain decisions? What are the interests of the players in question? What are the consequences and, of course, the legality of foreign policy choices. In a new book, Joseph Nye, professor emeritus and former dean of the Harvard Kennedy School, asks another question about foreign policy. Do morals matter? Jack Goldsmith sat down with Nye to discuss his new book "Do Morals Matter?: Presidents and Foreign Policy from FDR to Trump." They discussed the ethical and theoretical factors by which Nye judged each president before going through many of the cases he focuses on in the book.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>benjamin.wittes@lawfareblog.com (The Lawfare Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f0892a612d454d40bb20c1551e34beeb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f0892a612d454d40bb20c1551e34beeb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The 11th Hour with Brian Williams : Day 1,142: Trump praises coronavirus response as cases rack up and markets spiral</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Trump contradicted other members of his administration on its coronavirus response as the number of cases confirmed continues to tick up and stock markets again went down. Plus, we discuss the next phase of the 2020 campaign. Joining us are Shannon Pettypiece, Jonathan Allen, Lanhee Chen, Maya Wiley, Victoria DeFrancesco Soto, and Rep. Ro Khanna all join.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (The 11th Hour with Brian Williams)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">92074f29ed7b46ad8dc5769ee1d76001</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/92074f29ed7b46ad8dc5769ee1d76001/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 21:23:12 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Last Word with Lawrence O’Donnell : Trump response to coronavirus outbreak continues to confound after U.S. death toll reaches at least 15</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Tonight on The Last Word: President Trump’s response to the coronavirus outbreak continues to receive criticism, especially after calling the Governor Jay Inslee a “snake” and falsely claiming that coronavirus tests are available to all who want them during a visit to the CDC earlier today. In a surprise move, Trump has replaced Mick Mulvaney with Rep. Mark Meadows as his chief of staff. Plus, more on the 2020 race as Bernie Sanders turns up his criticisms of Joe Biden, and a Last Word on Alabama Gov. Kay Ivey following the execution of Nathaniel Woods. Dr. Celine Gounder, Gene Sperling, Sara Nelson, Rick Stengel, and Zerlina Maxwell join Lawrence O’Donnell. Neal Katyal also joins to discuss AG William Barr after a federal judge demanded that the DOJ let him review the unredacted Mueller report to ensure that redactions were “not tainted” by Barr.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (The Last Word with Lawrence O’Donnell)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">44c26cb1be8d4091b1efee70f20a2f3a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/44c26cb1be8d4091b1efee70f20a2f3a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 20:25:25 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>ESPN Chicago GameNight : 3/6 8PM: NBA Top 25 Under 25</title><description>"Generation Next": We discuss the top 25 players under the age of 25 in the NBA, and "who replaces Lebron as the face of the NBA?"</description><author>feedback@goodkarmabrands.com (ESPN Chicago GameNight)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b7097f0cf614471e982b106ba20bf6b6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b7097f0cf614471e982b106ba20bf6b6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 19:07:52 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC Nightly News with Lester Holt : Friday, March 6, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At least 21 people test positive for coronavirus on cruise ship held off California coast, South by Southwest canceled over coronavirus fears, and how the outbreak is impacting American businesses.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (NBC Nightly News with Lester Holt)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">19eeea17b54747ceae0e85411c64e0f7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/19eeea17b54747ceae0e85411c64e0f7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 19:02:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The David J. Harris Jr Show : Daily Show: Dems Vote For Sexual Predators, Ilhan Omar Loses it, MSNBC's Massive Blunder and @realDonaldTrump!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Tune into the Daily show with David J. Harris Jr. 4 PM PST / 7 PM EST. Catch the highlights, exclusive interviews, and more wherever you get your podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@davidharrisjr.com (The David J. Harris Jr Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a3485587759a491db4da9ef993f17e05</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a3485587759a491db4da9ef993f17e05/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 18:45:34 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mark Levin Podcast : Mark Levin Audio Rewind - 3/6/20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On Friday's Mark Levin Show, Republicans in the Senate are lurching leftward. There is massive spending going on and the thirst for cheap labor is in full swing as they expand legal immigration. Mitch McConnell is allowing all of this to go on despite its effect on our country. Then, Chinese journalist Chen Quishi visited Hong Kong and that's when everything changed. He uploaded a video of the Hong Kong protests to a social media site and that's when his trip was cut short by the Chinese police and lawyers association for a month-long interrogation by multiple Chinese government agencies. Chen and his colleague Fong have disappeared again and have not been seen since. Sadly, the media has ignored the actions of the genocidal Chinese regime. The media has also miscalculated the cost of Mike Bloomberg's campaign spending making simple arithmetical errors on live TV. While they claim that there's too much money in politics, it seems that there's too little IQ in American newsrooms. Also, the media claims that the coronavirus response has been handled clumsily; have they ever criticized the handling of the Flu? A virus is a virus. President Trump was right when he said that the fake news was the enemy of the people. Later, it’s a dangerous trend when the losers of elections coalesce with critics of the winner to persecute the winner of the election, and lamentably this isn't happening in a tyrannical communist country — it happened here in the U.S and is happening right now in Israel. Afterward, no white man, nor any black man has done more to end slavery in America than Abraham Lincoln, yet, the 1619 project rejects this truth.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wwopodcasts@westwoodone.com (Mark Levin Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1dccc90c3d01468e820a484517397c43</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1dccc90c3d01468e820a484517397c43/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 18:33:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>All In with Chris Hayes : Trump taps Mark Meadows to replace Mulvaney as chief of staff</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Tonight: Donald Trump's grand deception in the face of a pandemic. Plus, how markets understand coronavirus better than the President. Then, how the Democratic race was turned on its head in 7 short days—and how African American voters are driving that change.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (All In with Chris Hayes)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ab5e971a77584b86a26556ac69fb635c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ab5e971a77584b86a26556ac69fb635c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 18:16:18 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Gist : Biden Has the Obama Coalition</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On the Gist, the International Criminal Court.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the interview, musician Stephen Malkmus is here to talk about his new album &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/album/3SAhjjtkodnZ9cEiiOiTAA"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Traditional Techniques&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. He and Mike discuss the various instruments he used, tennis, and Santa Con.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the spiel, Biden’s got the Obama coalition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slate Plus members get bonus segments and ad-free podcast feeds. &lt;a href="https://my.slate.com/plus?utm_medium=link&amp;amp;utm_campaign=plus_pod&amp;amp;utm_content=The_Gist&amp;amp;utm_source=show_notes"&gt;Sign up&lt;/a&gt; now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thegist@slate.com (The Gist)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e2b2f552618548c8badf0b8d53759078</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e2b2f552618548c8badf0b8d53759078/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 18:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Freedomizer Radio : The Delusion Solution</title><description>Delusion Solution-  What is really happening to our state, to our country, and to our world? What does the future hold? Will our educational system continue to dumb down our children?  Has America arrived at the point of no return?”

Are you ready to make sense of current events, to know the truth, to pierce the veil? Join myself Tara Dawn as (your host) and Rudy Smith (my co-host) as we will be bringing you the News and how it relates to the times we live in. How does it affect you the individual, and we as a nation of diverse backgrounds, what it means for people of faith, and how we can make informed decisions concerning the times we live in. Watching with our ears and listening with our eyes to bring you solutions to the many delusions that bombard us daily.

Join us Every Friday from 6-9pacific/9-12 midnight eastern. Call in number: 319-527-6208

Also please join our FB page: Click Here to Like 

https://www.facebook.com/Delusion.Solution/

You can also find us here at Minds.com: 

https://www.minds.com/Delusion_Solution</description><author>Proof@freedomizerradio.com (Freedomizer Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9492724aec564635b3265b4bc0adf9a6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9492724aec564635b3265b4bc0adf9a6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 18:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Beat with Ari Melber : Elizabeth Warren praises Biden's character as he builds delegate lead</title><description>&lt;p&gt;MSNBC's Ari Melber hosts "The Beat." Jadakiss and Dan Abrams join for "Fallback Friday."&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ari@msnbc.com (The Beat with Ari Melber)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">11789237ba1d4b81ac2799ec26991b76</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/11789237ba1d4b81ac2799ec26991b76/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 17:05:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>We the People : The Future of the CFPB</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Richard Cordray, the first Director of the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau from 2012-2017, and Ilya Shapiro, the co-author of an amicus brief in support of &lt;em&gt;Seila Law, &lt;/em&gt;joined host Jeffrey Rosen to discuss the &lt;em&gt;Seila Law LLC v. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau &lt;/em&gt;case. This case, which the Supreme Court heard oral arguments in on Tuesday, is a challenge to the constitutionality of the leadership structure of the CFPB, and its outcome could affect the future of the agency as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CFPB is a regulatory agency responsible for consumer protection in the financial sector. Currently, the president can only fire the CFPB director “for cause,” i.e. only for wrongdoing, not for a policy disagreement. This lawsuit asks whether that restriction violates presidential power and the separation of powers, and, if it does, can it be struck down without invalidating the entire Dodd-Frank Act, which created the CFPB? This episode explores those questions and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Questions or comments about the podcast? Email us at podcast@constitutioncenter.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jmcdermott@constitutioncenter.org (We the People)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ecad5050d6f941e9b2122b65ae74f295</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ecad5050d6f941e9b2122b65ae74f295/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 17:01:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Stu Does America : Ep 19 | Stu Does Medicare For All: It's Not What You're Expecting  | Guests: Robby Soave &amp; Grant Stinchfield</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Stu does … Medicare for All! There's a lot of myths and confusing polls surrounding Medicare for All, so Stu's here to give you the lowdown on what it ACTUALLY means. Spoiler: It ain't great. And, Reason's Robby Soave calls in to explain why the radical Left abandoned the most woke of their candidates on Super Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ccardon@blazemedia.com (Stu Does America)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ee038bb56ac04d02ae7550744b5e484f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ee038bb56ac04d02ae7550744b5e484f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Two Minutes of Truth with Phil Valentine : Liberals Are Horrible at Math</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Did Bloomberg really spend a million dollars per person in his presidential campaign? Not hardly. Liberals are horrible at math.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>phil@philvalentine.com (Two Minutes of Truth with Phil Valentine)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3dae3ce1ea694d4cb460b649c52c5144</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3dae3ce1ea694d4cb460b649c52c5144/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 16:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The News &amp; Why It Matters : Ep 486 | Anxiety Management: The Reason Bill Clinton Says He Had Affair</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A new IG report shows that the FBI dropped the ball on domestic terrorist attacks in the U.S., with over 20 attacks since 9/11, and Rand Paul calls out former FBI Director James Comey on it. Former President Bill Clinton tells "Hillary" documentary filmmakers that he only had the affair with Monica Lewinsky to "manage his anxiety" about being president. And Hillary Clinton claims she had NO idea he was having the affair. Interesting. And Democrats are bad at math, as Brian Williams interviews a guest who made the bold claim that Michael Bloomberg could have given every American one million dollars instead of spending $500 million on campaign ads. Didn't realize there were only 500 people in America! And Elizabeth Warren lost because ... sexism. And Tito's Vodka had to actually warn people that you cannot use its vodka as hand sanitizer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today's Sponsor:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take the Ruff Greens 14-Day JumpStart Challenge today for just $14.95 and see the difference in your dog in 14 days or less. If you want to see your dog thrive again, just go to https://www.ruffgreens.com/blaze&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tcardon@glennbeck.com (The News &amp; Why It Matters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">adc054beff034ced80440cd2761739f4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/adc054beff034ced80440cd2761739f4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 15:13:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Deadline: White House : "He wants to be the bride at the wedding, the corpse at the funeral"</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Nicolle Wallace discusses the credibility crisis the White House faces as the coronavirus continues to spread. Plus, a federal judge criticizes the attorney general and a new poll shows Joe Biden with a significant lead over Bernie Sanders nationally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joined by: New York Times political reporter Nick Confessore, Princeton University's Eddie Glaude, former top State Department official Rick Stengel, NBC News senior business correspondent Stephanie Ruhle, politics reporter for the Daily Beast Betsy Woodruff Swan, Dr. Amy Compton-Phillips, The Bulwark editor-at-large Charlie Sykes, and National Action Network president Reverend Al Sharpton&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (Deadline: White House)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4f88c02e5b2740f6ae87fa5a799f6601</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4f88c02e5b2740f6ae87fa5a799f6601/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 15:09:39 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WSJ What’s News : Coronavirus Sparks More Turbulence on Wall Street</title><description>P.M. Edition for March 6th: Wall Street caps off a tumultuous week with another steep decline. The Wall Street Journal's Paul Vigna looks at the market's winners and losers for the week. Also, immigration officials will begin collecting DNA samples from migrants crossing the border. Michelle Hackman looks at how the plan is likely to raise privacy concerns. J.R. Whalen hosts.&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@dowjones.com (WSJ What’s News)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">77c27961de1748a7a558d068f3febd3d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/77c27961de1748a7a558d068f3febd3d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 14:38:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ticket: Politics from The Atlantic : Beating Donald Trump, with David Plouffe</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The campaign manager behind Obama’s 2008 election breaks down the state of the Democratic party. What do Bernie Sanders and Joe Biden each need to do to win the nomination? And for an election Plouffe says has probably “the biggest stakes the country's ever known,” what do Democrats have to do to defeat President Trump?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcastproduct@theatlantic.com (The Ticket: Politics from The Atlantic)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bd11ac25431d483ea2fe9e0f62290694</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bd11ac25431d483ea2fe9e0f62290694/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 14:36:49 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Daily Detroit : Fun Things To Do In March Plus Restaurant Openings And Closings Around Metro Detroit</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The weekend is here and that means the fun lane is open here at Daily Detroit. Joining Jer and Sven Gustafson in the studio is our “man about town,” who drinks and eats all the things, Devon O’Reilly.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We’re going to hit on some of the fun stuff happening around town this next month, the hot spots and openings to go to. And, sadly, the closings.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Some of the places and events covered include:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;St. Patrick’s Day in Corktown: 3/15 Marche Du Nain Rouge: 3/22 Detroit Tigers Opening Day: 3/30&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Openings: Ferndale Project Joe Louis Southern Kitchen Condado Tacos Planthropie Congregation Farmer Frank’s Bea’s&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Closings: Fort Street Galley Craftwork, last day is March 7 Gold Cash Gold Greenspace Cafe in Ferndale El Guapo Granite City in the RenCen Kid Rock Made in Detroit&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For sale: Polonia in Hamtramck&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>dailydetroit@gmail.com (Daily Detroit)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d02a932ae7bb4014bf6be39e71b0f658</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d02a932ae7bb4014bf6be39e71b0f658/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 14:32:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Savage Nation Podcast : Are You Suffering From Corona-Phobia?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you fearful of the Coronavirus? How has your daily life been affected?  Are we better safe than sorry?  Should we take a pollyanna view of this?  Savage has a premonition, the virus will mutate in the homeless community; Bill Clinton excuses Monica Lewinsky affair saying he did it to help his anxiety; Homosexuals in Iran are having sex reassignment surgery to avoid execution. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wwopodcasts@westwoodone.com (The Savage Nation Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bf863c1f5080447387853f1e91f5ecf0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bf863c1f5080447387853f1e91f5ecf0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 14:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>CNN News Briefing : Evening news briefing from CNN</title><description>https://www.cnn.com/videos/us/2020/03/06/daily-news-briefing-03062020-2.cnn &lt;a href="http://knit.audio/podcast-advertising"&gt;via Knit&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcast@turner.com (CNN News Briefing)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">643b0599759d41f89c20d6f139eb5714</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/643b0599759d41f89c20d6f139eb5714/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 14:17:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Journal. : Why So Few CEOs Are Women</title><description>Fewer than 6% of CEOs are women. A Wall Street Journal study offers a new explanation for why. WSJ's Vanessa Fuhrmans looks at what keeps women from the chief executive job.</description><author>podcasts@dowjones.com (The Journal.)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">519abddf157e491eaa7e43aa86b9d27c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/519abddf157e491eaa7e43aa86b9d27c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 14:15:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ricochet Podcast : 486. My Corona</title><description>Rob Long is off this week, Law Talk&amp;#8217;s John Yoo is sitting in. We&amp;#8217;ve got Henry Olsen (he of The Horse Race podcast right here on this network) to chat about Super Duper Tuesday, Joementum!,  and whether we&amp;#8217;ve seen the last of the Socialist. Then, our friend and advisor Dr. George Savage stops by the tell [&amp;#8230;]</description><author>support@ricochet.com (Ricochet Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b36b04130e24487897dfe81add1df575</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b36b04130e24487897dfe81add1df575/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 14:02:14 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Tim Pool Daily Show : Warren's FAILURE Exposes Feminist Democrat Hypocrisy, Refuse To Accept Hillary And Warren Are Awful</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Warren's FAILURE Exposes Feminist Democrat Hypocrisy, Refuse To Accept Hillary And Warren Are Awful. Rachel Maddow held a exit interview with Elizabeth Warren and said with her exit it was the end for a female president in their lifetimes completely ignoring Tulsi Gabbard who is still in the race.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warren did substantially better than Gabbard but it was the establishment and the progressives who smeared Tulsi and went after her in underhanded ways.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton actually claimed she lost because she was a woman, several high profile Democratic strategists said it was because Warren and Hillary are women but many of these people smeared Tulsi.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When they go after Tulsi its principle but when they lose its gender.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can't have it both ways&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can't go after Republicans for being the party of old white men, complain that your candidate was treated unfairly but then target a female candidate with smears.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the new polling shows us anything its that for one Trump is going to win in November but more importantly it shows that the Democratic party and Democratic voters only care about winning and they will support whoever they think will win regardless of policy be it far left or moderate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="http://timcast.com/donate"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (http://timcast.com/donate)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tim@timcast.com (Tim Pool Daily Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">40f8d1d807f54f9d9930e73f07eca125</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/40f8d1d807f54f9d9930e73f07eca125/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 14:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Skimm This : When Your Side Hustle is Free: Female Unpaid Labor</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Supreme Court heard its first major case on abortion access with a strong new conservative majority on the bench. We’ll dive into what the outcome of this case could mean for the future of abortion access in the US. Meanwhile, this Sunday is International Women’s Day. We talked to some women – and their partners – about how they share the workload at home. Also on the show: how people around the world are getting creative when it comes to telling people to wash their hands. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>skimmthis@theskimm.com (Skimm This)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5c3c38ba4c3f449cba612fd28cf15ede</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5c3c38ba4c3f449cba612fd28cf15ede/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 13:51:39 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>National Review's Radio Free California Podcast : Episode 109: California’s Not-So-Super Tuesday</title><description>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;California’s Dem voters go for Bernie Sander but conversely appear to have killed a teachers-union-backed $15 billion bond. Meanwhile, California lawmakers tackle the state&amp;#8217;s decline with proposals to end gender segregation in toy stores, eliminate price disparities between men’s and women’s products, and replace the phrase “at-risk” with “at-promise.” Bonus! &lt;span class="il"&gt;Will&lt;/span&gt; California do for pre-K education what it has done for K–12 (please, God, no!), and David breaks down a Supreme Court case that lefties fear &lt;span class="il"&gt;will&lt;/span&gt; unravel the administrative state. Intro music by Metalachi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="mailto:dbahnsen@thebahnsengroup.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;dbahnsen@thebahnsengroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="mailto:Will@calpolicycenter.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;span class="il"&gt;Will&lt;/span&gt;@calpolicycenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/DavidBahnsen" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://twitter.com/DavidBahnsen&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1583503556820000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNGo6CgkV4uveJlFTRA3Z73ZAtdkLw"&gt;@DavidBahnsen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/WillSwaim" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://twitter.com/WillSwaim&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1583503556820000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNEYoOU5wAXnEzh2ainZ-17zGke3vg"&gt;@WillSwaim&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TheRadioFreeCA" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://twitter.com/TheRadioFreeCA&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1583503556820000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHrw1Jamkl2oFrhy6vgy0BZl9JkoQ"&gt;@TheRadioFreeCA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Show Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article240601601.html?" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article240601601.html?&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1583503556820000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNGsYY10p4tQRRJvDWc0xCUDiPC4Ow"&gt;‘Gender neutral’ plan for toys would get rid of boys’ and girls’ aisles in California stores&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article240401766.htmlhttps://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article240401766.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article240401766.htmlhttps://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article240401766.html&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1583503556820000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHNaCOhOJMgQQEY0tQnKJyW8a7UKw"&gt;Dem proposal would eliminate the “pink-tax” &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/california-replaces-the-phrase-at-risk-with-at-promise-to-describe-troubled-youth-in-legal-code?fbclid=IwAR1mV1uDXSvdxRQ34Rhe-DTmW8TqnwANLgpZtpbHM-z2SB6lS1ls6ixh6M8" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/california-replaces-the-phrase-at-risk-with-at-promise-to-describe-troubled-youth-in-legal-code?fbclid%3DIwAR1mV1uDXSvdxRQ34Rhe-DTmW8TqnwANLgpZtpbHM-z2SB6lS1ls6ixh6M8&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1583503556820000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHHvhAWhIwD10fCykmORTr5XezgZA"&gt;California replaces the phrase ‘at-risk’ with ‘at-promise’ to describe troubled youth in legal code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-03-01/gop-candidate-for-l-a-congressional-district-tweets-coronavirus-conspiracy-theory" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-03-01/gop-candidate-for-l-a-congressional-district-tweets-coronavirus-conspiracy-theory&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1583503556821000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNE4MhTtGPjSMvfYx-oK_vsabp3D5A"&gt;GOP candidate for L.A. congressional district tweets coronavirus conspiracy theory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2020/03/02/elizabeth-warren-wanted-blood-teeth-left-floor-cfpb-fight-now-it-faces-us-supreme-court/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2020/03/02/elizabeth-warren-wanted-blood-teeth-left-floor-cfpb-fight-now-it-faces-us-supreme-court/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1583503556821000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNH3-vMwIvXw3I8HkiV0jk8344e7Eg"&gt;Elizabeth Warren wanted ‘blood and teeth left on the floor’ in CFPB fight. Now the battle moves to the U.S. Supreme Court.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="http://calretort.com/2020/02/public-preschool-could-shrink-growth-of-charters-in-ca/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=http://calretort.com/2020/02/public-preschool-could-shrink-growth-of-charters-in-ca/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1583503556821000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHk8Ze3fcCJmOdYSQ04WF54lYOWPw"&gt;Public Preschool could shrink growth of charters in CA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://californiapolicycenter.org/government-sanctioned-child-abuse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://californiapolicycenter.org/government-sanctioned-child-abuse/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1583503556821000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFeQHx4warU5O65Jz-W9gi3m3IlVQ"&gt;Government sanctioned child abuse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://californiapolicycenter.org/californias-k-12-spending-exceeds-20000-per-pupil/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://californiapolicycenter.org/californias-k-12-spending-exceeds-20000-per-pupil/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1583503556821000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHTUdDALYDpV4BHGnNBQTC4d7jAhQ"&gt;California’s K-12 spending exceeds $20,000 per pupil&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>studio@nationalreview.com (National Review's Radio Free California Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f5dfce8f252f4f11a15add8d7419c811</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f5dfce8f252f4f11a15add8d7419c811/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 13:50:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>New York NOW : Assembly Minority Leader Will Barclay, Coronavirus, Solitary Confinement</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Assembly Republican Leader Will Barclay talks about the state Legislature's response to the novel coronavirus, the state budget, bail reform, and more. The coronavirus, or COVID-19, hit New York this week, with more than a dozen cases diagnosed in the span of six days. Democrats in New York want to overhaul the state's laws on solitary confinement, but a bill with majority support hasn't moved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more: &lt;a href='https://nynow.wmht.org'&gt;nynow.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@wmht.org (New York NOW)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5f9b96c54b7b44ce9e16f585aa5afaa1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5f9b96c54b7b44ce9e16f585aa5afaa1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 13:34:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Get 2 the Point : David Frerking talks about ‘What Really Matters’</title><description>&lt;p&gt;David Frerking of Appleton is a new author, and you might recognize the story he is telling.  His son Jacob, a young man with autism, was granted a wish to become a law enforcement officer through the Make-A-Wish foundation.   Jacob was diagnosed with a rare form of cancer, law enforcement officers from across the Fox Valley embraced Jacob and made him part of their community.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hear more about Jacob Frerking’s journey through his father’s eyes in this episode of Get 2 the Point podcast. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tmiller@wbay.com (Get 2 the Point)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f9d71eb9a2094b338e939679db72dc20</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f9d71eb9a2094b338e939679db72dc20/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 13:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WSJ Opinion: Potomac Watch : Chuck Schumer Threatens the Supreme Court</title><description>Chuck Schumer threatens the Supreme Court&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@dowjones.com (WSJ Opinion: Potomac Watch)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3de6095a4fe54fcf8664376916f5d19e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3de6095a4fe54fcf8664376916f5d19e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 13:11:27 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Yorker Radio Hour : And Then There Were Two</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Just over a week ago, Bernie Sanders seemed to be the front-runner for the Democratic nomination. Then came some prominent withdrawals from the race, and, on Super Tuesday, the resurgence of Joe Biden’s campaign. (Tulsi Gabbard of Hawaii remains in the race, but has no chance of winning the nomination.) But the narrowing of the field only highlights the gulf between the Party’s moderate center and its energized Left.  David Remnick talks with Amy Davidson Sorkin, a political columnist for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;The New Yorker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt;, about the possibility of a contested Convention. Then Remnick interviews Michael Kazin, an historian and the co-editor of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dissent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt; magazine. Kazin points out that Sanders is struggling against a headwind: even voters sympathetic to democratic socialism may vote for a pragmatist if they think Biden is more likely to beat the incumbent President in November. But Sanders seems unlikely to moderate his message. “There is a problem,” Kazin tells David Remnick. “A divided party—a party that’s divided at the Convention—never has won in American politics.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (The New Yorker Radio Hour)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9cf0df65cde74cffa4ab1c6d4020ecde</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9cf0df65cde74cffa4ab1c6d4020ecde/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 13:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rush Limbaugh Show : The Rush Limbaugh Show Podcast - Mar 06 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;PODCAST SUMMARY HOUR 1:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Dems back off blaming Trump for coronavirus because it’s not becoming the crisis they wanted. Drive-Bys blame sexism for Fauxcahontas loss, Trump says she lost because of “lack of talent”. Crazy Bernie can be bought. MSNBC says Bloomberg could have given every American $1 million with what he spent on campaign; math doesn’t add up. GOP could flip 7 House seats in California? The mortality rate for coronavirus is what Rush said it would be, .01-1%, not 2-3%. David Plouffe: Coronavirus is opportunity for Democrats to win. Schumer threatens Supreme Court justices. Libs cancelling meetings over coronavirus. Caller on “the rich” fires up Rush.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PODCAST SUMMARY HOUR 2:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Trump is handling the coronavirus by remaining calm. This will pass. CDC response. Trump tours tornado damage in Tennessee. Trump has the ability to make things seem okay. Rush gains weight. Great jobs numbers. Economy can withstand coronavirus. Trump at Fox town hall on why he left his great life to be president: to save the country. Rush defends "the rich".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PODCAST SUMMARY HOUR 3:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Rush on demonizing "the rich", how success is different than what he imagined. Happiness can't be derived from revenge. Jeff Bezos' mansion. Should we fear the coronavirus? Rush's theory on creation, death and the coronavirus. Clinton says he had affair with Lewinsky to relieve anxiety. Schumer threatens judges. Democrats have killed millions of their own voters through abortion.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (The Rush Limbaugh Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4b032970e90342cf9daf14804d1e06b7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4b032970e90342cf9daf14804d1e06b7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 12:25:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Erick Erickson Show : Democrats Grapple With Sexism</title><author>erick@theresurgent.com (The Erick Erickson Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7b77091978f84b3ca0f610b74b6e6c19</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7b77091978f84b3ca0f610b74b6e6c19/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 12:19:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bannon's War Room : Ep 34- Pandemic: Reality Sets In</title><description>Steve Bannon and Jack Maxey are joined by Jason Miller to discuss the reality of the pandemic as it sets in to our economy and our health infrastructure.</description><author>admin@citizensoftheamericanrepublic.org (Bannon's War Room)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f4e7226dba184194848649bc03aa48f8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f4e7226dba184194848649bc03aa48f8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 11:44:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Rome Daily Sentinel - Cinema Podcast : March 6, 2020 - &amp;quot;The Invisible Man&amp;quot;</title><description>It's not hard to see why Sean Ian Mills thinks &amp;quot;The Invisible Man&amp;quot; is a good movie!  Hopefully his cold doesn't morph into a Coronavirus, which is doing real doing real damage to the international movie industry.</description><author>podcasts@rnymedia.com (Rome Daily Sentinel - Cinema Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9ab5b362cae54fa7a9e95fbba4af9979</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9ab5b362cae54fa7a9e95fbba4af9979/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 11:04:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Buck Sexton Show : MSNBC Can't Math Good</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Season 4, Episode 47.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Trump joins Fox News and lays out some interesting topics, Elizabeth Warren and other Dems claim sexism and will Michigan become the place that Bernie Sanders ends his campaign in?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>teambuck@iheartmedia.com (The Buck Sexton Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">647c7f8e737b48d4b25ead2bfde8c8ef</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/647c7f8e737b48d4b25ead2bfde8c8ef/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 10:37:35 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Matt Walsh Show : Ep. 439 - The Reward For Selling Your Soul</title><description>&lt;p&gt;An actress brags that killing her child enabled her to have a career. But the fact that she traded in her child and her soul for a career on the D-list only shows how foolish and tragic the pro-abortion mentality is. Also, five headlines including the supposedly controversial execution of a man convicted of killing three police officers even though he didn't pull the trigger. And today I cancel MSNBC for what is perhaps the stupidest segment ever to be aired on cable news.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out The Cold War: What We Saw, a new podcast written and presented by Bill Whittle at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar&lt;/a&gt;. In Part 1 we peel back the layers of mystery cloaking the Terror state run by the Kremlin, and watch as America takes its first small steps onto the stage of world leadership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like The Matt Walsh Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: WALSH and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/Walsh"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/Walsh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mattwalshshow@dailywire.com (The Matt Walsh Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">00ab058b53564c50b90b54fbd431e458</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/00ab058b53564c50b90b54fbd431e458/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 10:06:25 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Two-Minute Briefing : The Evening Briefing: Friday March 6</title><description>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Second UK virus death: Man in his 80s dies in hospital - latest virus news http://bit.ly/2Tt9feV |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How many are there?: Where in the UK have cases of coronavirus been detected http://bit.ly/2TwnH6e |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coronavirus in France: Emmanuel Macron calls on citizens to limit visits to old people's homes http://bit.ly/2VRALVm |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markets hit: FTSE drops on virus fears as global shares plunge - live http://bit.ly/3cCl0Yk |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;'No need' to stockpile: Health Secretary says food supplies will not run dry http://bit.ly/2wCl2yA |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold standard:&amp;nbsp;Taiwan shows the way on epidemic response http://bit.ly/330HTAi |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;'I'm not here for one last payday': Jamie Carragher meets Carlo Ancelotti&amp;nbsp;http://bit.ly/2Ir0WdC |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stunt backfires: Man sent to prison for licking ice cream in Walmart before putting it back on the shelf http://bit.ly/3cEoo4D |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read all these articles with a digital Telegraph subscription - from £2 per week. Sign up here: http://bit.ly/2WRuvh9. If you're enjoying my audio briefings, please consider encouraging others to sign up for FREE here: http://bit.ly/2XxhVAI.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@telegraph.co.uk (The Two-Minute Briefing)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">23ac989c20f94154bf0d114af2a1476a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/23ac989c20f94154bf0d114af2a1476a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 10:02:29 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Checks and Balance : Checks and Balance: Joementum</title><description>&lt;p&gt;"They don't call it Super Tuesday for nothing." Those were Joe Biden’s words after his &lt;a href="https://www.economist.com/united-states/2020/03/05/joe-biden-has-pulled-off-one-of-the-great-political-comebacks" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;astonishing comeback&lt;/a&gt; this week. Votes in 14 states catapulted him into the lead in the delegate count that decides the Democratic Party nomination. The former Vice President’s resurrection poses &lt;a href="https://www.economist.com/leaders/2020/03/05/joe-biden-redux" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;new questions&lt;/a&gt; about a campaign that had been all but written off. Does he have the character and organisation to beat Bernie Sanders, then President Trump? The Economist’s US editor John Prideaux looks into Joe Biden’s past and his plans. New York bureau chief Charlotte Howard and Washington correspondent Jon Fasman join him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subscribe to &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; for full access to print, digital and audio editions: &lt;a href="http://www.economist.com/pod2020" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.economist.com/pod2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>radio@economist.com (Checks and Balance)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3611bc79d6bf483f8acfac5bf9659793</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3611bc79d6bf483f8acfac5bf9659793/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 09:51:01 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Houston Matters : Friday’s Show: Media Coverage Of The Coronavirus, And Going To Mexico For Health Care (March 6, 2020)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On Friday's Houston Matters: When it comes to the coronavirus, how can the media strike a balance between informing the public and over-preparing -- or even scaring people unnecessarily? Also this hour: Why it’s worth it for some Houstonians to go to Mexico for medical procedures or medication. Plus, we break down The Good, The Bad, and The Ugly of the week's news. And local music photographer Dave Clements talks about his work.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@houstonpublicmedia.org (Houston Matters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b8689f6a3d05435fb87d92b876d8f7dd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b8689f6a3d05435fb87d92b876d8f7dd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 09:35:38 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dan Bongino Show : The Media Has Abandoned the Country, Again (Ep 1198)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, I address the economic impact of the Coronavirus outbreak along with the incredible US jobs report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I also address a stunning piece of information from the FBI that changes everything, yet has received scant media coverage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;News Picks:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/economy-defied-early-coronavirus-fears-in-february-with-273-000-new-jobs-unemployment-at-3-5"&gt;Huge job numbers for February&lt;/a&gt;, despite the Coronavirus outbreak. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://therightscoop.com/video-romney-not-happy-about-senate-investigation-into-hunter-biden/"&gt;Romney screws us, again&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The latest Republican Primary numbers show &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/columnists/primaries-show-trump-gop-strength"&gt;unprecedented strength for President Trump&lt;/a&gt; within the GOP. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A federal judge engages in a &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/judge-questions-barrs-credibility-in-handling-mueller-report-and-may-make-more-public"&gt;bizarre attack on Attorney General Bill Barr&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/fisa-court-mistakenly-says-fusion-gps-was-digging-up-dirt-on-hillary-clinton-not-trump"&gt;FISA court mistakenly says&lt;/a&gt; Fusion GPS was targeting Hillary Clinton. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://thefederalist.com/2020/03/05/hemingway-if-bloomberg-couldnt-buy-2020-how-could-russia-buy-2016/"&gt;Bloomberg couldn’t buy the election with hundreds of millions&lt;/a&gt; so how did the Russians “buy it” with thousands? Absurd.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;President Trump is &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/campaigns/con-trolling-the-campaign-trump-soaks-up-spotlight-and-drives-his-opponents-to-distraction"&gt;trolling the Democrats into a black-hole&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Copyright Bongino Inc All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@bongino.com (The Dan Bongino Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1281810f93db412ab751c75dd5ccfeaa</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1281810f93db412ab751c75dd5ccfeaa/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 09:28:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>On the Media : Our Bodies, Ourselves</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The press called out President Trump after he dismissed an alarming coronavirus statistic on – quote – a “hunch.” On this week’s On The Media, what both Trump and his critics miss in their pursuit of certainty. Plus, why the political scientist who predicted the 2018 midterms thinks Democrats will beat Trump in 2020. And, how the White House is seeking to re-write international norms about “women’s health,” “women’s rights,” and “gender equality” by avoiding those very words.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Jon Cohen [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/sciencecohen"&gt;@sciencecohen&lt;/a&gt;], staff writer for &lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt;, on the various difficulties of reporting on COVID-19. &lt;a href="http://www.wnycstudios.org/This%20is%20a%20segment%20from%20our%20March%206,%202020%20program,%20Our%20Bodies,%20Ourselves."&gt;Listen.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. &lt;a href="https://history.yale.edu/people/frank-snowden"&gt;Frank Snowden&lt;/a&gt;, professor emeritus of medical history at Yale University, on the lessons from historical epidemics. &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/otm/segments/infectious-disease-hold-societies-really-are-on-the-media"&gt;Listen.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Rachel Bitecofer [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/RachelBitecofer"&gt;@RachelBitecofer&lt;/a&gt;], political scientist at Christopher Newport University, on what she sees as Super Tuesday's clear lessons. &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/otm/segments/how-democrats-win-2020"&gt;Listen.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. Jessica Glenza [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/JessicaGlenza"&gt;@JessicaGlenza&lt;/a&gt;], health reporter for The Guardian, on the embattled language of women's health. &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/otm/segments/on-the-media-from-ally-to-obstructionist" target="_blank"&gt;Listen&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Music from this week's show:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Accentuate the Positive by Syd Dale Double Dozen and Alec Gould&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Carmen Fantasy by Anderson and Roe&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cellar Door by Michael Andrews&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Chicago Sunset by Charlie Musselwhite&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;First Drive by Clive Carroll and John Renbourn&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fallen Leaves by Marcus Ciscar&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Starlings by Vijay Iyer Trio&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (On the Media)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8136f2da58174b39bdd049fb0644c7cd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8136f2da58174b39bdd049fb0644c7cd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill O’Reilly’s No Spin News and Analysis : The O'Reilly Update, March 6, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Super Tuesday has come and gone… Democrats across the USA have now voted in 18 different states; allocating about a third of the delegates available before the convention…&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@www.billoreilly.com (Bill O’Reilly’s No Spin News and Analysis)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">75bed50653f74ea99e0248da1af82062</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/75bed50653f74ea99e0248da1af82062/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 08:45:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Marketplace Morning Report : The jobs report before the COVID-19 storm</title><description>&lt;p&gt;February jobs report shows no signs of COVID-19. What a state of emergency declaration actually means. How the T-Mobile-Sprint merger could affect cheaper, prepaid phone plans.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>MorningReportComments@marketplace.org (Marketplace Morning Report)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">14d1e37b7e414174856d623eccb39167</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/14d1e37b7e414174856d623eccb39167/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 08:40:11 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>CBS This Morning - News on the Go : 3/6: Coronavirus on the rise.  Prince Harry and Meghan Markle are back in Britain for their last official appearances.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The number of cases in the U.S. surges, while the global total passes 100,000.&amp;nbsp;People on a giant cruise ship off San Francisco are tested for the disease. We hear from some of the passengers on board. The U.S. government is getting some criticism in the race to respond to the crisis. Investors worried about the coronavirus are bracing for what could be another tough day on wall street. The fight to be the Democrats' presidential nominee is heating up -- including on Twitter. Former Vice President Joe Biden and Senator Bernie Sanders battled over Social Security last night, at one point telling each other to -- "get real.” An Alabama man has been executed, despite pleas to save his life. Harvey Weinstein is waking up this morning on the Rikers Island jail complex in New York. The mother of two missing children will face a judge in Idaho today, after being extradited to her home state from Hawaii. Prince Harry and Meghan Markle are back in Britain for their last official appearances as senior members of the royal family.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>CBSNetworkRadioNewsWeb@cbsnews.com (CBS This Morning - News on the Go)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">09b450f2881641449efbab8e8913b24e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/09b450f2881641449efbab8e8913b24e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 08:07:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>TJ Trout : Super Tuesday recap with Joe Monahan</title><description>NM political blogger Joe Monahan chats about Super Tuesday, NM and ABQ politics on News Radio KKOB.</description><author>jared.hart@cumulus.com (TJ Trout)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2edb85bfbd5f415aa6a5db3cc7f353a1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2edb85bfbd5f415aa6a5db3cc7f353a1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 07:47:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Trending Stories Taking Over podcast | T.S.T.O. : 024 | Hot Ones, Romo money, MEGXIT, iGaga, Corona Virus, FAST FOOD WARS</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Watch the full show: &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/9L2RQE0zx-0"&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are BACK with another episode of the TSTO!!! &amp;nbsp;This week we discuss the new Hot Ones TV show, Romo makin MONEY, MEGXIT gets worse, Corona virus, and FAST FOOD BREAKFAST WARS!.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let us know what you think in the comments!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yahoo!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Todd, Jake, + Kris&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/tsto/message</description><author>tstoshow@gmail.com (The Trending Stories Taking Over podcast | T.S.T.O.)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">316452e560244003be490fa3ae9d7aa8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/316452e560244003be490fa3ae9d7aa8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Coronavirus Covid 19 podcast - news, alerts, and updates on the corona virus : Coronavirus news, updates and information for 03-06-2020 COVID-19 AM Alert</title><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;030620 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is Coronavirus 4-1-1.  The latest Coronavirus info for Friday March 6th, 2020. The global total of cases has passed 100,000 according to Johns Hopkins University.The current number of cases is 100, 278.Congress has approved 8.3 billion in emergency spending to fight COVID-19, reports the New York Times. As Colorado, Maryland and Nevada are the latest states to confirm cases of the virus in the U.S, relays ABC News.Maryland, joins California and Washington State in declaring a “State of Emergency” relays the Washington Post.New York is monitoring 2,773 people who have self-quarantined, reports The New York Times.  Passengers aboard a cruise ship outside of California, await test results as 45 people showed symptoms or the virus.  There are about 2500 people on board according to CNN.  Vatican City has confirmed its first case of COVID-19, while the population is only 1,000 it welcomes millions of visitors each year.  NBC News notes, The Pope has tested negative for the virus.  Iran has closed 60,000 mosques, according to The Washington Post. In a Thursday press conference, The World Health Organization stated, “This is not a drill. This is not the time to give up. This is not a time for excuses. This is a time for pulling out all the stops. Countries have been planning for scenarios like this for decades. Now is the time to act on those plans.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The locations of U.S. and country diagnoses in a moment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There have been 233 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in 20 states.  Cases in Nebraska are only among “repatriated citizens”.    Known active locations, are as follows: Washington 75, California 60, New York 22, Texas 14, Nebraska 13, Illinois 5, Florida 4, Maryland 3, Arizona, Georgia, Massachusetts, New Hampshire, New Jersey, Oregon, Rhode Island 2, Colorado, North Carolina, Tennessee, Utah, Wisconsin 1. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Global cases outside of China: Republic of Korea 6,593, Iran 4,747, Italy 3,858, Germany 577, France 423, Japan 381, Spain 360,  Switzerland 138, Singapore 130, United Kingdom 116, Belgium 109, Norway 106, Sweden 101, Malaysia 83, Netherlands 82, Australia 60, Kuwait 58, Bahrain 55, Canada and Thailand 48, Austria 47, Greece 45, Iceland 37, Iraq 35, India 31, United Arab Emirates 29, Denmark 23, San Marino 21, Algeria 17, Israel, Lebanon, Oman and Vietnam 16, Egypt and Finland 15, Ecuador 13, Czech Republic 12, Croatia 11, Estonia 10, Portugal and Qatar 8, Azerbaijan, Belarus, Ireland, Pakistan and Romania 6, Mexico, Philippines and Saudi Arabia 5, Brazil, Chile, Georgia, Indonesia, New Zealand, Palestine, Russian Federation and Senegal 4, St. Barth’s 3, Argentina, Bosnia and Herzegovina, Hungary, Luxembourg and Morocco 2, Afghanistan, Andorra, Armenia, Bhutan, Cambodia, Cameroon, Costa Rica, Dominican Republic, Faroe Islands, Jordan, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Monaco, Nepal, Nigeria, North Macedonia, Poland, Serbia, Slovakia, South Africa, Sri Lanka, Tunisia, Ukraine and Vatican City 1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another Coronavirus 411 update daily.  Find the latest information at C-D-C dot GOV-slash-Coronavirus or ask your smart speaker for “The Coronavirus 4-1-1 Podcast”.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>william@soundthatbrands.com (Coronavirus Covid 19 podcast - news, alerts, and updates on the corona virus)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0b9c85d90f1a403785e4ef480b8c456f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0b9c85d90f1a403785e4ef480b8c456f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 06:48:17 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Morning Joe : Morning Joe 3/6/20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Morning Joe panel recaps the flurry of 2020 political news from this week.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (Morning Joe)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3f70983e185f4abfa868086dcca27d5e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3f70983e185f4abfa868086dcca27d5e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 05:02:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Election 2020: Updates from The Washington Post : Elizabeth Warren's exit from the race ignites a conversation about sexism in politics</title><description>As Elizabeth Warren decides whether to endorse either of the two male candidates remaining in the Democratic race for president, her supporters are left to contemplate a factor that many believe contributed significantly to her loss: she’s female.</description><author>jessica.stahl@washpost.com (Election 2020: Updates from The Washington Post)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">88b8db89c1b34914aec2585c3f016ecf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/88b8db89c1b34914aec2585c3f016ecf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 04:39:27 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Sky News Daily : How should we adapt during the COVID-19 crisis? And the Northern Triangle's femicide problem | 6 March 2020</title><description>On this edition of the Sky News Daily podcast with Dermot Murnaghan, we examine how different industries are faring during the coronavirus crisis – talking to Sky’s technology correspondent Rowland Manthorpe and Sam Dumitriu, research director at The Entrepreneurs Network. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;We also hear from our chief correspondent Stuart Ramsay about what he has witnessed while reporting on the killing of women in Central America’s Northern Triangle region.</description><author>radio@sky.uk (Sky News Daily)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">348b5424a54c431fbeff55caf9b0c947</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/348b5424a54c431fbeff55caf9b0c947/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 04:33:27 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Daily 202's Big Idea : A cruise ship with thousands aboard awaits tests results for coronavirus off California</title><description>Military helicopters delivered testing kits Thursday to a cruise ship being held off the coast of California, as officials in Washington faced angry questions about whether the vessel is set to become the latest breeding ground for the coronavirus.</description><author>jessica.stahl@washpost.com (The Daily 202's Big Idea)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6e6aca39712a41a5afd11c520a98f2a1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6e6aca39712a41a5afd11c520a98f2a1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 04:33:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>RTÉ - Today with Sean O'Rourke : The Gathering</title><description>Thomas Byrne, F.F. TD Meath East, Josepha Madigan, F.G. TD Dublin Rathdown, Colette Browne, Irish Independent Columnist and Barrister, Brenda Power, Columnist irish Daily Mail and Sunday Times</description><author>radio.player@rte.ie (RTÉ - Today with Sean O'Rourke)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2df2ec6dbaaa490892d18861bc1a006b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2df2ec6dbaaa490892d18861bc1a006b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Baltimore Sun : Baltimore Sun - March 6, 2020</title><description>Good morning. Expect showers before 4 p.m. and clouds throughout the day. Highs of 48 and lows of 34 are forecast. The child support system ends up hurting some of Maryland’s poorest families and communities, especially those in Baltimore. A new investigation by The Baltimore Sun shows child support is another corrosive force in a city dealing with high poverty and crime.</description><author>distribution@spokenlayer.com (Baltimore Sun)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">af64fea58d484b63a80a36ab634ebff7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/af64fea58d484b63a80a36ab634ebff7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 03:03:29 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>AJC : Atlanta Journal-Constitution 3/6/20</title><description>Good morning. It's Friday, March 6th. I’m Lucas Dixon, and here are today's headlines from the Atlanta Journal-Constitution. Today will be breezy with plenty of sunshine and a high of 52. Tonight will be clear and chilly with a low of 32. Our top story is: The Georgia economy got off to a stronger than usual start in January, adding 9,800 jobs, the state Department of Labor announced yesterday.</description><author>distribution@spokenlayer.com (AJC)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f0fb057923104576bfe3df5f96390198</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f0fb057923104576bfe3df5f96390198/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 03:01:31 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Relatable with Allie Beth Stuckey : Ep 221 | Biden or Bernie?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Who should we want to run against Trump? Biden, who doesn't seem to know what's going on, or Bernie the communist?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ccardon@glennbeck.com (Relatable with Allie Beth Stuckey)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">db00b3b0bf2b4b2f87f891f8df0512e7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/db00b3b0bf2b4b2f87f891f8df0512e7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Intelligence : Nevertheless, she persisted: the futility of restricting abortion</title><description>&lt;p&gt;America’s Supreme Court is again tussling with the age-old question of abortion rights. Internationally the picture is very different; abortions are becoming easier, safer and more legally protected. We look back on the life of Katherine Johnson, a pioneering black woman who helped put men on the moon. And our annual glass-ceiling index ranks countries on workplace equality for women.For full access to print, digital and audio editions of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;, subscribe here &lt;a href="http://www.economist.com/radiooffer" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.economist.com/radiooffer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>radio@economist.com (The Intelligence)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">789a038e61224b56916ba2ea7180b118</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/789a038e61224b56916ba2ea7180b118/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 02:59:10 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Daily : The Almost-Peace Deal</title><description>&lt;p&gt;After years of false starts, the United States has signed a landmark deal with the Taliban to end the war in Afghanistan. We traveled to the front lines of the war — and to the signing ceremony in Doha, Qatar — to investigate whether peace is actually possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guest: &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/by/mujib-mashal?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt;Mujib Mashal&lt;/a&gt;, senior correspondent for The New York Times in Afghanistan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on today’s episode, visit nytimes.com/thedaily.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background reading:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/29/world/asia/us-taliban-afghanistan.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; agreement between Washington and the Taliban&lt;/a&gt; seemed to be an important first step in ending the war in Afghanistan.&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/04/world/asia/afghanistan-taliban-violence.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; Then the violence started again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zalmay Khalilzad, the Afghan-born American envoy and architect of the deal, seemed to have been handed an impossible and thankless assignment. Here’s&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/01/world/asia/zalmay-khalilzad-afghanistan-taliban.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; how he pulled it off&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (The Daily)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a64ba63d74e348ac9c6034afc94401cf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a64ba63d74e348ac9c6034afc94401cf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 02:50:24 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Coronavirus: Fact vs Fiction : Facts &amp; Fears</title><description>CNN Chief Medical Correspondent Dr. Sanjay Gupta and CNN Anchor Anderson Cooper speak with top health experts and answer pressing audience questions as part of a special town hall on the global impact of the coronavirus. &lt;a href="http://knit.audio/podcast-advertising"&gt;via Knit&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcast@turner.com (Coronavirus: Fact vs Fiction)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9c4a171b25ce479380abb42e61e66ab9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9c4a171b25ce479380abb42e61e66ab9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 02:30:16 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>What Next | Daily News and Analysis : WN TBD: Did the Internet Doom a Pregnancy?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Slate Plus members get ad-free podcasts and bonus episodes of shows like Slow Burn and Dear Prudence. &lt;a href="https://my.slate.com/plus?utm_medium=link&amp;amp;utm_campaign=plus_pod&amp;amp;utm_content=What_Next&amp;amp;utm_source=show_notes"&gt;Sign up now&lt;/a&gt; to listen and support our work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For pregnant women in the U.S., there are plenty of reasons to mistrust the medical establishment. Mortality rates are high compared to other western countries, and one-third of women in the U.S. give birth by C-section. It’s no wonder that many women turn to the internet for alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week, the story of one woman who was drawn into a network of private Facebook groups dedicated to the idea of ‘freebirth,’ or unassisted birth. And what happens when the misinformation shared in these private groups has real-life consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guest: &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/BrandyZadrozny"&gt;Brandy Zadrozny&lt;/a&gt;, reporter for NBC News. You can read her reporting on ‘freebirth’ &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/she-wanted-freebirth-no-doctors-online-groups-convinced-her-it-n1140096"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tj.raphael@slate.com (What Next | Daily News and Analysis)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">850aa592c61c4eb7a5c75ae8e62d63f2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/850aa592c61c4eb7a5c75ae8e62d63f2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Honey Badger Radio : Refusing the feminist bully label | HBR Talk 123</title><description>Join HBR Talk as we hand the “bully” label back to the cry-bully feminists who use it as a tool of political censorship.</description><author>feeds@spreaker.com (Honey Badger Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c2d272f6300f471d931e099618352ff2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c2d272f6300f471d931e099618352ff2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 01:17:23 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>the NewsWorthy : Travel Trouble, Percy Goes to Mars &amp; Spring Forward - Friday, March 6th, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The news to know for Friday, March 6th, 2020! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What to know today about the major impact of the new coronavirus on the travel industry: from empty airports to new policies and even advice about certain hand sanitizer...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Plus: more plans for space vacations, get ready to spring forward this weekend, and a reason to unplug that can make you money.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Those stories and more in less than 10 minutes!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Award-winning broadcast journalist and former TV news reporter Erica Mandy breaks it all down for you. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Head to &lt;a href= "http://www.thenewsworthy.com/"&gt;www.theNewsWorthy.com&lt;/a&gt; or see sources below to read more about any of the stories mentioned today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This episode is brought to you by &lt;a href= "http://www.Zola.com/newsworthy"&gt;www.Zola.com/newsworthy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href= "http://www.MagicSpoon.com/newswrothy"&gt;www.MagicSpoon.com/newsworthy&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em style= "font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;"&gt; Become a NewsWorthy INSIDER! Learn more here: &lt;a href= "http://www.TheNewsWorthy.com/insider"&gt;www.TheNewsWorthy.com/insider&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sources:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;COVID-19 - U.S. Status: &lt;a href= "https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/05/politics/mike-pence-coronavirus-testing-trump/index.html"&gt; CNN&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://apnews.com/cd307bb7eba7668733a32e2364f3e5f5"&gt;AP&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/live-blog/coronavirus-updates-live-california-declares-emergency-governments-race-stop-spread-n1150561/ncrd1151096#liveBlogHeader"&gt; NBC News&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2020/03/coronavirus-death-toll-rises-12-latest-updates-200305231909069.html"&gt; Al Jazeera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Travel Issues: &lt;a href= "https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/05/us/cruise-ship-california.html"&gt; NYT&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2020/03/05/coronavirus-princess-cruise-passengers-wait-coronavirus-tests/4962112002/"&gt; USA Today&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.washingtonpost.com/travel/2020/03/02/airlines-are-offering-flexible-travel-options-adapt-spread-coronavirus-heres-what-we-know-so-far/"&gt; WaPo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Economic Impact: &lt;a href= "https://www.wsj.com/articles/global-markets-follow-u-s-stocks-higher-11583376176?mod=hp_lead_pos1"&gt; WSJ&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/05/us-markets-dow-futures-indicate-opening-drop.html"&gt; CNBC&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.politico.com/newsletters/politico-pulse/2020/03/05/whats-in-the-coronavirus-funding-package-785879"&gt; Politico&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/05/senate-passes-8point3-billion-coronavirus-bill-sending-it-to-trumps-desk.html"&gt; CNBC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mueller Report Review: &lt;a href= "https://apnews.com/fe8eee387b53888c478a24021fc101aa"&gt;AP&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.foxnews.com/politics/federal-judge-slams-ag-barr-over-mueller-report-vows-to-review-unredacted-version"&gt; Fox News&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/05/politics/judge-mueller-report-barr/index.html"&gt; CNN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Elizabeth Warren Out: &lt;a href= "https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/sen-elizabeth-warren-suspends-presidential-run-source/story?id=67499055&amp;cid=clicksource_4380645_10_heads_posts_card_hed"&gt; ABC News&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-warren/elizabeth-warren-ends-2020-democratic-white-house-bid-says-we-will-persist-idUSKBN20S21S"&gt; Reuters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Trump to Visit Tennessee: &lt;a href= "https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/president-trump-visit-tornado-ravaged-tennessee-69422196"&gt; ABC News&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/severe-thunderstorms-flood-threat-to-target-the-southeast-thursday/695993"&gt; Accuweather&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/03/03/trump-tour-tornado-damage-tennessee-friday/4938048002/"&gt; USA Today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Daylight Saving Time: &lt;a href= "https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/03/04/daylight-savings-time-coming-sunday-get-ready-spring-forward/4952272002/?for-guid=eb4e6047-24e3-e911-ac30-90b11c343abd&amp;"&gt; USA Today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mars Rover Gets a Name: &lt;a href= "https://www.nbcnews.com/science/space/nasa-s-new-mars-rover-gets-name-percy-short-n1150961"&gt; NBC News&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nasa-mars-rover-perseverance-seventh-grade-winner/"&gt; CBS News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;SpaceX Sending Tourists to Space: &lt;a href= "https://www.theverge.com/2020/3/5/21166657/spacex-tourists-iss-international-space-station-orbit-falcon-9-dragon"&gt; The Verge&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/05/science/axiom-space-station.html"&gt; NYT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Facebook Takes Down Trump Campaign Ads: &lt;a href= "https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2020/03/05/facebook-removes-trump-ads/"&gt; Washington Post&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/wireStory/pelosi-lambasts-facebook-trump-ad-week-census-69413906?cid=clicksource_4380645_2_heads_hero_live_headlines_hed"&gt; ABC News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;DIY Hand Sanitizer: &lt;a href= "https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/03/health/coronavirus-diy-hand-sanitizer-trnd/index.html"&gt; CNN&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink/coronavirus-vodka-hand-sanitizer"&gt; Fox News&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/TitosVodka/status/1235342746619195395"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nat’l Day of Unplugging: &lt;a href= "https://mashable.com/article/hinge-date-national-day-of-unplugging/"&gt; Mashable&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.nationaldayofunplugging.com/"&gt;Nat’l Day of Unplugging&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.unplugwithhinge.com/"&gt;Hinge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Feel Good Friday - &lt;a href= "https://apnews.com/199088376310dfda47e5c058cb978748"&gt;AP&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.wral.com/roxboro-woman-celebrates-100th-birthday-by-going-to-jail/18994340/"&gt; WRAL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>staff@theNewsWorthy.com (the NewsWorthy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d0b180a6c18a4472ba8d932366d86b9f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d0b180a6c18a4472ba8d932366d86b9f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:40:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>RUMBLE with MICHAEL MOORE : Ep. 47: The Christopher Nolan/Memento Primary</title><description>&lt;p&gt;What if the sun rose on the West? What if, on Tuesday night at 8pm ET, the first Super Tuesday results had been announced from the largest and most diverse state in the country, California?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;”Huge win for Bernie Sanders! A huge delegate lead!"&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An hour later, in conservative, Mormon, Utah, &lt;em&gt;“the winner is....Bernie Sanders!”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then Colorado comes next…&lt;em&gt;”another victory for Bernie Sanders! And in a key swing state!”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How we were presented the results on Tuesday night, which has turned this into a two-person race between Joe Biden and Bernie Sanders with only a handful of delegates&amp;nbsp;separating them, has greatly affected the public perception of the race. While Bernie Sanders is now the underdog, it is a close race, and the American people must hear vigorous debates between Biden and Sanders about who they are, what they believe, what their plans are for the country and how they will defeat Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/rumble-with-michael-moore/message</description><author>podcasts39+10fc9a30@anchor.fm (RUMBLE with MICHAEL MOORE)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3f4a486969b04ca3800cb1215cb05a9c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3f4a486969b04ca3800cb1215cb05a9c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:06:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Wars Daily : Lactation Wasn’t Even a Business. Why Breastfeeding Room Startups are On a Tear</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today is Friday, March 6, and we’re looking at Mamava vs. Leche Lounge. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>iwonder@wondery.com (Business Wars Daily)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">37bed0299336421dbf977cc3ca7fa3c9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/37bed0299336421dbf977cc3ca7fa3c9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ao Ponto (podcast do jornal O Globo) : E se o machismo acabasse amanhã?</title><description>Às vésperas do Dia Internacional da Mulher, O GLOBO publica nesta sexta-feira um vídeo com os depoimentos de 11 mulheres que revelam o que fariam caso o machismo acabasse amanhã. O material faz parte de uma série de reportagens especiais para o mês da mulher. São relatos como o da chefe de cozinha Flávia Quaresma, da escritora Heloísa Buarque de Holanda e da atriz Erika Januza. A data também marca o primeiro ano do Celina, um espaço na Redação para tratar das questões de gênero. Neste episódio do Ao Ponto, a editora do Celina, Renata Izaal, e a jornalista Leda Antunes, que colabora com o time do Celina desde abril de 2019, vão contar como foi a experiência de conversar com outras mulheres sobre o machismo e ainda falam sobre os bastidores do Celina e as atrações preparadas para essa data especial.</description><author>maggi@oglobo.com.br (Ao Ponto (podcast do jornal O Globo))</author><guid isPermaLink="false">05bffe7b674f46a6988107ca56018cd2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/05bffe7b674f46a6988107ca56018cd2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 23:55:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The News : Friday, March 6</title><description>Turkey and Russia reach a ceasefire deal in Idlib, Senator Warren drops out of the race for the Democratic nomination, and the U. releases a travel advisory for spring break in light of the outbreak of COVID-19.</description><author>managingeditor@dailyprincetonian.com (The News)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">dd0505e326394040aa5c237a7f2248a1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/dd0505e326394040aa5c237a7f2248a1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 22:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Opening Arguments : OA366: Your Guide to the Coronavirus!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Today's episode breaks down &lt;em&gt;force majeure&lt;/em&gt; clauses in contracts and takes a look at what might happen in the next few weeks as the world prepares to deal with COVID-19 coronavirus. Along the way we also tackle the news of the week, including the baffling decision out of the DC Circuit not to require Don McGahn to testify. You won't want to miss this episode!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We begin, however, with some recurring Vice Presidential/line of succession questions and take a mini-deep-dive into the absolutely bonkers elections of 1796 and 1800 that produced &lt;a href= "https://constitutioncenter.org/interactive-constitution/amendment/amendment-xii"&gt; the 12th Amendment&lt;/a&gt;, and what it says about vice-presidential qualifications.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;After that, it's time for our main segment on coronavirus, which includes a deep dive into various cases where contracts have been broken due to "acts of god." Is a global pandemic an "act of god?" Listen, find out, and you'll soon be able to whip out four-part tests if your hotel tries to cancel your room due to coronavirus scares.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Then, it's time to pick apart the D.C. Circuit's 2-1 baffling opinion that the House Oversight Committee &lt;em&gt;lacks standing&lt;/em&gt; to go to a court to enforce its subpoena over Don McGahn. This is technically an "Andrew Was Wrong," because Andrew did not imagine that any judges with functioning brain cells could have authored an opinion this bad. Find out what's next!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;After all that, it's time for a brand new Thomas Takes the Bar Exam involving a tainted witness identification. And remember that you too can play along by sharing out this episode on social media and using the hashtag #T3BE.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Appearances&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;None! If you’d like to have either of us as a guest on your show, drop us an email at &lt;a href= "mailto:openarguments@gmail.com"&gt;openarguments@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show Notes &amp; Links&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;For all your Vice Presidential qualification questions, check out &lt;a href= "https://constitutioncenter.org/interactive-constitution/amendment/amendment-xii"&gt; the 12th Amendment&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Here's &lt;a href= "http://openargs.com/wp-content/uploads/McGahn-ruling-1.pdf"&gt;the D.C. Circuit's decision in McGahn&lt;/a&gt;, and we also referenced &lt;a href= "https://scholar.google.com/scholar_case?case=3363577568877703610"&gt;&lt;em&gt; Raines v. Byrd&lt;/em&gt;, 521 U.S. 811 (1997)&lt;/a&gt; and, of course, Opening Arguments's good friend Richard Nixon in &lt;a href= "https://scholar.google.com/scholar_case?case=5132513257326080850"&gt;&lt;em&gt; United States v. Nixon&lt;/em&gt;, 418 U.S. 683, 696-97 (1974)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Finally, you can read &lt;a href= "https://chicagounbound.uchicago.edu/cgi/viewcontent.cgi?article=5469&amp;context=uclrev"&gt; Josh Chafetz's law review article, "Executive Branch Contempt of Congress&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;-Support us on Patreon at: &lt;a href= "http://patreon.com/law"&gt;patreon.com/law&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;-Follow us on Twitter:  &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/openargs"&gt;@Openargs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;-Facebook:  &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/openargs/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/openargs/&lt;/a&gt;, and don’t forget the &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/YodelMountain"&gt;OA Facebook Community&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;-For show-related questions, check out the &lt;a href= "http://openargswiki.wikidot.com/"&gt;Opening Arguments Wiki&lt;/a&gt;, which now has its own Twitter feed!  &lt;a href= "http://twitter.com/oawiki"&gt;@oawiki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;-Remember to check out our &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCztCiOpNCnDZ16gk9VYPBDQ"&gt;YouTube Channel&lt;/a&gt;  for Opening Arguments: The Briefs and other specials!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;-And finally, remember that you can email us at &lt;a href= "mailto:openarguments@gmail.com"&gt;openarguments@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>openarguments@gmail.com (Opening Arguments)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ba95e478696c4e74b6410bb90eb91921</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ba95e478696c4e74b6410bb90eb91921/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 21:26:37 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Commercial Awareness Podcast : Episode 42: Flybe Administration, Floodplain Property and more</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Contact: &lt;a href="mailto:commawarepod@gmail.com"&gt;commawarepod@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram: @&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/commawarepod/?hl=en"&gt;commawarepod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Links for the headlines:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Air France COVID-19&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cityam.com/air-france-to-cut-1500-jobs-in-attempt-to-limit-coronavirus-impact/"&gt;https://www.cityam.com/air-france-to-cut-1500-jobs-in-attempt-to-limit-coronavirus-impact/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://uk.reuters.com/article/us-healthcare-coronavirus-airlines/airlines-face-100-billion-plus-virus-hit-discounts-wouldnt-do-any-good-idUKKBN20S11G"&gt;https://uk.reuters.com/article/us-healthcare-coronavirus-airlines/airlines-face-100-billion-plus-virus-hit-discounts-wouldnt-do-any-good-idUKKBN20S11G&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FCA Libor Warning&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cityam.com/fca-tells-asset-managers-to-gear-up-for-the-end-of-libor/"&gt;https://www.cityam.com/fca-tells-asset-managers-to-gear-up-for-the-end-of-libor/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Airbnb Data Sharing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.airbnb.com/airbnb-signs-data-sharing-partnership-with-european-commission/"&gt;https://news.airbnb.com/airbnb-signs-data-sharing-partnership-with-european-commission/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Electric Tax Break&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.smmt.co.uk/2020/03/uk-new-car-market-falls-2-9-in-february-as-industry-calls-for-tax-free-evs-to-kick-start-demand/"&gt;https://www.smmt.co.uk/2020/03/uk-new-car-market-falls-2-9-in-february-as-industry-calls-for-tax-free-evs-to-kick-start-demand/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;South East Consolidation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelawyer.com/moore-blatch-barlow-robbins-merger/"&gt;https://www.thelawyer.com/moore-blatch-barlow-robbins-merger/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CMA Interventionism&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ae2951a0-5b85-11ea-b0ab-339c2307bcd4"&gt;https://www.ft.com/content/ae2951a0-5b85-11ea-b0ab-339c2307bcd4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Property Floodplains&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2020/feb/23/more-than-11000-homes-to-be-built-on-land-at-high-risk-of-flooding%22%20%5Ct%20%22_blank"&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2020/feb/23/more-than-11000-homes-to-be-built-on-land-at-high-risk-of-flooding&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2020/feb/21/new-homes-in-flood-risk-areas-not-covered-by-insurance-scheme"&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2020/feb/21/new-homes-in-flood-risk-areas-not-covered-by-insurance-scheme&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.floodre.co.uk/how-flood-re-works/"&gt;https://www.floodre.co.uk/how-flood-re-works/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flybe Administration&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2020/mar/05/flybe-collapses-two-months-after-government-announces-rescue"&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/business/2020/mar/05/flybe-collapses-two-months-after-government-announces-rescue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2020/03/05/flybe-administration-inside-story-airlines-collapse/"&gt;https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2020/03/05/flybe-administration-inside-story-airlines-collapse/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelawyer.com/bclp-on-call-as-flybe-falls-into-administration/"&gt;https://www.thelawyer.com/bclp-on-call-as-flybe-falls-into-administration/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coronavirus and Contracts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tltsolicitors.com/insights-and-events/insight/coronavirus--what-is-the-impact-of-your-business/"&gt;https://www.tltsolicitors.com/insights-and-events/insight/coronavirus--what-is-the-impact-of-your-business/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Created by: Tapiwa Museba&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts8+75b7794@anchor.fm (The Commercial Awareness Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d0acd2037a374079ad872f4ed92eda4e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d0acd2037a374079ad872f4ed92eda4e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 21:26:16 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FT News Briefing : Friday, March 6</title><description>&lt;p&gt;US stocks dropped as Treasury yields touched records lows on Thursday and bank share price falls led the way, struggling Chinese ride-hailing group Didi Chuxing is suffering a further blow due to the coronavirus, and ExxonMobil says it will avoid a “beauty match” on carbon emissions as rivals set out targets. Plus, the world’s biggest oil traders slashed global demand forecasts with growth falling to the weakest levels since the financial crisis. The FT’s Anjli Raval explains how this adds pressure on Opec to cut output. &lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>newsbriefing@ft.com (FT News Briefing)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">03d2f5ffc5684c7792a467ab6ed9fb9c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/03d2f5ffc5684c7792a467ab6ed9fb9c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Townhall Review | Conservative Commentary On Today's News : Biden Surges after Super Tuesday Triumph</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Townhall Review &amp;ndash; March 7, 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hughhewitt.com/"&gt;Hugh Hewitt&lt;/a&gt; talks with NBC News correspondent &lt;a href="http://www.msnbc.com/msnbc-live/steve-kornacki-biography"&gt;Steve Kornacki&lt;/a&gt; about the latest in the Democratic primary race to the nomination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mikeonline.com/"&gt;Mike Gallagher&lt;/a&gt; weighs in on the battle for the nomination that is now between Bernie Sanders and Joe Biden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hughhewitt.com/"&gt;Hugh Hewitt&lt;/a&gt; and Trump Campaign Spokesman &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/tim-murtaugh-64b5689"&gt;Tim Murtaugh&lt;/a&gt; talk about the possibilities of a campaign between President Trump and former Vice President Joe Biden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hughhewitt.com/"&gt;Hugh Hewitt&lt;/a&gt; talks with &lt;a href="https://www.adflegal.org/detailspages/biography-details/david-a.-cortman"&gt;David Cortman&lt;/a&gt; of the Alliance Defending Freedom about a religious freedom case that is now headed to the Supreme Court.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sebgorka.com/"&gt;Sebastian Gorka&lt;/a&gt; chats with &lt;a href="https://www.judicialwatch.org/tag/chris-farrell/"&gt;Chris Farrell&lt;/a&gt; of Judicial Watch about their upcoming deposition of &lt;a href="https://www.hillaryclinton.com/"&gt;Hillary Clinton&lt;/a&gt; regarding her personal servers and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2012_Benghazi_attack"&gt;Benghazi&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://omny.fm/shows/chicagos-morning-answer-with-dan-proft-amy-jacobso"&gt;Dan Proft and Amy Jacobson&lt;/a&gt; talk with Epoch Times investigative reporter &lt;a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/author-joshua-philipp"&gt;Josh Philipp&lt;/a&gt; about China&amp;rsquo;s handling of the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/index.html"&gt;Coronavirus&lt;/a&gt; outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dennisprager.com/"&gt;Dennis Prager&lt;/a&gt; talks about a &amp;ldquo;Never Trumper&amp;rdquo; who now says if Bernie Sander is the Democratic nominee, he will vote for President Trump.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thr@salemmedia.com (Townhall Review | Conservative Commentary On Today's News)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1f35015710d0415b84e1414de3a30e98</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1f35015710d0415b84e1414de3a30e98/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Today in Focus : Grounded: why Heathrow's third runway may never happen</title><description>Last week the appeal court declared the proposed Heathrow expansion plans illegal and in breach of the UK’s climate change commitments under the Paris agreement. Is this the end of the third runway? And: how our quest for a good night’s sleep is leading to a landfill crisis. Help support our independent journalism at &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://www.theguardian.com/infocus&amp;quot;&amp;gt;theguardian.com/infocus&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;</description><author>userhelp@theguardian.com (Today in Focus)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c30ad516d7384e559c7da7a5f9a39146</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c30ad516d7384e559c7da7a5f9a39146/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 19:00:25 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MarketBuzz : 448: Sensex, Nifty set to open lower; Yes Bank, SBI, M&amp;M, Lupin in focus</title><description>The Indian markets are likely to open sharply lower on Friday tracking sell-off in global equities on fears of a prolonged world economic slowdown due to the coronavirus outbreak. At 7 am, the SGX Nifty was trading 271 points or 2.41 percent lower at 10,959.00, indicating a negative start for the Sensex and Nifty50.</description><author>sunep.imchen@nw18.com (MarketBuzz)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3129455fa9284cc18e953c0eabebba8f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3129455fa9284cc18e953c0eabebba8f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 18:48:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Advisory Opinions : Qualified Immunity Rap Battles</title><description>&lt;p&gt;David and Sarah have Super Tuesday numbers to dive into, oral arguments in Louisiana's Supreme Court abortion case, FISA reform, qualified immunity, and is it okay to arrest six-year-olds?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>caleb@thedispatch.com (Advisory Opinions)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">eedd94ddc43c42f5ae0a525447e3d27d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/eedd94ddc43c42f5ae0a525447e3d27d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 17:19:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Brothers Talk : The Brothers Talk Episode 4: Black-on-Black</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Rod, Scott, &amp;amp; Norm discuss the negative connotations of Black-on-Black as in crime, race relations, and stereotypes...&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thebrotherstalk@gmail.com (The Brothers Talk)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9e138a4e227645c2bda9ad4214e5a80b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9e138a4e227645c2bda9ad4214e5a80b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The KrisAnne Hall Show : Episode 1054 Congressional Criminals - Above The Law?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://youtu.be/IPCVhXLg0M4"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch the KrisAnne Hall Show on YouTube&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What will happen to America's political aristocracy as they continue to blatantly break the law?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A special introduction to the minds of REAL millennials, not the ones the media wants you to see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ensure this Excellent Constitution Training Continues!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Partner with The KrisAnne Hall Daily Journal and be a part of the force that will restore Americans with their Constitutional Principles!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To JOIN with us just simply Go to &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.krisannehall.com/index.php/donate"&gt;https://www.krisannehall.com/index.php/donate&lt;/a&gt; and give OR&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Text- impact2020 to 33777&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Subscribe to the KrisAnne Hall YouTube Channel &lt;a href="http://youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=krisannehall1"&gt;http://youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=krisannehall1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Books, DVDs and On Demand Seminars by KrisAnne Hall at &lt;a href="https://krisannehall.com/"&gt;https://KrisAnneHall.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Support this podcast: &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/the-krisanne-hall-show/support" rel="payment"&gt;https://anchor.fm/the-krisanne-hall-show/support&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts44+f0b3c04@anchor.fm (The KrisAnne Hall Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d07663a74ac741d7b0194a3065c29f7e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d07663a74ac741d7b0194a3065c29f7e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 16:30:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bold and Blunt : How to Save America</title><description>&lt;p&gt;If you want to save America -- really, truly save America -- it's going to take more than voting Republican this November. It's going to take a widespread, national return to Judeo-Christian values. And to start, Dr. Michael Youssef, internationally-known pastor and founder of Leading The Way ministries, has written a book that lays out well the road that must be traveled: "Saving Christianity." Pure and simple, saving America starts with saving Christianity.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>media@washingtontimes.com (Bold and Blunt)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c67672ed26ee4b6d8ff9147db444bde8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c67672ed26ee4b6d8ff9147db444bde8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 15:36:12 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Left Anchor : Episode 124 PREVIEW - Super Tuesday and Warren Drops Out</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this excerpt we discuss how to help Democratic voters realize that a Biden nomination is the risk it is. &lt;a href='https://www.patreon.com/posts/34617760'&gt;Subscribe here&lt;/a&gt; to hear the whole thing!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>catchment.basin@gmail.com (Left Anchor)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bbbe2fc26e204cd8999c3a8ddb17fbea</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bbbe2fc26e204cd8999c3a8ddb17fbea/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 15:32:24 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>News In Context : News In Context: Human Library with Derek Wolfgram &amp; Jenny Barnes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Redwood City Library Director Derek Wolfgram and Library Services Supervisor Jenny Barnes talk about the Redwood City Public Library's Human Library, which helps to bridge divides by allowing readers to check out human "books" and have a conversation across difference.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>newsincontextpodcast@gmail.com (News In Context)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0e9d65600c9d40ebae6046e8b4d1bc02</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0e9d65600c9d40ebae6046e8b4d1bc02/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 14:15:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Into America : Into the Fight for Lindsey Graham's Seat</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Lindsey Graham is a giant in politics. The three-term Republican Senator has served more than two decades in Congress.&amp;nbsp;He’s now a close ally to President&amp;nbsp;Donald Trump.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He’s also up for re-election in 2020, and for the first time ever he’s facing a serious challenge to his South Carolina Senate seat. The fight comes from Jaime Harrison, a young, black Democrat, and a relative newcomer to the national stage. Harrison has raised more money than any Democrat running for the seat in state history, but he’s still a relative unknown.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this episode of&amp;nbsp;Into America,&amp;nbsp;Trymaine Lee talks to Harrison and Graham’s&amp;nbsp;campaign, to find out why both&amp;nbsp;believe they will win.&amp;nbsp;And we visit&amp;nbsp;the red city of&amp;nbsp;Greenville, to&amp;nbsp;talk to a voter who&amp;nbsp;has supported Graham in the past and is now backing Harrison.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further Reading:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/south-carolina-voters-no-insurance-deep-medical-debt-swayed-health-n1144406" target="_blank"&gt;South Carolina voters with no insurance, deep medical debt swayed by health care&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (Into America)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8207319c021d41ec9b97a51250d449d7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8207319c021d41ec9b97a51250d449d7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 14:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>John Solomon Reports : The real story about how former Missouri Gov. Eric Greitens was pushed from office</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Investigations reveal how a felony case against him was built on lies that included perjury&amp;nbsp;and hiding exculpatory evidence.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>media@justthenews.com (John Solomon Reports)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8246db97a6c0472396582925c0f308c5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8246db97a6c0472396582925c0f308c5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 13:31:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>This Is America with Rich Valdes Podcast : Cantankerous Chuck &amp; el Caríbe</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today,&amp;nbsp;Rich looks at Sen. Chuck Schumer's 'fighting words' toward two Supreme Court Justices and his #SorryNotSorry comments after he had to tuck his tail and apologize for the threats he made. Then, President Trump addressed the Latino Coalition Summit yesterday highlighting his successes with Americans of Hispanic heritage. Plus, the latest on a quarantined cruise ship in the Caribbean (el&amp;nbsp;Car&amp;iacute;be).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://paypal.me/RichValdes" rel="payment"&gt;Support the show.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>rsementa@gmail.com (This Is America with Rich Valdes Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">319e443020b240e9a8a46b9f88392d96</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/319e443020b240e9a8a46b9f88392d96/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 13:02:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Asset : BONUS-The Truth about Vladmir Putin's Reign of International Terror</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Russian investigative journalists Andrei Soldatov and Irina Borogan risk their lives every day to expose the truth about Vladamir Putin's murder sprees around the world, including in the United States and Great Britain. In wide-ranging exclusive interview with Max Bergmann, the host of The Asset podcast, Soldatov and Borogan explain how and why Putin orders international assassinations and the reason there are little to no consequences for the Russian leader.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To hear the full interview, please subscribe to our Patreon page.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://www.patreon.com/posts/34596098/edit&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@theassetpodcast.org (The Asset)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e91045a2fcbf4836a6b9faf9b6b0e41e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e91045a2fcbf4836a6b9faf9b6b0e41e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 12:45:14 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Andrew Klavan Show : Ep. 856 - Schumer Chooses the Thug Life</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Let us kill our children or else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out The Cold War: What We Saw, a new podcast written and presented by Bill Whittle at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar&lt;/a&gt;. In Part 1 we peel back the layers of mystery cloaking the Terror state run by the Kremlin, and watch as America takes its first small steps onto the stage of world leadership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like The Andrew Klavan Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: KLAVAN and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/Klavan"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/Klavan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>andrewklavanshow@dailywire.com (The Andrew Klavan Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d37c64358ab3442ca17eb446c06cc162</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d37c64358ab3442ca17eb446c06cc162/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 11:35:24 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sara Carter Show : Roger Stone’s advice for Bernie Sanders: Bring Elizabeth Warren on as your VP</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Sara A. Carter interviewed Trump ally Roger Stone who is facing a 40 month prison sentence. Stone is under gag order and restricted from speaking about his trial. He is, however, speaking about the Democratic primary pool and had some advice for Bernie Sanders. He said he absolutely believes President Trump will sweep the nation in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>support@thesaracartershow.com (The Sara Carter Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6d8c2d7888cb4ef594b2ce238cc3fc7f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6d8c2d7888cb4ef594b2ce238cc3fc7f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 10:57:27 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>7am : My name’s Scott Morrison, and I have a truth problem</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week Scott Morrison finally told the truth about his attempt to invite Hillsong founder Brian Houston to a White House dinner. At the same time more details have emerged about his office&amp;rsquo;s involvement in the sports grants scandal. Today, Paul Bongiorno on the bigger questions being asked about trust and the prime minister&amp;rsquo;s relationship to the truth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guest:&lt;/strong&gt; Columnist for &lt;em&gt;The Saturday Paper&lt;/em&gt; Paul Bongiorno.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background reading:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thesaturdaypaper.com.au/"&gt;The Saturday Paper&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://themonthly.com.au/"&gt;The Monthly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on today&amp;rsquo;s episode, visit &lt;a href="http://7ampodcast.com.au"&gt;7ampodcast.com.au&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jadeb@schwartzmedia.com.au (7am)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">92555735887e47c6990a3fe24cd6451a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/92555735887e47c6990a3fe24cd6451a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Michael Knowles Show : Ep. 506 - The Establishment Always Wins</title><description>&lt;p&gt;After paying more than $12 million per delegate, Mike Bloomberg drops out of the presidential race and endorses Joe Biden. Meanwhile, Bernie Sanders releases a new ad starring former president Barack Obama. We will examine why the establishment always wins. Then, at a pro-abortion rally, Rashida Tlaib shrieks, and Chuck Schumer threatens two Supreme Courts justices. We will examine why pro-abortion activists always seem so crazy. Finally, Alex Trebek gives us all some much-needed perspective, and finally the Mailbag!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out The Cold War: What We Saw, a new podcast written and presented by Bill Whittle at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar&lt;/a&gt;. In Part 1 we peel back the layers of mystery cloaking the Terror state run by the Kremlin, and watch as America takes its first small steps onto the stage of world leadership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like The Michael Knowles Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: KNOWLES and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/Knowles"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/Knowles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>michaelknowlesshow@dailywire.com (The Michael Knowles Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">730fb192c53445f0bf4a3179b4a4e79c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/730fb192c53445f0bf4a3179b4a4e79c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 08:21:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hold These Truths with Dan Crenshaw : The Truth About Gun Bans, Violent Crime, and Universal Background Checks. What Really Happens When Firearms are Banned, with Dr. John Lott</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. John Lott is an economist and a world-recognized expert on guns and crime. What happens in communities where guns are banned? Do universal background checks really accomplish what advocates say - or are there unintended consequences? How does gun ownership empower the weakest members of society? Dr. Lott has spent decades researching the statistics behind questions like these, and his answers may surprise you.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr. Lott is Founder and President of the Crime Prevention Research Center. He has published over 100 articles in peer-reviewed academic journals and written nine books, including “More Guns, Less Crime,” “The Bias Against Guns,” and “Freedomnomics.”&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>danny.walden@mail.house.gov (Hold These Truths with Dan Crenshaw)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c0806e34276f4ade8eb11734123565f5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c0806e34276f4ade8eb11734123565f5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 07:09:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Pega'os En La Mañana con Julio Rivera Saniel : Pega'os en la Mañana - Jueves, 5 de marzo de 2020</title><author>radioisladigital@gmail.com (Pega'os En La Mañana con Julio Rivera Saniel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c4d1e3db2c794ae6a5432029ec721dc0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c4d1e3db2c794ae6a5432029ec721dc0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 06:56:31 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Building Tomorrow : Afro-Futurism</title><description>&lt;p&gt;If you watched the 2018 blockbuster&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Black Panther&lt;/em&gt;, then you’ve encountered a genre known as Afro-Futurism, in which predominately African-American authors use science fiction to explore black liberation in a technological advanced future. These are the kinds of stories that spark the creative energy of the next generation of engineers, scientists, and entrepreneurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this episode, we interview Dr. Moradewun Adejunmobi about Afro-Futurism and what it signals about future expectations. Then we talk to Justin Hamilton from Zipline, a drone startup in Africa that is making science fiction into science fact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is the power of science fiction? What is Afrofuturism? Why can't a drone delivery company who delivers life-saving treatments test their product in the United States?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>av@libertarianism.org (Building Tomorrow)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2f99e150970245bdab07eb633162ac5b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2f99e150970245bdab07eb633162ac5b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 03:13:34 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Verdict with Ted Cruz : Ep. 16 - How Nigel Farage Won Brexit</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Nigel Farage joins Senator Ted Cruz and Michael Knowles to break down what led to the UK’s dramatic exit from the EU, discuss what Huawei's spy tech could mean for the Five Eyes relationship, and drop a few bombshells about the most important issue of our time, Megxit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verdict is co-hosted by Senator Ted Cruz and Michael Knowles. To hear more of Michael, check out The Michael Knowles Show on Youtube, Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you stream your favorite podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>verdictcruz@gmail.com (Verdict with Ted Cruz)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ef40911db48b4f1297a0f5b87f6dc147</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ef40911db48b4f1297a0f5b87f6dc147/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>2020 Politics War Room : James Carville Wraps Up Super Tuesday and Roger Altman Analyzes the Economy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/jamescarville"&gt;James Carville&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/AlHuntDC"&gt;Al Hunt&lt;/a&gt; analyze Joe Biden's super Super Tuesday taking the delegate lead over Bernie Sanders. &lt;a href= "https://www.evercore.com/bios/roger-c-altman/"&gt;Evercore CEO Roger Altman&lt;/a&gt; examines the volatility of the stock market amidst CoronaVirus concerns.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;2020 Politics War Room is produced by &lt;a href= "https://ncpodcasts.com/"&gt;Native Creative Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>politicswarroom@gmail.com (2020 Politics War Room)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">038a6afedcef43a59dfe33428f479e2d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/038a6afedcef43a59dfe33428f479e2d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Views from Hong Kong : Hong Kong budget recap</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to another episode of Views from Hong Kong!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our main topic for this week is the budget that was presented on the 26th of February. Topics covered include the 10,000 HKD cash handout to all adult permanent residents, the various other programmes and schemes in the budget and a discussion of the longer term outlook for Hong Kong.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow us on twitter @viewshk. Located here: &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/viewshk"&gt;https://twitter.com/viewshk&lt;/a&gt; and do contact us at viewshk@outlook.com if you have any questions/comments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disclaimer: The views and opinions expressed on the podcast are those of the authors only and do not necessarily reflect the views of any other person or organisation. The authors do not give advice via the podcast and do not warrant or represent the accuracy, completeness, correctness, suitability or validity of any information given on the podcast.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>viewshk@outlook.com (Views from Hong Kong)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1f7b44ec73d3485f8e4fe9ee2e501aa0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1f7b44ec73d3485f8e4fe9ee2e501aa0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Throughline : Public Universal Friend</title><description>America in the run-up to the Revolutionary War wasn't just a period of dramatic political change, it was also a time of great religious and social instability, anxiety and experimentation. And in the midst of it all there arose a self-proclaimed genderless prophet — the Public Universal Friend. This week, how the Public Universal Friend rocked society's norms and paved the way for others to reject religious and gender expectations for centuries to come.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (Throughline)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cf37b8b2419a468fb3c0d6b22cc803ee</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cf37b8b2419a468fb3c0d6b22cc803ee/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 21:07:40 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Argument : How Biden Came Back</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Super Tuesday has left the Democratic primary race with two clear front runners: Senator Bernie Sanders and former Vice President Joe Biden. The columnists debate how we got here, and what this week's voting results mean for the rest of the 2020 race. Then, as the coronavirus epidemic approaches pandemic status, how alarmed should we feel and what can be done to limit the spread of the disease? Plus, Michelle suggests you walk through fire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For background reading on this episode, visit&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/column/the-argument" target="_blank"&gt;nytimes.com/theargument&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>argument@nytimes.com (The Argument)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e3c62952fd3f4fbfb3f0e39cf4d00c1c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e3c62952fd3f4fbfb3f0e39cf4d00c1c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Global Dispatches -- World News That Matters : How China's Demand for Soybeans is Fueling the Destruction of the Amazon Rainforest</title><description>&lt;p&gt;China is by far the world's largest importer of soy, which is uses mostly as feed for pigs. Brazil is the second largest soybean producer in the world, after the United States, and the vast majority of Brazilian soy ends up in China.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In recent years, as the trade war between the United States and China threatened to disrupt Chinese soy supplies, Beijing began making big investments in Brazil. This includes a potential new railway -- the so-called grain train -- that would link Brazilian soy fields to its ports. The problem is, from an environmental point of view, these fields are mostly in the heart of the lush Amazon rainforest. As Chinese demands for Brazilian soy have increased, so too has the pace of deforestation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;My guest today, Melissa Chan, co-authored a piece in The Atlantic that examines the impact that Chinese demand for soy is having on the region of Brazil where it is mostly grown. The piece, titled: China Wants Food. Brazil Pays the Price, was supported by the Pulitzer Center. Melissa Chan's co-author is Heriberto Araujo.   &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We kick off discussing the significance of a single road in the Amazon called BR 163, before having a broader conversation about the relationship between china, brazil, soybeans and climate change. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is one of those stories that has such immense explanatory power that touches on geo-politics, the rise of china and the power of Chinese consumers, and of course, climate change. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2020/02/china-brazil-amazon-environment-pork/606601/"&gt;  https:///www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2020/02/china-brazil-amazon-environment-pork/606601/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>globaldispatchespodcast@gmail.com (Global Dispatches -- World News That Matters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">08f596b461ea49d781a5362c2f18453e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/08f596b461ea49d781a5362c2f18453e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FAQ NYC : Episode 73: The Safe Choice?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Progressive strategist Rebecca Katz joins Chrissy, Harry and Alex for a look at the shaken state of the Democratic party following Super Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>justdafaq@gmail.com (FAQ NYC)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4d92b24d321f4f08b72455db64bdcae3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4d92b24d321f4f08b72455db64bdcae3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 18:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Deconstructed with Mehdi Hasan : Can Biden Still Be Stopped?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s being described as one of the biggest turnarounds in presidential primary history. After disappointing results in Iowa, New Hampshire, and Nevada, Joe Biden appeared to be fading in Bernie Sanders’ rearview mirror. Then came his crushing win in South Carolina, after which Tom Steyer, Amy Klobuchar, and Pete Buttigieg all dropped out of the race. Klobuchar and Buttigieg, along with former candidate Beto O’Rourke, then endorsed Biden, cementing the growing consensus among establishment Democrats that the former Vice President is the best positioned candidate to stop Bernie. Where does all this leave the Democratic race? Mehdi talks to Intercept DC bureau chief Ryan Grim and to Larry Cohen of Our Revolution about Biden's big night and about Bernie’s path forward. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@theintercept.com (Deconstructed with Mehdi Hasan)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f732339a8d784b09a1e20c0443e59d5d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f732339a8d784b09a1e20c0443e59d5d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 15:39:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Max &amp; Murphy : Episode 202: Assessing Coronavirus In NYC - Threat, Preparation, &amp; Response</title><description>Episode 202: Assessing Coronavirus In NYC - Threat, Preparation, &amp; Response by Max &amp; Murphy</description><author>gothamgazette@gmail.com (Max &amp; Murphy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0776d031c3c44c5d93346d6eafc30473</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0776d031c3c44c5d93346d6eafc30473/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 15:28:37 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Campaign HQ with David Plouffe : The Biden Surge</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Anita Dunn senior adviser for Biden for President about what happened Super Tuesday, their plans for the upcoming states, and how they plan to strengthen their campaign to compete against both Bernie Sanders and Donald Trump.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@cadence13.com (Campaign HQ with David Plouffe)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">05d5b74903a5496aa5e3d4d9b82a1427</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/05d5b74903a5496aa5e3d4d9b82a1427/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 13:53:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The McCarthy Report : Episode 73: Risking a Taliban Deal</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today on &lt;i data-stringify-type="italic"&gt;The McCarthy Report&lt;/i&gt;, Andy and Rich discuss the United States’ ongoing negotiations with the Taliban, a reignited FISA controversy, and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>studio@nationalreview.com (The McCarthy Report)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1a70c967b3e44be48a9dbaf7f5981791</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1a70c967b3e44be48a9dbaf7f5981791/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 13:51:15 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dispatch Podcast : Joe's Super Tuesday</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Sarah, Steve, Jonah, and David have a lot to discuss after Joe Biden's campaign roared back to life with a number of big wins on Super Tuesday. Sarah also gets the guy's thoughts on the latest with coronavirus and the Afghanistan peace deal.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>caleb@thedispatch.com (The Dispatch Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a67b1deb913e42539dbcf1e4dd16738b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a67b1deb913e42539dbcf1e4dd16738b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 13:44:01 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Carnegie Council Audio Podcast : Biden, Sanders, &amp; Foreign Policy after Super Tuesday, with Nikolas Gvosdev</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Senior Fellow Nikolas Gvosdev looks at the foreign policy discussions after Super Tuesday, with only Joe Biden and Bernie Sanders left with realistic chances at the Democratic nomination. When it comes to the U.S. role in the world, what are the big differences between these two candidates? Is Biden's "restorationist" agenda risky? And looking ahead to a post-Trump future, how have relationships changed between the U.S. and its allies?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>carnegieitunes@cceia.org (Carnegie Council Audio Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8abba07fb1a147bbb47274cd2bb3281a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8abba07fb1a147bbb47274cd2bb3281a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 12:31:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Editors : Episode 193: A Shocking Super Tuesday</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week on &lt;i data-stringify-type="italic"&gt;The Editors&lt;/i&gt;, Rich, Charlie, Michael, and Jim dissect last night’s voting outcomes and consider Joe Biden’s new front-runner status.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Light Items&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rich: Being a germaphobe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charlie: &lt;em&gt;Pet Sounds&lt;/em&gt; by the Beach Boys.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michael: &lt;em&gt;Better Call Saul&lt;/em&gt; season 5. Wow!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jim: My 12-year-old son’s a black belt now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Editors’ Picks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rich: &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/03/nanny-state-napoleon/"&gt;Kyle Smith’s piece on Bloomberg in the new issue&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charlie: &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/02/bernie-sanders-hates-america/"&gt;Kevin on Sanders hating America&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michael: Douglas Murray, “&lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/magazine/2020/03/09/after-brexit-britain-carries-on/"&gt;After Brexit, Britain Carries On&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jim: Dan McLaughlin’s observations &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/03/baby-boomers-become-senior-citizens-gen-x-confronts-middle-age/"&gt;about generational changes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Editors&lt;/em&gt; is hosted by Rich Lowry and produced by Sarah Schutte.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>studio@nationalreview.com (The Editors)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cd098cbbeba143e389a17f9e633a53a5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cd098cbbeba143e389a17f9e633a53a5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 12:16:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Individual 1 podcast : Joe Biden's Shocking Super Tuesday Win</title><description>&lt;div&gt;John is excited to break down the remarkable comeback of Joe Biden and what his amazing Super Tuesday victory means. Then John examines Trump's insanity towards his former AG Jeff Sessions.&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>batoul.peters@globalstorynetwork.com (Individual 1 podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4c140878bbae40d9a26f033b9bf5be81</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4c140878bbae40d9a26f033b9bf5be81/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 11:29:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sunflower News Podcast  : WSU Students From the Wichita Pro Bono Immigration Clinic</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week we talk with two students from Wichita State who work for the Wichita Pro Bono Immigration Clinic. Freshman Nicole Bloomquist is the clinic's co-president, and she interns at the Immigration Law and Advocacy Center. Also joining us is freshman Hannah Ezell - a clinic board member and caseworker. The two talk about the work they do to help immigrants in the Wichita community and how lucky they feel to contribute to immigration cases in a meaningful way at such a young age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Sunflower News Podcast is a service of &lt;a href="https://thesunflower.com/" rel="ugc noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;The Sunflower &lt;/a&gt;at Wichita State University. This episode was hosted by Audrey E. Korte and produced by Kyle Landolfi and Audrey E. Korte. It also features original music, courtesy of Ramsey Jamaleddine. Check him out on SoundCloud at &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/fury-10" rel="ugc noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;https://soundcloud.com/fury-10&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find The Sunflower News Podcast on eight different podcast platforms, for free - search for The Sunflower News Podcast or listen to it on Spotify or in your browser at &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/dashboard/episode/anchor.fm/sunflowernews" rel="ugc noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;anchor.fm/sunflowernews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for tuning in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like what you hear give us a shoutout on social media (#SNPWSU) and remember sharing is caring.&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/sunflowernews/message</description><author>Multimedia@thesunflower.com (The Sunflower News Podcast )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1ac591884ff54ea594ad0dcf961a1d4a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1ac591884ff54ea594ad0dcf961a1d4a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 11:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>BE THE PEOPLE : 🎧 Exposing the Risks of America’s Dependence on China for Medicine</title><description>We often read food labels before purchasing food products. We do this because we care about the health and safety of our families. What about the drugs in our medicine cabinets? Millions of Americans are taking drugs made in China that lack the Food and Drug Administration safety inspections we take for granted in America. Joining me today to discuss this critical issue is Rosemary Gibson, a senior advisor with the Hastings Center, a bio-ethics research institute. Gibson and Janardan P. Singh are co-authors of China RX: Exposing the Risks of America’s Dependence on China for Medicine.&lt;br /&gt;
For Further Insight:&lt;br /&gt;
Website: &lt;a href="http://www.rosemarygibson.org/about.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;http://www.rosemarygibson.org/about.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:gibsonr@thehastingscenter.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;gibsonr@thehastingscenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Follow on Twitter: &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Rosemary100" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://twitter.com/Rosemary100&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Link to CSPAN Show: &lt;a href="https://www.c-span.org/video/?445077-2/china-rx" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://www.c-span.org/video/?445077-2/china-rx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Book:  &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2Coots0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;China RX: Exposing the Risks of America’s Dependence on China for Medicine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;</description><author>Talk@AmericaOutLoud.com (BE THE PEOPLE)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e8fd39e18091426db8b0bd82dd5a290f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e8fd39e18091426db8b0bd82dd5a290f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 10:09:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Graham Allen’s Dear America Podcast : EP 71 | America NEEDS Fortitude! | Guest: Dan Crenshaw</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We sit down with Dan Crenshaw to talk about his new book "Fortitude". Mental fortitude is desperately needed in America. The outrage mob and cancel culture are destroying civil discourse. Also, will Dan start responding to Graham's late night texts?! Get ready to laugh. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WeThePeopleHolsters.com/GRAHAM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ExpressVPN.com/GRAHAM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RedArrowWeapons.com OFFER CODE: RecallRalph&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TacPack.com OFFER CODE: GRAHAM&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>dearamerica76@gmail.com (Graham Allen’s Dear America Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">81e1b3824b41451d8dbd7f7bd99035ab</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/81e1b3824b41451d8dbd7f7bd99035ab/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Commentary Magazine Podcast : Our Counterrevolution</title><description>The results of the Super Tuesday contests are in, and they were especially ugly for Bernie Sanders. There’s no disguising the COMMENTARY podcast’s satisfaction with this generally unforeseen turn of events. But does Joe Biden’s revival mean that the Democratic Party’s drift toward socialism has been stopped or is it merely postponed?</description><author>feeds@soundcloud.com (Commentary Magazine Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7be9fda1f22648aebf65c3b64332c6d2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7be9fda1f22648aebf65c3b64332c6d2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 09:00:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump, Inc.  : The Family Business</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This episode of Trump, Inc. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/trumpinc/episodes/trump-inc-family-business"&gt;&lt;em&gt;was originally released&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; on September 18, 2019. We’ll be back next week with a new episode of Trump, Inc.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We've done dozens of episodes over since Donald Trump took office, detailing how predatory lenders are &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/trump-inc-podcast-payday-lenders-spent-1-million-at-a-trump-resort-and-cashed-in"&gt;paying the president&lt;/a&gt;, how Trump has profited from &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/trump-inc-new-evidence-emerges-of-possible-wrongdoing-by-trump-inaugural-committee"&gt;his own inauguration&lt;/a&gt; and how Trump's friends have sought to use their &lt;a href="https://features.propublica.org/trump-inc-podcast/sheldon-adelson-casino-magnate-trump-macau-and-japan/"&gt;access&lt;/a&gt; in pursuit of &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/trump-inc-podcast-elliott-broidy-all-access-pass"&gt;profit&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We've noticed something along the way. It's not just that the president has mixed his business and governing. It's that the way Trump does business is spreading across the government. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trump's company isn't like most big businesses. It is accountable to only one man, it has &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/trump-inc-podcast-money-laundering-and-the-trump-taj-mahal"&gt;broken the rules&lt;/a&gt;, and those promoting it have long engaged in what Trump has dubbed, ahem, "&lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/ivanka-donald-trump-jr-close-to-being-charged-felony-fraud"&gt;truthful&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://features.propublica.org/trump-inc-podcast/trump-family-business-panama-city-khafif/"&gt;hyperbole&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those traits are now popping up in the government. It may seem like the news from Washington is a cacophony of scandals. But they fit clear patterns — patterns that Trump has brought with him from his business.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (Trump, Inc. )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">52605c12ce10429188c17fc0423fe579</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/52605c12ce10429188c17fc0423fe579/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Between The Lines Radio Newsmagazine podcast : Between The Lines -  March 4, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;• Yale&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;University's&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;School&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;of&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Public&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Health's Hanna Ehrlich: &lt;/b&gt;Rejection of Profit-Driven Public Health Systems Key to Combatting Future Pandemics&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;b&gt;Campaign&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;for&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;America’s&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Future's Robert&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Borosage: &lt;/b&gt;Sanders' Movement-Driven Progressive Campaign Attracts Opposition From Corporate Democrats&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• "&lt;b&gt;Megafire:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;The&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Race&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;to&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Extinguish&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;a&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Deadly&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Epidemic&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;of&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Flame" author Michael&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Kodas: &lt;/b&gt;Australia’s Wildfires Foreshadow What’s in Store for our World Facing Catastrophic Climate Change&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;• Bob Nixon's Under-reported News Summary&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;• Sectarian riots break out in New Delhi, India during Trump's visit&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;• Trump's U.S. troop withdrawal from Africa command worries African leaders&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;• Bernie Sanders gambles on "new voter” strategy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visit our website at &lt;a href="https://btlonline.org/"&gt;BTLonline.org&lt;/a&gt; for more information, links, transcripts and in-depth interviews. (Updates after 3 p.m. ET Wednesdays) Follow us on Facebook at BetweenTheLinesRadioNewsmagazine and on Twitter @BTLRadioNews. Join our Patreon community at Patreon.com/BetweenTheLinesRadioNewsmagazine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="https://secure.givelively.org/donate/squeaky-wheel-productions/support-progressive-voices-to-defend-democracy-and-fight-fascism"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (https://secure.givelively.org/donate/squeaky-wheel-productions/support-progressive-voices-to-defend-democracy-and-fight-fascism)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>contact@btlonline.org (Between The Lines Radio Newsmagazine podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1862d32453e24e209a2dc871f4ff6a02</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1862d32453e24e209a2dc871f4ff6a02/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>City Journal's 10 Blocks : Fathers Behind Bars</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.city-journal.org/contributor/rafael-mangual_909" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-auth="NotApplicable"&gt;Rafael Mangual&lt;/a&gt; joins &lt;a href= "https://www.city-journal.org/contributor/kay-s-hymowitz_90" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Kay Hymowitz&lt;/a&gt; to discuss evidence suggesting that children are often better off when criminal parents are imprisoned—the subject of Mangual's story, "&lt;a title= "https://www.city-journal.org/fathers-families-incarceration-harm" href= "https://www.city-journal.org/fathers-families-incarceration-harm" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-auth="NotApplicable"&gt;Fathers, Families, and Incarceration&lt;/a&gt;," from the Winter 2020 Issue of &lt;em&gt;City Journal&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A common criticism of incarceration in the United States, notes Mangual, is that it harms children by taking parents or siblings out of their homes. But recent studies show that children living with a parent who engages in high levels of antisocial behavior may be worse off than kids with incarcerated parents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/CityJournalPodcasts/~4/X9ENrpzIMsk" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>aricks@manhattan-institute.org (City Journal's 10 Blocks)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">35eb81a3f94f4f08bb5c092acd75be2d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/35eb81a3f94f4f08bb5c092acd75be2d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WFUV's Cityscape : Strike a Chord: 'Unlonleying' the Planet</title><description>Even in a city as densely populated as New York, people can be — or at least feel — very alone. And the fact of the matter is loneliness can have serious consequences on a person’s physical and mental health.   &lt;a href="https://www.thatjillian.com/"&gt;Jillian Richardson&lt;/a&gt; is on a mission to make the world less lonely. She's the founder of The Joy List. It’s described as a resource for people to find events that they can go to by themselves, and leave with a new friend. Jillian’s also the author of the book &lt;em&gt;Unlonely Planet: How Healthy Congregations Can Change the World&lt;/em&gt;. She's our guest in this special presentation, produced in conjunction with &lt;a href= "https://bronxnet.org/watch/videos/9062/"&gt;BronxNet Television&lt;/a&gt;.</description><author>newsroom@wfuv.org (WFUV's Cityscape)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">744c89c9bed74f2291bdf91d1b4eb433</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/744c89c9bed74f2291bdf91d1b4eb433/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Beating Around The Bush : S3E7 - BOM, Bottled OJ, Fodder, Jacinda &amp; Sea Lake Selfies</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week’s take on the news relating to rural and regional Australia with Fleur Anderson and Wade Dabinett.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agribusiness&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Surely the BOM hasn't got it wrong?!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.farmweekly.com.au/story/6654388/bom-defends-summer-dry-forecast-in-spite-of-wet-spell/?cs=4770" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.farmweekly.com.au/story/6654388/bom-defends-summer-dry-forecast-in-spite-of-wet-spell/?cs=4770&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Bottled OJ under threat&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2020-02-26/orange-juice-in-bottles-under-threat-in-australia/12001156" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2020-02-26/orange-juice-in-bottles-under-threat-in-australia/12001156&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Politics:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Only a quarter of water for fodder program delivered&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2020-02-28/only-a-quarter-of-water-for-fodder-delivered-to-farms/11979452" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.abc.net.au/news/2020-02-28/only-a-quarter-of-water-for-fodder-delivered-to-farms/11979452&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Community&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Jacinda Adern burns ScoMo while he stands 1m away. Respectful? In her rights? Election motivations to appear decisive?&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.news.com.au/finance/work/leaders/jacinda-ardern-slams-australias-deportation-policy-during-joint-press-conference-with-scott-morrison/news-story/541f839dd9c2c8c375bec88b8544f45b" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.news.com.au/finance/work/leaders/jacinda-ardern-slams-australias-deportation-policy-during-joint-press-conference-with-scott-morrison/news-story/541f839dd9c2c8c375bec88b8544f45b&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Selfies on the salt lake&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2020-03-01/victoria-selfies-sea-lake-chinese-media-weibo-farmers-wife/11998822" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.abc.net.au/news/2020-03-01/victoria-selfies-sea-lake-chinese-media-weibo-farmers-wife/11998822&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Follow Us:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Join the Rural Business Collective community and join the conversation over at &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/ruralbusinesscollective/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/ruralbusinesscollective/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/ruralbusinesscollective/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Beating Around the Bush is the podcast of the &lt;a href="https://www.ruralbusinesscollective.com.au/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Rural Business Collective&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.ruralbusinesscollective.com.au/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;www.ruralbusinesscollective.com.au&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This is a &lt;a href="https://www.cahootsradio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Cahoots Radio&lt;/a&gt; production edited by Skye Manson &lt;a href="https://www.cahootsradio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;www.cahootsradio.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Hosted by &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/wade-dabinett-947763167" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Wade Dabinett&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/wade-dabinett-947763167/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/in/wade-dabinett-947763167/&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/fleuranderson/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Fleur Anderson&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/fleuranderson/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/in/fleuranderson/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Let us know your favourite news stories for the week on email - &lt;a&gt;podcasts@ruralbusinesscollective.com.au&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>fleur@thecahootsgroup.com.au (Beating Around The Bush)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0ed7b2bd5deb4fb9a5578fca126afc68</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0ed7b2bd5deb4fb9a5578fca126afc68/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:45:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Chuck ToddCast: Meet the Press : Super Tuesday Recap with Carrie Dann and Mark Murray</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Chuck Todd sits down with the First Read team for a late night recap (or is it early morning?) of everything we learned on Super Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>matt.rivera@nbcuni.com (The Chuck ToddCast: Meet the Press)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b606ee91f14e4413a983f257224dad25</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b606ee91f14e4413a983f257224dad25/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:17:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Deep Background with Noah Feldman : The View from Beijing</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In an effort to curtail the spread of coronavirus, much of China is essentially under lockdown. Pulitzer-Prize winning journalist Ian Johnson talks about what life is like in the capital city.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marketing@pushkin.fm (Deep Background with Noah Feldman)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5d54222a72e142ddb6563300a4ae24f9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5d54222a72e142ddb6563300a4ae24f9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>You Decide with Errol Louis : Rebecca Traister: Women, Politics and the Uncertain Road Ahead</title><description>&lt;p id="cq-gen278"&gt;How will women vote in 2020? What will happen with down-ballot elections? And what do Maine voters truly think of Senator Susan Collins?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="cq-gen279"&gt;Rebecca Traister, who has written about women in politics at length, joined Errol ahead of Super Tuesday to try to answer those questions. She talks about the role of women’s rage in politics, warns about the media’s intense focus on the race for the White House and analyzes the different campaigns, including Elizabeth Warren’s. She also explores what we should learn from the 2018 midterm elections as we head deeper into the primary season. And she discusses her recent profile in New York Magazine of Maine Senator Susan Collins.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="cq-gen280"&gt;MENTIONED IN THIS EPISODE:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="cq-gen281"&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.simonandschuster.com/books/Good-and-Mad/Rebecca-Traister/9781501181818" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Good and Mad: The Revolutionary Power of Women's Anger&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="cq-gen282"&gt;JOIN THE CONVERSATION&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="cq-gen283"&gt;Do you have any thoughts or questions for Errol? Weigh in on twitter with the hashtag &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/hashtag/ny1youdecide"&gt;#NY1YouDecide&lt;/a&gt; or give us a call at 212-379-3440 and leave a message.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>michael.zilman@charter.com (You Decide with Errol Louis)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6c91a73c13ce45ca81fc3a815a475b2b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6c91a73c13ce45ca81fc3a815a475b2b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Federalist Radio Hour : Super Tuesday And Coronavirus</title><description>The Federalist's Culture Editor Emily Jashinsky and Senior Editor Christopher Bedford discuss the political fallout after Super Tuesday and the coronavirus pandemic.</description><author>info@podcastone.com (The Federalist Radio Hour)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8610d97bfbc34c19b12d4d178da051b9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8610d97bfbc34c19b12d4d178da051b9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Make Me Smart with Kai and Molly : What did the Fed just do?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As if you needed more evidence that the COVID-19 outbreak has ripple effects through the economy, the Federal Reserve cut interest rates by a half point this morning. It&amp;#8217;s a very unusual move, unseen since 2008. So we&amp;#8217;re going to take some time today to talk though what that cut means, what the Fed is saying about coronavirus, the market reaction and whether or not we should even care about stocks when there&amp;#8217;s a pandemic brewing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>makemesmart@marketplace.org (Make Me Smart with Kai and Molly)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2b0629cac83b4252b27b347fa4601757</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2b0629cac83b4252b27b347fa4601757/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 16:07:52 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Curtis &amp; Juliet Podcast : 3-3-20: Comeback Joe Biden?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Another case of Coronavirus is confirmed in New York. The crew still is concerned that Juliet may have it. Can Joe Biden pull out wins on Super Tuesday?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>OGpodcastnetwork@gmail.com (Curtis &amp; Juliet Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a65f713c2ddd4d8fbf3f2c5c4a8a4c86</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a65f713c2ddd4d8fbf3f2c5c4a8a4c86/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 13:15:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Prickly Politics : Race for NY-12: Suraj Patel</title><description>Prickly Podcast co-host Andrew Millman interviews Suraj Patel, a candidate for New York's 12th congressional district challenging incumbent Rep. Carolyn Maloney. In Prickly Politics Interviews, he talks about his "Family Opportunity Guarantee" and how he'd be a different Member of Congress compared to his opponent. Check back next week for the first Prickly Politics Explains...</description><author>pricklypodcast@gmail.com (Prickly Politics)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">71911b9a64fd4e95872da27ee7cff836</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/71911b9a64fd4e95872da27ee7cff836/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 12:21:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Realignment : Ep. 27: Jane Coaston, Covering the Right's Realignment</title><description>Jane Coaston, Vox senior politics reporter and co-host of The Weeds podcast, joins The Realignment to discuss the state of the conservative movement.</description><author>phegseth@hudson.org (The Realignment)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">86ce04e5fe594dfabd0fad5a0efa7b9e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/86ce04e5fe594dfabd0fad5a0efa7b9e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 04:00:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Effective Compassion : Episode 10: Community First Village</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Just outside Austin city limits, hundreds of tiny homes and RV sites are scattered over 51-acres. The Community First Village is home to many formerly chronic homeless men and women. On the surface, it may look like just another housing initiative, but here, relationships transform simple houses into something much more significant. Anna Johansen and Charissa Koh visit with Alan Graham, the village founder.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>feedback@worldandeverything.com (Effective Compassion)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">772aa442af1842539a8a2fce4ee6823c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/772aa442af1842539a8a2fce4ee6823c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:15:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Is This Happening? with Chris Hayes : Exile and Basketball with Enes Kanter</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Enes Kanter is a wanted man in his home country of Turkey. He’s long been a vocal critic of Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan and it’s come at a high cost. At 6′ 10″, Kanter also happens to play for the Boston Celtics in the NBA. How he came to sit at this intersection is a riveting story, one that involves an NBA draft at age 19, a failed coup d'état, and a system of retribution by the Turkish government that targets not only Kanter but the family he left behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;YOU MIGHT ALSO LIKE:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/think/opinion/evening-uneven-professional-playing-field-howard-bryant-podcast-transcript-ncna1119676" target="_blank"&gt;The Uneven Playing Field with Howard Bryant&lt;/a&gt; (Jan 24)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>think@nbcuni.com (Why Is This Happening? with Chris Hayes)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">379d83cf3482488db48c51747b09cbe0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/379d83cf3482488db48c51747b09cbe0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hardball with Chris Matthews : Chris Matthews announces retirement</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Chris Matthews is announcing his retirement from Hardball.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (Hardball with Chris Matthews)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9afe4c824c8a48e5befea2d8925fdbe0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9afe4c824c8a48e5befea2d8925fdbe0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 21:41:34 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hear the Bern : 47 - Which Side Are You On? (Live w/ The Dig, Michael Brooks, &amp; Natalie Shure)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Airplane delays kept Briahna from a joint live show in Boston with Daniel Denvir's The Dig podcast and the Michael Brooks Show last weekend, but we're including a portion of that show featuring Natalie Shure here. Listen to the full show: &lt;a href="https://www.thedigradio.com/podcast/bernie-2020-with-michael-brooks-and-natalie-shure/"&gt;https://www.thedigradio.com/podcast/bernie-2020-with-michael-brooks-and-natalie-shure/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, a short clip of Briahna's conversation with Karen Hunter from the Karen Hunter Show in which they discuss billionaires, poverty, and talking to those with whom you disagree. Watch the full interview: &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/ZTYjF-oSYb8"&gt;https://youtu.be/ZTYjF-oSYb8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Michael Brooks Show: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCh2UY1hxlMr4_7Az_iQ82HQ"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCh2UY1hxlMr4_7Az_iQ82HQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Dig: &lt;a href="https://www.thedigradio.com"&gt;https://www.thedigradio.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Natalie Shure on Twitter: &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/nataliesurely"&gt;https://twitter.com/nataliesurely&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Which Side Are You On" by RevolutionarySongCircle is licensed under a Creative Commons BY license: &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/revolutionarysongcircle/which-side-are-you-on"&gt;https://soundcloud.com/revolutionarysongcircle/which-side-are-you-on&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hearthebern@berniesanders.com (Hear the Bern)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">722fa99e46ab40e0b1fead6a456d58f3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/722fa99e46ab40e0b1fead6a456d58f3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 21:34:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hot Zone with Chuck Holton : Episode 295 - Peace in Afghanistan?  Or not?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;CNN and MSNBC have exactly ZERO stories on their websites about the historic peace deal in Afghanistan. Here's a podcast devoted to helping you understand what you need to know about this historic event that may well signal the FINAL end to the war...or not.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>holtocw@gmail.com (The Hot Zone with Chuck Holton)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">20b87f0b2f7346aba6449abde2345304</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/20b87f0b2f7346aba6449abde2345304/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>I'm Calling Bovine Scatology : A Living Wage Solves Everything?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Bernie Sanders and the socialists continue to harp on a "living wage." What does that even mean? And will it solve everything? Will it solve anything? Phil Valentine calls bovine scatology on that.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>phil@philvalentine.com (I'm Calling Bovine Scatology)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b7a26d7a88164bb184534be9bf3ea1cd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b7a26d7a88164bb184534be9bf3ea1cd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 10:00:29 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ben Shapiro Show : Ep. 964 - The Biden Comeback</title><description>Biden swamps the competition in South Carolina, Super Tuesday approacheth and that right quick, and the Trump administration deals with fallout from the spread of coronavirus.

Check out The Cold War: What We Saw, a new podcast written and presented by Bill Whittle at  https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar. In Part 1 we peel back the layers of mystery cloaking the Terror state run by the Kremlin, and watch as America takes its first small steps onto the stage of world leadership.

If you like The Ben Shapiro Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: SHAPIRO and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at https://www.dailywire.com/Shapiro</description><author>benshapiroshow@dailywire.com (The Ben Shapiro Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">79ab6dc22e3d49a592dae418d64e14e4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/79ab6dc22e3d49a592dae418d64e14e4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 09:45:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>UnAborted : Kristan Hawkins | Students for Life of America</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Kristan Hawkins is the President of Students for Life of America (SFLA), the largest pro-life youth organization in the world. With over 1,200 student chapters across all 50-states, SFLA is leading the pro-life generation towards abolition. Labeled by Media Matters as “One of the 4 worst anti-abortion misinformers,” a title she wears with pride, Kristan is a wife, mother, speaker, author, and host of the podcast &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href='https://podcasts.apple.com/ca/podcast/explicitly-pro-life/id1460746245'&gt;Explicitly Pro-Life&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;Kristan and I sat down in DC last month during the March for Life to discuss her story, the state of the pro-life movement, and what it means to be pro-life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Date: 03/02/20&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>seth@prolifetraining.com (UnAborted)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">76d21221a0a0472a96b0c13db9437fa7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/76d21221a0a0472a96b0c13db9437fa7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 08:03:56 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Catchup : Ep.59 - Coronavirus: Is it time to panic?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Coronavirus is spreading like...a virus. Businesses around the world are shutting down, schools are cancelled, events postponed... but in America, it's mostly business-as-usual. Is it time to panic about the Coronavirus? Is it a pandemic waiting to happen? Or much ado about nothing, at least in the U.S.? We talk about that, and more, in this week's episode of The Catchup Podcast! Join the discussion!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow Us:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://Facebook.com/thecatchupcast"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://Instagram.com/thecatchupcast"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://Facebook.com/NoSignalRocks"&gt;No Signal Band Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="https://www.facebook.com/TheCatchupCast/"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (https://www.facebook.com/TheCatchupCast/)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>stratocast24@yahoo.com (The Catchup)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b0052338811a4941b3d43ff9915d3666</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b0052338811a4941b3d43ff9915d3666/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Blinders Off : Necropolis Pt. 3: The Great Fire of 1849</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Great Fire of 1849 is something of a forgotten tragedy in St. Louis history.  Join your brave hosts and Christopher Alan Gordon of the Missouri Historical Society as they explore the cause and lasting effects of the "Appalling Calamity."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Homegrown Guest: Josh Stevens of Reedy Press.  &lt;a href= "https://www.reedypress.com/"&gt;https://www.reedypress.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For more info, read our &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/blindersoffgreatfire"&gt;show notes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Questions?  Comments? Corrections?  Reach out to us at &lt;a href= "mailto:BlindersOffPodcast@gmail.com"&gt;BlindersOffPodcast@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/blindersoffpodcast/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/blindersoffSTL"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/blindersoffpodcast/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Also visit our website and read our blog at &lt;a href= "http://www.blindersoff.show"&gt;BlindersOff.show&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>blindersoffpodcast@gmail.com (Blinders Off)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">becd118e62214a3497fa5cb6ffefe8f5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/becd118e62214a3497fa5cb6ffefe8f5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 17:55:24 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Young Nation Radio : Culture. What is it?</title><description>Culture is the the word of day &amp; the zenith of a spicy convo between Cali Rashad and Rocky B. on Episode 3 of Young Nation Radio! Your hosts explore their personal definitions of culture and in some cases may not always agree...Tune in! Subscribe!</description><author>podcasts49+1047150c@anchor.fm (Young Nation Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2272952d301644efbab30c9bd9bfee00</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2272952d301644efbab30c9bd9bfee00/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 14:21:11 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MEDIA INDIGENA : Indigenous current affairs : Ep. 199: Is Alberta becoming a police-state?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;THIS WEEK: Is Alberta becoming a police-state? At least one critic thinks so, after the province’s recent introduction of Bill 1. Labelled the “Critical Infrastructure Defence Act," the bill will, in the words of the Premier, create new “stiff penalties for anyone who riots on or seeks to impair critical economic infrastructure.” Penalties he says are necessary in light of the “general atmosphere of lawlessness” created by recent Wet'suwet'en solidarity actions across the country.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Joining host/producer Rick Harp this week to discuss the bill and why some fear its repercussions for activism (not least, Indigenous activism) are Ken Williams, assistant professor with the University of Alberta’s department of drama, and Brock Pitawanakwat, Associate Professor of Indigenous Studies at York University.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;// Our theme is 'nesting' by birocratic.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>indigena.group@gmail.com (MEDIA INDIGENA : Indigenous current affairs)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">dc720d7023af44299effd0751373c3ff</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/dc720d7023af44299effd0751373c3ff/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 12:51:36 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>AM Joy : Sen. Doug Jones: Biden can bring back normalcy, heal and unite</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Joe Biden as the 2020 Democratic presidential candidate is strongly supported by Sen. Doug Jones (D-Alabama) who tells Joy Reid, "We're trying to bring this country back to some normalcy and unite people. I think Joe Biden has that ability." And: Joe Biden winning the South Carolina Democratic primary is discussed by U.S. Senate candidate Jaime Harrison who tells Joy Reid regarding what is believed to be record-high voter turnout, "It says to me that this new south is emerging and as I've been saying South Carolina is going to be the tip of the spear." Then: The Donald Trump administration’s coronavirus response is discussed by former Obama official Dr. Kavita Patel who tells Joy Reid that the statements of Trump administration leaders such as Sec. of State Mike Pompeo are, "sending a message to the world that there is no room in the Trump administration for facts." Plus: The Selma march for voting rights in Alabama and Bloody Sunday are being commemorated this Sunday, March 1, 2020 to honor the 55th anniversary of this historic milestone of the Civil Rights Movement, which is Sunday, March 8. Rep. Terri Sewell, whose hometown is Selma, tells Joy Reid, "It’s a time to be renewed from the inspiration of folks like Rep. John Lewis, for us to rededicate ourselves to the cause they fought for." All this and more in this Sunday edition of AM JOY on MSNBC.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (AM Joy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">93fc4a6e1fcb48af8037941f70b378e7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/93fc4a6e1fcb48af8037941f70b378e7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 11:04:32 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC Meet the Press : March 1 - Former V.P. Joe Biden, Pete Buttigieg and Vice President Mike Pence</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former V.P. Joe Biden joins Meet the Press the day after a sweeping victory in South Carolina to discuss his strategy moving into Super Tuesday.  Pete Buttigieg talks about his campaign’s next steps after not winning any delegates in South Carolina. Vice President Mike Pence addresses the administration’s response to the coronavirus. Eddie Glaude Jr., Peggy Noonan, Kristen Welker and Robert Gibbs join the panel.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>MeetThePress@nbcuni.com (NBC Meet the Press)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8b84225188af46f6b63f114a07509611</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8b84225188af46f6b63f114a07509611/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 08:54:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Al Franken Podcast : Pulitzer Prize Winner Dave Fahrenthold Catches Us Up on Trump’s Corruption</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In a time of an international health and economic crises, it’s good to have a POTUS who can be trusted by the world community. Instead, we have a grifter with an entire family of money-grubbing, lying grifters.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>paulwoodywoodhull@gmail.com (The Al Franken Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6d7c80be7293428db80bb8390c5a1dbe</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6d7c80be7293428db80bb8390c5a1dbe/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Candace Owens Show : The Candace Owens Show: Charles Blain</title><description>Does the free market have the answers needed to solve urban issues, such as crime, poverty, stifling regulations and incarcerations that plague our inner cities? Charles Blain, founder of Urban Reform, discusses these solutions on this episode of The Candace Owens Show.</description><author>tylerg@prageru.com (The Candace Owens Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">49a99c8ea3fc47e2a46e2a3adb7ab794</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/49a99c8ea3fc47e2a46e2a3adb7ab794/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 06:00:10 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hot Take : Feb 2020: More Fucking Greenwashing! With Guest Co-Host Maddie Stone</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Guest co-host Maddie Stone, Earther founder-turned-freelance science journalist talks us through the latest tech and climate angles. Plus: shifts in how financial reporters are talking about climate, the spread of climate misinformation, and media taps into the climate feelings of Gen Z.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reading list: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The High Stakes Fight Over Bolivia’s Lithium, &lt;/em&gt;Protocol:  &lt;a href="https://www.protocol.com/bolivia-lithium-morales"&gt;https://www.protocol.com/bolivia-lithium-morales&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;$10 Billion? In This Climate?? &lt;/em&gt;The Atlantic: &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/02/jeff-bezos-will-struggle-spend-10-billion-climate-change/606733/"&gt;https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/02/jeff-bezos-will-struggle-spend-10-billion-climate-change/606733/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Jeff Bezos Climate Superpower that's Bigger than $10 Billion &lt;/em&gt;Earther: &lt;a href="https://earther.gizmodo.com/the-jeff-bezos-climate-superpower-thats-bigger-than-10-1841771004"&gt;https://earther.gizmodo.com/the-jeff-bezos-climate-superpower-thats-bigger-than-10-1841771004&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Once Again, Why Fossil Fuels Are on the Wrong Side of History &lt;/em&gt;Real Money: &lt;a href="https://realmoney.thestreet.com/jim-cramer/jim-cramer-once-again-why-fossil-fuels-are-on-the-wrong-side-of-history-15227698"&gt;https://realmoney.thestreet.com/jim-cramer/jim-cramer-once-again-why-fossil-fuels-are-on-the-wrong-side-of-history-15227698&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Climate has emerged as a real political issue &lt;/em&gt;The Atlantic: &lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/02/poll-us-voters-really-do-care-about-climate-change/606907/"&gt;https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/02/poll-us-voters-really-do-care-about-climate-change/606907/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Trump's Biggest Vulnerability Is His Climate Change Denial &lt;/em&gt;Mother Jones: &lt;a href="https://www.motherjones.com/environment/2020/02/trumps-biggest-vulnerability-is-his-climate-change-denial/"&gt;https://www.motherjones.com/environment/2020/02/trumps-biggest-vulnerability-is-his-climate-change-denial/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Revealed: Quarter of all tweets about climate crisis written by bots &lt;/em&gt;The Guardian &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/feb/21/climate-tweets-twitter-bots-analysis"&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/feb/21/climate-tweets-twitter-bots-analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Beware oil execs in environmentalists' clothing &lt;/em&gt;The Guardian &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2020/feb/14/oil-execs-environmentalists-bp-change-oil-climate"&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2020/feb/14/oil-execs-environmentalists-bp-change-oil-climate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Guardian to ban advertising from fossil fuel firms &lt;/em&gt;The Guardian &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/media/2020/jan/29/guardian-to-ban-advertising-from-fossil-fuel-firms-climate-crisis#show-draft-epics"&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/media/2020/jan/29/guardian-to-ban-advertising-from-fossil-fuel-firms-climate-crisis#show-draft-epics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Is Your Favorite News Source Shilling for Big Oil? &lt;/em&gt;The Nation &lt;a href="https://www.thenation.com/article/environment/media-fossil-fuel-ads/"&gt;https://www.thenation.com/article/environment/media-fossil-fuel-ads/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;How climate experts think about raising children who will inherit a planet in crisis &lt;/em&gt;The Washington Post &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/on-parenting/how-climate-experts-think-about-raising-children-who-will-inherit-a-planet-in-crisis/2020/02/14/b4f3405a-4e69-11ea-b721-9f4cdc90bc1c_story.html"&gt;https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/on-parenting/how-climate-experts-think-about-raising-children-who-will-inherit-a-planet-in-crisis/2020/02/14/b4f3405a-4e69-11ea-b721-9f4cdc90bc1c_story.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Environmental Burden of Generation Z &lt;/em&gt;Washington Post Magazine &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/magazine/2020/02/03/eco-anxiety-is-overwhelming-kids-wheres-line-between-education-alarmism/?arc404=true"&gt;https://www.washingtonpost.com/magazine/2020/02/03/eco-anxiety-is-overwhelming-kids-wheres-line-between-education-alarmism/?arc404=true&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Climate Denial by Any Other Name &lt;/em&gt;Drilled News &lt;a href="https://www.drillednews.com/post/climate-denial-by-any-other-name"&gt;https://www.drillednews.com/post/climate-denial-by-any-other-name&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why I Quit Being a Climate Activist &lt;/em&gt;Vice &lt;a href="https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/g5x5ny/why-i-quit-being-a-climate-activist"&gt;https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/g5x5ny/why-i-quit-being-a-climate-activist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>amy@criticalfrequency.org (Hot Take)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">580511c894ec4a8da2e2d52f5b0d1853</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/580511c894ec4a8da2e2d52f5b0d1853/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>HYPAT med Jennifer &amp; Julia : 2.7 Är kärleken blind?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hänt i veckan: Kina och Corona är 2020s ofrivilliga samtalsämne, gamers utsätts för Swatting och Harvey Weinstein fälls för våldtäkt. Netflix egna produktion Love Is Blind toppar listorna och vi kan inte få nog av serien! Kan man faktiskt bli kär i någon utan att ha sett personen?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instagram: @hypatpodcast @hipsterjefe @juliahqvist&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jennifer.carp@ymail.com (HYPAT med Jennifer &amp; Julia)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">974388004e5749e4baba023d73cf85e2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/974388004e5749e4baba023d73cf85e2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Twelve O'clock Siren : The Episode That Never Was</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Matthew James and Jason kick around a number of topics.  &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leonard Alumni Basketball Tournament Coming Up&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leonard Elementary Fun Run&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leonard Picnic Sponsorships and 1100 Springs at the Picnic.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Much much more is discussed in this 1:30 guestless episode. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jameshartley1@gmail.com (The Twelve O'clock Siren)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">06b12be1b4ac40aa8a2ea1eae979c50e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/06b12be1b4ac40aa8a2ea1eae979c50e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 09:14:17 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Amicus With Dahlia Lithwick | Law, Justice, and the Courts : Have Progressives Lost the Courts for Good?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Dahlia Lithwick asks the new president of the American Constitution Society, Russ Feingold, if it’s too late for progressives to respond to the conservative steamroller that is the Federalist Society. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slate Plus members have access to a bonus segment in which Slate’s Mark Joseph&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stern breaks down the headlines, cases, cert grants, and conundrums from the Supreme Court and federal appellate courts. To start your free two-week trial go to &lt;a href="http://slate.com/amicusplus"&gt;slate.com/amicusplus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Podcast production by Sara Burningham.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>amicus@slate.com (Amicus With Dahlia Lithwick | Law, Justice, and the Courts)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8a2c6f52558e4b6c89bdfc7370448c7a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8a2c6f52558e4b6c89bdfc7370448c7a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Impeachment, Explained : Weeds 2020: The Bernie electability debate</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Weeds 2020! Every other Saturday Ezra and Matt will be exploring a wide range of topics related to the 2020 race. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the Nevada caucuses, Bernie Sanders has become the clear frontrunner in the 2020 Democratic primary, spurring lots of debate over whether he could win in the general election. We discuss where the electability conversation often goes off-the-rails, why discussing electability in 2020 is so different than 1964 or 1972, the case for and against Bernie’s electability prospects, and the strongest attacks that Trump could make against Sanders and Joe Biden. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, we discuss Ezra’s favorite topic of all time: the filibuster. Ezra gives a brief history of this weird procedural tool, and we discuss why so many current Senators are against eliminating it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2020/1/7/21002895/bernie-sanders-2020-electability"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"&lt;/strong&gt;Bernie Sanders can unify Democrats and beat Trump in 2020"&lt;/a&gt; by Matthew Yglesias, Vox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2020/1/15/21054083/elizabeth-warren-2020-democratic-primary"&gt;"The case for Elizabeth Warren"&lt;/a&gt; by Ezra Klein, Vox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/videos/2019/6/17/18681798/filibuster-senate-broke-video"&gt;"How the filibuster broke the US Senate"&lt;/a&gt; by Alvin Chang, Vox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2020/01/bernie-sanders-electable-trump-2020-nomination-popular-socialism.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"&lt;/strong&gt;Running Bernie Sanders Against Trump Would Be an Act of Insanity"&lt;/a&gt; by Jonathan Chait, Intelligencer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/02/sanderss-pricey-tax-and-spending-plans/607105/"&gt;"The Sixty Trillion Dollar Man"&lt;/a&gt; by Ronald brownstein, Atlantic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://prospect.org/day-one-agenda/using-presidential-power-executive-authority/"&gt;"The Day One Agenda"&lt;/a&gt; by David Dayen, American Prospect&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hosts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matthew Yglesias (&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/mattyglesias"&gt;@mattyglesias&lt;/a&gt;), Senior correspondent, Vox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ezra Klein (&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ezraklein?s=20"&gt;@ezraklein&lt;/a&gt;), Editor-at-large, Vox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Vox&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vox is a news network that helps you cut through the noise and understand what's really driving the events in the headlines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow Us&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/future-perfect"&gt;Vox.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook group:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/2XUajwq"&gt;The Weeds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasting@voxmedia.com (Impeachment, Explained)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">51b1adc451574f84aa2a450fda258794</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/51b1adc451574f84aa2a450fda258794/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Overwatch : E13: Governing After ISIS: What’s Next for the Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF), America’s local partner in northeastern Syria, was instrumental in the fight against ISIS and is working to fill the vacuum it left behind. In this episode of Overwatch, ISW’s Research Director Jennifer Cafarella, new Middle East Portfolio Manager Nicholas Heras, and Syria Research Assistant John Dunford discuss the structure and behavior of the SDF, the group’s relationship with the US military, the unique challenges it faces in governing, and its efforts to prevent the resurgence of ISIS within local populations.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>press@understandingwar.org (Overwatch)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">32a94500287e4d609f23e5348a2896bf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/32a94500287e4d609f23e5348a2896bf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 11:35:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Field : Biden’s Last Hope</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former vice president Joseph R. Biden Jr. was once a clear front-runner in the race for the Democratic nomination. Now, he is fighting back from a string of losses and staking his candidacy on his ability to win tomorrow’s South Carolina primary, the first in a state with a large black population. But will he win, and if the margin isn’t as decisive as he hopes, can he stay in the race? Guest: &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/by/astead-w-herndon" target="_blank"&gt;Astead W. Herndon&lt;/a&gt;, who covers national politics for The New York Times traveled to South Carolina with Clare Toeniskoetter and Annie Brown, producers on “The Daily.” For more information on today’s episode, visit nytimes.com/thedaily.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background reading:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new poll showed Mr. Biden with&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/live/2020/south-carolina-primary-02-27#south-carolina-monmouth-poll-biden" target="_blank"&gt; a wide lead in South Carolina&lt;/a&gt;, with Senator Bernie Sanders and hedge fund billionaire Tom Steyer trailing behind.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mr. Biden lashed out after reports that&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/02/sanders-obama-primary-challenge/606709/" target="_blank"&gt; Mr, Sanders considered mounting a primary challenge&lt;/a&gt; to President Barack Obama in 2012, saying it was “one of the reasons I resent Bernie.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Churches have long played the primary role in mobilizing black support in South Carolina.&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/02/27/us/politics/black-church-elections.html" target="_blank"&gt; So how are candidates faring among congregations&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (The Field)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">65343dd9972949dfa6f7df22cf3df110</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/65343dd9972949dfa6f7df22cf3df110/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 03:03:38 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The SCNS Live Podcast : SCNS Live Season 9 Episode 5 - Special Guest Cole Houston from All-Con</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We got your news, Special guest Patrick from The Lan Cave. And Jedi Cole from All-Con is here to tell us all about All-Con 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit &lt;a href='https://www.all-con.org'&gt;https://www.all-con.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.facebook.com/events/1089169861422169/'&gt; https://www.facebook.com/events/1089169861422169/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://www.extra-life.org/index.cfm?fuseaction=donordrive.participant&amp;participantID=403600&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>admin@untitledscns.com (The SCNS Live Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d8807fd0d55d4c2b853bf668630e0c11</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d8807fd0d55d4c2b853bf668630e0c11/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:26:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Gettysburg Connection Podcast : The Adams County Emergency Services Center Answers 911 Calls and Prepares for Disasters [Episode 23]</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;Keeping Adams County residents safe is a big job, and it takes a big team to do it.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;The work is handled in part by the staff at the Adams County Emergency Services Center, located on Greenamyer Lane East of Gettysburg. The center coordinates police, fire, and EMS services for the entire county.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;In addition to the 911 center the team also monitors hazardous wastes, and is the home of the county&amp;#8217;s disaster preparation team.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/022820_0123_TheAdamsCou1.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bladen&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;In this episode I talk with the Directory of Emergency Services, Warren P. Bladen, who explains how the 911 center works and all of the other missions of the emergency services center provides.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/022820_0123_TheAdamsCou2.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/022820_0123_TheAdamsCou3.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;img src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/022820_0123_TheAdamsCou4.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;img src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/022820_0123_TheAdamsCou5.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mail@gettysburgconnection.org (Gettysburg Connection Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e7602d71d7504e6b85640a1654094dcb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e7602d71d7504e6b85640a1654094dcb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 17:23:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bag Man : BONUS: Introducing Into America</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As a bonus for Bag Man listeners, we’re sharing a special preview of Into America, a new podcast about politics, about policy, and the power that both have in shaping the lives of the American people. It is hosted by Trymaine Lee and features the journalists of NBC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the first episode, Trymaine heads to East New York, a community that experienced more stops than any other part of New York City under Former Mayor Bloomberg’s stop and frisk policy. In order to have a real shot at the Democratic nomination, Bloomberg needs the support of Black voters. Days before announcing his candidacy, Bloomberg apologized for the policing tactic. But will his past decision to champion the use of stop and frisk hurt his chances? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subscribe to Into America now: &lt;a href="https://link.chtbl.com/7BcTGqT3?sid=description" target="_blank"&gt;https://link.chtbl.com/7BcTGqT3?sid=description&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (Bag Man)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">73126ec0518e41788485089ec68532a0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/73126ec0518e41788485089ec68532a0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 15:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MORNINGS with BOB MARRONE on Radio Westchester ™ : Local Westchester Yorktown Heights Top News Stories of the Day - February 27, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://radiowestchester.com/february-27-2020-6-am-10-am/"&gt;February 27, 2020 – 6 AM – 10 AM&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://radiowestchester.com"&gt;Radio Westchester ™ Local NYC Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>production@radiowestchester.com (MORNINGS with BOB MARRONE on Radio Westchester ™)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1b177f46abe547f0a52a91ab0a683af5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1b177f46abe547f0a52a91ab0a683af5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 14:14:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Australia in the World : Ep. 41: Richard Maude on the Indo-Pacific, models of world politics, and Australian foreign policy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week Allan and Darren interview Richard Maude, who needs no introduction to regular observers of Australian foreign policy. Until recently, Richard was Deputy Secretary, Indo-Pacific Group, in the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade. Prior to that, he headed the task force responsible for drafting the 2017 Foreign Policy White Paper. From 2013-2016, Richard was Director-General of the Office of National Assessments, and before that he was senior adviser on foreign policy and national security to Prime Minister Julia Gillard. Richard has now taken on a new position at the Asia Society Policy Institute as the inaugural Executive Director, Policy, and Senior Fellow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Allan commences the discussion by asking Richard how he thinks about the “Indo-Pacific” and to describe Australia’s Indo-Pacific strategy. How has the world changed since Richard started working on the Australian Foreign Policy White Paper back in 2016? Darren describes his own shock at the events of 2016, and asks Richard whether he has ever been personally surprised by any events in international affairs which, in turn, caused him to update his own “model” of the world. The conversation then returns to a familiar theme of recent episodes of the podcast, sovereignty, and the logic of Prime Minister Scott Morrison’s emphasis on the concept in developing his government’s foreign policy. Allan contrasts the challenges to the rules-based order that shaped the 2017 Foreign Policy White Paper—in particular relating to the Law of the Sea—with those that have come since, especially emanating from Australia’s allies. Is there still an order to defend and how does a country like Australia do it? And in doing so, will Australia need to be willing to accept trade-offs, such as deemphasising liberalism and democracy, in order to get cooperation on global challenges like climate change, war, or trade?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The conversation moves to China, with Darren asking Richard the extent to which China’s domestic politics factors into his model of China’s behaviour on the world stage, and what major questions remain in his mind regarding China over the coming years. Closer to home, Darren asks whether Richard accepts the premise of two warring “tribes” in the Canberra policymaking community regarding China, and Richard’s answer speaks more broadly to the issue of how to integrate security and economic perspectives into policymaking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the final part of the podcast, Allan asks the perennial question of why those who believe that foreign policy is a critical element of Australian statecraft have been unable to convince successive governments to invest in it, while Darren wonders how foreign policy successes can be measured. The podcast concludes with Richard describing his new role with the Asia Society Policy Institute, and reflections on how think tanks and academics can most effectively attract the attention and shape the views of ministers and policy advisers in Canberra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, we invite our listeners to email us at this address: &lt;a href='mailto:australia.world.pod@gmail.com'&gt;australia.world.pod@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; We welcome feedback, requests and suggestions. You can also contact Darren on twitter @limdarrenj &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We thank AIIA intern Isabel Hancock for research and audio editing, Rory Stenning for composing our theme music and Angus Blackman for technical support in studio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Relevant links&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Maude’s biography via the Asia Society Policy Institute: &lt;a href='https://asiasociety.org/policy-institute/richard-maude'&gt;https://asiasociety.org/policy-institute/richard-maude&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Maude, “Charting a Course for Australia in a Changing Asia”, Asia Society Policy Institute, 13 February 2020: &lt;a href='https://asiasociety.org/australia/charting-course-australia-changing-asia'&gt;https://asiasociety.org/australia/charting-course-australia-changing-asia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Kehoe, “The division in Canberra over China”, Australian Financial Review, 2 December 2019: &lt;a href='https://www.afr.com/policy/foreign-affairs/china-power-struggle-in-canberra-20191128-p53f27'&gt;https://www.afr.com/policy/foreign-affairs/china-power-struggle-in-canberra-20191128-p53f27&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>australia.world.pod@gmail.com (Australia in the World)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">aa3f5441fbdc40998ee6ac2d78b618a1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/aa3f5441fbdc40998ee6ac2d78b618a1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 11:03:15 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FontCast : Setting the record straight with Robin Gray</title><description>&lt;div&gt;FontCast's second season is off with a bang. Former Tasmanian Premier Robin Gray talks exclusively with Brad Stansfield, and Brad Nowland about the release of his new tell-all book Proud to be Tasmanian. The leader of the state's first Liberal majority government opened up about how his political memoirs would set the record straight after his political opponents had spent decades spreading misinformation about the success of his government.&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>samikin@me.com (FontCast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7548f942d5cf474cb03f17b08308e172</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7548f942d5cf474cb03f17b08308e172/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 11:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Full Frontal Honesty in Real Estate  : How To Buy A Home NOW in Phoenix Arizona 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;How do you win the bidding wars to purchase a home in Phoenix right now?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What are the top 5 ways to save money &amp;amp; WIN the bidding war for the nicest homes?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Krista Bergh stops by to chat for a bit&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts37+b93548@anchor.fm (Full Frontal Honesty in Real Estate )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">29ddfe262a8b4f75be4f4f290a5e27d0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/29ddfe262a8b4f75be4f4f290a5e27d0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 10:31:49 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Latest : The South Carolina Debate</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On the debate stage in Charleston, candidates went after Senator Bernie Sanders, painting his potential nomination as dangerous for the party and questioning his chances of winning against President Trump. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The Latest,” from the team behind “The Daily,” brings you the most important developments on today’s biggest news stories. You can find more information about it&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/column/the-latest" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (The Latest)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a9cf726f0eca478388f160f9e0ebc78b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a9cf726f0eca478388f160f9e0ebc78b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 02:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Pronoia Now Network : Secrets to Happy Healthy Living - Ep 121</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Learn how to beat those PMS blues for both women AND men!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mysticandwizard@gmail.com (Pronoia Now Network)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0a8f33266eca45cabbc69fe209ea6a06</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0a8f33266eca45cabbc69fe209ea6a06/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 17:34:54 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Jay Talk : Episode 16: Luke Mitchell Joins</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, the boys talk with Creighton soccer player Luke Mitchell. Luke talks about his path to Creighton, the team this year, and his haircut business 'Creighton Cuts.' Follow @CreightonCuts on Instagram and DM him if you are interested in a haircut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Later on in the episode (32:13), Tyger talks with Demi Brown, the founder of the Creighton College Diabetes Network. Either email &lt;a href='mailto:creighton@collegediabetesnetwork.org'&gt;creighton@collegediabetesnetwork.org&lt;/a&gt; or follow @creighton.cdn on Instagram for more information. &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">b8e914ea87e74d75a3968b75a0ec9da4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b8e914ea87e74d75a3968b75a0ec9da4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 14:51:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Brendan O'Neill Show : Claire Fox: inside the European Parliament</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Claire Fox, the former Brexit Party MEP and director of the Academy of Ideas, talks to Brendan O’Neill about her time in the European Parliament, the demonisation of Leave voters, and how to make democracy come alive after Brexit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Claire is also the co-convenor of ‘Changing Politics for Good: What Next?’, which will take place at the Cheshire Conference Centre in Stockport on 29 February. Get tickets: &lt;a href='https://www.changepolitics4good.co.uk/'&gt;https://www.changepolitics4good.co.uk/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thebrendanoneillshow@spiked-online.com (The Brendan O'Neill Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ae797ecf7b6b48449f358350331779c3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ae797ecf7b6b48449f358350331779c3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 12:44:12 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Patriots Fight Media : Q Drops 2/24/20 Obama Insurgency and Clinton Foundation Whistleblowing</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Q poses the question: Was the Obama Administration leading an insurgency against the U.S.? And Clinton Foundation whistleblower Nate Cain tells all in a podcast interview.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ford@patriotsfight.com (Patriots Fight Media)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ac41aada45804dbe8d249bbc1428edac</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ac41aada45804dbe8d249bbc1428edac/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>So You Wanna Be President? with Chris Matthews : 6 - Go Negative</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It's the oldest, worst, and most effective part of American politics: go negative. Voters say they hate it, but it works. There's no way to frame your opponent's weakness any better. Chris deconstructs history's hardest hits—and how they were so effective—with Andrea Mitchell, senior Washington correspondent for NBC News and host of "Andrea Mitchell Reports," and Mike Murphy, who's handled media and strategy for Republicans running for President, the US Senate, and governorships.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (So You Wanna Be President? with Chris Matthews)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fedfa350faf4417a9d807d6758dde840</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fedfa350faf4417a9d807d6758dde840/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>BTS with CTV News Vancouver : Solidarity, Disruption and Spin: Covering Canada-Wide Demonstrations</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For &lt;a href="https://bc.ctvnews.ca/timeline-rail-disruptions-by-wet-suwet-en-supporters-across-canada-1.4815263"&gt;weeks&lt;/a&gt;, demonstrations in support of hereditary chiefs of the Wet'suwet'en First Nation in northern British Columbia have resulted in in unprecedented rallies, blockaded railroads and intentionally disrupted commuter routes for drivers and transit users alike -- not to mention attempts to stall legislators in the capitol and even taking their placards to the premier's own home. The issue of whether or not to allow the Coastal GasLink natural gas pipeline has &lt;a href="https://bc.ctvnews.ca/here-s-how-b-c-approached-land-rights-after-major-court-ruling-1.4818299"&gt;deeply fractured&lt;/a&gt; the Wet'suwet'en community and Canadians at large have been divided on whether protests are lawful and acceptable expressions of support for First Nations or illegal acts of disruption that should result in arrest. As the days go on, the impacts are increasingly felt by people &lt;a href="'Barricades%20must%20now%20come%20down,'%20PM%20Trudeau%20says%20of%20rail%20blockades"&gt;across the country&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hard at work to report on the daily goings-on and the larger picture of what's at play are journalists scrambling to get to the &lt;a href="https://bc.ctvnews.ca/new-blockade-started-on-train-tracks-in-east-vancouver-1.4824103"&gt;latest barricade&lt;/a&gt;, protest and sit-in -- despite increasing hostility from the demonstrators themselves. It's a challenging but important task, so reporters and videographers are getting creative in order to cover all aspects of the developments, despite significant logistical and geographic hurdles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;BTS with CTV Vancouver&lt;/em&gt; host &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/pennydaflos"&gt;Penny Daflos&lt;/a&gt; discusses the complexities of reporting on this issue with reporter &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/allisonm_hurst"&gt;Allison Hurst&lt;/a&gt; and their colleague, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MelanieNagyCTV"&gt;Melanie Nagy&lt;/a&gt;, Vancouver bureau chief for CTV National News.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>iheartradiopodcasts@bellmedia.ca (BTS with CTV News Vancouver)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a5dbce1e18e2426b8869b215222a2b2f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a5dbce1e18e2426b8869b215222a2b2f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 16:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Capitol J : Special Edition: Medill in Germany</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Joe Snell and Alec Bose report on their trip to U.S. Army Headquarters Europe in Wiesbaden, Germany. &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">1ee68bab849d43c2b0c4c2fb5354920d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1ee68bab849d43c2b0c4c2fb5354920d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 06:12:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Under-Told: Verbatim : Zola Nene’s Post-Apartheid Kitchen</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In 1994, Nelson Mandela’s election marked the end of apartheid and the beginning of democracy in South Africa. But the scars of racial segregation haven’t healed yet. Infrastructure designed for 5 million white South Africans has failed to support the majority black population of over 56 million power outages and water shortages are a part of daily life. Zola Nene was 10 years old when apartheid ended. Today her cookbooks and television appearances have made her a famous and beloved celebrity chef. Our director Fred de Sam Lazaro, talked to Zola in a Cape Town coffee shop about cooking in a post apartheid kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>undertold@stthomas.edu (Under-Told: Verbatim)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">508850d7fb9a49a6b706bc119a3d3058</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/508850d7fb9a49a6b706bc119a3d3058/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 14:40:27 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The M-U Experience : Valentine's Day Episode</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today on The M-U Experience, our team is reading the break up letters they have written to things they don't like. We hope you enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>carlie.mobley@moulton-udell.org (The M-U Experience)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8707123143e24e218431d8d73d3034ce</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8707123143e24e218431d8d73d3034ce/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Uncommon Knowledge : The World According to Thiel</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Recorded on January 17, 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peter Thiel, the cofounder of PayPal and Palantir; early investor in Facebook, LinkedIn, and SpaceX; and the founder of the Thiel Fellowship, which encourages young people to drop out of college to start their own businesses, is interviewed live on stage in front of the members of the Mont Pelerin Society. This wide-ranging conversation covers globalization, the continuing and ever-growing threat from China and what the United States can and can’t do it about, what the rise of Bernie Sanders means for the future of US capitalism, the “derangement” (Thiel’s phrase) of Silicon Valley in the last decade, the scourge of political correctness on campuses and in society at large, and why Thiel thinks we should rethink the doctrine of American exceptionalism.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>institutionhoover@gmail.com (Uncommon Knowledge)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">53c50814c0c9463084b8e380ea61cbe6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/53c50814c0c9463084b8e380ea61cbe6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 08:42:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Choice : The Argument: Why Endorse Elizabeth Warren and Amy Klobuchar?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Host Katie Kingsbury visits Opinion's other podcast, "The Argument," to defend the editorial board's two endorsements for Senators Elizabeth Warren and Amy Klobuchar against her disagreeing colleagues Ross Douthat, Michelle Goldberg and David Leonhardt. They talk about the current political moment, each of the Democratic contenders, and the path to the nomination. For background reading on this episode, click here or search for &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/23/opinion/the-argument-endorsement-klobuchar-warren.html" target="_blank"&gt;nytimes.com/theargument&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>opinionpodcasts@nytimes.com (The Choice)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">79c3c9035c6a45e7b16b949c5893a9fa</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/79c3c9035c6a45e7b16b949c5893a9fa/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sean Klitzner Show : The #YangGang</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Tonight gets political. We talk about the top democrats running for office. I can't promise anything we say is serious.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>SeanKlitzner@gmail.com (The Sean Klitzner Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4c849be0f5524fbc8b96efe74a78d32e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4c849be0f5524fbc8b96efe74a78d32e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 20:16:09 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>