<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My News feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My news episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My News feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 03:33:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>The 11th Hour with Brian Williams : Day 1,114: President Payback fires Ukraine witnesses Vindman and Sondland</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Trump has fired two key officials who provided critical testimony during the House inquiry into the president's conduct with Ukraine. Peter Baker joins to discuss. We discuss that, plus the latest news from the Democratic field with Peter Baker, Ashley Parker, Carol Leonnig, Rick Wilson, Steve Kornacki, Donna Edwards, Jon Ralston, and Jonathan Allen.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (The 11th Hour with Brian Williams)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">30a9e58d4f7443c19b7b5eaccd5e5a50</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/30a9e58d4f7443c19b7b5eaccd5e5a50/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 18:17:12 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Beat with Ari Melber : Sanders and Buttigieg tied for lead in latest NBC News/Marist poll</title><description>&lt;p&gt;MSNBC's Ari Melber hosts "The Beat" live in New Hampshire, days before the pivotal Primary. A new NBC / Marist poll shows Bernie Sanders and Pete Buttigieg surging with Elizabeth Warren in third and Joe Biden flagging. The new poll comes as Biden left New Hampshire for a reported "last ditch" meeting in Delaware.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ari@msnbc.com (The Beat with Ari Melber)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4a8cbf2365aa40a6815cf4cf1910facd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4a8cbf2365aa40a6815cf4cf1910facd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 17:49:21 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Gist : Moshe Kasher Surfs the Crowd</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On the Gist, Central Casting strikes again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the interview, comedian Moshe Kasher is here to talk about his new comedy album &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/album/4ep9AeWnt2K0qJL1d3JvAE?si=eTccanOtTOSuznN4p9_O9A"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Crowdsurfing&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. He and Mike discuss the difference between crowd work and prepared material, and the history of Moshe’s family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the spiel, Nancy ripping his speech. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slate Plus members get bonus segments and ad-free podcast feeds. &lt;a href="https://my.slate.com/plus?utm_medium=link&amp;amp;utm_campaign=plus_pod&amp;amp;utm_content=The_Gist&amp;amp;utm_source=show_notes"&gt;Sign up&lt;/a&gt; now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thegist@slate.com (The Gist)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">49dd1ebc379f4cf5932ec6500fd2c968</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/49dd1ebc379f4cf5932ec6500fd2c968/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 17:49:15 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hardball with Chris Matthews : Gordon Sondland recalled as EU Ambassador</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Gordon Sondland, ambassador to the European Union, who was another prominent witness in the impeachment inquiry has also been recalled from his post by the president. In a statement Sondland writes "I was advised today that the president intends to recall me effective immediately as the Untied States Ambassador to the European Union."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (Hardball with Chris Matthews)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ce1c921bc5eb433a90970317692d660b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ce1c921bc5eb433a90970317692d660b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 17:43:43 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The News &amp; Why It Matters : Ep 465 | Iowa: STILL No Winner, but Joe Biden Is Definitely the Loser | Guest: Josh Hammer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As we head into New Hampshire, the Associated Press is unable to declare a winner of the Iowa caucuses, and DNC Chair Tom Perez is asking for a recount since the margin is too close! But the biggest story from Iowa is the BIGGEST loser, aka former Vice President Joe Biden. Will Joe drop out after New Hampshire? And BIG news from the White House today says that Qassim al-Rimi, the leader of al Qaeda in the Arabian Peninsula, was killed in an airstrike in Yemen. As we head into election 2020, President Trump's approval rating is higher than President Obama's first term. Re-election, anyone?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tcardon@glennbeck.com (The News &amp; Why It Matters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">372ab9c9cf8143659c805dd4aac428ca</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/372ab9c9cf8143659c805dd4aac428ca/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 17:38:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The KrisAnne Hall Show : Episode 1039 Marxism, Race &amp; Slavery</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://youtu.be/w0zLTSrAnKo"&gt;Watch the KrisAnne Hall Show on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JC breaks down the essential elements of the enemies design to divide &amp;amp; distract Americans from the real threat to our way of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ensure this Excellent Constitution Training Continues! Partner with The KrisAnne Hall Daily Journal and be a part of the force that will restore Americans with their Constitutional Principles! To JOIN with us just simple text- impact2020 to 33777&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Subscribe to the KrisAnne Hall YouTube Channel &lt;a href="http://youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=krisannehall1"&gt;http://youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=krisannehall1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Books, DVDs and On Demand Seminars by KrisAnne Hall at &lt;a href="https://krisannehall.com/"&gt;https://KrisAnneHall.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Support this podcast: &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/the-krisanne-hall-show/support" rel="payment"&gt;https://anchor.fm/the-krisanne-hall-show/support&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts44+f0b3c04@anchor.fm (The KrisAnne Hall Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">78e8b05282d347989d28ed931eafd5ea</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/78e8b05282d347989d28ed931eafd5ea/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 17:29:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FOX News Radio Newscast : 8PM EDT 02/07/2020 Newscast</title><description>Latest FOX News hourly newscast.&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=w6Gmb3YO3UU:VO--DS7HkZE:yIl2AUoC8zA"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=yIl2AUoC8zA" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=w6Gmb3YO3UU:VO--DS7HkZE:qj6IDK7rITs"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=qj6IDK7rITs" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=w6Gmb3YO3UU:VO--DS7HkZE:O3QAOHgViy4"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=O3QAOHgViy4" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=w6Gmb3YO3UU:VO--DS7HkZE:I9og5sOYxJI"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=I9og5sOYxJI" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/FoxNewsRadio/~4/w6Gmb3YO3UU" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>podcast@foxnewsradio.com (FOX News Radio Newscast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cd4a7c545e314f8c876f621ee9011a41</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cd4a7c545e314f8c876f621ee9011a41/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 17:07:50 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>NPR News Now : NPR News: 02-07-2020 8PM ET</title><description>NPR News: 02-07-2020 8PM ET</description><author>PodCasts@npr.org (NPR News Now)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">994c0ae8e79b4bfc9f5ddbc27ba144c0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/994c0ae8e79b4bfc9f5ddbc27ba144c0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Left, Right &amp; Center : Iowa</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It was a full week. On Monday, the Iowa caucuses were a bit of a meltdown for Democrats, but did the mess sort of, maybe help some of the candidates? Kind of. What happened to Joe Biden? And what happens when you’re a reporter covering a caucus and you see things obviously going wrong? **Tim Carney **and &lt;strong&gt;Olivia Nuzzi&lt;/strong&gt; talk about what they witnessed in Iowa and how the campaigns are taking it as they head to New Hampshire. Election law expert &lt;strong&gt;Rick Hasen&lt;/strong&gt; lays out the damage done in Iowa and what he’s concerned about as the primary season continues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;President Trump gave his state of the union address on Tuesday and it was a three-in-one kind of speech with all the reality show trimmings we’ve come to expect. The panel discusses that and analyzes the Democrats’ messaging about the economy in Michigan Governor Gretchen Whitmer’s response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And on Wednesday, the Senate acquitted President Trump in the impeachment inquiry. Mitt Romney was the only Republican — this time and in history — who voted to convict and remove the president on one of the articles.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@kcrw.org (Left, Right &amp; Center)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f81e919af6d441e5b42fa18f3423b1c7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f81e919af6d441e5b42fa18f3423b1c7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 16:03:45 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Deadline: White House : “Rise like a phoenix from the ashes”</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Nicolle Wallace looks ahead to next week’s New Hampshire primary as a new poll shows Pete Buttigieg surging. Plus, a Trump political appointee comes out in support of a 2020 Democratic candidate, the president looks to seek revenge against national security officials who testified in the impeachment investigation, and Sanders attacks Bloomberg over his wealth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joined by: Amy Walter of the Cook Political Report, politics editor for The Root Jason Johnson, Associated Press White House reporter Jonathan Lemire, president of the National Action Network Reverend Al Sharpton, The Bulwark editor-at-large Charlie Sykes, and senior Washington correspondent for Politico Anna Palmer&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (Deadline: White House)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">18a371613a034928a603cec736c5f743</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/18a371613a034928a603cec736c5f743/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 15:20:39 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WSJ What’s News : Hiring Off To Strong Start in 2020</title><description>P.M. Edition for February 7th: Employers added 225,000 jobs to the U.S. economy in January. Eric Morath has more on the numbers. Plus, Byron Tau on a WSJ exclusive: how federal immigration agencies are using cell phone location data. Annmarie Fertoli hosts.&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@dowjones.com (WSJ What’s News)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">64a0f695480842eb8abb9d63fe30a03f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/64a0f695480842eb8abb9d63fe30a03f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 14:21:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Skimm This : In the Spotlight: Dem Debate Preview, Weinstein Trial, Oscars</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s Friday night, and some 2020 democratic candidates will be spending theirs in...New Hampshire for the eighth democratic debate. We’ll tell you why some of the candidates are hoping to put this ‘No Good, Very Bad’ week behind them. Meanwhile, football season is already making a comeback with a brand new league called the XFL. And this one’s taking your bets (legally). Also on today’s show: Harvey Weinstein’s defense team calls its first witnesses, and a historic first to keep an ear out for at the Oscars on Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To receive gambling addiction help 24/7/365, call or text the National Problem Gambling Helpline at 1-800-522-4700.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>skimmthis@theskimm.com (Skimm This)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bb5d0b1bfa724f4d983b39de9d30a4e8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bb5d0b1bfa724f4d983b39de9d30a4e8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 13:44:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Lawfare Podcast : The Lawfare Podcast Special Edition: An "Election Meltdown" in Iowa</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The 2020 election cycle opened up with a dramatic failure, as the Iowa caucus was marred by a delayed announcement of the caucus results and an abundance of misinformation about its cause. It was a painful demonstration of the importance of election security and election infrastructure. We put together a special edition podcast to discuss what went wrong in Iowa and the factors that have increased mistrust in American elections. Benjamin Wittes interviewed Richard Hasen, an election-law expert and the author of “Election Meltdown: Dirty Tricks, Distrust, and the Threat to American Democracy.” The two talked about Hasen’s new book, about the flaws that can plague elections and about how to think about electoral legitimacy. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>benjamin.wittes@lawfareblog.com (The Lawfare Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">99c023308f584c84b9f06147766e0866</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/99c023308f584c84b9f06147766e0866/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 13:35:40 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Post Reports : ‘Unshackled and unleashed’: Trump, post-acquittal</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Today on Post Reports, Philip Rucker describes what the presidency could look like post-impeachment. And ahead of Sunday’s Academy Awards, Sarah Hashemi considers whether gendered categories should be eliminated from award shows.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Read more:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Historians and legal experts say President Trump’s acquittal could have profound ramifications for &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/a-massive-historical-story-trumps-impending-acquittal-could-have-profound-ramifications-for-future-presidents/2020/02/01/e314c6d2-4484-11ea-aa6a-083d01b3ed18_story.html"&gt;what future presidents consider permissible conduct&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The Oscars have a gender problem. &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/arts-entertainment/2020/02/05/non-binary-actors-are-asking-awards-like-oscars-emmys-change-heres-one-way-fix-them/"&gt;Non-binary actors have some solutions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Subscribe to The Washington Post: &lt;a href="https://postreports.com/offer"&gt;https://postreports.com/offer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>jessica.stahl@washpost.com (Post Reports)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4ccff09ce19b4eb4b9458de2130a8de4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4ccff09ce19b4eb4b9458de2130a8de4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 13:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WSJ Opinion: Potomac Watch : Sanders and Buttigieg Take the Democratic Lead</title><description>Sanders and Buttigieg take the Democratic lead.&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@dowjones.com (WSJ Opinion: Potomac Watch)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ad8a85ae5f8c4cf99db09be9042148ca</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ad8a85ae5f8c4cf99db09be9042148ca/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 13:21:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ricochet Podcast : 482. The Greatest Week</title><description>A debacle in Iowa, a triumphant State of The Union speech, a rip-off, a socialist, a small town mayor with a big win &amp;#8212; you name it, we discuss it on this week&amp;#8217;s edition of The Big Show, aka The Ricochet Podcast. To help us sort through it all, we&amp;#8217;ve got the great Deb Saunders, [&amp;#8230;]</description><author>support@ricochet.com (Ricochet Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">558fe21ddc4b42e39b9fe04a819d126e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/558fe21ddc4b42e39b9fe04a819d126e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 13:12:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Yorker Radio Hour : The Black Vote in 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The last time a Democrat won the White House, he had enormous support from black voters; lower support from black voters was one of many reasons Hillary Clinton lost in 2016. Marcus Ferrell, a political organizer from Atlanta, tells Radio Hour about the importance of turning out “unlikely voters” in order to win an election, which, for him, means black men. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/jelani-cobb"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jelani Cobb&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;New Yorker&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;staff writer and historian, points out that the four Democratic front-runners, all of whom are white, may struggle to get the turnout they need. Cobb tells David Remnick that Joe Biden’s strong lead may begin to fall after his weak showing among largely white voters in Iowa; Pete Buttigieg has very low support among South Carolina voters, and even faces opposition from black constituents in his home town, South Bend. But Bernie Sanders, Cobb says, seems to have made inroads with at least younger black voters since 2016. Plus, a&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;New Yorker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;staffer picks three favorites.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (The New Yorker Radio Hour)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0fcd6928bfa848a39576aae3492ccd3e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0fcd6928bfa848a39576aae3492ccd3e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 13:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Daily Detroit : Bus ridership up, "slumlords" are called out in Detroit suit plus Fletcher on Andre Drummond trade</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On today's show:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;SMART bus ridership is up, led by the growth of their FAST Service on Woodward, Michigan and Gratiot. Go figure, you do a frequent service that shows up on time and people use it?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The city of Detroit is suing three major landlords who they call slumlords, wanting the court to call their businesses public nuisances.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And Fletcher Sharpe joins us to talk about the Andre Drummond trade from the Pistons to the Cavaliers, what's next for the team, and has some updates on Detroit City FC. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If this is the first time meeting our show, we’re on Apple Podcasts: &lt;a href= "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/daily-detroit/id1220563942"&gt;https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/daily-detroit/id1220563942&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Spotify: &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/show/1Yhv8nSylVWxlZilRhi4X9"&gt;https://open.spotify.com/show/1Yhv8nSylVWxlZilRhi4X9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And although the show will always be free, our members help make it available for everyone else. Become a member on Patreon: &lt;a href= "http://www.patreon.com/dailydetroit"&gt;http://www.patreon.com/dailydetroit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>dailydetroit@gmail.com (Daily Detroit)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9e2607751d3b43d988ae6070e6d860ca</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9e2607751d3b43d988ae6070e6d860ca/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 12:58:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Buck Sexton Show : Impeachment Was All Bull****</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Season 4, Episode 27.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jobs numbers are up big, Pelosi vs. Trump continues on and Cocaine Mitch is a hero for the GOP. Tiana Lowe joins Buck in studio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>teambuck@iheartmedia.com (The Buck Sexton Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">84e9e4bb5e8a4276be3838e41eaa4b23</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/84e9e4bb5e8a4276be3838e41eaa4b23/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 12:28:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Erick Erickson Show : #EERS S9 Ep23: Off to the Races</title><description>Today on the show the President takes a victory lap, Democrats and the media faint, the Democrat debate tonight will get nastier, anti-vaxxers kill another child, things may be getting worse with China and the coronavirus and socialism is an evil disease.</description><author>erick@theresurgent.com (The Erick Erickson Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e0bf1a30f43f4dff8217d5e08f251c06</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e0bf1a30f43f4dff8217d5e08f251c06/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 12:18:52 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Tim Pool Daily Show : Democratic Party Is COLLAPSING, Chaos Erupts As Voters Quit, Turnout TANKS, And DNC CHEATS Bernie</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Democratic Party Is COLLAPSING, Chaos Erupts As Voters Quit, Turnout TANKS, And DNC CHEATS Bernie. James Carville appeared on MSNBC and in a now viral clip claims the Democrats are out of their minds, candidates are campaigning on fringe issues, and Trump's approval is higher than its ever been.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Panic erupted within the party due to low voter turnout and the only response Bernie Sanders gave as to why he should be chosen as the nominee is that he can drive voter turnout.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If that were true why did so few come to caucus for Bernie in Iowa?&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders did win the popular vote count but total turnout was still low. If Bernie could attract new voters where were they?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the issue isn't just the failures of the Democrats but also that they are being accused by progressives and the far left of cheating Bernie to boost Buttigieg.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several Democratic precinct captains are complaining that the results posted by the IDP/DNC are just wrong. yet even with this Bernie won't call for a recount.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="http://timcast.com/donate"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (http://timcast.com/donate)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tim@timcast.com (Tim Pool Daily Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b666f63b1f3142099324becfa4b8ef73</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b666f63b1f3142099324becfa4b8ef73/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Savage Nation Podcast : What Does Blue and Red America See Eye-to-Eye On?  Plus Climate Fraud</title><description>&lt;p&gt;James Carville says the Democrats have lost their minds; What can red and blue Americans agree on? Pope Francis is calling for "Global Wealth Distribution," Savage has an idea on how he can fund his program himself; PBS special on climate change has things backwards to push an agenda; is America ready for a gay president?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marc Morano, founder of climatedepot.com, joins to debunk Climate Change myths.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wwopodcasts@westwoodone.com (The Savage Nation Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4154de8d8ec34a00be300ee66430672d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4154de8d8ec34a00be300ee66430672d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 11:59:52 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Glenn Beck Program : Obama’s Secret War Exposed | Guests: Bill O’Reilly &amp; Nick Di Paolo | 2/7/20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;What happened to our missing $1.8 billion in Ukraine? Last night’s special, “Ukraine: The Final Piece (The Billion-Dollar Question),” follows the money to Ukraine’s “Tony Soprano,” who financed its war with Russia. Did Obama use taxpayer money to fund a proxy war? Former Secretary of State John Kerry seems to think so. Comedian Nick Di Paolo gives a politically incorrect take on the State of the Union, coronavirus, and how Trump is cleaning house. And it’s a Bill O’Reilly Friday to end a packed week! Bill updates his 2020 predictions after the Iowa caucus disaster, recaps Trump’s Oprah-style SOTU, and asks what’s next for … Romney. And head researcher Jason Buttrill outlines the Ukraine timeline you haven’t seen anywhere else.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ccardon@blazemedia.com (The Glenn Beck Program)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4eca254be1ea40abb69f1b3c7836df59</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4eca254be1ea40abb69f1b3c7836df59/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 10:11:43 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Briefing : The Evening Briefing: Friday February 7</title><description>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coronavirus victim: British man diagnosed on quarantined cruise ship - *free to read* http://bit.ly/31B9sPQ |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coronavirus liveblog: Outpouring of grief in China as doctor who tried to warn about the virus dies - *free to read* http://bit.ly/2H9NsC1&amp;nbsp;|&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Macron makes move: France demands UK aligns with EU rules forever in return for Brexit trade deal&amp;nbsp;http://bit.ly/31EhKGO |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Phillip Schofield: TV presenter reveals he is gay&amp;nbsp;http://bit.ly/37bS98Z |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oasis v Beatles: Allegations relatives of Liam and Ringo involved in 'fight in Tesco' - *free to read* http://bit.ly/2OyL7Fa |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Laura Bates: Natalie Wood rumours won't die with Kirk Douglas http://bit.ly/39aQkL0 |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read all these articles with a digital Telegraph subscription - from £2 per week. Sign up here: http://bit.ly/2WRuvh9. If you're enjoying my audio briefings, please consider encouraging others to sign up for FREE here: http://bit.ly/2XxhVAI.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@telegraph.co.uk (The Briefing)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d86f50425f01493f8891504d38cb3e81</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d86f50425f01493f8891504d38cb3e81/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 09:52:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dan Bongino Show : Trump’s Secret Weapon (Ep 1176)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, I address President Trump&amp;rsquo;s secret weapon in the 2020 re-election campaign. I also address the explosive connections between the Spygate plotters, the deep-state, and the Clintons. Finally, I discuss the troubling &amp;ldquo;New Way Forward&amp;rdquo; legislation and the blow-out new jobs numbers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;News Picks:&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/economy-beats-expectations-with-225-000-jobs-in-january-unemployment-3-6"&gt;More blowout jobs numbers&lt;/a&gt; in the flourishing Trump economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bongino.com/tired-of-losing-after-acquittal-liberals-complain-about-unfair-senate/"&gt;Loser liberals are tired of losing&lt;/a&gt; and are now complaint about the &amp;ldquo;unfair&amp;rdquo; Senate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://justthenews.com/key-witness-told-team-mueller-russia-collusion-evidence-found.html"&gt;An explosive new article&lt;/a&gt; by John Solomon indicating that the infamous Paul Manafort &amp;ldquo;Black Ledger&amp;rdquo; was a fraud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/national-security/russian-government-initiative-gave-millions-to-clinton-foundation/"&gt;This 2016 article&lt;/a&gt; describes the troubling connections between the Clintons and a suspected Russian espionage effort.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/coup-has-started-whistleblowers-attorney-said-in-2017-posts-calling-for-impeachment"&gt;This 2019 article&lt;/a&gt; addresses the strange behavior of the fake whistleblower&amp;rsquo;s attorney.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;President Trump&amp;rsquo;s re-election chances &lt;a href="https://bongino.com/president-trumps-re-election-odds-hit-record-high-day-after-acquittal/"&gt;hit a record high&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/wage-growth-slowed-for-a-good-reason"&gt;An interesting article&lt;/a&gt; about wage growth, productivity, and the Trump economy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Copyright Dan Bongino All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@bongino.com (The Dan Bongino Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">471446540d57421b9825b0e416054b9f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/471446540d57421b9825b0e416054b9f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 09:33:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Matt Walsh Show : Ep. 422 - The Barbaric Extremism Of The Democratic Party</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Pete Buttigieg was given the opportunity to come out against killing fully developed infants moments before birth, but declined. He is a coward and an extremist. Just like the rest of the Democratic field. Also, AOC says it's impossible to "pull yourself up by the bootstraps." Interesting point coming from a bartender-turned-congresswoman. And David Hogg continues to be brainwashed by his college education. It's a fascinating process to watch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out The Cold War: What We Saw, a new podcast written and presented by Bill Whittle at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar&lt;/a&gt;. In Part 1 we peel back the layers of mystery cloaking the Terror state run by the Kremlin, and watch as America takes its first small steps onto the stage of world leadership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like The Matt Walsh Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: WALSH and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/Walsh"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/Walsh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mattwalshshow@dailywire.com (The Matt Walsh Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3ad0fadbf1614408bf9be128f8ba65fc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3ad0fadbf1614408bf9be128f8ba65fc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 09:30:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>KRDO Newsradio 105.5 FM • 1240 AM • 92.5 FM : The KRDO Weekly Businesscast with Ted Robertson - February 7, 2020</title><description>&lt;p style="text-align:justify;"&gt;A new climbing gym opening on the Springs' NE side; bad weather is wreaking a bit of havoc for business; stocks are up; Pizza Hut is getting a fixxer-upper, and Boeing is finding new software issues with the grounded 737.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Listen Now!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ted.robertson@krdo.com (KRDO Newsradio 105.5 FM • 1240 AM • 92.5 FM)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8f503fbb5c964cb6a1cff9c1d4bfdca2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8f503fbb5c964cb6a1cff9c1d4bfdca2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 09:27:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ben Shapiro Show : Ep. 949 - Mr. Trump’s Wild Ride</title><description>Trump celebrates his own personal Festivus with the ceremonial airing of grievances after his acquittal, Bernie gains momentum as Biden panics, and China shows that communism isn’t great at problem-solving.

If you like The Ben Shapiro Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: SHAPIRO and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at https://www.dailywire.com/Shapiro</description><author>benshapiroshow@dailywire.com (The Ben Shapiro Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">985cd6afdfcb479798a67ba60200d0a4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/985cd6afdfcb479798a67ba60200d0a4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 09:22:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Checks and Balance : Checks and Balance: Left Bern</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Might America choose a socialist president? Ahead in the polls for the &lt;a href="https://www.economist.com/united-states/2020/02/06/waiting-for-bernie-in-new-hampshire" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;New Hampshire primary&lt;/a&gt;, Bernie Sanders’ grip on the left of the &lt;a href="https://www.economist.com/leaders/2020/02/06/the-democratic-primaries-will-be-a-contest-between-radicals-and-repairers" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Democratic Party&lt;/a&gt; is strengthening. The Senator from Vermont is the American left’s best chance in decades to defy political gravity. John Prideaux, The Economist’s US editor, looks at the history of socialism in America and James Astill, Lexington columnist, assesses Senator Sanders’ chances. Checks and Balance regulars Charlotte Howard and Jon Fasman also consider how Sanders might fare against President Trump and the similarities between the two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.economist.com/pod2020" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.economist.com/pod2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>radio@economist.com (Checks and Balance)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b68e87b0119045a1860c5a6085d643c9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b68e87b0119045a1860c5a6085d643c9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 09:19:46 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>On the Media : Picture-Perfect Democracy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The sloppy roll-out of Iowa results prompted disinformation and confusion over the mechanics of the caucus system. This week, On the Media looks at the origins of the nomination process to explain how we got here. Plus, local reporters in New Hampshire examine the power struggle at the heart of the upcoming contest. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Galen Druke [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/galendruke"&gt;@galendruke&lt;/a&gt;] on the history of America's unique primary system. &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/otm/segments/primer-primaries-on-the-media"&gt;Listen.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Reporters Jack Rodolico [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/JackRodolico" target="_blank"&gt;@JackRodolico&lt;/a&gt;], Lauren Chooljian [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/laurenchooljian"&gt;@laurenchooljian&lt;/a&gt;], and Casey McDermott [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/caseymcdermott"&gt;@caseymcdermott&lt;/a&gt;] on Dixville Notch's mythical status. &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/otm/segments/dixville-notch"&gt;Listen.&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Lauren Chooljian [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/laurenchooljian"&gt;@laurenchooljian&lt;/a&gt;] examines how New Hampshire's local press benefits from being a first-in-the-nation primary. &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/otm/segments/privilege-being-first-on-the-media"&gt;Listen.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Music from this week's show: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sacred Oracle by John Zorn&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Young at Heart by Brad Mehldau&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Camping Store by Clive Carroll and John Renbourn&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Milestones by Bill Evan Trio&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (On the Media)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5d8bc6ce2b414d649c0c1d3b4429db3d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5d8bc6ce2b414d649c0c1d3b4429db3d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bannon's War Room : Ep 154: BONUS War Room – The Road to New Hampshire</title><description>Jason Miller, Raheem Kassam, Steve Bannon, and Greg Manz discuss the breaking jobs numbers, the latest with the Democratic Party candidates and the Iowa debacle, the new reports about Hunter Biden and allegations of corruption, and how New Hampshire might stack up.</description><author>admin@citizensoftheamericanrepublic.org (Bannon's War Room)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">62fe70a6bc32400da9adf5fec078d72f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/62fe70a6bc32400da9adf5fec078d72f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 08:47:01 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill O’Reilly’s No Spin News and Analysis : The O'Reilly Update, February 7, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@www.billoreilly.com (Bill O’Reilly’s No Spin News and Analysis)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c62d604827804c5e8552b05a78bb24ef</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c62d604827804c5e8552b05a78bb24ef/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 08:45:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>CBS This Morning - News on the Go : 2/7:  More Americans test positive for coronavirus. Powerful and deadly winter storm is taking aim at the Northeast, after leaving path of destruction across the South.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;More Americans test positive for coronavirus on a huge cruise ship docked in Japan. The total number of cases on board triples in one day. Americans in quarantine there tell us what it's like. A deadly winter punch targets the Northeast after lashing the Southeast with strong winds and heavy rain. We have the weekend forecast. Democrats and Republicans in Washington are moving on after a long and bitter impeachment fight, but President Trump is not ready to let it go. Iowa Democrats say they have finally reported all the results from Monday’s caucus but CBS News cannot call a winner. Attorneys for disgraced movie mogul Harvey Weinstein will call witnesses today, to try to discredit evidence he engaged in a pattern of criminal sexual behavior. Weinstein is on trial for allegedly raping one woman and assaulting another. He's always maintained what he did was consensual.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>CBSNetworkRadioNewsWeb@cbsnews.com (CBS This Morning - News on the Go)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">55f5371699a74c8a96064cb3703ec223</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/55f5371699a74c8a96064cb3703ec223/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 08:24:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>TJ Trout : Roundhouse outlook, Free For All</title><description>TJ chats with Tom Garrity from the roundhouse on issues facing NM.  Plus State Sen. Mark Moores checks in to chat about his bill to help student athletes and their mental health and a free for all with the callers on News Radio KKOB.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">9c5e3361a4cb415ead33904e30c85eaa</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9c5e3361a4cb415ead33904e30c85eaa/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 08:02:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Marketplace Morning Report : There is power in an actors union</title><description>&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#8217;s the link between good weather and job creation? A bipartisan coalition of senators pushes legislation to help compete with Chinese tech giant Huawei. Plus, new SAG-AFTRA Foundation President Courtney B. Vance talks about diversity and his work helping struggling and out-of-work actors.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>MorningReportComments@marketplace.org (Marketplace Morning Report)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d8b16e9060fa4e6d997072f98d7b888f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d8b16e9060fa4e6d997072f98d7b888f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 08:00:46 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Honey Badger Radio : Benevolent sexism: Feminism as the arbiter of compassion | HBR Talk 119</title><description>Join HBR Talk as we discuss the concept of “benevolent sexism,” and the not so benevolent ways feminists use it to sweep men’s issues under the rug.&lt;br /&gt;Wait, is it sexist to associate feminists with something that sounds like housework?</description><author>feeds@spreaker.com (Honey Badger Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e636c907d4f24fc49fdff769982ed7d2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e636c907d4f24fc49fdff769982ed7d2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 07:48:41 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Rome Daily Sentinel - Cinema Podcast : February 7, 2020 - &amp;quot;Oscar Predictions&amp;quot;</title><description>Sean Ian Mills takes a stab at "The Rhythm Section" and follows up with a stab at Oscar predictions! Featuring special guest Nicole Hawley from the Daily Sentinel!</description><author>podcasts@rnymedia.com (Rome Daily Sentinel - Cinema Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f3ab4589ac5c4d2c8f52d23bf51e7682</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f3ab4589ac5c4d2c8f52d23bf51e7682/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 05:42:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Morning Joe : Morning Joe 2/7/20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Morning Joe compares and contrasts Bill Clinton's public response to impeachment to the public remarks President Trump gave on Thursday. And, Joe Scarborough discusses President Trump's remarks at Thursday's National Prayer Breakfast and why he says Trump mocked the words of Jesus Christ and got away with it.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (Morning Joe)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">019e7926a5ed40f285a2aabba4a8dc36</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/019e7926a5ed40f285a2aabba4a8dc36/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 05:07:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Election 2020: Updates from The Washington Post : Joe Biden is nowhere to be found in New Hampshire</title><description>From "The Daily 202" podcast: Biden spent yesterday huddling with his top advisers at his home in Wilmington, Del., seeking a reset and perhaps a last-ditch effort to save his candidacy, beginning with a debate tonight.</description><author>jessica.stahl@washpost.com (Election 2020: Updates from The Washington Post)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e9c38425ce67407c8280ff46f91114f7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e9c38425ce67407c8280ff46f91114f7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 04:55:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Daily 202's Big Idea : A Chinese hero dies after trying to sound the alarm about the coronavirus</title><description>A Chinese doctor who was silenced by police for trying to share news about the new coronavirus long before Chinese health authorities disclosed its full threat died after coming down with the illness.</description><author>jessica.stahl@washpost.com (The Daily 202's Big Idea)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ea819dcf6b0b481590378337901729fe</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ea819dcf6b0b481590378337901729fe/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 04:42:37 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>CNN News Briefing : Morning news briefing from CNN</title><description>https://www.cnn.com/videos/us/2020/02/07/daily-news-briefing-02072020-1.cnn &lt;a href="http://knit.audio/podcast-advertising"&gt;via Knit&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcast@turner.com (CNN News Briefing)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2d7522d3ca5a40dea1055bbc20629265</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2d7522d3ca5a40dea1055bbc20629265/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 04:10:56 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>RTÉ - Today with Sean O'Rourke : Election 2020 : Campaign Wrap</title><description>Barry Lenihan, RTE, Drivetime, Niamh Lyons, Today With Sean O'Rourke, Michael Gallagher, Professor of Comparative Government, Trinity College, Dublin</description><author>radio.player@rte.ie (RTÉ - Today with Sean O'Rourke)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1d2eb412e9a14b229017a243f9cfbb6c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1d2eb412e9a14b229017a243f9cfbb6c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Baltimore Sun : The Baltimore Sun - Feb. 6, 2020</title><description>Good morning. The forecast today in Baltimore calls for a high chance of rain and powerful winds, with highs around 55 and a low of around 31. I'm Sam Scholl and here are the top headlines from the Baltimore Sun for Friday, February 7.   Police say they have arrested the man suspected of shooting and wounding two detectives Wednesday night, ending the daylong manhunt that locked down a suburban peninsula in northern Anne Arundel County. Officers announced shortly after 3 p.m.</description><author>distribution@spokenlayer.com (Baltimore Sun)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">20c626ca70a54f07848c13a3c7992990</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/20c626ca70a54f07848c13a3c7992990/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 03:03:23 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Houston Matters : Friday’s Show: Parking In Bike Lanes, And Downtown On Weeknights (Feb. 7, 2020)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On Friday's Houston Matters: We learn about the problem of drivers parking in bike lanes around the city.  Also this hour: What would it take to attract more visitors to downtown Houston on weeknights? Plus, we break down The Good, The Bad, and The Ugly of the week's news. And Texas-born singer Phoebe Ryan talks about balancing bipolar disorder with the demands of performing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@houstonpublicmedia.org (Houston Matters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ce859f1773254672af1ede4a35d4510e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ce859f1773254672af1ede4a35d4510e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 03:00:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Relatable with Allie Beth Stuckey : Ep 210 | Taylor, You Need To Calm Down</title><description>&lt;p&gt;First, we discuss Trump's SOTU speech, his acquittal in the impeachment trial, and the results of the Iowa caucus. Will the Democrats find a candidate? Then we discuss Taylor Swift's new Netflix documentary, "Miss Americana."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hydrant starts at just a buck a packet for a 30-day supply. You can save even more with a monthly subscription. And for 25% off your first order, go to https://www.drinkhydrant.com and enter promo code &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;allie&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; at checkout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If there’s a break-in, SimpliSafe uses real video evidence to give police an eye-witness account of the crime. You’ll get FREE shipping and a 60-day risk free trial. You’ve got nothing to lose! Visit &lt;a href="https://simplisafe.com/allie"&gt;https://simplisafe.com/allie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ccardon@glennbeck.com (Relatable with Allie Beth Stuckey)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ee707d73bf9946b1b3f489deb669d3ed</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ee707d73bf9946b1b3f489deb669d3ed/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Intelligence : From out of left field: Ireland’s election</title><description>&lt;p&gt;After the adulation, the discontent. Voters are abandoning the party of the young, progressive leader Leo Varadkar, with many supporting Sinn Fein, a party with a violent history. Our obituaries editor looks back on the life of Homero Gómez, a renowned logger-turned-butterfly-activist. And the coyotes invading America’s cities. For full access to print, digital and audio editions of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;, subscribe here &lt;a href="http://www.economist.com/radiooffer" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.economist.com/radiooffer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>radio@economist.com (The Intelligence)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0a5299f8badf49d1867293469a44c8c7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0a5299f8badf49d1867293469a44c8c7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 02:59:11 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Up First : Friday, February 7, 2020</title><description>The full results from Iowa are finally in, and it's essentially a tie. What kind of pressure will Pete Buttigieg and Bernie Sanders get from the other candidates in Friday's Democratic debate, and how will they take on each another? In China, people are grieving for a doctor who raised an early alarm about the coronavirus. And a former Olympic doctor said he was fired by the U.S. Olympic and Paralympic Committee for reporting abuse cases. Now he's filing a lawsuit against the committee.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (Up First)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c6f5f3721fc54a4ab3f7a1a5cc77b5ab</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c6f5f3721fc54a4ab3f7a1a5cc77b5ab/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 02:53:29 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best of Coast to Coast AM : The Art Of War - Best of Coast to Coast AM - 2/07/20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;George Noory and Gary Gagliardi, discuss Sun Tzu’s The Art of War, Gary sheds light on the ancient Chinese philosopher's principles of "winning without conflict" and how these ideas can apply to peoples' personal lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts@rsvmedia.com (The Best of Coast to Coast AM)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">00b6315713fc447ebbd5c2998a73fefb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/00b6315713fc447ebbd5c2998a73fefb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 02:52:56 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Sky News Daily : The Daily with Dermot Murnaghan: Can authorities curb spread of coronavirus?</title><description>On this edition of the Sky News Daily podcast with Dermot Murnaghan we discuss the growing impact and spread of the coronavirus.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also speak to our special correspondent Alex Crawford about how it's affecting everyday life in Hong Kong.</description><author>radio@sky.uk (Sky News Daily)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">efc0d19acb034226827c1d5884fd06e3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/efc0d19acb034226827c1d5884fd06e3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 02:50:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Daily : ‘He Deserves to Have a Voice’</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In the trial of Harvey Weinstein, six women have taken the stand, each making similar accusations of rape and sexual assault against the movie producer. Throughout their testimony, Weinstein’s defense lawyers have portrayed those encounters as consensual and suggested that in many cases it was the women who wanted something from Mr. Weinstein. His lawyers have seized on the fact that the two women whose accounts are at the center of the criminal charges in his New York trial agreed to have sex and friendly contact with Mr. Weinstein after they were allegedly victimized. Today, one of The Times reporters who broke the story of Mr. Weinstein’s alleged abuse more than two years ago speaks with Donna Rotunno, the lawyer behind Mr. Weinstein’s legal strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guests: &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/by/megan-twohey?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt;Megan Twohey&lt;/a&gt;, an investigative reporter for The Times and co-author of “&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2019/09/08/books/review/she-said-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt;She Said: Breaking the Sexual Harassment Story That Helped Ignite a Movement&lt;/a&gt;," spoke with&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/search?query=donna+rotunno?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; Donna Rotunno&lt;/a&gt;, Harvey Weinstein’s lead defense lawyer. For more information on today’s episode, visit nytimes.com/thedaily.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background reading:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Long before an avalanche of allegations against Mr. Weinstein set off a global reckoning over sexual harassment,&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/14/nyregion/weinstein-woman-metoo.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; Ms. Rotunno was steadily building a career&lt;/a&gt; as a criminal lawyer in Chicago with an unusual specialty: defending men accused of sex crimes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Haven’t been following the trial?&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/06/nyregion/harvey-weinstein-trial.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; Here’s what’s happened so far&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (The Daily)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7d55a7638ff94dfca685ab7321753231</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7d55a7638ff94dfca685ab7321753231/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 02:50:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Start Here : Same Split, Different Day</title><description>With the New Hampshire debate looming, Bernie Sanders re-ignites a war with the Democratic National Committee. President Trump basks in the glow of acquittal, why signaling possible retribution to his enemies. And the first witness to speak on Harvey Weinstein's behalf gets torched in cross-examination.

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt; Like the show? Leave a review: http://bit.ly/ReviewStartHere &lt;p&gt; Follow @StartHereABC for exclusive content, show updates and more:&lt;br&gt; - Twitter: https://www.twitter.com/starthereabc&lt;br&gt; - Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/starthereabc&lt;br&gt; - Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/starthereabc &lt;p&gt; Discover more ABC News podcasts: http://www.abcnewspodcasts.com &lt;p&gt; Start Here is produced by ABC Audio. For more information: http://www.abcnewspodcasts.com</description><author>abc.podcast.support@abc.com (Start Here)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">00c392c5880347a58d673ce4d786e29e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/00c392c5880347a58d673ce4d786e29e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 02:30:11 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Commercial Awareness Podcast : Episode 39: Changing Landscapes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Contact: commawarepod@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram: @&lt;a href="shorturl.at/bmBFH"&gt;commawarepod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;M&amp;amp;A Slowdown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2f798e54-4570-11ea-aeb3-955839e06441"&gt;https://www.ft.com/content/2f798e54-4570-11ea-aeb3-955839e06441&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coronavirus Update&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/6a108d2a-4830-11ea-aee2-9ddbdc86190d"&gt;https://www.ft.com/content/6a108d2a-4830-11ea-aee2-9ddbdc86190d&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/cd0c7eb2-6725-4730-9bd2-2ece50b85841"&gt;https://www.ft.com/content/cd0c7eb2-6725-4730-9bd2-2ece50b85841&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-51397677"&gt;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-51397677&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Lewis Challenges&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2020/feb/06/new-john-lewis-chair-sharon-white-store-closures-job-losses"&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/business/2020/feb/06/new-john-lewis-chair-sharon-white-store-closures-job-losses&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huawei-Verizon IP Lawsuit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ba9f1cce-48c7-11ea-aeb3-955839e06441"&gt;https://www.ft.com/content/ba9f1cce-48c7-11ea-aeb3-955839e06441&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deal News&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelawyer.com/aston-martin-lawrence-stroll-rescue/"&gt;https://www.thelawyer.com/aston-martin-lawrence-stroll-rescue/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boeing Update&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-51407951"&gt;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-51407951&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GS-Amazon Partnership&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/41866efe-4521-11ea-aeb3-955839e06441"&gt;https://www.ft.com/content/41866efe-4521-11ea-aeb3-955839e06441&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/goldman-sachs-eyes-smb-loans-through-amazon-2020-2"&gt;https://www.businessinsider.com/goldman-sachs-eyes-smb-loans-through-amazon-2020-2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/f5e13448-4296-11ea-abea-0c7a29cd66fe"&gt;https://www.ft.com/content/f5e13448-4296-11ea-abea-0c7a29cd66fe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4326520e-42f3-11ea-a43a-c4b328d9061c"&gt;https://www.ft.com/content/4326520e-42f3-11ea-a43a-c4b328d9061c&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://qz.com/1796096/goldman-sachs-is-becoming-an-ally-for-tech-firms-like-amazon/"&gt;https://qz.com/1796096/goldman-sachs-is-becoming-an-ally-for-tech-firms-like-amazon/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="shorturl.at/bxSY1"&gt;shorturl.at/bxSY1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Konexo Partners GT&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelawyer.com/eversheds-newlaw-platform-strikes-partnership-deal-with-grant-thornton/"&gt;https://www.thelawyer.com/eversheds-newlaw-platform-strikes-partnership-deal-with-grant-thornton/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bankofengland.co.uk/-/media/boe/files/markets/benchmarks/what-you-need-to-know-about-libor-transition"&gt;https://www.bankofengland.co.uk/-/media/boe/files/markets/benchmarks/what-you-need-to-know-about-libor-transition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ey.com/en_gl/banking-capital-markets/ten-things-you-need-to-know-about-the-ibor-transition"&gt;https://www.ey.com/en_gl/banking-capital-markets/ten-things-you-need-to-know-about-the-ibor-transition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bankofengland.co.uk/markets/transition-to-sterling-risk-free-rates-from-libor"&gt;https://www.bankofengland.co.uk/markets/transition-to-sterling-risk-free-rates-from-libor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-19199683"&gt;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-19199683&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Car Ban Moved&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-51366123"&gt;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-51366123&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/46bfd6e2-473a-11ea-aee2-9ddbdc86190d"&gt;https://www.ft.com/content/46bfd6e2-473a-11ea-aee2-9ddbdc86190d&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2020/02/04/hybrid-car-fiasco-kick-face-drivers/"&gt;https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2020/02/04/hybrid-car-fiasco-kick-face-drivers/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Created, Written and Hosted by: Tapiwa Museba&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episode Contributor: Matthieu Lawson&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts8+75b7794@anchor.fm (The Commercial Awareness Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5b6ba7ed0b0348c4a868d256057ed876</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5b6ba7ed0b0348c4a868d256057ed876/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 02:24:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>What Next | Daily News and Analysis : WN TBD: Iowa’s App-ocalypse</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On Monday, the Iowa caucuses went off the rails. As the hours stretched into days, and still the results remained unclear, a new piece of election technology was identified as a central cause of the delay. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An app designed to make the election process speedier and more secure had the opposite effect. And its failure is symptomatic of deep-rooted issues in the way the Democratic Party develops and deploys election technology. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, what exactly went wrong on Monday? And what does it say about the party’s effort to regain its digital edge in 2020?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tj.raphael@slate.com (What Next | Daily News and Analysis)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ecd532b9a6b9456d89b60b53e62a387b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ecd532b9a6b9456d89b60b53e62a387b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Get 2 the Point : Tim Hanna--Appleton's Mayor looks back</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This April, the city of Appleton will have its first new mayor in 24 years.  Tim Hanna made the decision to not seek re-election.  After a long career in government, Mayor Hanna has a lot of stories to tell. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hanna details the failed basketball tryout that got him interested in government, his time on the city council when he asked a question and got an answer that left him stumped, to the 1996 mayoral election that ended up before the Wisconsin Court of Appeals.   Hear much more on these stories in this week’s episode.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tmiller@wbay.com (Get 2 the Point)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">186c7938734446ff88731ca80556b2a3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/186c7938734446ff88731ca80556b2a3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>the NewsWorthy : Trump Celebrates, New Travel Rules &amp; Oscars Preview - Friday, February 7th, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The news to know for Friday, February 7th, 2020! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What to know today about President Trump's victory lap, tonight's Democratic debate, and new rules for some international travel...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Plus: a Google Maps update, Instagram's new 'unfollow' tools, and an Oscars preview.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Those stories and more in less than 10 minutes!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Award-winning broadcast journalist and former TV news reporter Erica Mandy breaks it all down for you. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Head to &lt;a href= "http://www.thenewsworthy.com/"&gt;www.theNewsWorthy.com&lt;/a&gt; or see sources below to read more about any of the stories mentioned today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This episode is brought to you by Magic Spoon. Go to &lt;a href="http://magicspoon.com/newsworthy"&gt;http://magicspoon.com/newsworthy&lt;/a&gt; and use promo code 'newsworthy' for free shipping.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;And by the Celeb News Ride Home podcast.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;GIVEAWAY: Leave a review at &lt;a href= "http://www.Podchaser.com/newsworthy"&gt;Podchaser.com/newsworthy&lt;/a&gt; (by Feb 9th, 2020) for a chance to win a prize package.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em style= "font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;"&gt; Become a NewsWorthy INSIDER! Learn more here: &lt;a href= "http://www.TheNewsWorthy.com/insider"&gt;www.TheNewsWorthy.com/insider&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sources:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Trump Celebrates Acquittal: &lt;a href= "https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/481863-trump-holds-white-house-celebration-for-impeachment-acquittal"&gt; The Hill&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-respond-senate-trial-acquittal-noon-remarks-white/story?id=68800473&amp;cid=clicksource_4380645_2_heads_hero_live_hero_hed"&gt; ABC News&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://apnews.com/504e331eeec5107afbe757e8d241a16d"&gt;AP&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/06/us/politics/hunter-biden-investigation.html?action=click&amp;module=Top%20Stories&amp;pgtype=Homepage"&gt; NYT&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/06/us/politics/trump-impeachment.html?action=click&amp;module=Top%20Stories&amp;pgtype=Homepage"&gt; NYT&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/trump-lashes-out-at-democrats-in-cheering-his-acquittal-as-pelosi-declares-him-impeached-forever/2020/02/06/2148e47a-48f3-11ea-b4d9-29cc419287eb_story.html"&gt; Washington Post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dem Debate Tonight: &lt;a href= "https://time.com/5773016/february-democratic-debates/"&gt;TIME&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/481865-sanders-blasts-dnc-rules-that-could-allow-bloomberg-to-debate"&gt; The Hill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;DNC Calls for Results Review: &lt;a href= "https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/live-blog/iowa-caucuses-live-updates-2020-democrats-make-their-final-pitches-n1128596"&gt; NBC News&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/06/politics/iowa-caucus-results/index.html"&gt; CNN&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.nytimes.com/live/2020/iowa-caucus-nh-primary-02-06?action=click&amp;module=Top%20Stories&amp;pgtype=Homepage"&gt; NYT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Chinese Doctor Warned of Coronavirus: &lt;a href= "https://apnews.com/905489d29a3d4f8788f17a40003548a0"&gt;AP&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/feb/06/whistleblower-chinese-doctor-dies-from-coronavirus"&gt; The Guardian&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;2.24 to Honor Kobe Bryant: &lt;a href= "https://sports.yahoo.com/staples-center-will-host-public-memorial-for-kobe-bryant-on-feb-24-215645094.html"&gt; Yahoo Sports&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.eonline.com/news/1118007/kobe-bryant-s-public-memorial-set-for-february-24-all-the-details"&gt; E! News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Last-Minute NBA Trades: &lt;a href= "https://www.si.com/nba/2020/02/06/nba-trade-deadline-live-blog-rumors-updates"&gt; Sports Illustrated&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.nba.com/article/2020/02/06/nba-trade-deadline-buzz-feb-6"&gt; NBA.com&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nba/knicks/2020/02/06/knicks-clippers-wizards-trade-marcus-morris-isaiah-thomas/4681862002/?for-guid=eb4e6047-24e3-e911-ac30-90b11c343abd&amp;"&gt; USA Today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;New Yorkers &amp; Global Entry: &lt;a href= "https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/02/06/trump-dhs-blocks-new-york-drivers-global-entry-trusted-traveler/4676815002/?for-guid=eb4e6047-24e3-e911-ac30-90b11c343abd&amp;utm_source=usatoday-The%20Short%20List&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=narrative&amp;utm_term=article_body"&gt; USA Today&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.wsj.com/articles/homeland-security-steps-up-feud-as-it-blocks-new-yorkers-from-global-entry-program-11581023240"&gt; WSJ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gov’t Gives First OK to Driverless Van:  &lt;a href= "https://www.theverge.com/2020/2/6/21125358/nuro-self-driving-delivery-robot-r2-fmvss-exemption"&gt; The Verge&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.businessinsider.com/nuro-first-self-driving-company-exemption-safety-standards-2020-2"&gt; Business Insider&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.axios.com/feds-clear-the-way-for-nuros-driverless-deliveries-de9db97f-113d-45c6-9606-48f8e207949a.html"&gt; Axios&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Google Maps Update: &lt;a href= "https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/05/google-maps-for-iphone-and-android-update-whats-new.html"&gt; CNBC&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.cnet.com/news/google-redesigns-maps-app-adds-details-on-public-transit-safety-accessibility/"&gt; Cnet&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.theverge.com/2020/2/6/21125275/google-maps-15th-anniversary-new-icon-tabs-design-transit-information-live-view-update-features"&gt; The Verge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Instagram Unfollow Tools: &lt;a href= "https://www.engadget.com/2020/02/06/instagram-will-tell-you-which-of-your-boring-friends-to-unfollow/"&gt; Engadget&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://techcrunch.com/2020/02/06/instagram-least-interacted-with/"&gt; TechCrunch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Oscars Preview: &lt;a href= "https://oscar.go.com/news/oscar-news/final-list-of-oscar-2020-presenter-include-tom-hanks-natalie-portman-chris-rock"&gt; Oscars.com&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/oscar-nominations-2020-complete-list-nominees-updating-live-1267880"&gt; Hollywood Reporter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Snow Moon: &lt;a href= "https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/05/weather/snow-moon-february-trnd/index.html"&gt; CNN&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.cbsnews.com/news/supermoon-february-2020-snow-full-moon-illuminate-night-sky-this-weekend/"&gt; CBS News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Feel Good Friday - Prisoners Learn Coding: &lt;a href= "https://www.wtxl.com/news/national/program-teaches-prisoners-coding-so-they-can-land-tech-jobs-once-released"&gt; WTXL&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://thelastmile.org/"&gt;TheLastMile.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>staff@theNewsWorthy.com (the NewsWorthy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">efd943d310db4e57bc14961ef32371f8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/efd943d310db4e57bc14961ef32371f8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Wars Daily : McDonald’s, Wendy’s Peck Away at Breakfast with New Chicken Sandwiches</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today is Friday, February 7, and we’re looking at McDonald’s vs. Wendy’s. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>iwonder@wondery.com (Business Wars Daily)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b451151948294e4d891b92a03d5acf6b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b451151948294e4d891b92a03d5acf6b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ao Ponto (podcast do jornal O Globo) : Quer saber como é a votação do Oscar? Com a palavra, a jurada</title><description>A produtora Vânia Catani já participou de mais de 25 produções, como "O Palhaço", de 2011, e "O Filme da minha vida", de 2017, e tem seu nome reconhecido no Brasil e no exterior. Não à toa, desde a edição do Oscar em 2019, ela é uma entre as oito mil pessoas escolhidas para votar na maior festa do cinema mundial, portanto, integrante da Academy of Motion Pictures Arts and Science ou, simplesmente, a Academia. No Ao Ponto desta sexta-feira, Catani conta como é o trabalho de escolher os melhores filmes do ano. Só não pode entregar em quem votou. Por isso, o critico de cinema e editor-executivo do GLOBO André Miranda também participa deste episódio e fala sobre suas apostas para a edição deste domingo (9). Ele também comenta as chances de "Democracia em Vertigem", um dos indicados para o prêmio de Melhor Filme Internacional.</description><author>maggi@oglobo.com.br (Ao Ponto (podcast do jornal O Globo))</author><guid isPermaLink="false">26d4d583db0b483282375e87da0fe81f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/26d4d583db0b483282375e87da0fe81f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 23:55:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Federalist Radio Hour : Trump's Acquittal, Romney's Stand, And Biden's Fate</title><description>Federalist Senior Editors Mollie Hemingway and Christopher Bedford join Ben Domenech in studio for a break down of this week's acquittal of Donald Trump, Mitt Romney's anti-Trump conviction, and were the 2020 candidates stand going into New Hampshire and South Carolina primaries.</description><author>info@podcastone.com (The Federalist Radio Hour)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">67dc4b8a8bf642e0be902fa676bebaf2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/67dc4b8a8bf642e0be902fa676bebaf2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FT News Briefing : Friday, February 7</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Uber shares traded higher after hours on Thursday after the ride-hailing company promised profitability in the final quarter of this year, officials in London and Washington told the FT that Donald Trump vented in “apoplectic” fury at Boris Johnson over Britain’s decision to allow China’s Huawei a role in its 5G mobile networks, and activist hedge fund Elliott Management has built a stake worth $2.5bn in SoftBank Group and is pressing for changes. Plus, the FT’s Tom Hancock has been quarantined after reporting on the coronavirus in Wuhan. He explains how a crackdown on information about the virus in Wuhan allowed the disease to spread more widely.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>newsbriefing@ft.com (FT News Briefing)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4fead393aca249bb917750a65e512447</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4fead393aca249bb917750a65e512447/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Townhall Review | Conservative Commentary On Today's News : Democrats Have Disastrous Week with Iowa Debacle, Pelosi Tear, Trump Acquittal, Booming Economy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Townhall Review &amp;ndash; February 8, 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hughhewitt.com/"&gt;Hugh Hewitt&lt;/a&gt; discusses the moment Speaker &lt;a href="https://pelosi.house.gov/"&gt;Nancy Pelosi&lt;/a&gt; tore up her copy of &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/people/donald-j-trump/"&gt;President Trump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo;s State of the Union speech and more with Georgia Senator &lt;a href="https://www.perdue.senate.gov/"&gt;David Perdue&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.srnonline.com/show/the-dan-proft-show"&gt;Dan Proft&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://omny.fm/shows/chicagos-morning-answer-with-dan-proft-amy-jacobso"&gt;Amy Jacobson&lt;/a&gt; talk with &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/author/rich-lowry/"&gt;Rich Lowry&lt;/a&gt;, editor of &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/"&gt;National Review&lt;/a&gt;, about the State of the Union, the Democrat&amp;rsquo;s nomination race and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dennisprager.com/"&gt;Dennis Prager&lt;/a&gt; and journalist &lt;a href="https://fedsoc.org/contributors/john-fund"&gt;John Fund&lt;/a&gt; talk about the latest &lt;a href="https://www.gallup.com/home.aspx"&gt;Gallup&lt;/a&gt; poll showing President Trump&amp;rsquo;s approval rating at an all-time high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sebgorka.com/"&gt;Sebastian Gorka&lt;/a&gt; discuss the failed impeachment effort with historian &lt;a href="http://victorhanson.com/"&gt;Victor Davis Hanson&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dennisprager.com/"&gt;Dennis Prager&lt;/a&gt; explains the highly deceptive $11 million Super Bowl ad for presidential candidate &amp;nbsp;and billionaire &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michael_Bloomberg"&gt;Michael Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mikeonline.com/"&gt;Mike Gallagher&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://salemmedia.com/"&gt;Salem Media&lt;/a&gt; Vice President &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Phil_Boyce"&gt;Phil Boyce&lt;/a&gt; talk about &lt;a href="https://www.rushlimbaugh.com/"&gt;Rush Limbaugh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo;s recent announcement that he has advanced lung cancer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dennisprager.com/"&gt;Dennis Prager&lt;/a&gt; evaluates the appropriateness of the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Bowl_LIV_halftime_show"&gt;Super Bowl&lt;/a&gt; half time show for young children that were watching&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thr@salemmedia.com (Townhall Review | Conservative Commentary On Today's News)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a74837665c454cf0991aaf38be8318d1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a74837665c454cf0991aaf38be8318d1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ticket: Politics from The Atlantic : The New Hampshire Primary, with Chris Pappas</title><description>&lt;p&gt;After the chaos of Iowa, New Hampshire is set to deliver the first clear results of the 2020 presidential race. And on the show to preview the first primary vote is New Hampshire Congressman Chris Pappas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The freshman Democrat is new to Washington, but he's been around Granite State politics his entire life. He was elected state representative at 22, but has been meeting presidential candidates since he was 7. His family's Manchester restaurant has been a waypoint on the trail to the White House for decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He discusses New Hampshire politics, his state's fight against the opioid crisis, and his choice next Tuesday (both who he's voting for, and whether to do a ballot selfie.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcastproduct@theatlantic.com (The Ticket: Politics from The Atlantic)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0f03095e96b24aecb1998f12a157ecb8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0f03095e96b24aecb1998f12a157ecb8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 20:45:48 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sean Klitzner Show : The #YangGang</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Tonight gets political. We talk about the top democrats running for office. I can't promise anything we say is serious.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>SeanKlitzner@gmail.com (The Sean Klitzner Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4c849be0f5524fbc8b96efe74a78d32e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4c849be0f5524fbc8b96efe74a78d32e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 20:16:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Last Word with Lawrence O’Donnell : Trump's prayer breakfast rant shows he doesn't understand what love is</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Tonight on The Last Word: President Trump turned today’s National Prayer Breakfast – an event meant for reflection and empathy – into an opportunity to lash out at his political foes, including Speaker Pelosi, who explained during a presser why she tore up Trump’s speech after the State of the Union. Lawrence explains how Trump’s rants today show that he does not understand the concept of love. Plus, with 100% reporting, the Iowa caucuses are still too close to call, with both Bernie Sanders and Pete Buttigieg claiming victory. Rep. Hakeem Jeffries, Sen. Ed Markey, Cecile Richards, James Pindell, and Gene Sperling join Lawrence O’Donnell.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (The Last Word with Lawrence O’Donnell)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fa36e5a99df94ef7bd8e3c0e8dccd749</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fa36e5a99df94ef7bd8e3c0e8dccd749/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 20:15:34 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rachel Maddow Show : Perez on Iowa caucus problems: 'This was a major league failure'</title><description>&lt;p&gt;9:23 Perez on Iowa caucus problems: 'This was a major league failure'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;9:34 Perez unconcerned about Iowa turnout: 'The energy is everywhere'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;9:55 Schumer to disheartened Democrats: 'Don't give up!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (The Rachel Maddow Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b3ad0093e59e4ab69d5c338d59b3c016</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b3ad0093e59e4ab69d5c338d59b3c016/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 20:10:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hot Zone with Chuck Holton : Episode 284 - A Tour of the Border Wall</title><description>&lt;p&gt;I take a tour of the new 3-mile stretch of privately-funded border wall outside of McAllen, Texas&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>holtocw@gmail.com (The Hot Zone with Chuck Holton)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">47b2d3c8ae7847c0884eaa01fcb9566d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/47b2d3c8ae7847c0884eaa01fcb9566d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 19:54:32 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Today in Focus : Why are the Oscars still so white?</title><description>Following a strikingly white and male list of Bafta nominees, this year’s Academy Awards shortlists are barely more diverse. It’s a chronic problem in an industry running out of excuses for its slow pace of change. Lanre Bakare examines why the Oscars are still so white. Plus: Joan E Greve on a hectic week of US politics. Help support our independent journalism at &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://www.theguardian.com/infocus&amp;quot;&amp;gt;theguardian.com/infocus&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;</description><author>userhelp@theguardian.com (Today in Focus)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">48e50320563948cead621aeceb00ffaf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/48e50320563948cead621aeceb00ffaf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MarketBuzz : 430: Sensex, Nifty likely to open little changed; Wipro, Bharti Airtel, Hero MotoCorp in focus</title><description>Indian benchmark indices BSE Sensex and NSE’s Nifty50 are likely to open little changed on Friday, tracing flat trades in global markets over rising concerns of coronavirus in China. However, the RBI’s move to provide further credit support to ailing sectors may aid markets. At 7:14 am, the SGX Nifty was trading 3 points or 0.02 percent lower at 12,126.50, hinting at a flat beginning for the Sensex and Nifty50.</description><author>sunep.imchen@nw18.com (MarketBuzz)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d91bf372354f450e9d0b43da87559ad9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d91bf372354f450e9d0b43da87559ad9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 18:39:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>All In with Chris Hayes : Trump delivers his real State of the Union during White House victory lap</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Tonight: how Donald Trump's post-impeachment performance brings the stakes of 2020 into stark relief. Then, how the White House is now mobilizing the executive branch for retribution. Plus, Senator Elizabeth Warren joins Chris live in New Hampshire.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (All In with Chris Hayes)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6ee86771ba124dbc9310be06079deba2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6ee86771ba124dbc9310be06079deba2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 18:25:50 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mark Levin Podcast : Mark Levin Audio Rewind - 2/6/20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On Thursday’s Mark Levin Show, Brian Mudd of WJNO fills in. President Trump celebrated his acquittal and ridiculed Rep. Adam Schiff for being a failed screenwriter and trying to bring those skills to Washington. He went on to criticize Speaker Pelosi in his remarks as well. Then, the latest Gallup poll has Republican favorability at 51% today, it was at 43% in September when impeachment was announced. The Democrats' underhanded corruption and efforts to impeach has backfired. Later, Qasim al Rimi the Al Qaeda operative suspected to be in charge of their breach of our military base in Orlando has been killed in a U.S drone strike. Also, the Iowa app maker that bungled the count of caucus votes was hired by Pete Buttigieg for app-making services and billed eight times the amount it billed others. Buttigieg was in the lead but is now tied with Bernie Sanders.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wwopodcasts@westwoodone.com (Mark Levin Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a136fa60f22c481a8964eecd24ff6dc2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a136fa60f22c481a8964eecd24ff6dc2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 18:15:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Freedomizer Radio : Proof Negative Radio Show: REAL Patriot News</title><description>Welcome to the Proof Negative Radio Show! We have been on air since January 2010. We focus on alternative news, independent politics, &amp; health and wellness.

We reserve the right to go off topic and have fun on air as well.

Freedomizer Radio does NOT embrace socialism, or pursue what the 1% global elites want us to do or think.

We do not monitor this chat room. We do ask everyone check out our website http://www.freedomizerradio.com where everyone can listen live and join our chat room.</description><author>Proof@freedomizerradio.com (Freedomizer Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1d2783135ac140c5b60069a7ae16deff</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1d2783135ac140c5b60069a7ae16deff/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 18:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>We the People : An Impeachment Trial Recap</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This live conversation at George Washington Law School recaps the arguments presented on both sides of the impeachment trial. GW Law professor Andrew Knaggs – who served in the Trump administration’s Department of Defense – presents arguments against convicting the president, and his colleague Professor Peter Smith – a former Justice Department lawyer – presents pro-conviction arguments. They discuss the facts and circumstances surrounding President Trump’s impeachment, how “mixed motive” situations should be dealt with, what constitutes obstruction of Congress, whether or not impeachable offenses must be crimes, and more. Host Jeffrey Rosen moderates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Questions or comments about the podcast? Email us at podcast@constitutioncenter.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jmcdermott@constitutioncenter.org (We the People)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">20ad4ce7f7de499c8b912bbb36066c83</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/20ad4ce7f7de499c8b912bbb36066c83/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 17:29:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Twelve O'clock Siren : Episode - 23.5</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Coach Houston Nutt recap. Sans Jason, sadly.   We chat about our HGTV submission. The Super Bowl. And a variety of other things. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jameshartley1@gmail.com (The Twelve O'clock Siren)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">215bf921d26c4c43a5acc6281bbf4f72</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/215bf921d26c4c43a5acc6281bbf4f72/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 17:07:30 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC Nightly News with Lester Holt : Thursday, February 6, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;25 million people under winter weather alerts across the Midwest and Northeast, new safety concerns over Evenflo ‘big kid’ booster seats, and astronaut Christina Koch returns to Earth after record-breaking spaceflight. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (NBC Nightly News with Lester Holt)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">56964fba031246628235c1441902be96</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/56964fba031246628235c1441902be96/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 16:58:37 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Newscast : We’re all Newscasters now</title><description>The podcast formerly known as Brexitcast is here! And guess what? We’re still wanging on about Brexit. Emma Vardy joins us from the Irish election campaign and Adam has some podcasting tips for the new kids in town across the pond.

Producers: Emma Close &amp; Ione Wells
Editor: Dino Sofos</description><author>RadioMusic.Support@bbc.co.uk (Newscast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4b3a41e2c3ce4e23bc3bc38f3304f522</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4b3a41e2c3ce4e23bc3bc38f3304f522/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 14:44:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>This Is America with Rich Valdes Podcast : Attacked, Acquitted, and (Illegal) Alien Absconders</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Speaker Pelosi attacks American tradition at President Trump's State of The Union address and tears the President's speech. Then, the Senate votes " Not Guilty" on both articles of impeachment effectively exonerating the president through the acquittal announced by Supreme Court Chief Justice John Roberts. Plus, over 100 illegal aliens were arrested for criminal offenses here and abroad.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comment and follow on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/richvaldes"&gt;Twitter&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://facebook.com/RichValdesCompany"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or visit us at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://richvaldes.com/"&gt;RichValdes.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Portions of today's program are brought to you by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://justfacts.com/rich"&gt;JustFacts.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://paypal.me/RichValdes" rel="payment"&gt;Support the show.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>rsementa@gmail.com (This Is America with Rich Valdes Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">03368eec66ee4aa38635e8d31ca4e65e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/03368eec66ee4aa38635e8d31ca4e65e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 14:38:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The McCarthy Report : Episode 71: It’s Over! We Hope . . .</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today on &lt;i data-stringify-type="italic"&gt;The McCarthy Report&lt;/i&gt;, Andy and Rich discuss the end of the impeachment trial and Mitt Romney’s controversial vote.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>studio@nationalreview.com (The McCarthy Report)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ce046f8b62864d9baea972b55f1db2ec</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ce046f8b62864d9baea972b55f1db2ec/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 13:43:30 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sara Carter Show : Coronavirus: Chinese Communist Party Tries To Blame US For Outbreak</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Sara A. Carter spoke with Gordon Chang, an expert on China. Chang told Carter that the Chinese Communist Party is becoming increasingly vulnerable as the Coronavirus spreads. He also said that the regime is trying to spread a rumor that Coronavirus is U.S. created.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>support@thesaracartershow.com (The Sara Carter Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">980ada2032ff44b892e09fb60acd4a5d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/980ada2032ff44b892e09fb60acd4a5d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 13:26:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>John Solomon Reports : Carter Page slams FBI's Chris Wray</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Agents are covering up FISA abuses committed by fellow comrades.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>media@justthenews.com (John Solomon Reports)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">58834669813b404697750ec5ca999638</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/58834669813b404697750ec5ca999638/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Andrew Klavan Show : Ep. 841 - Dems' No Good Very Bad Week</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Mitt Romney is tired of winning, but the rest of us are having a blast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like The Andrew Klavan Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: KLAVAN and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/Klavan"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/Klavan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>andrewklavanshow@dailywire.com (The Andrew Klavan Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">475dddb475d74ce9a0ae8766a436f924</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/475dddb475d74ce9a0ae8766a436f924/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 11:34:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FontCast : Summer Series - Terry Field, part two</title><description>&lt;div&gt;Terry Field, former Chief of Staff to Premier David Bartlett, is back for the second part of his Summer Series long form interview. He picks up from the high point of the Labor Party's victory in the 1998 state election. Terry also makes some bold predictions for the current government after Will Hodgman's retirement. &lt;/div&gt;</description><author>samikin@me.com (FontCast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f0bc305bbdfe4c5e8d43fd89f94d6290</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f0bc305bbdfe4c5e8d43fd89f94d6290/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 11:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Pega'os En La Mañana con Julio Rivera Saniel : Pega'os en la Mañana- Jueves, 6 de febrero de 2020</title><author>radioisladigital@gmail.com (Pega'os En La Mañana con Julio Rivera Saniel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d861b61e2d944c96b44544bf0ad47c8d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d861b61e2d944c96b44544bf0ad47c8d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 09:43:23 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>7am : Barnaby Joyce’s failed coup</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Barnaby Joyce lost his leadership tilt but has reopened a schism in the Coalition on climate policy. Paul Bongiorno on what Joyce promised - and the challenges he has created for Scott Morrison.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guest:&lt;/strong&gt; Columnist for &lt;em&gt;The Saturday Paper&lt;/em&gt; Paul Bongiorno.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background reading:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thesaturdaypaper.com.au/"&gt;The Saturday Paper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.themonthly.com.au/"&gt;The Monthly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on today&amp;rsquo;s episode, visit &lt;a href="https://7ampodcast.com.au/"&gt;7ampodcast.com.au.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jadeb@schwartzmedia.com.au (7am)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e858684993e94f5b9a0c265172178134</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e858684993e94f5b9a0c265172178134/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Michael Knowles Show : Ep. 491 - Mitt Romney Has Always Been Awful</title><description>&lt;p&gt;President Trump has officially been acquitted in the Senate’s farce impeachment trial. But not before snake-in-the-grass Mitt Romney gets in one last snip before being relegated to ignominy and obscurity. We will compare sanctimonious backstabbers with serious and successful conservatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like The Michael Knowles Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: KNOWLES and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/Knowles"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/Knowles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>michaelknowlesshow@dailywire.com (The Michael Knowles Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6dffc8fa4ff64e24893d81cba6b5e9ea</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6dffc8fa4ff64e24893d81cba6b5e9ea/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 08:54:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Building Tomorrow : Venture Capital Built Silicon Valley</title><description>&lt;p&gt;While fans of the show&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Silicon Valley&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;might not have much regard for the role of venture capital in technological innovation, the reality is that venture capitalists do more than act as ATMs for startups. They provide crucial business, marketing, and legal expertise, all of which are necessary to actually get a product to market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;But while venture capital might seem obvious to us today, it was a radical idea in the mid-20th century. Paul interviews Spencer Ante about his biography of the founding father of venture capital, Georges Doriot, a French immigrant who revolutionized the way startups are funded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is the relationship between venture capital and start-up owners? Who was Georges Doriot and how did he change the world of venture capital? How is venture capital regulated by the SEC? What barriers do venture capitalists face?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info+5e309ca47cd7f6767ff252f3@mg.pippa.io (Building Tomorrow)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e3c510c82c254b69bc9f292ac53dd3ce</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e3c510c82c254b69bc9f292ac53dd3ce/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 06:20:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Verdict with Ted Cruz : Ep. 12 - It All Comes Down To This</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Senate votes on whether or not to remove the President, one Republican defects, and the stakes couldn’t be higher moving forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This show was co-hosted by Senator Ted Cruz and Michael Knowles. To hear more of Michael, check out The Michael Knowles Show on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you stream your favorite podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>verdictcruz@gmail.com (Verdict with Ted Cruz)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">865e70983b884220a8cc3cfb37c5d474</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/865e70983b884220a8cc3cfb37c5d474/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 05:39:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Statesman Podcast : The Sinn Féin Surge</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On this week's New Statesman Podcast, Stephen Bush and Anoosh Chakelian are joined by Ailbhe Rea and Patrick Maguire to talk about the latest setbacks in the rollout of Universal Credit. Then, in You Ask Us, they take your question on scoping out new MPs for gossip fodder, and, finally, Ailbhe reports back from the Republic of Ireland ahead of the upcoming election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;New Statesman&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;digital subscriber you can get advert free access to this podcast by visiting&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.newstatesman.com/nssubscribers" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;newstatesman.com/nssubscribers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you haven't signed up yet, visit&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.newstatesman.com/subscribe" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;newstatesman.com/subscribe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to purchase your subscription.&amp;nbsp;Send us your questions for future episodes via Twitter&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.twitter.com/ns_podcasts" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;@ns_podcasts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>helen@newstatesman.co.uk (The New Statesman Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4e20d35ed2d04fd982d2146638491f10</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4e20d35ed2d04fd982d2146638491f10/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 02:00:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Throughline : She Got Next</title><description>There are more female candidates in this presidential campaign cycle than at any other time in American history. But women were running for the highest office before they could even vote. How three women ran and challenged the notion of who could and should be president of the United States.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (Throughline)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f04afe9636d340f9842b84186834524f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f04afe9636d340f9842b84186834524f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 23:14:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Left Anchor : Episode 118 - Bernie Won Iowa</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Ryan is back from vacation so we return with a discussion of the Iowa clusterfuck: How Bernie edged out Pete Buttigieg in the popular vote and tied in pleged delegates, how Biden collapsed, how and why the caucus was bungled so horribly, and what it maybe means for the next few primaries. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>catchment.basin@gmail.com (Left Anchor)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">22f5f0fda56541a990101e0eae4ff75c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/22f5f0fda56541a990101e0eae4ff75c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 21:29:37 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Argument : What Did We Learn in Iowa?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;What does the debacle of the Iowa caucuses mean for the trajectory of the 2020 Democratic race? The columnists discuss the Democratic electorate's neat split on the ground in Iowa, Bernie Sanders's path to the nomination, and whether the Hawkeye State still deserves its first-in-the-nation status. Then, how worried should we be about the Wuhan coronavirus — and what does its spread say about China’s global standing? For background reading on this episode, visit&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/column/the-argument" target="_blank"&gt;nytimes.com/theargument&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>argument@nytimes.com (The Argument)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f78b28d12e19494597833c4cc3d1cb1b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f78b28d12e19494597833c4cc3d1cb1b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>RUMBLE with MICHAEL MOORE : Ep. 33: EMERGENCY PODCAST SYSTEM — The Senate Has Seceded From The Union</title><description>&lt;p&gt;"So here’s what’s going to happen. Trump is a recidivist (a serial con man, serial rapist, serial liar). He will take the Senate’s vote today as permission to keep breaking the law — but in ways that will shock even you &amp;amp; me — and frighten the entire country to act."&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/rumble-with-michael-moore/message</description><author>podcasts39+10fc9a30@anchor.fm (RUMBLE with MICHAEL MOORE)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">24fcd690ed5a448585a62cfc792db72f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/24fcd690ed5a448585a62cfc792db72f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 20:45:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Article II: Inside Impeachment : Not Guilty</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Senators voted to acquit President Trump, finding him not guilty on two articles of impeachment. Senator Mitt Romney, a Republican from Utah, surprised the public by voting to convict President Trump on the first article: abuse of power. He is the first Senator in history to vote against their party in favor of removing the president from office. Otherwise, the votes fell along party lines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alex Moe, NBC News Capitol Hill Producer, recaps the final historic hours on the Senate floor and where Trump—and the American public—might go from here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further Reading:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/trump-impeachment-sen-doug-jones-says-he-will-vote-convict-n1130756" target="_blank"&gt;Senate acquits Trump on both impeachment charges&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/full-text-romney-s-speech-why-he-ll-vote-convict-n1130936" target="_blank"&gt;Full text: Romney's speech on why he'll vote to convict Trump of abuse of power&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>articletwopodcast@gmail.com (Article II: Inside Impeachment)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3743ac2361914375ac23b83882155b70</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3743ac2361914375ac23b83882155b70/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 20:17:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>ESPN Chicago GameNight : 2-5 9 PM: Andre Snellings</title><description>"At Least We're Not The Knicks": What direction should the Cubs go with Kris Bryant amid the trade rumors? Also, ESPN NBA Reporter Andre Snellings joins the show to break down the Bulls woes and the NBA Trade Deadline.</description><author>feedback@goodkarmabrands.com (ESPN Chicago GameNight)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">418a655479f14cdd942f06562ecc58da</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/418a655479f14cdd942f06562ecc58da/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 20:04:08 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Pronoia Now Network : These Evolving Times for 2-5-2020!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A Tribe Called CHEESE!!  Living Robots!?  Graphene from Trash!  Anti-Viral Sugar??  How to Eat Air?  British X-Files to be Released!  California Bans Animal-Tested Cosmetics!  Florida's Bold Move to protect Everglades and MORE!!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mysticandwizard@gmail.com (Pronoia Now Network)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ecec28a51f2d49d8ac78f021612d7520</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ecec28a51f2d49d8ac78f021612d7520/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 19:52:54 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Global Dispatches -- World News That Matters : The Fight Against 'Neglected Tropical Diseases' Gets a Boost</title><description>&lt;p&gt;There is a category of diseases that sickens, injures and kills the poorest people on the planet. These are called &lt;a href= "https://www.who.int/neglected_diseases/diseases/en/"&gt;Neglected Tropical Diseases&lt;/a&gt; or NTDs You may be familiar with some of them, like leprosy, guinea worm disease or River Blindness; but you have probably never heard of most of them--I know I have not. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But these diseases, combined, affect nearly 1.7 billion people around the world and further add to the costs of developing economies. So, in an effort to make these diseases a little less neglected, about eight years ago governments, philanthropies, UN agencies and NGOs came together to design and implement strategies to reduce and ultimately eliminate many of these diseases.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On the line with me today is someone who has been at the very forefront of that effort. &lt;a href= "https://www.huffpost.com/author/thoko-elphick-pooley?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS8&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAE0ALkh4oxiIdiiTIgSS51Lk2KvOF_Orn8uum1mN-vLdFZtmq5J_xR2Cf66QaJD4YgXchVMzmHKPfdRmhKiufwWRWdftuTmAq1ch2g9nS43s-d2xdc2_1puXb2nOJ1VJ2N2Iq0VMfRRkstmP8RTU0rHNAh-gy0BNQOP6CbGbMOWj"&gt; Dr. Thoko Elphick-Pooley&lt;/a&gt; is the director of a collective called &lt;a href="https://unitingtocombatntds.org/"&gt;Uniting to Combat NTDS&lt;/a&gt;. We discuss the progress that has been made towards the elimination of NTDs and also what strategies have been most effective in combating these diseases. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As it happens, we spoke on the first-ever &lt;a href= "https://worldntdday.org/"&gt;World NTD Day&lt;/a&gt;, so I kick off asking Dr. Elphick-Pooley about the significance of having a new world day around Neglected Tropical Diseases. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.undispatch.com/"&gt;https://www.undispatch.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.undispatch.com/category/podcast/"&gt;https://www.undispatch.com/category/podcast/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.globaldispatchespodcast.com/"&gt;https://www.globaldispatchespodcast.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>globaldispatchespodcast@gmail.com (Global Dispatches -- World News That Matters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">85eb8223d78d431ca6e25aff943b8c77</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/85eb8223d78d431ca6e25aff943b8c77/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Deconstructed with Mehdi Hasan : Rigged: The Acquittal of Donald J Trump</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As predicted, the Republican-controlled Senate voted on Wednesday to find President Donald J. Trump not guilty on both articles of impeachment brought by the House of Representatives. It was a party-line vote, with one notable exception: Utah Senator Mitt Romney became the first Senator in U.S. history to vote to remove a president of his own party. Democratic Senators Jeff Merkley of Oregon and Brian Schatz of Hawaii, who both voted to remove the President, joined Mehdi Hasan by phone shortly after the vote to discuss the implications of Trump’s acquittal for the future of the Senate.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@theintercept.com (Deconstructed with Mehdi Hasan)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">939a56fde698426e90f97d43b6659fc1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/939a56fde698426e90f97d43b6659fc1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 17:58:50 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FiveThirtyEight Politics : The Results In Iowa</title><description>The crew discusses the results -- so far -- from the Iowa caucuses. They also check in on the race in New Hampshire and the vote to acquit President Trump.</description><author>espndigitalaudiocontent@espn.com (FiveThirtyEight Politics)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c55fb4cdc58a46dab040246adf2cbc73</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c55fb4cdc58a46dab040246adf2cbc73/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 16:25:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bold and Blunt : Removing the Sour Taste of Nancy Pelosi</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Impeachment has ended, with a big fat zero for Democrats -- like we didn't see that one coming, right? Now it's time to heal. And what better way to kick it off with today's National Prayer Breakfast. Tune in to hear as Gov. Mike Huckabee tells what makes America great -- and how to keep it that way.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>media@washingtontimes.com (Bold and Blunt)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2a046ee4835540feb34e776fc213df4c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2a046ee4835540feb34e776fc213df4c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 15:29:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>National Review's Radio Free California Podcast : Episode 106: Here’s Wishing the Governor Didn’t Love Us So Much</title><description>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Governor Gavin Newsom introduces a record-setting state budget he says proves what “big-hearted government” can do and proposes a state takeover of private utilities, including PG&amp;amp;E. In other news: we&amp;#8217;ll discuss the case against Assemblyman Bill Brough (R., Dana Point), and school kids dousing themselves in fake oil to fight climate change in Sacramento. Intro music by Metalachi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="mailto:dbahnsen@thebahnsengroup.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;dbahnsen@thebahnsengroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="mailto:Will@calpolicycenter.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;span class="il"&gt;Will&lt;/span&gt;@calpolicycenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span id="m_4124646736231928874gmail-docs-internal-guid-cd11aa91-7fff-d013-c77c-1fd7d60df777"&gt;Show&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span id="m_4124646736231928874gmail-docs-internal-guid-cd11aa91-7fff-d013-c77c-1fd7d60df777"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ocregister.com/2020/01/13/gavin-newsoms-budget-proposal-is-big-and-irresponsible/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.ocregister.com/2020/01/13/gavin-newsoms-budget-proposal-is-big-and-irresponsible/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258086000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFsjTWKTp31Dn4yUX4IBqRkGKO7mw"&gt;Gavin Newsom’s big budget proposal is bloated and irresponsible&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article239050443.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article239050443.html&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258086000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNF5j6qL24XKmuLrVng9HwtI-Q1myg"&gt;California state budget breaks record, tops $220 billion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://californiapolicycenter.org/newsoms-2020-21-budget-a-big-pie-but-empty-calories/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://californiapolicycenter.org/newsoms-2020-21-budget-a-big-pie-but-empty-calories/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258086000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHcioqGgDcdeBYMC6hQg0CDOqSZMw"&gt;Newsom’s 2020-21 Budget – A big pie but empty calories&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.politico.com/states/california/story/2020/01/10/newsom-proposes-medicaid-benefits-for-undocumented-senior-citizens-1248937?fbclid=IwAR3l25K0Z58ey9unZF7hxycfO-r0G5bRq8xAdcZTQS_0J86J0_b6UrVfGXk" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.politico.com/states/california/story/2020/01/10/newsom-proposes-medicaid-benefits-for-undocumented-senior-citizens-1248937?fbclid%3DIwAR3l25K0Z58ey9unZF7hxycfO-r0G5bRq8xAdcZTQS_0J86J0_b6UrVfGXk&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258086000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFc9Qe8Hr1jvCHnl4gLwSPxMrBhHw"&gt;Newsom proposes Medicaid benefits for undocumented senior citizens&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/the-state-worker/article239461768.html#storylink=cpy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/the-state-worker/article239461768.html%23storylink%3Dcpy&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258087000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNF2cvy5dWZsj_1Fmou_mF2R9FJVqw"&gt;Gavin Newsom’s budget would make state government bigger. Can California sustain the spending?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://calmatters.org/commentary/budget-entitlements-as-economy-slows/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://calmatters.org/commentary/budget-entitlements-as-economy-slows/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258087000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNH8HqeFQuh3bxA1q-0XLabhPUMI8g"&gt;More entitlements as economy slows?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-01-29/high-profile-california-housing-bill-to-allow-mid-rise-apartments-near-transit-falls-short?utm_source=Essential+California&amp;amp;utm_campaign=5f010e98b4-EMAIL_CAMPAIGN_2020_01_31_01_15&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_term=0_6e35f7f85b-5f010e98b4-84210865" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-01-29/high-profile-california-housing-bill-to-allow-mid-rise-apartments-near-transit-falls-short?utm_source%3DEssential%2BCalifornia%26utm_campaign%3D5f010e98b4-EMAIL_CAMPAIGN_2020_01_31_01_15%26utm_medium%3Demail%26utm_term%3D0_6e35f7f85b-5f010e98b4-84210865&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258087000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNEX6igV6rnFuqt06cPA_4-kkFwcAQ"&gt;SB50 fails again&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sacbee.com/article239806898.html?fbclid=IwAR2-GZTmiZ7aW7q26hC6CVQJQnVZa0Yje1Xgn4kW6VjuvyLWJHZflpReGQ8" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.sacbee.com/article239806898.html?fbclid%3DIwAR2-GZTmiZ7aW7q26hC6CVQJQnVZa0Yje1Xgn4kW6VjuvyLWJHZflpReGQ8&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258087000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFvoonxFinr_fNuof--WOhWO0lXww"&gt;Teens drench themselves in fake oil in climate change protest at California pension fund&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article239920693.html?fbclid=IwAR0UyG4uljsgIbTM-o5CxuIUbSgtfZ8OvzMm-x83cVpxTD2Jd3Y4sv9iyBw" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article239920693.html?fbclid%3DIwAR0UyG4uljsgIbTM-o5CxuIUbSgtfZ8OvzMm-x83cVpxTD2Jd3Y4sv9iyBw&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258087000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNF8-vzTpXd4kY7-8GMxxWV09aGFvg"&gt;Should California take over PG&amp;amp;E? San Francisco Democrat proposes a public utility&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ocregister.com/2020/02/04/the-case-against-bill-brough/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.ocregister.com/2020/02/04/the-case-against-bill-brough/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1581014258087000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNExIIbZvD2S9uvDXNaCe6luvGJHJw"&gt;The case against Bill Brough&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>studio@nationalreview.com (National Review's Radio Free California Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d2dd12ea940146e59647ffaa89107886</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d2dd12ea940146e59647ffaa89107886/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 14:57:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Can He Do That? : A president acquitted. The balance of power tested.</title><description>&lt;div&gt;The United States Senate &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/impeachment-trial-live-updates/2020/02/05/a7a79daa-4807-11ea-ab15-b5df3261b710_story.html?itid=hp_hp-bignews3_impeachment-ticker-1020am%3Aprime-time%2Fpromo"&gt;acquitted President Trump&lt;/a&gt; on charges — brought by the House of Representatives — of abuse of power and obstruction of Congress.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;The vote fell largely along party lines, with one exceptions. Sen. Mitt Romney of Utah historically voted with the Democrats to convict the president on the first article: abuse of power. That marked the first time in American history that a member of the president’s own party has voted to remove him. Romney voted with Republicans to acquit Trump on the second article: obstruction of congress.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This moment is only the third time in U.S. history that the Senate has held an impeachment trial. The Senate has never voted to convict and remove a president.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;An impeachment trial in the Senate means Congress is deciding where to draw lines around presidential conduct: What’s acceptable, what’s inappropriate and what rises to the level of “high crimes and misdemeanors?”&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Over the course of the Senate trial, House managers and Trump’s lawyers engaged in arguments for their respective positions. Trump’s acquittal can be interpreted as a reflection of the Senate agreeing with those arguments.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;And if that’s case, which of the Trump team’s arguments have established new precedent? How might this acquittal embolden not only this president, but future presidents? At the end of this partisan impeachment process, has the balance of power shifted in this country and can the pendulum ever swing back toward equilibrium?&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Related episodes: &lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/podcasts/can-he-do-that/a-divided-congress-and-a-presidency-on-the-line/"&gt;A divided Congress and a presidency on the line&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/podcasts/can-he-do-that/watchdog-says-the-hold-on-ukraine-aid-violated-the-law-will-it-matter-in-the-senate-trial/"&gt;Watchdog says the hold on Ukraine aid violated the law. Will it matter in the Senate trial?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>jessica.stahl@washpost.com (Can He Do That?)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a8122563017946e9b45f621bbad8c970</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a8122563017946e9b45f621bbad8c970/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 14:33:31 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Editors : Episode 189: Was It Great or Was It Tearable?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s our largest &lt;i data-stringify-type="italic"&gt;Editors&lt;/i&gt; group yet! Rich is joined by Charlie, Michael, Jim, Luke, and Alexandra for a discussion of the Iowa caucus debacle, the impeachment vote, and last night’s State of the Union address.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Light Items&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rich: Not a fan of covering the Iowa caucus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charlie: World War II in color.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michael: Irish elections.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jim: Nespresso machines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Luke: The Great British Baking Show.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alexandra: Trips to two new states: Iowa and Washington.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Editors’ Picks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rich: Daniel Mahoney’s cover piece for the new issue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charlie: &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/02/49ers-head-coach-kyle-shanahan-success-running-game-passing-league/"&gt;John Hirschauer on the Super Bowl&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michael: &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/02/charles-lieber-case-why-american-scientists-take-chinese-money/"&gt;Daniel Tenreiro on Chinese funding&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jim: NR’s coverage from Iowa (Rich Lowry, Alexandra DeSanctis, and John McCormack).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Luke: &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/podcasts/constitutionally-speaking/"&gt;Constitutionally Speaking is back&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alexandra: KDW on homelessness form the upcoming print issue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Editors&lt;/em&gt; is hosted by Rich Lowry and produced by Sarah Schutte.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>studio@nationalreview.com (The Editors)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8b2966473d1243d3aa4c449302a210c9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8b2966473d1243d3aa4c449302a210c9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 14:25:45 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Chuck ToddCast: Meet the Press : Iowa Caucus "App-ocalypse" kicks off chaotic month: Jonathan Martin and Eugene Scott</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Days after the Iowa caucuses, results are still ambiguous. But one thing is clear: the fallout will scramble the field of Democratic candidates as the New Hampshire primary approaches.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>matt.rivera@nbcuni.com (The Chuck ToddCast: Meet the Press)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e499125d0b2042919170f3079290bafb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e499125d0b2042919170f3079290bafb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 14:17:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Individual 1 podcast : Mitt Romney Stands Up For What Is Right.</title><description>&lt;div&gt;John gets emotional describing the moment that Mitt Romney announced that he would vote to convict Trump as the sham impeachment trial ends. He then explains why he believes that Trump is now favored to be re-elected. &lt;/div&gt;</description><author>batoul.peters@globalstorynetwork.com (Individual 1 podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d4fca3bc3f5c48309cbcca2fe4eed15d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d4fca3bc3f5c48309cbcca2fe4eed15d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 12:38:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Carnegie Council Audio Podcast : Democratic Candidates &amp; Foreign Policy after Iowa, with Nikolas Gvosdev</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With the (incomplete) results of the Iowa Caucus putting the spotlight on Pete Buttigieg and Bernie Sanders, what do we know about their foreign policy platforms? How do they differentiate themselves from Joe Biden? Senior Fellow Nikolas Gvosdev shares his thoughts and touches on voters' possible perception of Sanders as a "socialist" and how climate change could become an issue in this election.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>carnegieitunes@cceia.org (Carnegie Council Audio Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a59b53aa57b245cd897ce1bcebbf78d4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a59b53aa57b245cd897ce1bcebbf78d4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 11:14:22 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Graham Allen’s Dear America Podcast : EP 63 | Pelosi is an Embarrassment - The State of the Union Recap</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The State of the Union was glorious. Trump's achievements cannot be denied and yet the Democrats we're miserable. Pelosi has angered a lot of folks by tearing up Trump's speech. Graham Allen and the crew recap the highlights.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My Patriot Supply&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PreparewithGraham.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RedArrowWeapons.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>dearamerica76@gmail.com (Graham Allen’s Dear America Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6c40db260e1e4b9d8f9ce8671ccccdfe</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6c40db260e1e4b9d8f9ce8671ccccdfe/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 11:13:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump, Inc.  : An Intimate Dinner with President Trump</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Lev Parnas and Igor Fruman have attained notoriety for their parts in the Ukraine mess. They’re both Soviet-born U.S. citizens who worked closely with the president’s personal lawyer, Rudy Giuliani, serving as emissaries in the campaign to oust then-U.S. Ambassador Marie Yovanovitch and press Ukraine’s government to investigate Joe Biden’s son. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But Parnas and Fruman also exemplify the shattering of norms when it comes to the influence of big money in politics during the administration of President Donald Trump.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Parnas and Fruman are not the first people that we've seen fit this mold of someone with deep foreign connections, who's never given campaign contributions before, suddenly starts giving large amounts of political contributions and then shows up at exclusive events,” said Robert Maguire, the research director at &lt;a href="https://www.citizensforethics.org/"&gt;Citizens for Responsibility and Ethics in Washington&lt;/a&gt;, or CREW. But he says they can be a model for what to look for: political newcomers suddenly making big donations, often using an LLC to obscure their identity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parnas and Fruman now &lt;a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/pr/lev-parnas-and-igor-fruman-charged-conspiring-violate-straw-and-foreign-donor-bans"&gt;face federal criminal charges for&lt;/a&gt;, among other things, allegedly funneling foreign money into U.S. elections and trying to hide its source. (They’ve pleaded not guilty.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The law is clear on this: “At the most basic level, one is not allowed to solicit, accept, or receive any foreign money in connection with a US election at the state, federal, or local level,” said Ellen Weintraub, a member of the Federal Election Commission. In practice, though, it’s perhaps easier than ever for foreign money to enter the American political system undetected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Learn more about how you can dig into campaign finance documents yourself with &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/reporting-recipe-how-to-identify-suspicious-campaign-finance-records"&gt;our new Reporting Recipe&lt;/a&gt;. Read about &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/trump-inc-2020-how-parnas-and-frumans-dodgy-donation-was-uncovered-by-two-people-using-google-translate"&gt;how watchdogs identified Parnas and Fruman’s suspicious campaign contributions&lt;/a&gt; at ProPublica. An earlier version of this story incorrectly identified FEC vice-chair Steven Walther as a Republican; he is an independent.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (Trump, Inc. )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">33f4a865e82c4ef09d97da9e66aee062</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/33f4a865e82c4ef09d97da9e66aee062/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Commentary Magazine Podcast : Biden Bombs and Trump Transcends</title><description>Donald Trump struck an interesting note in his State of the Union address, highlighting the gauzy if oversimplified version of American history out of favor in intellectual circles. Was it a savvy move? Also, Iowa’s mess of a caucus did send one clear signal: Joe Biden isn’t the frontrunner anymore.</description><author>feeds@soundcloud.com (Commentary Magazine Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">29de5c9a5baa4098ad95d50ec208aeeb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/29de5c9a5baa4098ad95d50ec208aeeb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 08:33:52 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Stu Does America Podcast : ‘Stu Does America’ Premiere – We Totally Said February 10, Right?!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s like how people remember the "BerenSTEIN Bears" instead of the "BerenSTAIN Bears," right? (It’s totally "Berenstain.") You were under the impression that "Stu Does America" would be launching today, February 4. But "Stu Does America" ACTUALLY premieres next Monday, February 10! Isn’t that hilarious?! Actually, the less funny reason for the delay is that I had to go to Washington, D.C., to cover the State of the Union address. I sincerely apologize for the delay, but I promise the show will be worth the wait when you tune in next week, February 10 on BlazeTV, YouTube, and wherever you download your podcasts! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Find out more at &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.StuDoesAmerica.com&amp;amp;redir_token=gAFA43LDjbIBe-DpAGcXf-zxTLF8MTU4MTAwMjA3NEAxNTgwOTE1Njc0&amp;amp;event=video_description&amp;amp;v=nMhzpb-iAGg"&gt;http://www.StuDoesAmerica.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ccardon@blazemedia.com (Stu Does America Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">06b7b84e256d4d6ba14d60b16940f0ae</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/06b7b84e256d4d6ba14d60b16940f0ae/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 07:16:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Between The Lines Radio Newsmagazine podcast : Between The Lines - Feb. 5, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Sham Trump Impeachment Trial Acquittal Erodes Congressional Oversight of Presidential Abuse of Power; Trump’s Destabilizing Middle East Peace Plan is Dead on Arrival; Indigenous Art Exhibit’s Emblems of Colonial Violence and the Resilient People Who Made Them&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visit our website at &lt;a href="https://btlonline.org/"&gt;BTLonline.org&lt;/a&gt; for more information, links, transcripts and in-depth interviews. (Updates after 3 p.m. ET Wednesdays) Follow us on Facebook at BetweenTheLinesRadioNewsmagazine and on Twitter @BTLRadioNews. Join our Patreon community at Patreon.com/BetweenTheLinesRadioNewsmagazine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="https://secure.givelively.org/donate/squeaky-wheel-productions/support-progressive-voices-to-defend-democracy-and-fight-fascism"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (https://secure.givelively.org/donate/squeaky-wheel-productions/support-progressive-voices-to-defend-democracy-and-fight-fascism)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>contact@btlonline.org (Between The Lines Radio Newsmagazine podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">65cb74d6d54643b5aa1fccb2f8a8b60d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/65cb74d6d54643b5aa1fccb2f8a8b60d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>BE THE PEOPLE : 🎧 How to Lower Cost by Unrigging the Rigged Healthcare System</title><description>Many Americans are concerned about the rising cost of healthcare and are looking for ways to cut costs. One way to cut costs and improve the quality and delivery of healthcare is to eliminate the middlemen standing between patients and doctors and hospitals and suppliers. In this episode, I interview Ralph Weber. Weber is a Canadian born entrepreneur, a registered employee benefits consultant, and the founder of Medibid. Medibid is a portal that enables a person or an employee to make an online request for best pricing of a medical procedure. He is also the author of &lt;a href="https://shop.americaoutloud.com/content/rigged-how-insurance-ruined-healthcare-and-how-fix-it" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Rigged: How Insurance Ruined Healthcare (And How to Fix It).&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For Further Insight:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Website: &lt;a href="http://www.medibid.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;www.MediBid.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Book: &lt;a href="https://shop.americaoutloud.com/content/rigged-how-insurance-ruined-healthcare-and-how-fix-it" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Rigged: How Insurance Ruined Healthcare (And How to Fix It).&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><author>speakup@malcolmoutloud.com (BE THE PEOPLE)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0273f105f56d4862a5087d65626cf883</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0273f105f56d4862a5087d65626cf883/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 06:02:22 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Realignment : Ep. 23: Christopher Caldwell, The Age of Entitlement</title><description>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Caldwell's Book, "Age of Entitlement:" &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Age-Entitlement-America-Since-Sixties/dp/1501106899"&gt;https://www.amazon.com/Age-Entitlement-America-Since-Sixties/dp/1501106899&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Caldwell's appearance on Tucker Carlson Tonight: &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/opinion/christopher-caldwell-americas-two-constitutions-competing-visions-of-a-more-perfect-union"&gt;https://www.foxnews.com/opinion/christopher-caldwell-americas-two-constitutions-competing-visions-of-a-more-perfect-union&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>phegseth@hudson.org (The Realignment)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2f0da833763e48ae9c491ef58a64e760</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2f0da833763e48ae9c491ef58a64e760/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 04:00:01 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WFUV's Cityscape : New Life for Obsolete Religious Buildings</title><description>The repurposing of houses of worship has become a trend across the United States. As congregations face dwindling numbers, they’re often left with the choice of selling the buildings they can no longer afford or finding new uses for them. On this week's Cityscape, we’re looking at what happens when a dying church takes on a new life.</description><author>newsroom@wfuv.org (WFUV's Cityscape)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">acc728e651e64dc0a7b7aebf9bd21027</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/acc728e651e64dc0a7b7aebf9bd21027/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC Meet the Press : Wondery presents WeCrashed</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Rise and Fall of WeWork is a stunning story of hope and hubris. WeWork was the poster child for a new economy. Its founders wanted to revolutionize everything about the way people lived their lives. Its charismatic founder Adam Neumann had an intoxicating vision for the company - but did it ever match the reality?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subscribe today:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://wondery.fm/wecrashedMTP" target="_blank"&gt;wondery.fm/wecrashedMTP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>MeetThePress@nbcuni.com (NBC Meet the Press)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2c9f8eb3c7534b3b8b9afd637fa9f057</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2c9f8eb3c7534b3b8b9afd637fa9f057/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Campaign HQ with David Plouffe : Steve Schmidt on New Hampshire and the general</title><description>&lt;p&gt;David explains where the campaigns stand coming out of Iowa’s delayed results as the candidates head to New Hampshire. Then, Steve Schmidt joins David to talk about New Hampshire, a state he knows well and The Lincoln Project, whose mission is to defeat President Trump and Trumpism at the ballot box. Schmidt is a national political strategist who previously worked for President George W. Bush, Senator John McCain and Governor Arnold Schwarzenegger.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@cadence13.com (Campaign HQ with David Plouffe)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c51789b1dc0f4b5f935d439ff10480c6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c51789b1dc0f4b5f935d439ff10480c6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Beating Around The Bush : S3E3Bonus - Nationals leadership - an interview with Sue Middleton</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week's BATB bonus episode: Nationals leadership - an interview with Sue Middleton.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Follow Us:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Join the Rural Business Collective community and join the conversation over at &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/ruralbusinesscollective/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/ruralbusinesscollective/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/ruralbusinesscollective/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Beating Around the Bush is the podcast of the &lt;a href="https://www.ruralbusinesscollective.com.au/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Rural Business Collective&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.ruralbusinesscollective.com.au/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;www.ruralbusinesscollective.com.au&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This is a &lt;a href="https://www.cahootsradio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Cahoots Radio&lt;/a&gt; production edited by Skye Manson &lt;a href="https://www.cahootsradio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;www.cahootsradio.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Hosted by &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/wade-dabinett-947763167" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Wade Dabinett&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/wade-dabinett-947763167/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/in/wade-dabinett-947763167/&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/fleuranderson/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Fleur Anderson&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/fleuranderson/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/in/fleuranderson/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Let us know your favourite news stories for the week on email - &lt;a&gt;podcasts@ruralbusinesscollective.com.au&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>fleur@thecahootsgroup.com.au (Beating Around The Bush)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">36e2a075900d40f9899fe4c586340218</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/36e2a075900d40f9899fe4c586340218/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 21:55:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Latest : What Happened in Iowa?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;After a night of chaos and confusion at the Iowa caucuses, and nearly a full day since the results were initially expected, the state’s Democratic Party has announced only partial numbers, from 62 percent of precincts. We look at what the debacle in Iowa will mean for the results — when they’re finally released.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The Latest,” from the team behind “The Daily,” brings you the most important developments on today’s biggest news stories. You can find more information about it &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/column/the-latest" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (The Latest)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6dd0d3add65341bb916ebf0e64d642ff</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6dd0d3add65341bb916ebf0e64d642ff/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 19:11:10 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Views from Hong Kong : Protests and panic amidst an epidemic</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Welcome to another episode of Views from Hong Kong!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus continues to dominate both the news and our lives here in Hong Kong.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Topics discussed this week include updates on the ongoing epidemic along with discussion of an interesting article posted by the Supreme People's Court of the PRC and a nascent union movement in Hong Kong.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have questions/comments, please write to us at viewshk@outlook.com. We would love to hear from you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow us on twitter @viewshk. Located here: https://twitter.com/viewshk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disclaimer: The views and opinions expressed on the podcast are those of the authors only and do not necessarily reflect the views of any other person or organisation. The authors do not give advice via the podcast and do not warrant or represent the accuracy, completeness, correctness, suitability or validity of any information given on the podcast.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>viewshk@outlook.com (Views from Hong Kong)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2dda7506459c4b9abdc8431c3343ec86</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2dda7506459c4b9abdc8431c3343ec86/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dispatch Podcast : Episode 5: Incompetence</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Sarah, Steve, Jonah, and David take on what went wrong in Iowa and the future of the caucus, the president's third State of the Union address, and the end of the impeachment trial.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>caleb@thedispatch.com (The Dispatch Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b52cfb860c414996ac47e0445449099e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b52cfb860c414996ac47e0445449099e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Beat – CUNY Podcasts : The Rise and Fall of The Young Lords</title><description>&lt;br /&gt;
One of the most influential groups of the radical &amp;#8217;60s was the Young Lords, an organization of poor and working class Puerto Ricans that began as a street gang and rose to confront the racism of institutions from government to religion. Johanna Fernandez, a professor of history at Baruch College, traces their roots and tells the story of their rise and fall in The Young Lords: A Radical History. She talks about it with Beth Harpaz.&lt;br /&gt;</description><author>webservices@cuny.edu (Book Beat – CUNY Podcasts)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3a08a18ca5c748c798258b7d41e858af</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3a08a18ca5c748c798258b7d41e858af/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 15:38:14 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Make Me Smart with Kai and Molly : Do we have to call it the “internet of things”?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#8217;s a whole galaxy of connected items you can buy to ostensibly make your life easier: speakers, locks, coffee mugs, even dog collars. The so-called &amp;#8220;internet of things&amp;#8221; is already big and growing fast. By 2021, the market for all things connected is on track to pass $500 billion. There is no upfront connection or service fee to make these things work; we pay for them with our data. The Economist&amp;#8217;s technology editor, Tim Cross, walks us through privacy concerns, security concerns and 5G.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>makemesmart@marketplace.org (Make Me Smart with Kai and Molly)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bb07116270f249f59d202a4693c37c3b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bb07116270f249f59d202a4693c37c3b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 13:50:12 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Red Box Politics Podcast : Frankly, my dear, I don't give a Dom</title><description>&lt;p&gt;How powerful is the PM’s adviser? Matt Chorley is joined by Steven Swinford, The Times deputy political editor, to assess the waning influence of Dominic Cummings. Plus Matthew Moore, the media correspondent, on crisis at the BBC and Alice Thomson on getting the railways back on track.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>feeds@soundcloud.com (The Red Box Politics Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0fb2a53cf30e4b6b8f13226683dba3c6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0fb2a53cf30e4b6b8f13226683dba3c6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 06:59:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Is This Happening? with Chris Hayes : The Frontlines of Addiction with Beth Macy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This is an intimate portrait of what addiction looks like in America. From the board rooms of pharmaceutical companies to the living rooms across America, Beth Macy traces the path of devastation wrought by opioids. Her latest book, “Dopesick” gives life to the urgency of the epidemic, illustrating just how woefully insufficient the national response has been to the scale of the crisis. She lays out the often-insurmountable barriers that stand between someone suffering and the treatment they need, and why stigma may be the biggest obstacle of them all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RELATED READING:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.indiebound.org/book/9780316551304" target="_blank"&gt;Dopesick: Dealers, Doctors, and the Drug Company that Addicted America&lt;/a&gt; by Beth Macy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://projects.huffingtonpost.com/projects/dying-to-be-free-heroin-treatment#chapter-two" target="_blank"&gt;Dying to Be Free&lt;/a&gt; by Jason Cherkis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.indiebound.org/book/9780062854643" target="_blank"&gt;In Pain: A Bioethicist's Personal Struggle with Opioids&lt;/a&gt; by Travis Rieder&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/outlook/my-friend-and-i-both-took-heroin-he-overdosed-why-was-i-charged-for-his-death/2019/11/26/33ca4826-d965-11e9-bfb1-849887369476_story.html#click=https://t.co/DZYdxH6gtY" target="_blank"&gt;My friend and I both took heroin. He overdosed. Why was I charged with his death?&lt;/a&gt; By Morgan Godvin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;YOU MIGHT ALSO LIKE:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/think/opinion/dying-whiteness-jonathan-metzl-podcast-transcript-ncna987671" target="_blank"&gt;Dying of Whiteness with Jonathan Metzl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>think@nbcuni.com (Why Is This Happening? with Chris Hayes)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e4febdd0e7114522a8ca37ddfe24345b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e4febdd0e7114522a8ca37ddfe24345b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Under-Told: Verbatim : The Sioux Chef’s Seat at the Table</title><description>&lt;p&gt;While training as a chef, Sean Sherman learned French, Italian and other western styles of cooking, but he had no way of knowing what his ancestors ate. So he decided to find out himself. His cookbook, “The Sioux Chef’s Indigenous Kitchen,” won a James Beard award in 2018. Today, he and his partner Dana Thompson run “The Sioux Chef,” a project to revive indigenous traditions in the kitchen and encourage cheaper and healthier eating for everyone. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>undertold@stthomas.edu (Under-Told: Verbatim)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">37714d0a506b4a5c9824c7d059e3270b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/37714d0a506b4a5c9824c7d059e3270b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 12:08:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>UnAborted : When Great Forces Are on the Move | UnAborted Ep. 32</title><description>&lt;p&gt;After a year of momentous political and moral conflict over abortion, 2020 is already poised to be the best and the worst year in the abortion wars. As President Trump helps launch the pro-life movement into 2020 by becoming the first president to attend and speak at the March for Life, pledging his full support to protect every child, the enemies of unborn children become nastier and more committed to destroying both babies and human equality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We will examine the state of the abortion debate through Churchill’s timeless words: “&lt;em&gt;When great forces are on the move in the world, we learn we’re spirits, not animals. There’s something going on in time and space, and beyond time and space, which whether we like it or not, spells duty.&lt;/em&gt;” The conflict of these forces is bringing out the best of one movement and the worst of the other. Will you respond to the call of duty?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Date: 02/03/20&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>seth@prolifetraining.com (UnAborted)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ca5de642e42b43d89ce9b3a2b77d77e9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ca5de642e42b43d89ce9b3a2b77d77e9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 09:17:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hear the Bern : 43 - Yours in Struggle (w/ Barbara Smith)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Is there any term more vilified on the right than "identity politics"? Supposedly, "IDpol" is all about creating hierarchies of oppression, and the lower down the ranks you fall, the less value your voice has.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this episode, Briahna talks to Barbara Smith, who as part of the Combahee River Collective - a radical, black, feminist organization based in Boston - coined the term in the late 1970s. Barbara explains that, far from excluding people, her group meant to include everyone in a common struggle for liberation by recognizing the unique challenges that different groups face. "If Black women were free, it would mean that everyone else would have to be free since our freedom would necessitate the destruction of all the systems of oppression," the group wrote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smith recently endorsed Bernie for president, saying that our campaign and movement carries on the structural, intersectional politics for which she has fought all her life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Barbara Smith is an author, activist, independent scholar, and Nobel Peace Prize nominee. She lives in Albany.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Barbara Smith on Twitter: &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TheBarbaraSmith"&gt;https://twitter.com/TheBarbaraSmith&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hearthebern@berniesanders.com (Hear the Bern)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">439bea8e939e42b3bb49a0afb8d07e54</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/439bea8e939e42b3bb49a0afb8d07e54/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>I'm Calling Bovine Scatology : The Rich Don't Pay Their Fair Share?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It's the favorite talking point from the left. The rich don't pay their fair share. Is it true? Phil Valentine calls bovine scatology on that.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>phil@philvalentine.com (I'm Calling Bovine Scatology)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7004793668554edd914ccc8182a2d5e2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7004793668554edd914ccc8182a2d5e2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 05:46:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Catchup : Ep.55: Super Bowl Indoctrination, Coronavirus Going Viral, and Depositing Sleep Savings</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This episode, John and Denison focus their discussion on mental health, including conversation on the importance of a good night sleep, and finding an anchor one can use to know when they're in a good place. Then, the build-up to the Super Bowl is dominating headlines, as is the Coronavirus. Discussion on whether the hype is warranted on both subjects. It's an all-new Catchup. Join the discussion!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social Media Links:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://Facebook.com/TheCatchupCast"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://Instagram.com/TheCatchupCast"&gt;Instagram&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://Facebook.com/NoSignalRocks"&gt;No Signal FB Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="https://www.facebook.com/TheCatchupCast/"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (https://www.facebook.com/TheCatchupCast/)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>stratocast24@yahoo.com (The Catchup)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">aef378c4a99640eaae34a90b7cb0183b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/aef378c4a99640eaae34a90b7cb0183b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Brown Girls Guide to Politics : What Can We Expect in 2020?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;To learn more about the work of the NAACP Youth &amp; College Division, the League of Conservation Voters and the Planned Parenthood Action Fund, visit their websites:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://naacp.org/youth-college/" target="_blank"&gt;NAACP Youth &amp; College Division&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.lcv.org/" target="_blank"&gt;League of Conservation Voters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.plannedparenthoodaction.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Planned Parenthood Action Fund&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Brown Girls Guide to Politics Podcast is all about amplifying the voices of women who are too often forgotten in media coverage. Host A’shanti Gholar leads conversations with women changing the face of politics. In the BGG to Politics blog, A’shanti created a space for Women of Color to learn about the current state of women in politics, to support others breaking into the political sphere, and to celebrate incredible people changing the course of the country. A’shanti founded the blog and Wonder Media Network is thrilled to extend her platform to audio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow The BGG:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://thebgguide.com/"&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/thebgguide"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://instagram.com/thebgguide"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Wonder Media Network:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://wondermedianetwork.com/"&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/wmnmedia"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://instagram.com/wmn.media"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>pod@wondermedianetwork.com (The Brown Girls Guide to Politics)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e3258dc5b45044b29f0ca651334b0b23</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e3258dc5b45044b29f0ca651334b0b23/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 03:00:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Field : Iowa’s Electability Complex</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With Iowa voters making their choice and the 2020 election getting underway, we’re introducing a new show: one covering the country and its voters in the lead up to Nov. 3. In our first episode of “The Field,” we ask Democratic caucusgoers how they’re feeling about the election. Traveling around the state, we found anxious Iowans asking one question over and over: Who can beat President Trump? &lt;em&gt;Note: This episode contains strong language.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guests: &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/by/astead-w-herndon?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt;Astead W. Herndon&lt;/a&gt;, who covers national politics for The New York Times, and Austin Mitchell and Andy Mills, producers for “The Daily.” For more information on today’s episode, visit nytimes.com/thedaily.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background reading:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Confused by the Iowa caucuses?&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/01/31/us/politics/what-is-iowa-caucus.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; Here’s how they work&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The New York Times polled 584 Democrats likely to caucus in Iowa. Fifteen of them agreed to talk to us on camera.&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/01/30/us/politics/iowa-poll-voters.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; Here is what they told us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The state with a huge influence in picking presidential candidates doesn’t look much like the country as a whole, except in one very striking way:&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/02/us/politics/iowa-economy-2020.html?smid=pc-thedaily" target="_blank"&gt; a rapidly aging population&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (The Field)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b89e9f0273024c4bbfe39812255d2031</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b89e9f0273024c4bbfe39812255d2031/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 02:53:16 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>So You Wanna Be President? with Chris Matthews : 3 - The Walls Have Ears</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The country is always listening. Put another way: Don't say something you don't want every voter to hear.&amp;nbsp;On this episode, Chris Matthews&amp;nbsp;remember the candidates who forgot this lesson—and paid the price—with Susan Page, Washington Bureau Chief for USA Today, and author and historian Michael&amp;nbsp;Beschloss.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (So You Wanna Be President? with Chris Matthews)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">58e556a1ccca48f9a86d92a035f5e301</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/58e556a1ccca48f9a86d92a035f5e301/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Reasons to be Cheerful with Ed Miliband and Geoff Lloyd : 124. I'LL HAVE MY CHICKEN UNCHLORINATED PLEASE; a progressive vision for trade</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hello! Now we’ve left the EU, Britain will have an independent trade policy for the first time in decades. We ask Ruth Bergan from the Trade Justice Movement and Nicola Smith from the TUC what progressives should be calling for in future trade deals. Then Todd Tucker explains what we can learn from the trade debate amongst Democrats in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AND food writer and campaigner Jack Monroe chats about being vegan(ish)&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>reasons@cheerfulpodcast.com (Reasons to be Cheerful with Ed Miliband and Geoff Lloyd)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2c9bf40447d648ab8b57c3592765eac3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2c9bf40447d648ab8b57c3592765eac3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>AM Joy : Buttigieg addresses Des Moines Register poll, policing record</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Pete Buttigieg in Iowa on Sunday addressed the Des Moines Register poll being withdrawn right before the Iowa caucuses, reportedly because his name was left out during at least one polling call. The 2020 Democratic presidential candidate and former mayor of South Bend, Indiana also joins Joy Reid to discuss his record on policing, the inclusive meaning behind Buttigieg’s appeal to "heartland voters," and much more. And: Billionaires Mike Bloomberg and Tom Steyer are competing for the moderate vote in Iowa against Joe Biden, Pete Buttigieg, and Amy Klobuchar. How will the nicknamed ‘billionaire wing’ of the Democratic party fare in the Hawkeye State, particularly against progressives? Joy Reid and her panel discuss. Plus: The Iowa caucuses are upon us. The 2020 Democratic presidential field presents an unusual divide to voters of the Hawkeye State, between progressive candidates who rely on small donations, and self-funded billionaires dominating the airwaves will campaign ads. Tim O’Brien, senior advisor to billionaire Mike Bloomberg’s 2020 presidential campaign, joins Joy Reid to discuss.&amp;nbsp; Then: Michael Bloomberg "was the single biggest donor to women running in vulnerable districts in the 2018 midterms," senior advisor to Mike Bloomberg’s 2020 presidential campaign Tim O’Brien tells Joy Reid. Joy Reid and her panel discuss Bloomberg pouring money into downballot races and get out the vote efforts, versus the perception that he is “buying” his way into the 2020 Democratic presidential race. Finally: MSNBC's Trymaine Lee interview voters of color in Iowa for their views on the 2020 Democratic candidates, and more. All this and more in this Sunday edition of AM JOY on MSNBC.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (AM Joy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">937ed20b71fd4f9a925e08025ca2429f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/937ed20b71fd4f9a925e08025ca2429f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 11:15:27 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FOX News Sunday Audio Podcast : 2-2-2020 - FOX News Sunday Audio Podcast</title><description>&lt;p&gt;2-2-2020 - FOX News Sunday Audio Podcast&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@foxnewsradio.com (FOX News Sunday Audio Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6357935ff5fa4d40a78673fea6433e72</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6357935ff5fa4d40a78673fea6433e72/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 11:09:52 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Al Franken Podcast : John Mayer on Playing Guitar and Singing at the Same Time</title><description>&lt;p&gt;John Mayer talks about how he transitioned from pop star/tabloid fodder (recurrent Sexiest Man Alive) to the impossible challenge of filling Jerry Garcia’s gigantic shoes with Dead and Company, the current iteration of the Grateful Dead. (If you guessed Al is a big Dead Head, you might be right).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plus, an angry Al vents about the week's impeachment news.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>paulwoodywoodhull@gmail.com (The Al Franken Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ac5d6d3375634606987b486dfaa4f349</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ac5d6d3375634606987b486dfaa4f349/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Candace Owens Show : The Candace Owens Show: Tim Ballard</title><description>Slavery is alive and well today. Human trafficking is a booming business that is being propelled by both the powerful and our on-demand sexualized culture. Tim Ballard, former special agent and founder of Operation Underground Railroad, joins Candace to discuss how society aids this multi-billion-dollar criminal enterprise.</description><author>tylerg@prageru.com (The Candace Owens Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ff77bf7eb035405ebfe6932588ef64cc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ff77bf7eb035405ebfe6932588ef64cc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 02:00:20 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Amicus With Dahlia Lithwick | Law, Justice, and the Courts : Election Meltdown, Part 2</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the second part of a special five-part series of Amicus, Dahlia Lithwick is joined by election law professor Rick Hasen to take a close look at what happened with Michigan’s failed recounts in 2016, exploring how small mistakes can cause big problems in elections, and why democratic areas seem much more prone to incompetence in election administration. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rick Hasen’s new book &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/0300248199/?tag=slatmaga-20"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Election Meltdown&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;forms the basis for this special series of Amicus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join Slate for the &lt;a href="https://slate.com/live/amicus-live-w-dahlia-lithwick-andrew-gillum-and-more.html"&gt;Election Meltdown live show&lt;/a&gt; on Feb. 19 in Washington. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Podcast production by Sara Burningham.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>amicus@slate.com (Amicus With Dahlia Lithwick | Law, Justice, and the Courts)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">52ae54646528440e816e91fdc861e622</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/52ae54646528440e816e91fdc861e622/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hot Take : Jan 2020: No Chill</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The first month of 2020 proves that the climate story has no chill at all. From the Australian bushfires to big important stories on everything from climate vision to radiioactive fracking, the story just keeps getting bigger and crazier. Special guest co-host Meera Subramanian joins Mary and Amy to break it all down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;About Meera: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Meera Subramanian is an award-winning freelance journalist whose work has been published around the world, and her first book is &lt;em&gt;A River Runs Again: India’s Natural World in Crisis&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;from the Barren Cliffs of Rajasthan to the Farmlands of Karnatak&lt;/em&gt;a, published in 2015 by PublicAffairs. She is currently serving as the president of the Society of Environmental Journalists and the Currie C. and Thomas A. Barron Visiting Professor in the Environment and the Humanities at Princeton University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Reading list:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;United in Change, Meera Subramanian &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://orionmagazine.org/article/united-in-change/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://orionmagazine.org/article/united-in-change/&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s Not Just Australia, Rachel Ramirez&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://t.co/xCu8Qh7LUn?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/xCu8Qh7LUn?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;‘Scarier’ Than Hurricane Maria: A Deadly Earthquake Terrifies Puerto Rico&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://t.co/Gwlecq5FhV?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/Gwlecq5FhV?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At the 7th Democratic debate, candidates took every opportunity to talk climate, Zoya Tierstein &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://grist.org/politics/at-the-7th-democratic-debate-candidates-took-every-opportunity-to-talk-climate/"&gt;https://grist.org/politics/at-the-7th-democratic-debate-candidates-took-every-opportunity-to-talk-climate/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For the first time, the Alarmed are now the largest of Global Warming’s Six Americas &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://climatecommunication.yale.edu/publications/for-the-first-time-the-alarmed-are-now-the-largest-of-global-warmings-six-americas/"&gt;https://climatecommunication.yale.edu/publications/for-the-first-time-the-alarmed-are-now-the-largest-of-global-warmings-six-americas/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Emily Townsend's Resignation Email &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/media/2020/jan/10/news-corp-employee-climate-misinformation-bushfire-coverage-email"&gt;https://www.theguardian.com/media/2020/jan/10/news-corp-employee-climate-misinformation-bushfire-coverage-email&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We, the Media, must take some of the blame as Australia Burns&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;John Birmingham&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://t.co/eIp4YB9aOO?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/eIp4YB9aOO?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It's Not Arson, You Absolute Fucking Morons, Brian Kahn &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://earther.gizmodo.com/its-not-arson-you-absolute-fucking-morons-1840862475"&gt;https://earther.gizmodo.com/its-not-arson-you-absolute-fucking-morons-1840862475&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pregnant Women are Asking for Ultrasounds in Australia, Gina Rushton&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://t.co/XUTwPTsdWp?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/XUTwPTsdWp?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Concession to Climate Change I Will Not Make in the Atlantic, Jedediah Britton-Purdy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/01/becoming-parent-age-climate-crisis/604372/?utm_source=twitter&amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;utm_campaign=share"&gt;https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/01/becoming-parent-age-climate-crisis/604372/?utm_source=twitter&amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;utm_campaign=share&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noah’s Rainbow , James Murray&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.businessgreen.com/blog-post/3084916/noahs-rainbow-raising-children-in-an-age-of-climate-crisis"&gt;https://www.businessgreen.com/blog-post/3084916/noahs-rainbow-raising-children-in-an-age-of-climate-crisis&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon’s New Rationale for Working with Big Oil: Saving the Planet, Maddie Stone&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://t.co/kf8UxXdsrJ?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/kf8UxXdsrJ?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google and Amazon Are Now in the Oil Business, Adam Cole:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/recode/2020/1/3/21030688/google-amazon-ai-oil-gas"&gt;https://www.vox.com/recode/2020/1/3/21030688/google-amazon-ai-oil-gas&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;David Roberts, The Sad Truth About Our Boldest Climate Target &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/energy-and-environment/2020/1/3/21045263/climate-change-1-5-degrees-celsius-target-ipcc"&gt;https://www.vox.com/energy-and-environment/2020/1/3/21045263/climate-change-1-5-degrees-celsius-target-ipcc&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diego Arguedas Ortiz, Is It Wrong to be Hopeful About Climate Change? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://t.co/1Heh58QNcQ?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/1Heh58QNcQ?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking to the Future: In 2030, We Ended the Climate Emergency. Here’s How, Eric Holthaus &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://thecorrespondent.com/214/in-2030-we-ended-the-climate-emergency-heres-how/28330740746-6b15af77"&gt;https://thecorrespondent.com/214/in-2030-we-ended-the-climate-emergency-heres-how/28330740746-6b15af77&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Year in Climate Conversations, Emily Raboteau&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://t.co/UDePWvCr4L?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/UDePWvCr4L?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Baby Boomers: You Can Still Be Heroes in the Story of Climate Change, Laura McGann: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2020/1/8/21055097/baby-boomers-climate-change-australia"&gt;https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2020/1/8/21055097/baby-boomers-climate-change-australia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;STAND OUT PIECES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meera: What Climate Change Tells Us about Being Human by Genevieve Gunther &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://blogs.scientificamerican.com/observations/what-climate-change-tells-us-about-being-human/"&gt;https://blogs.scientificamerican.com/observations/what-climate-change-tells-us-about-being-human/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mary: Here Comes the Sun was an Anthem of Hope, Now It’s a Reminder of Climate Change, Amy Brady: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://t.co/8uA55iCI2M?amp=1"&gt;https://t.co/8uA55iCI2M?amp=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amy: America’s Radioactive Secret, by Justin Nobel &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-features/oil-gas-fracking-radioactive-investigation-937389/"&gt;https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-features/oil-gas-fracking-radioactive-investigation-937389/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>amy@criticalfrequency.org (Hot Take)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5eb0206d09c04bdbbab3a82c19100a5b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5eb0206d09c04bdbbab3a82c19100a5b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>HYPAT med Jennifer &amp; Julia : 2.3 Panikknapp på dejter och hur du tacklar kritik</title><description>&lt;p&gt;I veckans avsnitt rapporterar Julia vidare om Coronaviruset. Finns det ännu ett vaccin och var i världen är det som farligast just nu? Hon pratar också om Tinders nya panikknapp där du kan alarmera om något farligt händer under en dejt. Jennifer gör en djupdykning i Finlands nya lag där du får parkera på fel(!) sida om vägen och skillnaden mellan ekologiskt och GMO-odlad mat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Förutom nyheter diskuterar vi kritik och hur man själv ger feedback på ett bra sätt! Hur tacklar man negativ feedback? Finns det något sätt att bli mindre känslig för kommentarer och utsätts vi själv för sånt i jobbet? Det här och mycket mera i dagens avsnitt av HYPAT!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instagram: @hypatpodcast @hipsterjefe @juliahqvist&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jennifer.carp@ymail.com (HYPAT med Jennifer &amp; Julia)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">02189137eac149ac960ba8813ad04514</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/02189137eac149ac960ba8813ad04514/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Rick &amp; Bubba University Podcast : Ep 17 | An Unexpected Decade | Guest: Michael 'Helmsey' Helms</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, Rick &amp;amp; Bubba visit with teammate Michael Helms, aka "Helmsey." Find out how he met the guys and became one of the on-air personalities on the show.&amp;nbsp; From his completely unexpected path into radio and television to the creation of the "Kickoff Hour," it's been a unique journey of more than a decade on America&amp;rsquo;s favorite radio show.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@theblaze.com (Rick &amp; Bubba University Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f9cc314f059d47ccb5928df4c2777141</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f9cc314f059d47ccb5928df4c2777141/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Impeachment, Explained : The impeachment trial convicted American politics</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This episode, likely the final episode of this podcast, is a bit different: It’s a look not just at what happened this week, but at the deep lessons of impeachment, and the unresolved conflicts and contradictions we’re left with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Put simply, the Senate will acquit Donald Trump. But in refusing to even hear witnesses, they have convicted American politics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Want to contact the show? Reach out at &lt;a href="mailto:ezrakleinshow@vox.com"&gt;ezrakleinshow@vox.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ezra's book is available for pre-order! You can find it at &lt;a href="http://simonandschusterpublishing.com/why-were-polarized/"&gt;www.EzraKlein.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can subscribe to Ezra's other podcast &lt;em&gt;The Ezra Klein Show &lt;/em&gt;on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-ezra-klein-show/id1081584611"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/6NOJ6IkTb2GWMj1RpmtnxP"&gt;Spotify,&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.stitcher.com/podcast/vox/the-ezra-klein-show"&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; or wherever you get your podcasts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Credits: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Host - Ezra Klein&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Producer/Editor - Jeff Geld&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researcher - Roge Karma&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theme Music - Jon Natchez&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EP - Liz Nelson&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Special thanks to Andrew Prokop and Matt Yglesias&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasting@voxmedia.com (Impeachment, Explained)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1cdcb868687847dfb31408013354e7ff</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1cdcb868687847dfb31408013354e7ff/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MEDIA INDIGENA : Indigenous current affairs : Ep. 195: 'The Power Was With Us: Idle No More' (Pt. 2)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;THIS WEEK: Part 2 of our discussion on APTN’s new retrospective docuseries, “&lt;a href= "https://aptnnews.ca/thepowerwaswithus/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;The Power Was With Us&lt;/a&gt;: Idle No More.” Picking up where Kim, Candis and Rick left off &lt;a href= "http://mediaindigena.libsyn.com/ep-194-the-power-was-with-us-idle-no-more-pt-1" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;last episode&lt;/a&gt;—when they discussed the movement’s genesis—this time ‘round, Ken Williams (assistant professor, University of Alberta department of drama) and Brock Pitawanakwat (York University Associate Professor of Indigenous Studies) join Rick to explore the various crossroads confronting the different parties active at the time—and the consequences of their choices. To watch the series (co-directed and co-produced for APTN National News by Mr. Harp and Tim Fontaine), stream it via APTN’s Lumi service. To do so, visit &lt;a href="https://aptnlumi.ca/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;aptnlumi.ca&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;// Our theme is'nesting' by birocratic.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>indigena.group@gmail.com (MEDIA INDIGENA : Indigenous current affairs)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3aabe8a4e0624465963142e6ec83f225</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3aabe8a4e0624465963142e6ec83f225/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 15:45:29 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Asset : What's Next?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Max Bergmann, the host of the Asset Podcast, assesses the Impeachment Trial to date and handicaps what's ahead, as the end of Donald Trump's trial before the Senate looms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To hear the full episode, become a Patreon subscriber. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://www.patreon.com/posts/33614330&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@theassetpodcast.org (The Asset)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">52107dbf8c13443590b57ff7d8215756</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/52107dbf8c13443590b57ff7d8215756/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 08:26:43 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Trending Stories Taking Over podcast | T.S.T.O. : 019 | Kobe crash, Rogan canceled, Bieber fever, WARM + FUZZY!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Watch the full episode: https://youtu.be/DIAqTF6sUt0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is HAPPENING people of the interwebs?!?! &amp;nbsp;In this episode of the Trending Stories Taking Over show we peek in on the Impeachment trial, talk about the Kobe tragedy, Rogan being canceled, how much Jake LOVE Justin Beiber, and warm, fuzzy coffee. &amp;nbsp;ENJOY!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't forget about the giveaway: https://bit.ly/2RJDrBM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Todd + Jake&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/tsto/message</description><author>tstoshow@gmail.com (The Trending Stories Taking Over podcast | T.S.T.O.)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e0e178968d55488b96225f452905d265</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e0e178968d55488b96225f452905d265/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 01:09:20 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Choice : It's Not Our Choice To Make</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The board weighs the pros and cons of each Democratic primary candidate, and has a heated debate over what the party (and the country) needs in this moment. Katie reveals her choices, and argues why the 2020 primary is the moment that voters - not the editorial board - gets to decide the future of the Democratic party. Then, the world reacts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Find the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/01/13/opinion/election-nytimes-the-choice.html" target="_blank"&gt;unabridged and annotated transcript of the candidates's visits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to the board at nytimes.com/endorsements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produced by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://atwill.us/" target="_blank"&gt;At Will Media&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>opinionpodcasts@nytimes.com (The Choice)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">40e82932db324e8e96bd2be105f148f9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/40e82932db324e8e96bd2be105f148f9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 20:50:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The SCNS Live Podcast : SCNS Live Season 9 Episode 2: News on Transformers, Picard, Nintendo, Anime, and more</title><description>&lt;p&gt;So much news to cover this week guys. Thanks for joining us and chat along with the show. #News #Podcast #SCNSLive&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>admin@untitledscns.com (The SCNS Live Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7aec4cbb9e1f4047aefbe936c4a98898</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7aec4cbb9e1f4047aefbe936c4a98898/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 20:01:37 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Brendan O'Neill Show : Gisela Stuart: Brexit and belonging</title><description>&lt;p&gt;To mark Brexit Day, former Vote Leave chair Gisela Stuart sits down with Brendan to discuss the future of an independent Britain. Support spiked by becoming a regular donor: &lt;a href='https://www.spiked-online.com/donate-to-spiked/'&gt;https://www.spiked-online.com/donate-to-spiked/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thebrendanoneillshow@spiked-online.com (The Brendan O'Neill Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3aa2ddedac124b808ab7307f1ab45989</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3aa2ddedac124b808ab7307f1ab45989/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 15:24:20 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Overwatch : Putin Begins New Phase in Campaign to Retain Power</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Vladimir Putin's current term as Russia's President expires in 2024. Over the past two weeks, Putin reshuffled Russia's government, proposed a set of major changes to the Russian constitution, and pledged significant social spending. ISW's Russia Team Lead Nataliya Bugayova describes how this reshuffling fits into Putin's ongoing campaign to retain power and the subsequent vulnerabilities Putin will face as he manages this transition. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>press@understandingwar.org (Overwatch)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">576129b05aed462c970bbd469d2ae1c9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/576129b05aed462c970bbd469d2ae1c9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 13:51:14 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>DriveTimes Podcast : Episode 14: Elephants, Mangos, and the Chamber of Secrets</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Come one come all to the next episode of the DriveTimes podcast where 2 dads discuss funny, interesting, and good story from throughout the week to give you some hope in life. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thedadbodsshow@gmail.com (DriveTimes Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">df9a97ebd6694825b1e210232b67ed9a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/df9a97ebd6694825b1e210232b67ed9a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 11:47:16 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Gettysburg Connection Podcast : It’s Tick Season in Adams County: How to Stay Safe from Lyme Disease [Episode 21]</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You probably know about Lyme Disease and you know that you can get it locally from deer ticks. But do you know that you that the most active season for those ticks is right now – in the middle of winter?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone  wp-image-21717" src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/stephanie_summers.jpg" alt="" width="390" height="488" srcset="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/stephanie_summers.jpg 941w, https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/stephanie_summers-240x300.jpg 240w, https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/stephanie_summers-819x1024.jpg 819w, https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/stephanie_summers-768x960.jpg 768w, https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/stephanie_summers-400x500.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 390px) 100vw, 390px" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this episode I talk with Stephanie Summers who is Adams County’s Mosquito Borne Disease Control &amp;amp; Conservation Technician. Her job is to keep an eye on disease-causing insects in the county, including mosquitos and ticks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stephanie talks about how to the county helps keep these insects under control and how you can stay safe from Lyme disease and West Nile Virus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class='photonic-wp-stream photonic-stream ' id='photonic-wp-stream-1'&gt;
&lt;ul id='photonic-wp-stream-1-container' class='title-display-tooltip photonic-level-1-container photonic-standard-layout photonic-thumbnail-effect-none' data-photonic-stream-total="5" data-photonic-stream-start="1" data-photonic-stream-end="5" data-photonic-stream-per-page="-1" data-photonic-stream-provider="wp" data-photonic-stream-query="order=ASC&amp;amp;orderby=post__in&amp;amp;id=21711&amp;amp;itemtag=figure&amp;amp;icontag=div&amp;amp;captiontag=figcaption&amp;amp;columns=1&amp;amp;size=thumbnail&amp;amp;include=21716,21715,21714,21713,21712&amp;amp;exclude=&amp;amp;link=&amp;amp;layout=square&amp;amp;more=&amp;amp;display=in-page&amp;amp;panel=&amp;amp;filter=&amp;amp;filter_type=include&amp;amp;fx=slide&amp;amp;timeout=4000&amp;amp;speed=1000&amp;amp;pause=1&amp;amp;strip-style=thumbs&amp;amp;controls=show&amp;amp;popup=hide&amp;amp;custom_classes=&amp;amp;alignment=&amp;amp;caption=title&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;count=-1&amp;amp;thumb_width=75&amp;amp;thumb_height=75&amp;amp;thumb_size=large&amp;amp;slide_size=large&amp;amp;slideshow_height=500&amp;amp;type=default&amp;amp;style=square&amp;amp;ids=21716,21715,21714,21713,21712&amp;amp;main_size=large"  data-photonic-gallery-columns="1"&gt;
&lt;li class="photonic-wp-image photonic-wp-photo photonic-gallery-1c photonic-level-1 photonic-thumb photonic-thumb-square"&gt;
			&lt;a  class='photonic-launch-gallery launch-gallery-swipebox swipebox'  rel='lightbox-photonic-wp-stream-1'  href="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/IMG_20200121_103603-768x1024.jpg" title="IMG_20200121_103603" data-title="&amp;lt;a href=&amp;#039;https://gettysburgconnection.org/its-tick-season-in-adams-county-how-to-stay-safe-from-lymes-disease-episode-21/img_20200121_103603/#main&amp;#039; &amp;gt;IMG_20200121_103603&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;" data-photonic-tooltip="IMG_20200121_103603"   data-photonic-media-type="image"   data-photonic-deep="gallery[photonic-wp-stream-1]/21716/" &gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;img alt="IMG_20200121_103603" src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/IMG_20200121_103603-768x1024.jpg"  class='square' /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;			&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="photonic-wp-image photonic-wp-photo photonic-gallery-1c photonic-level-1 photonic-thumb photonic-thumb-square"&gt;
			&lt;a  class='photonic-launch-gallery launch-gallery-swipebox swipebox'  rel='lightbox-photonic-wp-stream-1'  href="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/IMG_20200121_103531-1024x768.jpg" title="IMG_20200121_103531" data-title="&amp;lt;a href=&amp;#039;https://gettysburgconnection.org/its-tick-season-in-adams-county-how-to-stay-safe-from-lymes-disease-episode-21/img_20200121_103531/#main&amp;#039; &amp;gt;IMG_20200121_103531&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;" data-photonic-tooltip="IMG_20200121_103531"   data-photonic-media-type="image"   data-photonic-deep="gallery[photonic-wp-stream-1]/21715/" &gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;img alt="IMG_20200121_103531" src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/IMG_20200121_103531-1024x768.jpg"  class='square' /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;			&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="photonic-wp-image photonic-wp-photo photonic-gallery-1c photonic-level-1 photonic-thumb photonic-thumb-square"&gt;
			&lt;a  class='photonic-launch-gallery launch-gallery-swipebox swipebox'  rel='lightbox-photonic-wp-stream-1'  href="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/IMG_20200121_100321-768x1024.jpg" title="IMG_20200121_100321" data-title="&amp;lt;a href=&amp;#039;https://gettysburgconnection.org/its-tick-season-in-adams-county-how-to-stay-safe-from-lymes-disease-episode-21/img_20200121_100321/#main&amp;#039; &amp;gt;IMG_20200121_100321&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;" data-photonic-tooltip="IMG_20200121_100321"   data-photonic-media-type="image"   data-photonic-deep="gallery[photonic-wp-stream-1]/21714/" &gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;img alt="IMG_20200121_100321" src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/IMG_20200121_100321-768x1024.jpg"  class='square' /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;			&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="photonic-wp-image photonic-wp-photo photonic-gallery-1c photonic-level-1 photonic-thumb photonic-thumb-square"&gt;
			&lt;a  class='photonic-launch-gallery launch-gallery-swipebox swipebox'  rel='lightbox-photonic-wp-stream-1'  href="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/IMG_20200121_100315-768x1024.jpg" title="IMG_20200121_100315" data-title="&amp;lt;a href=&amp;#039;https://gettysburgconnection.org/its-tick-season-in-adams-county-how-to-stay-safe-from-lymes-disease-episode-21/img_20200121_100315/#main&amp;#039; &amp;gt;IMG_20200121_100315&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;" data-photonic-tooltip="IMG_20200121_100315"   data-photonic-media-type="image"   data-photonic-deep="gallery[photonic-wp-stream-1]/21713/" &gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;img alt="IMG_20200121_100315" src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/IMG_20200121_100315-768x1024.jpg"  class='square' /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;			&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="photonic-wp-image photonic-wp-photo photonic-gallery-1c photonic-level-1 photonic-thumb photonic-thumb-square"&gt;
			&lt;a  class='photonic-launch-gallery launch-gallery-swipebox swipebox'  rel='lightbox-photonic-wp-stream-1'  href="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/IMG_20200121_100308-768x1024.jpg" title="IMG_20200121_100308" data-title="&amp;lt;a href=&amp;#039;https://gettysburgconnection.org/its-tick-season-in-adams-county-how-to-stay-safe-from-lymes-disease-episode-21/img_20200121_100308/#main&amp;#039; &amp;gt;IMG_20200121_100308&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;" data-photonic-tooltip="IMG_20200121_100308"   data-photonic-media-type="image"   data-photonic-deep="gallery[photonic-wp-stream-1]/21712/" &gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;img alt="IMG_20200121_100308" src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/IMG_20200121_100308-768x1024.jpg"  class='square' /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;			&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;!-- ./photonic-level-1-container --&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span id='photonic-wp-stream-1-container-end'&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- .photonic-stream or .photonic-panel --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mail@gettysburgconnection.org (Gettysburg Connection Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1306f0fabfa743d48925c6ee6f713859</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1306f0fabfa743d48925c6ee6f713859/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 11:13:12 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Armstrong Simms Show : Coach K and Twitter Trends</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Armstrong discusses Coach K screaming at his OWN student section, and decides to comment on the day's Twitter Trends. Join me!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts44+e7b59a4@anchor.fm (The Armstrong Simms Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b2c5a240c29a4d42a54fd906f10902fc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b2c5a240c29a4d42a54fd906f10902fc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 15:02:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Australia in the World : Ep. 39: The 2020 Raisina Dialogue</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Allan and Darren try something different this episode, with Allan taking the lead in asking Darren about his experience attending the Raisina Dialogue, India’s flagship international affairs conference, held in New Delhi from 14-16 January 2020, and organised the Observer Research Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The conversation begins with an introduction to Raisina and comparisons with the Shangri-La Dialogue. Allan then asks Darren what his major takeaways were, starting with the current strategic debate in India. The conversation then moves to the often-fraught Sino-Indian relationship, before turning to the recent controversies inside India regarding the status of Muslims—how were these handled at the Dialogue? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From an Australian perspective, Prime Minister Scott Morrison was scheduled to give the keynote address, but had to cancel to remain in Australia to oversee the bushfire response. Nevertheless, Foreign Minister Marise Payne led a sizeable Australian contingent, and Darren offers some impressions regarding how Australian diplomats manage a foreign minister’s visit. Darren finishes with some personal reflections on the event and whether it changed his thinking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, we invite our listeners to email us at this address: &lt;a href='mailto:australia.world.pod@gmail.com'&gt;australia.world.pod@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; We welcome feedback, requests and suggestions. You can also contact Darren on twitter @limdarrenj&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to AIIA intern Isabel Hancock for research and audio editing and Rory Stenning for composing our theme music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Relevant links&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Observer Research Foundation, Raisina Dialogue homepage: &lt;a href='https://www.orfonline.org/raisina-dialogue/'&gt;https://www.orfonline.org/raisina-dialogue/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Videos of Raisina Dialogue 2020 Panels:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inaugural panel (including Stephen Harper): &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HZjUoIwDeTg'&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HZjUoIwDeTg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interview with Dr S. Jaishankar, Indian External Affairs Minister: &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KufSx9RW-q0'&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KufSx9RW-q0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Panel “Hacking Democracy: Defending Pluralism in the Digital Age” (including Stephen Harper and Marietje Schaake): &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vqtgZwwsGHY'&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vqtgZwwsGHY&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Panel “Plural Waters: Strengthening Democracy in the Indo-Pacific” (including Ram Madhav, BJP General Secretary): &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=byINgxdHSYc'&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=byINgxdHSYc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Final panel “Coalitions and Consensus: In Defense of Values that Matter” (including Foreign Minister Marise Payne and Deputy National Security Adviser Matt Pottinger): &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gotKrQTVKQ4'&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gotKrQTVKQ4&lt;/a&gt;    &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interview with Javad Zarif, Iranian Foreign Minister: &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yHIqnQHvrXY'&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yHIqnQHvrXY&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PM Scott Morrison’s Message for Raisina Dialogue 2020: &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YM023sUFvwg'&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YM023sUFvwg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Darren Lim, “Scott Morrison wasn’t at the Raisina Dialogue, but his ideas were”, Lowy Interpreter, 29 January 2019: &lt;a href='https://www.lowyinstitute.org/the-interpreter/scott-morrison-wasn-t-raisina-dialogue-his-ideas-were'&gt;https://www.lowyinstitute.org/the-interpreter/scott-morrison-wasn-t-raisina-dialogue-his-ideas-were&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>australia.world.pod@gmail.com (Australia in the World)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4ab7031cdc21408aa2753ba619247358</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4ab7031cdc21408aa2753ba619247358/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 11:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>bonkers.ie  : bonkers.ie Looks Closer: So you're approaching retirement age? Here's what you need to know.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A person who’s approaching retirement today, could, theoretically, spend almost as much time in retirement as they did while working. Which means retirement planning is something that needs to be taken seriously and considered carefully. So, in this episode of our Looks Closer series, we chat with Moneycube Co-Founder and Chief Financial Advisor to get the lowdown on what you need to know as you approach your golden years.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts44+e2b7d1c@anchor.fm (bonkers.ie )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4ce724d97fd646f5a216af94914b8306</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4ce724d97fd646f5a216af94914b8306/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 07:18:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Capitol J : Episode 2 - Reporting From The Center Of The EU</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Mark, Joe and Sara talk about their press visit to Brussels, Belgium to learn about the European Union and its institutions, sponsored by the EU Delegation to the United States. &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">f74215de9fa04560a9b0ac3d3a3c5588</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f74215de9fa04560a9b0ac3d3a3c5588/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 09:21:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Daily Bernie Podcast : Hillary Attacks Bernie as he Surges in the Polls</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Daily Bernie podcast is a short-form podcast to give the daily news about Bernie Sanders 2020 campaign and related news about progressive issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In today’s episode we discuss these headlines: Hillary Attacks Bernie as he Surges in the Polls; Bernie is 1st in Iowa and other states; Krystal Ball defends Bernie on CNN&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related links:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/ilikebernie-trends-after-hillary-clinton-says-nobody-likes-bernie-sanders-1483273"&gt;#ILIKEBERNIE TRENDS AFTER HILLARY CLINTON SAYS 'NOBODY LIKES' BERNIE SANDERS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/sanders-reacts-to-hillary-clintons-attack-says-on-a-good-day-my-wife-likes-me?via=twitter_page"&gt;Sanders Responds to Hillary Clinton’s Attack: ‘On a Good Day, My Wife Likes Me’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/480101-poll-sanders-leads-by-13-percentage-points-in-utah"&gt;Leading by 9 in New Iowa Poll, Sanders Says His Campaign Is 'Worst Nightmare' of Trump and Billionaire Class&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/oh-my-god-sanders-can-win-democrats-grapple-bernie-surge-n1123806"&gt;'Oh my God, Sanders can win': Democrats grapple with Bernie surge in Iowa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/480101-poll-sanders-leads-by-13-percentage-points-in-utah"&gt;Poll: Sanders up 13 points in Utah&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/22/politics/cnn-poll-sanders-biden-january-national/index.html"&gt;CNN poll: Bernie Sanders surges to join Biden atop Democratic presidential pack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Support the podcast!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Support the Daily Bernie podcast on Patreon: &lt;a href="http://patreon.com/dailyberniepod"&gt;http://patreon.com/dailyberniepod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Twitter: &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/TheDailyBernie"&gt;http://twitter.com/TheDailyBernie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Facebook: &lt;a href="http://facebook.com/dailyberniepod"&gt;http://facebook.com/dailyberniepod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Instagram: &lt;a href="http://instagram.com/dailyberniepod"&gt;http://instagram.com/dailyberniepod&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Website: &lt;a href="http://www.dailyberniepod.com/"&gt;http://www.dailyberniepod.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can find our podcast on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-daily-bernie-podcast/id1493033686?uo=4"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/0kh8ZxeLAgW1y6tjWx5mlS"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, and other podcast apps! Remember to rate, review, and subscribe!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Music:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Music from https://filmmusic.io&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;"Limit 70" by Kevin MacLeod (https://incompetech.com)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;License: CC BY (&lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/"&gt;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="http://patreon.com/dailybernpod"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (http://patreon.com/dailybernpod)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>dailyberniepod@gmail.com (The Daily Bernie Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e818288dfdbc4b578d43c28618f0d316</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e818288dfdbc4b578d43c28618f0d316/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Full Frontal Honesty in Real Estate  : Phoenix Real Estate Rising</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Phoenix real estate values headed upward, what are the wholesalers all about, and &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sam Smith&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; stops by to talk real estate.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts37+b93548@anchor.fm (Full Frontal Honesty in Real Estate )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">18ff0f0dc7cd4501a40e3b8a01b68e17</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/18ff0f0dc7cd4501a40e3b8a01b68e17/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 21:35:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>BTS with CTV News Vancouver : Flight 752: Finding &amp; Telling the Victims' Stories</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The world was shocked when a Ukrainian Airlines flight went down near Tehran, but when officials confirmed dozens of Canadians were on board our nation was stunned -- as journalists sprang into action to tell the stories of the innocent lives taken too soon. With so many &lt;a href="https://bc.ctvnews.ca/sorry-we-lost-you-grief-stricken-canadians-react-to-cause-of-plane-crash-1.4763547"&gt;victims in the Lower Mainland&lt;/a&gt;, CTV Vancouver journalists were inundated with heart-wrenching stories as communities mourned the tragedy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bc.ctvnews.ca/bts-podcast"&gt;BTS with CTV&lt;/a&gt; Vancouver host &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/PennyDaflos"&gt;Penny Daflos&lt;/a&gt; and reporter &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ctv_shannon"&gt;Shannon Paterson&lt;/a&gt; describe the difficult steps in finding the loved ones left behind, then respectfully conveying the loss felt by their families, friends, and communities. This is, quite simply, one of the toughest jobs reporters have, but they are often a welcome conduit for grieving loved ones to express their loss.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>iheartradiopodcasts@bellmedia.ca (BTS with CTV News Vancouver)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7e4bd092725a4b1f8a5a652076878067</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7e4bd092725a4b1f8a5a652076878067/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 19:35:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Patriots Fight Media : PFM: The Bidens - Part 1</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Part 1 of the expose of the Biden family and their internationally corrupt dealings. Showcased in this episode: Hunter Biden, Devon Archer, and Bohai Harvest RST -- the joint venture deal between the Biden family and the state of China.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ford@patriotsfight.com (Patriots Fight Media)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">20d1191c9f8940b291980c52801dd003</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/20d1191c9f8940b291980c52801dd003/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Blinders Off : STL Neighborhoods: Midtown 37 of 79</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Midtown is one of St. Louis' most well - loved neighborhoods...but how well do you know the area?  Can you tell the difference between “Historic Midtown”, “Midtown”, and “midtown”? Matt &amp; Lucas explore current boundaries, historical neighborhood designations, Art Deco cop shops, as well as test their knowledge of landmarks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Check out our &lt;a href= "http://bit.ly/midtownstl" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;show notes&lt;/a&gt; for additional information.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Questions? Comments?  Email us at &lt;a href= "mailto:BlindersOffPodcast@gmail.com"&gt;BlindersOffPodcast@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;, or reach out to us on &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/blindersoffpodcast/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/blindersoffpodcast/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/blindersoffSTL"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Original photos by Russell Ward, Landmark Mashup illustration by &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/missiadair/"&gt;Missi Adair&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Find us at &lt;a href= "https://www.blindersoff.show/"&gt;blindersoff.show&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>blindersoffpodcast@gmail.com (Blinders Off)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fd1d21de679e4249ac006fcf2a0f0071</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fd1d21de679e4249ac006fcf2a0f0071/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 12:48:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>On One with Angela Rye : Road to 2020: Pete Buttigieg</title><description>Live from Claflin University in South Carolina, Angela talks to Mayor Pete about student loan debt, living his truth, freezing eggs, and his challenges connecting with Black voters.</description><author>ononepod@loudspeakersnetwork.com (On One with Angela Rye)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">511e397db12349f896f53f3829bc5cac</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/511e397db12349f896f53f3829bc5cac/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 03:54:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Political Mind of Jerry Brown : BONUS: Jerry Brown on the 2020 Election, Education Policy, and His Next Portrait (LIVE in San Francisco)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Jerry Brown shares his thoughts on the 2020 election, his own presidential campaigns, efforts to reform his state education policies, and more with KQED&amp;#8217;s Scott Shafer. Recorded at the  Herbst Theatre in San Francisco on January 13, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ondemand@kqed.org (The Political Mind of Jerry Brown)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">62656bd1fb1344f5be5f3d366e216e4d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/62656bd1fb1344f5be5f3d366e216e4d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 17:59:25 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Women belong in the House : Bonus: Introducing Ordinary Equality</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/ordinary-equality/id1492330633"&gt;Subscribe now&lt;/a&gt; to hear Episode 1 of Ordinary Equality.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>pod@wondermedianetwork.com (Women belong in the House)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">077dd4f42a454833b9e14e9ffbebb842</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/077dd4f42a454833b9e14e9ffbebb842/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 03:00:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MORNINGS with BOB MARRONE on Radio Westchester ™ : Local Westchester Dobbs Ferry Top News Stories of the Day - January 13, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://radiowestchester.com/january-20-2020-6-am-10-am/"&gt;January 20, 2020 – 6 AM – 10 AM&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://radiowestchester.com"&gt;Radio Westchester ™ Local NYC Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>production@radiowestchester.com (MORNINGS with BOB MARRONE on Radio Westchester ™)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">73a680f6a29a404c8a9f6ff1f6ef76bf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/73a680f6a29a404c8a9f6ff1f6ef76bf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 15:09:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Uncommon Knowledge : The Impeachment Handbook with John Yoo &amp; Richard Epstein</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Recorded on January 15, 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The impeachment proceedings against President Trump has now reached the Senate and to help our viewers navigate the legal and political issues surrounding it, Peter Robinson sits down with the Hoover Institution’s Visiting Fellow John Yoo and Senior Fellow Richard Epstein, two of the foremost legal scholars in the country. We cover the Articles of Impeachment submitted by the U.S. House of Representatives, the pluses and minuses of calling witnesses, the role of Chief Justice of the Supreme Court John Roberts in the proceeding, and whether or not President Trump should testify on his own behalf. Finally, Peter asks Epstein and Yoo for their vote predictions on conviction and acquittal and gets their predictions for the election in November.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>institutionhoover@gmail.com (Uncommon Knowledge)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2fc972d4a51244f398f2b8e9ed8099cd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2fc972d4a51244f398f2b8e9ed8099cd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 07:48:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Jay Talk : Episode 14: Ian Silva Joins</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Bettendorf Legend Ian Silva joins the podcast. Ian and Tyger chop it up about winter break, Uncut Gems, their favorite coaching quotes, and leave you with some solid jokes. &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">bc32d15373f04c3ba4d3e5e06ac9b83a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bc32d15373f04c3ba4d3e5e06ac9b83a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 14:15:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Arctic Conversation Podcast : Episode 6</title><description>&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Arctic Dreams and Nightmares&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;In many ways the Arctic has been a region of international cooperation, especially in the sciences. Could the far north (or a portion of it) follow a path like Antarctica, and become a zone in which countries agree that scientific collaboration is the top priority? Or are we doomed to a future of territorial competition as the sea ice melts? This gets into the possibility of military conflict but doesn’t put it quite so much in the center of the conversation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;We also talk about development versus conservation: The Arctic is home to some amazing wildlife and as-yet undamaged ecosystems. But as people in Montana sometimes say, “you can’t eat the view.” Meaning, preservation of wildlife and wild places can in some cases make it hard for local people to earn a living. As industries move north the tension between economic development and conservation of land, water, air and creatures is increasing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;In this final episode for the first season we talk about future Arctic Dreams - and Nightmares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;Introduction by Anna Kireeva from Russia&lt;br&gt;Tim Andersson from Sweden&lt;br&gt;Thomas Nilsen from Norway&lt;/p&gt;





  

    
      
      
        
          
            
              &lt;img class="thumb-image" data-image="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5973071e2e69cf20a272c83f/1578299431485-HEW236H53XGQZI07IZVM/ke17ZwdGBToddI8pDm48kJUlZr2Ql5GtSKWrQpjur5t7gQa3H78H3Y0txjaiv_0fDoOvxcdMmMKkDsyUqMSsMWxHk725yiiHCCLfrh8O1z5QPOohDIaIeljMHgDF5CVlOqpeNLcJ80NK65_fV7S1UYapt4KGntwbjD1IFBRUBU6SRwXJogFYPCjZ6mtBiWtU3WUfc_ZsVm9Mi1E6FasEnQ/Cover_Art_Oil_Rig_1500x1500.png" data-image-dimensions="1500x1500" data-image-focal-point="0.5,0.5" alt="Cover_Art_Oil_Rig_1500x1500.png" data-load="false" data-image-id="5e1c3ee3e07fd3395102efc9" data-type="image" src="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5973071e2e69cf20a272c83f/1578299431485-HEW236H53XGQZI07IZVM/ke17ZwdGBToddI8pDm48kJUlZr2Ql5GtSKWrQpjur5t7gQa3H78H3Y0txjaiv_0fDoOvxcdMmMKkDsyUqMSsMWxHk725yiiHCCLfrh8O1z5QPOohDIaIeljMHgDF5CVlOqpeNLcJ80NK65_fV7S1UYapt4KGntwbjD1IFBRUBU6SRwXJogFYPCjZ6mtBiWtU3WUfc_ZsVm9Mi1E6FasEnQ/Cover_Art_Oil_Rig_1500x1500.png?format=1000w" /&gt;</description><author>arctic_conversation@barentspress.org (The Arctic Conversation Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e817ef105b0e44a387e6da2a315b5f5d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e817ef105b0e44a387e6da2a315b5f5d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 01:57:33 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>