<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My News feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My news episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My News feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 15:46:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>NPR News Now : NPR News: 02-29-2020 9AM ET</title><description>NPR News: 02-29-2020 9AM ET</description><author>PodCasts@npr.org (NPR News Now)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">20de409a1015420abffabfb111d92292</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/20de409a1015420abffabfb111d92292/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FOX News Radio Newscast : 8AM EDT 02/29/2020 Newscast</title><description>Latest FOX News hourly newscast.&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=jqqVCeAs-OE:-HZ4hmuBfUs:yIl2AUoC8zA"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=yIl2AUoC8zA" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=jqqVCeAs-OE:-HZ4hmuBfUs:qj6IDK7rITs"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=qj6IDK7rITs" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=jqqVCeAs-OE:-HZ4hmuBfUs:O3QAOHgViy4"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=O3QAOHgViy4" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?a=jqqVCeAs-OE:-HZ4hmuBfUs:I9og5sOYxJI"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~ff/FoxNewsRadio?d=I9og5sOYxJI" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/FoxNewsRadio/~4/jqqVCeAs-OE" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>podcast@foxnewsradio.com (FOX News Radio Newscast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3d028ec9439d46a09a0cdda6441a907b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3d028ec9439d46a09a0cdda6441a907b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 05:08:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Up First : Saturday, February 29, 2020</title><description>The coronavirus that causes the illness COVID-19 is spreading but the threat to the U.S. is still low, despite 3 new cases. In South Carolina, voters are casting ballots for Democratic presidential candidates. And a deal between the U.S. and Taliban is being signed in Doha, Qatar, today.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (Up First)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">521133f9fe304f58ad754ac5f7b7a1a6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/521133f9fe304f58ad754ac5f7b7a1a6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 04:35:58 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>KRDO Newsradio 105.5 FM • 1240 AM • 92.5 FM : A Man with a Secret - KRDO's Afternoon News with Ted Robertson - American Idol - February 28, 2020</title><description>&lt;p style="text-align:justify;"&gt;DeWayne Crocker, Jr., has had a secret for several months.  This Sunday that secret will finally be revealed on the national stage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify;"&gt;It was last year, Crocker's vocal talent was discovered online by a scout from &lt;a href='https://abc.com/shows/american-idol'&gt;American Idol&lt;/a&gt;.  When the Idol auditions rolled through Colorado Springs last September, he took advantage of the invitation. After his audition, the feedback was positive.  Being on stage is a weekly occurrence for Crocker: he's a worship leader at Emmanuel Baptist Church in Colorado Springs.  Of course, Crocker can't divulge any details about what came of his audition, despite his friends and family -- and reporters -- asking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Listen Now!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ted.robertson@krdo.com (KRDO Newsradio 105.5 FM • 1240 AM • 92.5 FM)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ae2734f3817244a4a69f95bc99f4b083</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ae2734f3817244a4a69f95bc99f4b083/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 04:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC Meet the Press : BONUS: Introducing Into America</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As a bonus for Meet The Press listeners, we’re sharing a special preview of Into America, a new podcast about politics, about policy, and the power that both have in shaping the lives of the American people. It is hosted by Trymaine Lee and features the journalists of NBC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the first episode, Trymaine heads to East New York, a community that experienced more stops than any other part of New York City under Former Mayor Bloomberg’s stop and frisk policy. In order to have a real shot at the Democratic nomination, Bloomberg needs the support of Black voters. Days before announcing his candidacy, Bloomberg apologized for the policing tactic. But will his past decision to champion the use of stop and frisk hurt his chances? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subscribe to Into America now: &lt;a href="https://link.chtbl.com/7BcTGqT3?sid=description" target="_blank"&gt;https://link.chtbl.com/7BcTGqT3?sid=description&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>MeetThePress@nbcuni.com (NBC Meet the Press)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b7c1cbe2caae4357b54ada5f8012dbfc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b7c1cbe2caae4357b54ada5f8012dbfc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Rick &amp; Bubba University Podcast : Ep 21 | What Clinton and Lynch Really Discussed on the Tarmac | Guest: Christoper Sign</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, Rick &amp;amp; Bubba visit with the award-winning journalist and author Christopher Sign. They discuss his new book, "Secret on the Tarmac," revealing new details about the hush-hush 2016 meeting between former President Clinton and former Attorney General Loretta Lynch. This explosive meeting cast a negative light over the FBI's investigation into Hillary Clinton's use of a private email server. There is so much that just doesn't add up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today's Sponsor:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CarShield: Get your vehicle covered by the ultimate in vehicle service protection before it's too late.CarShield has affordable protection plans that can save you thousands on a covered repair, including computers, GPS, electronics, and more. With CarShield, you’re behind the wheel of your plan. CarShield has customizable monthly plans with rates as low as $99 a month! CarShield has helped over one million customers! So, drive with confidence knowing you got coverage from America’s Number One Auto Protection Provider. Get covered by CarShield today. Call 800-CAR-6000 and mention code RICKBUBBA or visit &lt;a href="http://carshield.com"&gt;http://carshield.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@theblaze.com (Rick &amp; Bubba University Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cb485377694040469c3d8f95f2f37ad5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cb485377694040469c3d8f95f2f37ad5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 02:55:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best of Coast to Coast AM : UFOs and Nukes - Best of Coast to Coast AM - 2/28/20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;George Noory and author Richard Hastings explore his research into stories of UFOs being seen at US military bases to stop use of nuclear weapons, as well as details of his own case as a UFO abductee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts@rsvmedia.com (The Best of Coast to Coast AM)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ed4a659500cc4b6995285b4245000e29</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ed4a659500cc4b6995285b4245000e29/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 02:41:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The FOX News Rundown : Fox News Rundown Extra: What Life Is Like For A Coronavirus Patient</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Concerns over the coronavirus infected both Wall Street and Main Street this week, causing major market losses and triggering the Trump Administration to launch a special task force to ease fears.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One American remaining calm, however, is somebody who is actually infected with COVID19, Carl Goldman.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goldman was a passenger on the Diamond Princess Cruise and has been diagnosed with the coronavirus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this week, he joined host Dave Anthony on the Rundown tomorrow from a biocontainment unit at the University of Nebraska Medical Center to describe what it's like living with the disease and being quarantined both on the cruise ship and now in a hospital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goldman describe how he feels, the treatments he's receiving and how he's coping with isolation from the outside world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The interview was long and we were forced to edit for time. But we felt Goldman's perspective on the coronavirus crisis was important to hear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On The Fox News Rundown Extra you will hear our full unedited interview with coronavirus patient Carl Goldman. You'll hear every detail of what it's like living with the illness and get a better understanding of how medical professionals are trying to prevent a larger outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/FoxNewsRundown/~4/7_Oo0K2YNqo" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>podcasts@foxnewsradio.com (The FOX News Rundown)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c6ae7db6a732419b9f861187021be5ef</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c6ae7db6a732419b9f861187021be5ef/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Glenn Beck Program : Ep 69 | Leftists Need Black America, but Candace Owens Doesn’t Need the Left | The Glenn Beck Podcast</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The leftist media has tried to whitewash her, paint her as privileged, and call her a traitor to her race. But conservative activist and BLEXIT founder Candace Owens has had enough of the games and victimization. Once a leftist herself, she watched as the Left demonized cultural icons like Donald Trump and Kanye West and realized how dependent the Left is on black America. She has experienced firsthand how desperately the Left insists that black Americans are victims in the Trump era, especially when they disagree. But her rough upbringing and strong work ethic have led her to a different calling: to free black America from the bondage of progressivism. And like Kanye and Trump, she’s not letting any politician tell her what to believe.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ccardon@blazemedia.com (The Glenn Beck Program)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ac90506e8ed94181bcde94e2e1d683c9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ac90506e8ed94181bcde94e2e1d683c9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Business Wars Daily : Introducing Byers Market</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A new podcast hosted by NBC News Senior Media Reporter Dylan Byers that takes listeners behind the scenes of the rapidly changing world of technology and media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the first episode, Byers sits down one-on-one with Facebook COO Sheryl Sandberg for her first interview since the release of “Facebook: The Inside Story”, the explosive new book by tech writer Steven Levy, who had unfettered access to Facebook’s headquarters for three years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subscribe to Byers Market now:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://wondery.fm/NBCByersMarket" target="_blank"&gt;http://wondery.fm/NBCByersMarket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>iwonder@wondery.com (Business Wars Daily)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">48e563f122684593a5bd4cf5697b6f9e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/48e563f122684593a5bd4cf5697b6f9e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ben Shapiro Show : Leap Day Offer Alert!</title><description>Leap Day only comes once every four years, and we have some interesting facts about Leap Day plus an amazing offer for you to become an insider plus member today! So TODAY ONLY: get 2 years for the price of 1 when you begin an Insider Plus membership. That’s double the content at half the cost for our most popular membership level. No coupon code needed! Join here: dailywire.com/Shapiro</description><author>benshapiroshow@dailywire.com (The Ben Shapiro Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">85a438a6109743c390902eb4d67a132f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/85a438a6109743c390902eb4d67a132f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Amicus With Dahlia Lithwick | Law, Justice, and the Courts : Have Progressives Lost the Courts for Good?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Dahlia Lithwick asks the new president of the American Constitution Society, Russ Feingold, if it’s too late for progressives to respond to the conservative steamroller that is the Federalist Society. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slate Plus members have access to a bonus segment in which Slate’s Mark Joseph&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stern breaks down the headlines, cases, cert grants, and conundrums from the Supreme Court and federal appellate courts. To start your free two-week trial go to &lt;a href="http://slate.com/amicusplus"&gt;slate.com/amicusplus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Podcast production by Sara Burningham.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>amicus@slate.com (Amicus With Dahlia Lithwick | Law, Justice, and the Courts)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8a2c6f52558e4b6c89bdfc7370448c7a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8a2c6f52558e4b6c89bdfc7370448c7a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>RUMBLE with MICHAEL MOORE : Ep. 43: Super Tuesday Preview, Part 1 - Coronavirus Don</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Four days until Super Tuesday, Michael lays out the stakes of how important Tuesday's elections are what role coronavirus will play&amp;nbsp;in shaping our views of this election. &amp;nbsp;We are only as safe as the human being who has no health insurance or access to medical care. A nation that has millions of people who are not insured or are under-insured means that millions of American's are encouraged to NOT seek tests or treatment - which makes the coronavirus that much more dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;***********&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watch "SiCKO" here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://youtu.be/YbEQ7acb0IE"&gt;https://youtu.be/YbEQ7acb0IE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/rumble-with-michael-moore/message</description><author>podcasts39+10fc9a30@anchor.fm (RUMBLE with MICHAEL MOORE)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2e68419c198544beb2580549e55d22e6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2e68419c198544beb2580549e55d22e6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 22:13:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Lawfare Podcast : Philip Rucker and Carol Leonnig on 'A Very Stable Genius'</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Philip Rucker and Carol Leonnig are reporters at The Washington Post and the authors of the new book, 'A Very Stable Genius: Donald J. Trump's Testing of America.' This week, Susan Hennessey sat down with Rucker and Leonnig to talk about the new book, the president's interactions with his cabinet, his attitude toward the law, and the efficacy of his public attacks.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>benjamin.wittes@lawfareblog.com (The Lawfare Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">19f653b4be68404ba7ce05598ddd677a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/19f653b4be68404ba7ce05598ddd677a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Impeachment, Explained : Weeds 2020: The Bernie electability debate</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Weeds 2020! Every other Saturday Ezra and Matt will be exploring a wide range of topics related to the 2020 race. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the Nevada caucuses, Bernie Sanders has become the clear frontrunner in the 2020 Democratic primary, spurring lots of debate over whether he could win in the general election. We discuss where the electability conversation often goes off-the-rails, why discussing electability in 2020 is so different than 1964 or 1972, the case for and against Bernie’s electability prospects, and the strongest attacks that Trump could make against Sanders and Joe Biden. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, we discuss Ezra’s favorite topic of all time: the filibuster. Ezra gives a brief history of this weird procedural tool, and we discuss why so many current Senators are against eliminating it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2020/1/7/21002895/bernie-sanders-2020-electability"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"&lt;/strong&gt;Bernie Sanders can unify Democrats and beat Trump in 2020"&lt;/a&gt; by Matthew Yglesias, Vox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2020/1/15/21054083/elizabeth-warren-2020-democratic-primary"&gt;"The case for Elizabeth Warren"&lt;/a&gt; by Ezra Klein, Vox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/videos/2019/6/17/18681798/filibuster-senate-broke-video"&gt;"How the filibuster broke the US Senate"&lt;/a&gt; by Alvin Chang, Vox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2020/01/bernie-sanders-electable-trump-2020-nomination-popular-socialism.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"&lt;/strong&gt;Running Bernie Sanders Against Trump Would Be an Act of Insanity"&lt;/a&gt; by Jonathan Chait, Intelligencer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/02/sanderss-pricey-tax-and-spending-plans/607105/"&gt;"The Sixty Trillion Dollar Man"&lt;/a&gt; by Ronald brownstein, Atlantic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://prospect.org/day-one-agenda/using-presidential-power-executive-authority/"&gt;"The Day One Agenda"&lt;/a&gt; by David Dayen, American Prospect&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hosts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matthew Yglesias (&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/mattyglesias"&gt;@mattyglesias&lt;/a&gt;), Senior correspondent, Vox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ezra Klein (&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ezraklein?s=20"&gt;@ezraklein&lt;/a&gt;), Editor-at-large, Vox&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Vox&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vox is a news network that helps you cut through the noise and understand what's really driving the events in the headlines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow Us&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/future-perfect"&gt;Vox.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook group:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/2XUajwq"&gt;The Weeds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasting@voxmedia.com (Impeachment, Explained)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">51b1adc451574f84aa2a450fda258794</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/51b1adc451574f84aa2a450fda258794/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Verdict with Ted Cruz : Ep. 15 - A firsthand look at socialism</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Senator Cruz’s tia joins the show to share her firsthand experience living under Castro-era socialism and they consider what an America under President Bernie Sanders would look like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verdict is co-hosted by Senator Ted Cruz and Michael Knowles. To hear more of Michael, check out The Michael Knowles Show on Youtube, Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you stream your favorite podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>verdictcruz@gmail.com (Verdict with Ted Cruz)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7ac652be2c494eda954c49507922edd4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7ac652be2c494eda954c49507922edd4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 20:02:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Honey Badger Radio : Handing back the feminist rape apologist label | HBR Talk 122</title><description>HBR talk examines feminist media’s use of derogatory labels like “rape apologist” as a tool for gatekeeping the gender issues dialogue.</description><author>feeds@spreaker.com (Honey Badger Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0945abb9443b4d6c9cfa2635362c03de</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0945abb9443b4d6c9cfa2635362c03de/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 19:48:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>News In Context : News In Context: Context with John Zipperer of The Commonwealth Club</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Gina sits down with John Zipperer, Vice President of Editorial at The Commonwealth Club of California, to discuss the importance of contextualizing news to help better inform the public about the information we all need to know and understand to engage with our communities and society.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>newsincontextpodcast@gmail.com (News In Context)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">74a762b50f1c41da8b5f891b4a6da9a8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/74a762b50f1c41da8b5f891b4a6da9a8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 19:45:54 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Stu Does America : Ep 15 | Stu Does Knowles &amp; Kelly | Guests: Michael J. Knowles &amp; Jesse Kelly</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Stu does ... Michael J. Knowles and Jesse Kelly! Stu continues to party at CPAC, roping in the Daily Wire’s Michael J. Knowles to spend a few minutes talking election season and the rise of democratic socialism. And, Jesse Kelly from the Federalist swings in to break up the political monotony with some news of the day and, of course, the latest in sports.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ccardon@blazemedia.com (Stu Does America)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b70de27400454a33be94e5e612817078</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b70de27400454a33be94e5e612817078/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 18:37:45 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mark Levin Podcast : Mark Levin Audio Rewind - 2/28/20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On Friday’s Mark Levin show, can we simultaneously love our children and betray their generation and generations unborn? If you embrace Bernie Sanders and the democrats agenda, how can you love your children yet help to create an environment that will harm them? How much do you love your children when you support a Marxist ideology of a massive expansion of government which will smother the individual? Sanders policies would create an economic wrecking ball.  Also, Sanders and the democrats go on and on about hating certain corporations, but no company or corporation has the power of a centralized government. We don’t have to fear corporations, but we do have to fear a centralized tyranny. Our founding fathers believed that liberty wasn’t enough for freedom, its companion is virtue. The Sanders and democrat ideology is virtue less, which is why they come up with schemes to take from you. Later, while President Trump and his team worked to contain the coronavirus, Democrats busied themselves with his impeachment trial, leaving little time to pass the necessary legislation. From January 16 to February 5, the Senate was paralyzed by the House Democrats, Chuck Schumer and Nancy Pelosi with this outrageous impeachment trial where the Senators had to sit on their hands and couldn't pass any business.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wwopodcasts@westwoodone.com (Mark Levin Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7d7dbb6307c24fd7a0b67d493343665c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7d7dbb6307c24fd7a0b67d493343665c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 18:23:36 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Freedomizer Radio : The Delusion Solution</title><description>Delusion Solution-  What is really happening to our state, to our country, and to our world? What does the future hold? Will our educational system continue to dumb down our children?  Has America arrived at the point of no return?”

Are you ready to make sense of current events, to know the truth, to pierce the veil? Join myself Tara Dawn as (your host) and Rudy Smith (my co-host) as we will be bringing you the News and how it relates to the times we live in. How does it affect you the individual, and we as a nation of diverse backgrounds, what it means for people of faith, and how we can make informed decisions concerning the times we live in. Watching with our ears and listening with our eyes to bring you solutions to the many delusions that bombard us daily.

Join us Every Friday from 6-9pacific/9-12 midnight eastern. Call in number: 319-527-6208

Also please join our FB page: Click Here to Like 

https://www.facebook.com/Delusion.Solution/

You can also find us here at Minds.com: 

https://www.minds.com/Delusion_Solution</description><author>Proof@freedomizerradio.com (Freedomizer Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6aa95d3921054211b478039539336769</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6aa95d3921054211b478039539336769/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 18:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Gist : Busting Bernie’s Policy Myth</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On the Gist, complaining to the FCC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the interview, Maria Konnikova is back for another round of “Is That Bullshit?” This time she and Mike look into the light, blue light that is. Does it really affect sleep the way everybody claims it does? Should we all be buying those special glasses? Maria’s latest book is &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/0143109871/?tag=slatmaga-20"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Confidence Game&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the spiel, the filibuster and Medicare for all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thegist@slate.com (The Gist)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7cddc85a191f47f2b295577e2dc8bef0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7cddc85a191f47f2b295577e2dc8bef0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 17:20:34 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Two Minutes of Truth with Phil Valentine : Weaponizing Coronavirus Fear</title><description>&lt;p&gt;While President Trump takes decisive action to prevent an epidemic of coronavirus in the United States the Democrats are doing everything they can to politicize it. With the exception of one.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>phil@philvalentine.com (Two Minutes of Truth with Phil Valentine)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0e6c037507004fad8a7dddbe9ab04a72</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0e6c037507004fad8a7dddbe9ab04a72/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 16:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>New York NOW : Leader Crystal Peoples-Stokes, Marijuana, Prevailing Wage</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Assembly Majority Leader Crystal Peoples-Stokes joins us to talk about her support for legalizing marijuana in New York, the possibility of raising taxes on the wealthy, and more. Gov. Andrew Cuomo and other Democrats want to expand the number of construction projects that would require higher pay, called a prevailing wage. Reporter Josefa Velasquez joins Casey Seiler for the Reporters Roundtable.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@wmht.org (New York NOW)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f6331c2aed8c4844b2e6e794b6ca81e6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f6331c2aed8c4844b2e6e794b6ca81e6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 16:21:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ticket: Politics from The Atlantic : South Carolina, with Jennifer Palmieri</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former Clinton aide Jennifer Palmieri discusses the South Carolina primary, how 2020 is different than 2016, and how sexism still shapes American politics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcastproduct@theatlantic.com (The Ticket: Politics from The Atlantic)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">22fa4afb95c340739d41c1957d5fc694</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/22fa4afb95c340739d41c1957d5fc694/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 16:12:35 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ricochet Podcast : 485. The Most Interesting Virus in the World</title><description>The main topic? What else? The Coronavirus, which is roiling everything from the markets to the political arena and beyond. The Vice President is the new point man. Then we get down to the nitty gritty of the race for the Democratic nomination with Luke Thompson and talk to a sensible lefty about the environment [&amp;#8230;]</description><author>support@ricochet.com (Ricochet Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6521b1e4b3ff41e5a76b09048b6e735d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6521b1e4b3ff41e5a76b09048b6e735d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 16:07:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>CNN News Briefing : Evening news briefing from CNN</title><description>https://www.cnn.com/videos/us/2020/02/28/daily-news-briefing-02282020-2.cnn &lt;a href="http://knit.audio/podcast-advertising"&gt;via Knit&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcast@turner.com (CNN News Briefing)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6ce9f77927c34e2d8864399992850ac8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6ce9f77927c34e2d8864399992850ac8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 15:35:40 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The News &amp; Why It Matters : Ep 481 | The Race for the Coronavirus Cure</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Socialist Bernie Sanders pushes Sleepy Joe Biden out of the front-runner spot for the 2020 Democratic nomination with a record 31% support in a new Fox News poll. But in a South Carolina poll, Sleepy Joe takes the lead, and Charlamagne Tha God had very harsh words for Biden. Israeli scientists are reportedly only a few weeks away from the first vaccine to combat COVID-19. And in California and Massachusetts, coronavirus preparation means monitoring people. Meanwhile, California is at it again: Instead of focusing on the homeless population, it passes a bill requiring retailers to have gender-neutral floor spaces inside their stores.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tcardon@glennbeck.com (The News &amp; Why It Matters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8040ec75819c4c83a833554e8a50e584</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8040ec75819c4c83a833554e8a50e584/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 15:17:37 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WSJ What’s News : Court Blocks Trump's 'Remain in Mexico' Policy</title><description>P.M. Edition for February 28th: An appeals court has blocked the Trump administration's "Remain in Mexico" policy. But the Wall Street Journal's Michelle Hackman says the White House is using another program for fast deportation of migrants. Plus, the Journal's Jacob Schlesinger on how Democrats and Republicans interpret the strong economy in different ways. Charlie Turner hosts.&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@dowjones.com (WSJ What’s News)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d11c53549227473db53564883a4963a3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d11c53549227473db53564883a4963a3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 15:16:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Yorker Radio Hour : Rose McGowan on Harvey Weinstein’s Guilty Verdict, and Neuroscience on the Campaign Trail</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;After a Manhattan jury found Harvey Weinstein guilty of two of the sex crimes he was charged with, Ronan Farrow sat down with the actress Rose McGowan, one of the women to speak out against the movie producer, whom she has said raped her in 1997, at a film festival. McGowan tweeted about the assault in 2016, not naming Weinstein but leaving no doubt as to whom she was accusing. “&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Could you have imagined at that point,” Farrow asks her, that “we’d be sitting here talking about Harvey Weinstein getting convicted?” McGowan takes a long pause. “No. But I did think there could be a massive cultural shift. That I knew.”&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;McGowan later went on the record for Farrow’s&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/ronan-farrow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;reporting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;on the Weinstein case, which received a Pulitzer Prize and helped to launch the #MeToo movement. “It’s been an odyssey for both of us,” she said. Plus, using E.E.G. sensors and heart-rate monitors, a company investigates how political candidates engage our attention and emotions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (The New Yorker Radio Hour)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5c9f26e7480c43fbafc7c62645695877</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5c9f26e7480c43fbafc7c62645695877/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 14:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Skimm This : In the Red: The COVID-19 Market Downturn</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week, the stock market has been feeling the pain of COVID-19. We’ll look at what the current economic impact is and what a ‘market correction’ has to do with it. Meanwhile, the US and the Taliban are on the verge of a major peace deal. We’ll break down how the agreement could lead to the end of the US’s longest war. Also on today’s show: a look at pedestrian safety, the &lt;a href="http://theskimm.com/cpac"&gt;annual convention of conservative activists&lt;/a&gt;, and a leap-year tradition that could be skipped over. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PS: &lt;a href="https://www.nhtsa.gov/road-safety/pedestrian-safety"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; for more pedestrian safety tips. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>skimmthis@theskimm.com (Skimm This)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">191a5aa975224b2c8a3af8d1a86b1f31</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/191a5aa975224b2c8a3af8d1a86b1f31/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 13:55:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Journal. : What Bernie Sanders's Socialism Means</title><description>Bernie Sanders calls himself a democratic socialist, the first time a front-runner for the Democratic presidential nomination has done so. Eliza Collins, who covers Bernie Sanders, and Jon Hilsenrath, who covers economics, explain what that means for Sanders and his rivals.</description><author>podcasts@dowjones.com (The Journal.)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">00e38881f2c94d59a9fd6d15142ead71</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/00e38881f2c94d59a9fd6d15142ead71/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 13:37:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Daily Detroit : Trying 7 Flavors Of Hudsonville's Extra Indulgent Ice Cream</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Happy Friday everyone! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On today’s food-focused episode of Daily Detroit for Friday, February 28, 2020. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Fort Street Galley is no more after today, after being open for only 14 months. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Alley Taco in Midtown is &lt;a href= "https://www.oconnordetroit.com/property/alley-taco/"&gt;now for sale&lt;/a&gt;, you can buy it for $185,000. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And finally, Randy Walker joins us for an in-depth taste test of seven new Extra Indulgent &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/Hudsonvilleicecream/"&gt;Hudsonville Ice Cream&lt;/a&gt; flavors. Which ice cream reigns supreme?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to tell a friend about your Daily Detroit! We’re on Apple Podcasts: &lt;a href= "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/daily-detroit/id1220563942"&gt;https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/daily-detroit/id1220563942&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Spotify: &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/show/1Yhv8nSylVWxlZilRhi4X9"&gt;https://open.spotify.com/show/1Yhv8nSylVWxlZilRhi4X9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And although the show will always be free, our members help make it available for everyone else. Become a member on Patreon: &lt;a href="http://www.patreon.com/dailydetroit"&gt;http://www.patreon.com/dailydetroit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>dailydetroit@gmail.com (Daily Detroit)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1802e31c54d14be69281d32b15cde9e8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1802e31c54d14be69281d32b15cde9e8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 13:33:30 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Get 2 the Point : Happily Ever After Animal Sanctuary: Finding Forever Homes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Amanda Reitz had a dream, to start an animal sanctuary to give pets the best possible chance at finding a forever home.  But at the time she was still in college and people weren’t quite sold on the idea, including her own family initially. By 2006, Amanda had her parents involved transforming family property in Marion for a spacious sanctuary for animals. A couple years later, brother Marcus Reitz joined on with HEA full-time and they raised funds for a new adoption center in Ashwaubenon.  Hear the humble beginnings of HEA, from a Basset hound named Walter, to the plans to help animals across the country find forever homes.  &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tmiller@wbay.com (Get 2 the Point)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e7561cddf0364d878dc41a7125e53d6c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e7561cddf0364d878dc41a7125e53d6c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 13:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WSJ Opinion: Potomac Watch : The Biden Resurgence/Is the Coronavirus the New Russia?</title><description>The Biden Resurgence/Is the Coronavirus the New Russia?&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@dowjones.com (WSJ Opinion: Potomac Watch)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">71c8a7c6d1fb467fa59e6bd051307385</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/71c8a7c6d1fb467fa59e6bd051307385/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 13:02:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Tim Pool Daily Show : The US Has Been Infiltrated By The Chinese Communist Party, FBI ARRESTS US Academics In On The Take</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The US Has Been Infiltrated By The Chinese Communist Party, FBI ARRESTS US Academics In On The Take. For the past several decades America has been extracted by selfish politicians and personalities bent on making the quickest buck.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We all sat by as our manufacturing base was sold to foreign interests and politicians paved the way for the outsourcing of our jobs and production.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the past several months the FBI has arrested several US academics for taking money from Communist China and lying about it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers and scientists have sold our secrets for a personal profit, they have built labs in a foreign country and helped pop up an authoritarian regime in China.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In their own words the Chinese minister of propaganda has called on the country to spread propaganda around the world and it has worked.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether youre a democrat or republican this issue affects us all and if left ignored we will lose to an autocratic and authoritarian regime that has no regards for civil rights. The far left activists in the US can complain all they want but China's record is several orders of magnitude worse.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether you like Trump or not, what is going on with China must be addressed and its time Democrats joined the bipartisan battle to stop their encroachment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="http://timcast.com/donate"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (http://timcast.com/donate)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tim@timcast.com (Tim Pool Daily Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">633a604df5c84aa58bbb57d1b0cc7be0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/633a604df5c84aa58bbb57d1b0cc7be0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rush Limbaugh Show : The Rush Limbaugh Show Podcast - Feb 28 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;PODCAST SUMMARY HOUR 1:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coronavirus will end and economy will rebound. Apple TV app. Democrat primary operating outside of coronavirus panic. NYT Gail Collins: Call it the Trumpvirus. Will coronavirus shut down Trump rallies? Eight people show up for Bloomberg event. Apple stock buybacks. Donald Trump believes nothing is inevitable. Trump is a doer, a problem solver, not apocalyptic. Corona beer boycott. People adapt, we’re not going to be wiped out. Everything the left does is inevitable doom and gloom. Dr. Drew praises Pence’s record in Indiana, blasts press for creating hysteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PODCAST SUMMARY HOUR 2:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mick Mulvaney: Turn off the television for 24 hours. Donald Trump Jr. on Gail Collins column in NYT. Thomas Friedman: Coronavirus could be Katrina times ten, hurt Crazy Bernie. Operation Chaos in South Carolina. Biden tells others to quit. Biden admits he didn’t get arrested in South Africa. Brian Williams Virus? Dems plot to stop Bernie. Why media zeroes in on Rush. Market recovered while Rush is on the air. Hate-Trump opportunists looking to coronavirus. Tim Cook not panicked over threat to Apple supply chain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PODCAST SUMMARY HOUR 3:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vice President Pence joins Rush in the studio to discuss response to coronavirus. Ted Lieu asks snarky question to Secretary of State Pompeo. Democrats politicize everything. Johns Hopkins coronavirus tracker. Drive-By headlines criticizing Trump travel ban as overreaction, xenophobic, nationalistic. Grandmother reading her grandchildren's Rush Revere books.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (The Rush Limbaugh Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">08b5d1841f08421aa72ae797eaef7265</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/08b5d1841f08421aa72ae797eaef7265/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 11:59:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Max &amp; Murphy : Episode 201: Supporters of Democratic Presidential Candidates Make Their Case</title><description>Episode 201: Supporters of Democratic Presidential Candidates Make Their Case by Max &amp; Murphy</description><author>gothamgazette@gmail.com (Max &amp; Murphy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">59765bd0d03a4a07a55e3c570b4c8c1e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/59765bd0d03a4a07a55e3c570b4c8c1e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 11:58:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Overwatch : E13: Governing After ISIS: What’s Next for the Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF), America’s local partner in northeastern Syria, was instrumental in the fight against ISIS and is working to fill the vacuum it left behind. In this episode of Overwatch, ISW’s Research Director Jennifer Cafarella, new Middle East Portfolio Manager Nicholas Heras, and Syria Research Assistant John Dunford discuss the structure and behavior of the SDF, the group’s relationship with the US military, the unique challenges it faces in governing, and its efforts to prevent the resurgence of ISIS within local populations.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>press@understandingwar.org (Overwatch)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">32a94500287e4d609f23e5348a2896bf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/32a94500287e4d609f23e5348a2896bf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 11:35:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Buck Sexton Show : Bernie and Omar's Anti-Americanism</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Season 4, Episode 42.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ben Weingarten fills in for Buck!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>teambuck@iheartmedia.com (The Buck Sexton Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">610d6079173e47b69a9b7027783b0a2c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/610d6079173e47b69a9b7027783b0a2c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:46:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bannon's War Room : Ep. 28 War Room: Pandemic- Global Market Beatdown</title><description>Steve Bannon and Jack Maxey are joined by Miles Guo to discuss the global market meltdown worldwide due to the concerns around the coronavirus.</description><author>admin@citizensoftheamericanrepublic.org (Bannon's War Room)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7df2852714f54ff6aaa64313d3ede78b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7df2852714f54ff6aaa64313d3ede78b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:19:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dan Bongino Show : Another Mind-Blowing Connection (Ep 1192)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, I address the latest garbage from the lying Democrats about the Trump administration&amp;rsquo;s handling of the Coronavirus threat. I also address the reappearance of this key Spygate player as the scandal continues to grow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;News Picks:Unbelievable! Christopher Steele is &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trump-russia-dossier-was-valid-christopher-steele-defends-controversial-2016-report"&gt;still defending his garbage dossier&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/watchdog-files-foia-lawsuit-against-fbi-over-james-comeys-spies-in-the-white-house"&gt;This 2019 article&lt;/a&gt; provides additional background on why Anthony Ferrante is defending the dossier.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rod Rosenstein was &lt;a href="https://www.redstate.com/elizabeth-vaughn/2020/02/28/stunning-dan-bongino-reveals-fbi-302-dated-may-10-2017-of-fbi-team-tells-rod-rosenstein-the-president-is-not-a-suspect/"&gt;knee-deep in the Spygate scandal&lt;/a&gt; and new documents make the case.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Telling the media where to go is &lt;a href="https://www.bizpacreview.com/2020/02/28/dan-bongino-torpedoes-mediaite-at-cpac-you-guys-are-total-douchebags-and-aholes-891932"&gt;my specialty&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lt. General Flynn is &lt;a href="https://justthenews.com/government/federal-agencies/mike-flynn-seeking-total-exoneration-not-pardon-says-his-attorney"&gt;seeking exoneration&lt;/a&gt; in the witch hunt against him.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/d36d6c4de29f4d04beda3db00cb46104"&gt;Even the AP&lt;/a&gt; is calling BS on the Trump administration&amp;rsquo;s response to the Coronavirus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Copyright Bongino Inc All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@bongino.com (The Dan Bongino Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">734016b76fcc48558ee948d72fea0a88</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/734016b76fcc48558ee948d72fea0a88/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:00:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Two-Minute Briefing : The Evening Briefing: Friday February 28</title><description>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coronavirus live updates | British passenger on Diamond Princess cruise ship dies http://bit.ly/3aeLblA |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markets' downward spiral | FTSE 100 suffers biggest one-week drop since financial crisis http://bit.ly/2I5y1ve |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;London Marathon | Organisers 'closely monitoring' risk of coronavirus&amp;nbsp;http://bit.ly/2uDsAR8 |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Brexit trade deal | France warns EU will not accept 'cherry picking' from Boris Johnson http://bit.ly/3abk8Ys |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abbey Road Studios | Prince Harry joins Jon Bon Jovi to record new charity song http://bit.ly/397Xi3L |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Austin Healey | France will fear coronavirus hitting Grand Slam bid http://bit.ly/397XpfH |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How did weight get 'woke'? | When did dieting become such a dirty word? http://bit.ly/2I6vKjC |&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read all these articles with a digital Telegraph subscription - from £2 per week. Sign up here: http://bit.ly/2WRuvh9. If you're enjoying my audio briefings, please consider encouraging others to sign up for FREE here: http://bit.ly/2XxhVAI.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@telegraph.co.uk (The Two-Minute Briefing)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ffdf3d9d76774ca5a9567a323be59622</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ffdf3d9d76774ca5a9567a323be59622/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 09:43:38 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Checks and Balance : Checks and Balance: Crashing the party</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The centrists of the Democratic Party establishment have only a few days to figure out how to stop Bernie Sanders running away with the nomination. Something similar happened to the Republicans in 2016 when Donald Trump memed his way to the presidency to the horror of party grandees. Mainstream parties in European democracies have also faced challenges from the fringes. Is the era of the party machine over? Or are moderates simply losing the battle of ideas?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subscribe to The Economist for full access to print, digital and audio editions:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.economist.com/pod2020" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.economist.com/pod2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>radio@economist.com (Checks and Balance)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c84a7a53be1345f7bf3c9b05b02be89b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c84a7a53be1345f7bf3c9b05b02be89b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 09:26:36 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>On the Media : Black Swans</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As coronavirus spreads, the Center for Disease Control is warning Americans to take urgent precautions. Meanwhile, the White House says tune out and calm down. On this week’s On the Media, what to expect as COVID-19 threatens to make its way through a ruptured body politic. Plus, amid so much focus on electability, a look at the millions of voters who swing from voting “blue” to simply not voting at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Journalist [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Laurie_Garrett?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor"&gt;@Laurie_Garrett&lt;/a&gt;] on the nature of contagions and how a nation of so-called “epidemic voyeurs” is reacting to a possible pandemic on American soil. &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/otm/segments/epidemic-voyeurs-no-more"&gt;Listen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Farhad Manjoo [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/fmanjoo?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor"&gt;@fmanjoo]&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; opinion columnist, on making prediction in an unpredictable world. &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/otm/segments/chaos-and-certainty-on-the-media"&gt;Listen.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Ibram X. Kendi [&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/DrIbram"&gt;@DrIbram&lt;/a&gt;], executive director of the Antiracist Research and Policy Center at American University and author of &lt;em&gt;How to be an Antiracist&lt;/em&gt;, on the "other swing voter." &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/otm/segments/new-theory-swing-voters"&gt;Listen.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Music:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;John Zorn - Berotim&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cling Mansell &amp;amp; Kronos Quartet - Full Tense&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nino Rota/Enrico Peranunzi &amp;amp; Charlie Haden - Fellini’s Waltz&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Martyn Axe - German Lullaby&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nino Rota - Il Casanova de Frederico Fellini&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;David Bowie/Meridian String Quartet - Heroes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (On the Media)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f7ce6a40c8ad4347a830d75958b125b5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f7ce6a40c8ad4347a830d75958b125b5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill O’Reilly’s No Spin News and Analysis : The O'Reilly Update, February 28, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On today's O'Reilly Update, President Trump addressed the nation this week over growing fears of the Coronavirus…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plus, listeners sound off in Bill's Message of the Day.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@www.billoreilly.com (Bill O’Reilly’s No Spin News and Analysis)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">59897fb39b794217ba9f63da817e9497</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/59897fb39b794217ba9f63da817e9497/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 08:45:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Marketplace Morning Report : Making a correction</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Stock indices and bond yields are falling again on Friday. S&amp;amp;P 500 sees its fastest correction in history. One drug with the potential to fight coronavirus already in the development pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>MorningReportComments@marketplace.org (Marketplace Morning Report)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">970d61048cd04b4280c08fbdad6f653e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/970d61048cd04b4280c08fbdad6f653e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 08:04:46 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Benjamin Dixon Show : Episode 820 | South Carolina Election | Super Delegate Rules | Bloomberg Propaganda</title><description>*** Twice the show with none of the ads. Patreon.com/thebpdshow ***&lt;br /&gt;See you Monday.</description><author>thebpdshow@gmail.com (The Benjamin Dixon Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4e16f27ad0e24d428e885fb11e98ff6a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4e16f27ad0e24d428e885fb11e98ff6a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 08:04:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>TJ Trout : What's new at the Very Large Array</title><description>Dave Finley checks in from the Very Large Array and tells us what new research is happening on 96.3 News Radio KKOB.</description><author>jared.hart@cumulus.com (TJ Trout)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f27f011612ab4285a50ad112a7648077</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f27f011612ab4285a50ad112a7648077/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 07:27:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Relatable with Allie Beth Stuckey : Ep 218 | Stop Calling Me Beautiful | Guest: Phylicia Masonheimer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Phylicia Masonheimer, author of the new book "Stop Calling Me Beautiful," gives us insight into why it’s vital for women to move beyond superficial social media theology and into the depths of the Word of God.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ccardon@glennbeck.com (Relatable with Allie Beth Stuckey)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b365e8f4b46843ccb8d5efe333e28ebe</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b365e8f4b46843ccb8d5efe333e28ebe/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 07:26:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>CBS This Morning - News on the Go : 2/28: Stock markets continues to fall amidst coronavirus fears. Jury member from Harvey Weinstein trials speaks out.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Stock markets dive around the world while governments take urgent new steps to keep coronavirus from spreading. Dr. David Agus looks at how worried we should be. We expect more turmoil today, after coronavirus fears sent the Dow Jones industrial average down almost 1200 points -- its biggest one- day point drop ever. After an emergency meeting this morning, NATO is calling on Russia and Syria to stop what it calls their "indiscriminate air strikes" in northwest Syria. We're learning more about the gunman and the victims in the mass shooting at a Milwaukee brewery. We're learning exclusive new details about how the jury in the landmark trial of Harvey Weinstein reached this week's decision to convict him of first-degree criminal sexual act and third- degree rape. Democrats vote tomorrow in South Carolina’s primary, where Joe Biden now appears to be the heavy favorite.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>CBSNetworkRadioNewsWeb@cbsnews.com (CBS This Morning - News on the Go)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b00f291028b74328b0cbafafeb7f6a8d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b00f291028b74328b0cbafafeb7f6a8d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 07:13:01 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Coronavirus Covid 19 podcast - news, alerts, and updates on the corona virus : Coronavirus Covid 19 news, updates and information for 02/28/2020 a.m. alert</title><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;022820 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is Coronavirus 4-1-1.  The latest Coronavirus info for Friday February 28th, 2020.  Mexico reports their first case of COVID-19 notes The Guardian.  Azerbaijan, Belarus, Estonia, Lithuania, New Zealand, Nigeria and Pakistan also reported their first cases.  According to the New York Times, the case in Nigeria is the first in Sub-Saharan Africa and raises concerns on how an outbreak in Africa would affect the continent.The global total of cases has climbed to 83,300 with 2,858 deaths, the majority in mainland China reports CNN.The Washington Post reports Swiss officials have banned any gathering over 1000 people, this includes the upcoming Geneva International Motor Show which was to have opened next week.  CNN relays that 93 labs in the U.S. will be up and running by the weekend with a two-step test for COVID-19.  The New York Times reports there has been a whistle blower complaint in the U.S. claiming that federal health care workers did not have the proper training or safety equipment while working with quarantined Americans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The locations of U.S. and country diagnoses in a moment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There have been 60 confirmed cases of COVID-19 in the U.S.Of those 60, 6 have recovered and those patients removed from the following list.  Known active locations are as follows: California: 1 in Humboldt County, 1 in Los Angeles County, 1 in Orange County, 2 in San Benito County, 1 in Santa Clara County, 2 in San Diego County, 1 in Solano County  Massachusetts: 1 in Suffolk County Nebraska:  12 in Douglas County Texas:  6 in Bexar County Wisconsin:  1 in Dane County &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Global cases outside of China: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Afghanistan 1, Algeria 1, Australia 23, Austria 2, Azerbaijan 1, Bahrain 36, Belgium 1, Belarus 1, Brazil 1, Cambodia 1, Canada 14,Croatia 2, Denmark 1, Egypt 1, Estonia 1, Finland 2, France 38, Georgia 1, Germany 53, Greece 4, India 3, Iran 388, Iraq 5, Israel 3, Italy 650, Japan 222, Kuwait 45, Lebanon 3, Lithuania 1, Malaysia 25, Mexico 1, Nepal 1, Netherlands 2, New Zealand 1, Nigeria 1, Norway 1, North Macedonia 1, Oman 4, Pakistan 2, Philippines 3, Republic of Korea 2,337, Romania 1, Russian Federation 2, Singapore 96, Spain 25, Sri Lanka 1, Sweden 7, Switzerland 15, Thailand 41, United Arab Emirates 19, United Kingdom 19, Viet Nam 16.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another Coronavirus 411 update daily or as news breaks.  Find the latest information at C-D-C dot GOV-slash-Coronavirus or ask your smart speaker for “The Coronavirus 4-1-1 Podcast”.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>william@soundthatbrands.com (Coronavirus Covid 19 podcast - news, alerts, and updates on the corona virus)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">01de79d3cfd54a2983bd040f3c17c8da</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/01de79d3cfd54a2983bd040f3c17c8da/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 07:06:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Election 2020: Updates from The Washington Post : A surging Bernie Sanders shows few signs of making nice with Democrats</title><description>From "The Daily 202" podcast: Bernie Sanders spoke of “love and compassion” on the day he won the Nevada caucuses last week, extolling the power of “bringing people together,” signs of what some top aides say is Sanders’s new focus on unity.</description><author>jessica.stahl@washpost.com (Election 2020: Updates from The Washington Post)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b8ab210c09ca4c688aabb8e6e348339a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b8ab210c09ca4c688aabb8e6e348339a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 04:37:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Sky News Daily : Greta Thunberg: Climate champion or political pawn? | 28 February 2020</title><description>On this edition of the Sky News Daily podcast with Dermot Murnaghan, we take a look at the Swedish environmental activist's approach to the climate debate - is it the right one?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We also discuss the impact of such global attention on the teenager herself with James Woudhuysen, visiting professor at London South Bank University, and co-founder of the movement Green New Deal UK, Fatima-Zahra Ibrahim.</description><author>radio@sky.uk (Sky News Daily)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e13ff36ddb3f42f7ab1659d5f6b892e6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e13ff36ddb3f42f7ab1659d5f6b892e6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 04:34:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Daily 202's Big Idea : HHS whistleblower complaint alleges botched federal response to coronavirus</title><description>Officials at the Department of Health and Human Services sent more than a dozen workers to receive the first Americans evacuated from Wuhan, China without proper training for infection control or appropriate protective gear.</description><author>jessica.stahl@washpost.com (The Daily 202's Big Idea)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5153519a5b964ed4b3d307f3af1ab395</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5153519a5b964ed4b3d307f3af1ab395/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 04:32:46 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>RTÉ - Today with Sean O'Rourke : The Gathering</title><description>Louise O'Reilly, Sinn Fein TD Dublin Fingal, Grainne Ni Aodha, TheJournal.ie, Daniel McConnell, Political Editor Irish Examiner, Colm Brophy, Fine Gael TD Dublin Douth West</description><author>radio.player@rte.ie (RTÉ - Today with Sean O'Rourke)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">08ca6745064c4152af2b36a1bfd64bd9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/08ca6745064c4152af2b36a1bfd64bd9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Field : Biden’s Last Hope</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former vice president Joseph R. Biden Jr. was once a clear front-runner in the race for the Democratic nomination. Now, he is fighting back from a string of losses and staking his candidacy on his ability to win tomorrow’s South Carolina primary, the first in a state with a large black population. But will he win, and if the margin isn’t as decisive as he hopes, can he stay in the race? Guest: &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/by/astead-w-herndon" target="_blank"&gt;Astead W. Herndon&lt;/a&gt;, who covers national politics for The New York Times traveled to South Carolina with Clare Toeniskoetter and Annie Brown, producers on “The Daily.” For more information on today’s episode, visit nytimes.com/thedaily.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background reading:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new poll showed Mr. Biden with&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/live/2020/south-carolina-primary-02-27#south-carolina-monmouth-poll-biden" target="_blank"&gt; a wide lead in South Carolina&lt;/a&gt;, with Senator Bernie Sanders and hedge fund billionaire Tom Steyer trailing behind.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mr. Biden lashed out after reports that&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/02/sanders-obama-primary-challenge/606709/" target="_blank"&gt; Mr, Sanders considered mounting a primary challenge&lt;/a&gt; to President Barack Obama in 2012, saying it was “one of the reasons I resent Bernie.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Churches have long played the primary role in mobilizing black support in South Carolina.&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/02/27/us/politics/black-church-elections.html" target="_blank"&gt; So how are candidates faring among congregations&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (The Field)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">65343dd9972949dfa6f7df22cf3df110</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/65343dd9972949dfa6f7df22cf3df110/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 03:03:38 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Baltimore Sun : The Baltimore Sun - February 28th, 2020</title><description>Good morning. The forecast in Baltimore today calls for a chance of flurries before 10 a.m. in the afternoon, with a high of about 29 and a low of around 26. I'm Sam Scholl and here are the top headlines from the Baltimore Sun for Friday, February 28th. Former Baltimore Mayor Catherine Pugh was sentenced to three years in federal prison Thursday for a fraud scheme involving her “Healthy Holly” book series. Pugh asked U.S. District Judge Deborah K.</description><author>distribution@spokenlayer.com (Baltimore Sun)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7f7385db215f43f3943be6a330572c02</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7f7385db215f43f3943be6a330572c02/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 03:02:29 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Houston Matters : Friday’s Show: Water Main Break, And Preparing For Coronavirus (Feb. 28, 2020)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On Friday's Houston Matters: We get the latest on a massive water main break on Thursday that flooded the East Loop, stopped traffic, and cut off water supplies to many Houstonians. Also this hour: We learn about efforts to prepare Greater Houston for a potential outbreak of coronavirus. And, from crazy new foods available at the rodeo, to a building in Dallas that just wont be torn down, we discuss The Good, The Bad, and... &lt;a href="https://www.houstonpublicmedia.org/articles/shows/houston-matters/2020/02/28/362098/fridays-show-water-main-break-and-preparing-for-corona-virus-feb-28-2020/"&gt;Read More&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webmaster@houstonpublicmedia.org (Houston Matters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e3e187736d6a430f8d1f4db8eccebdb2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e3e187736d6a430f8d1f4db8eccebdb2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 03:00:20 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Brian Nichols Show : 103: Libertarian Presidential Candidate Dr. Jo Jorgensen</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Continuing with my interview series with Libertarian Presidential Candidates, I am joined on the show this week by (as promised) Dr. Jo Jorgensen!  Dr. Jo Jorgensen (Ph.D in Industrial/Organizational Psychology) was the Libertarian Party Vice-Presidential Nominee with Harry Browne in 1996 and is currently is a Senior Lecturer in Psychology at Clemson University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Jorgensen joins the show today to discuss her experience in Libertarain Party politics, her vision for the Libertarian Party and the liberty movement, and why she believe&amp;#39;s she is the best person to lead the Libertarian Party towards success in the 2020 election. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find Dr. Jorgensen Online-&lt;br&gt;
Website: &lt;a href="https://joj2020.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;https://joj2020.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Facebook: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/JoJorgensen2020/" rel="nofollow"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/JoJorgensen2020/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Twitter: &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Jo4liberty" rel="nofollow"&gt;https://twitter.com/Jo4liberty&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sponsored By:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.lp.org/briannicholsshow" rel="nofollow"&gt;The Libertarian Party&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.lp.org/briannicholsshow" rel="nofollow"&gt;What's the best way to advance liberty?

That's a question I get asked often. You can be an activist, an entrepreneur, a media personality, or politics.

That's why I decided to become a member of the largest pro-liberty party in the United States, the Libertarian Party.  I started my show with the goals to educate, enlighten, and inform, while also advancing the principles of liberty.

The LP is the largest political party in America that, at its core principles, embraces the values of individual liberty, property rights, and non-aggression.  The other two major parties have embraced tribal warfare versus principled debate. It's time we stop feeding the beast and put our money where out mouths are.  

That means putting petty bickering and nonsensical arguments aside and actually advancing liberty.  

The LP, like every political party, has its flaws. 

But instead of focusing on those flaws and tossing stones from the cheap seats, it's time we take personal responsibility (like we promote on a regular basis) and take some responsibility in making the LP the best it can be.

Go to https://www.lp.org/briannicholsshow and become a member today, and join me in making the LP the very best it can be!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.paypal.me/bnichols14" rel="payment"&gt;Support The Brian Nichols Show&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>spangle@wearelibertarians.com (The Brian Nichols Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">374dfedfe40548ecb15d5927960f94a3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/374dfedfe40548ecb15d5927960f94a3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Daily : The Field: Biden’s Last Hope</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Former vice president Joseph R. Biden Jr. was once a clear front-runner in the race for the Democratic nomination. Now, he is fighting back from a string of losses and staking his candidacy on his ability to win tomorrow’s South Carolina primary, the first in a state with a large black population. But will he win, and if the margin isn’t as decisive as he hopes, can he stay in the race? Guest: &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/by/astead-w-herndon" target="_blank"&gt;Astead W. Herndon&lt;/a&gt;, who covers national politics for The New York Times traveled to South Carolina with Clare Toeniskoetter and Annie Brown, producers on “The Daily.” For more information on today’s episode, visit nytimes.com/thedaily.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background reading:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new poll showed Mr. Biden with&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/live/2020/south-carolina-primary-02-27#south-carolina-monmouth-poll-biden" target="_blank"&gt; a wide lead in South Carolina&lt;/a&gt;, with Senator Bernie Sanders and hedge fund billionaire Tom Steyer trailing behind.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mr. Biden lashed out after reports that&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/02/sanders-obama-primary-challenge/606709/" target="_blank"&gt; Mr, Sanders considered mounting a primary challenge&lt;/a&gt; to President Barack Obama in 2012, saying it was “one of the reasons I resent Bernie.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Churches have long played the primary role in mobilizing black support in South Carolina.&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2020/02/27/us/politics/black-church-elections.html" target="_blank"&gt; So how are candidates faring among congregations&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (The Daily)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">842d6d2f97904a3abc65261eb20e202d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/842d6d2f97904a3abc65261eb20e202d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 02:55:39 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Intelligence : Playing with fire: Democrats may get Bern</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The senator’s rise in the Democratic primaries has echoes of Donald Trump’s road to the Republican nomination. He has already changed the tone of the race; can he win it? We take a look at the shadowy history of spies running front companies. And a look back on the life of “Mad Mike” Hoare, an accountant-turned-mercenary. For full access to print, digital and audio editions of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;, subscribe here &lt;a href="http://www.economist.com/radiooffer" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.economist.com/radiooffer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>radio@economist.com (The Intelligence)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8da94e46877e4bca9d5762cfc71e2eb1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8da94e46877e4bca9d5762cfc71e2eb1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 02:44:54 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Start Here : Fever Pitch</title><description>Markets plunge again amid skepticism that government agencies are fully equipped to stop COVID-19 from spreading further. The Biden campaign gets ready for its moment of truth in South Carolina. And riots in Delhi turn deadly.
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt; Like the show? Leave a review: http://bit.ly/ReviewStartHere &lt;p&gt; Follow @StartHereABC for exclusive content, show updates and more:&lt;br&gt; - Twitter: https://www.twitter.com/starthereabc&lt;br&gt; - Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/starthereabc&lt;br&gt; - Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/starthereabc &lt;p&gt; Discover more ABC News podcasts: http://www.abcnewspodcasts.com &lt;p&gt; Start Here is produced by ABC Audio. For more information: http://www.abcnewspodcasts.com</description><author>abc.podcast.support@abc.com (Start Here)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e6956df167104312b01e95211a1b028d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e6956df167104312b01e95211a1b028d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 02:30:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>What Next | Daily News and Analysis : WN TBD: Did Money Corrupt an A.I. Utopia?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;OpenAI was founded in 2015 with a billion dollars and an idealistic mission: Create artificial intelligence that could address humanity’s biggest problems, and do it out in the open. Then came the money problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guest: &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/_KarenHao"&gt;Karen Hao&lt;/a&gt;, senior A.I. reporter at MIT Tech Review&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lizzie O’Leary&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tj.raphael@slate.com (What Next | Daily News and Analysis)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a7af530db7334f2c873e2eda23f2fab4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a7af530db7334f2c873e2eda23f2fab4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>the NewsWorthy : Wall Street Plunge, Biggest Explosion in Universe &amp; Leap Day - Friday, February 28th, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The news to know for Friday, February 28th, 2020! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What to know today about the latest impact from the coronavirus disease, from Wall Street to schools, and we're talking about this weekend's important primary...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Plus: the biggest explosion in the universe, who is taking on Amazon Prime, and explaining Leap Day.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Those stories and more in less than 10 minutes!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Award-winning broadcast journalist and former TV news reporter Erica Mandy breaks it all down for you. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Head to &lt;a href= "http://www.thenewsworthy.com/"&gt;www.theNewsWorthy.com&lt;/a&gt; or see sources below to read more about any of the stories mentioned today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This episode is brought to you by &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href= "http://www.nativedeodorant.com/"&gt;www.NativeDeodorant.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;*Use the code 'newsworthy' for a special offer.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em style= "font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;"&gt; Become a NewsWorthy INSIDER! Learn more here: &lt;a href= "http://www.TheNewsWorthy.com/insider"&gt;www.TheNewsWorthy.com/insider&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sources:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Coronavirus Latest: &lt;a href= "https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/27/business/stock-market-coronavirus.html?action=click&amp;module=Top%20Stories&amp;pgtype=Homepage"&gt; NYT&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.nbcnews.com/business/markets/stocks-enter-correction-dow-plunges-500-points-coronavirus-fears-multiply-n1144116"&gt; NBC News&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.wsj.com/articles/global-stocks-extend-declines-as-coronavirus-concerns-mount-11582784087"&gt; WSJ&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://apnews.com/1631a414cfba8ae39dee4b82748b129b"&gt;AP&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/27/facebook-cancels-its-annual-developer-conference-amid-coronavirus-outbreak.html"&gt; CNBC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;South Carolina Primary: &lt;a href= "https://apnews.com/9dcb221f3339999529d9dbb9ed8bed51"&gt;AP&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.npr.org/2020/02/25/809161942/south-carolina-democratic-primary-debate-preview"&gt; NPR&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://thehill.com/homenews/sunday-talk-shows/484206-sunday-shows-preview-2020-candidates-look-to-south-carolina"&gt; The Hill&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/joe-biden-meets-his-make-or-break-moment-in-south-carolina/2020/02/26/59256c22-58ae-11ea-ab68-101ecfec2532_story.html"&gt; Washington Post&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.cbsnews.com/news/james-clyburn-endorsement-joe-biden-south-carolina-democratic-primary/"&gt; CBS News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Winter Storm Heads East: &lt;a href= "https://weather.com/storms/winter/news/2020-02-25-lake-effect-snow-forecast-great-lakes"&gt; Weather Channel&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://abcnews.go.com/US/winter-storm-heavy-snow-rain-hitting-northeast-biggest/story?id=69251791&amp;cid=clicksource_4380645_9_heads_posts_headlines_hed"&gt; ABC News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Biggest Explosion in Universe: &lt;a href= "https://www.space.com/biggest-cosmic-explosion-universe-discovery.html"&gt; Space.com&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/27/world/biggest-explosion-black-hole-universe-scn/index.html"&gt; CNN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Walmart+ vs. Amazon Prime?: &lt;a href= "https://www.vox.com/recode/2020/2/27/21154357/walmart-plus-walmart-grocery-delivery-unlimited-membership-amazon-prime"&gt; Recode&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;DoorDash Files for IPO: &lt;a href= "https://techcrunch.com/2020/02/27/doordash-ipo/"&gt;TechCrunch&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.wsj.com/articles/doordash-files-confidentially-for-ipo-11582815349"&gt; WSJ&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/27/doordash-ipo-company-confidentially-files-documents-with-sec.html"&gt; CNBC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Krispy Kreme Delivery: &lt;a href= "https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/food/2020/02/24/krispy-kreme-donuts-delivered-doughnut-delivery-starts-leap-day/4812632002/?for-guid=c2ce5934-a6d8-e911-ac30-90b11c343abd&amp;utm_source=usatoday-The%20Daily%20Money&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=baseline_greeting&amp;utm_term=list_article_thumb"&gt; USA Today&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink/krispy-kreme-delivery-leap-day-babies"&gt; Fox News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;LinkedIn Story Feature: &lt;a href= "https://www.forbes.com/sites/paularmstrongtech/2020/02/27/linkedin-to-launch-stories-product-and-yes-itll-be-terrible/#2e7a5cff773e"&gt; Forbes&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://www.theverge.com/2020/2/27/21156247/linkedin-testing-instagram-stories-feature-social-network-resumes-why"&gt; The Verge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Leap Day: &lt;a href= "https://www.usatoday.com/picture-gallery/life/2020/02/27/why-we-need-leap-day-and-other-surprising-facts-about-feb-29/111368024/"&gt; USA Today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Feel Good Friday - &lt;a href= "https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/2-year-old-hugs-grieving-delivery-driver-who-just-lost-his-daughter/"&gt; Good News Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>staff@theNewsWorthy.com (the NewsWorthy)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4476d5ca658f4c5b99b02d8ed8416d25</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4476d5ca658f4c5b99b02d8ed8416d25/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:55:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Advisory Opinions : Alligator Boots</title><description>&lt;p&gt;David and Sarah speak with Liz Murrill, Louisiana's solicitor general, about her case before the Supreme Court June Medical Services v. Russo. The three discuss the facts of the high-profile abortion case, legal strategy, and how Liz preps to face the nation's highest court.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>caleb@thedispatch.com (Advisory Opinions)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">aefe152115364471b2fc2f9a741b7c68</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/aefe152115364471b2fc2f9a741b7c68/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:22:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Deep Background with Noah Feldman : The Coronavirus Isn't Going Away</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Marc Lipsitch, an epidemiologist at Harvard University, predicts that between 40 to 70 percent of adults in the world will become infected with the coronavirus. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marketing@pushkin.fm (Deep Background with Noah Feldman)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f12e23c2ce2845ee83332804c2c78dfc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f12e23c2ce2845ee83332804c2c78dfc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ao Ponto (podcast do jornal O Globo) : A bolsa despencou. E daí?</title><description>Qual é a dinâmica da bolsa e por que o resultado dela impacta a todos, e não apenas a uma parcela muito pequena da população que investe no mercado de ações? Essas perguntas foram feitas pelo estudante de Direito Matheus Almeida Parreira de Souza, em e-mail encaminhado ao Ao Ponto na manhã de quinta-feira, após o tombo de 7% no índice da Bolsa de Valores de São Paulo. Por isso, nesse episódio, a economista Zeina Latif, consultora e doutora em Economia pela USP, vai explicar como a bolsa é importante tanto para quem tem ações como para quem não tem e analisa o impacto do coronavírus e das tensões políticas sobre o mercado. Ela projeta o comportamento da bolsa e do dólar daqui para frente.</description><author>maggi@oglobo.com.br (Ao Ponto (podcast do jornal O Globo))</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2e8906e7f1c14b26ac313d7f019d36cd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2e8906e7f1c14b26ac313d7f019d36cd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 23:55:12 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The News : Friday, February 28</title><description>Russia conducts an airstrike on Turkish forces in Idlib, the likely first case of community-spread COVID-19 in the U.S. appears in California, and the Princeton Debate Panel and Rikers Debate Project discuss enfranchisement of incarcerated individuals.</description><author>managingeditor@dailyprincetonian.com (The News)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e5a6fc3f8b224c75844818210d914cd3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e5a6fc3f8b224c75844818210d914cd3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 23:15:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Off Topic/On Politics : Harvey Weinstein's Conviction and What It Means for Manhattan's District Attorney</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Harvey Weinstein's case has reshaped the political conversation around sexual assault, but what does it mean for Manhattan District Attorney Cy Vance's political future? NY1's Zack Fink, Courtney Gross, and Juan Manuel Benitez analyze.  They also discuss how Chirlane McCray has changed the role of first lady of New York and whether she is considering a run for Brooklyn borough president.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Join the conversation on Twitter: &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/search?f=tweets&amp;q=%23NY1Offtopic" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;#NY1OffTop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/search?f=tweets&amp;q=%23NY1Offtopic"&gt;ic&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ZackFinkNews" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;@ZackFinkNews&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/JuanMaBenitez" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;@JuanMaBenitez&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/courtneycgross" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;@Courtneycgross&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Email: ny1podcasts@charter.com&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For more information: &lt;a href="http://ny1.com/offtopic" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;ny1.com/offtopic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>michael.zilman@charter.com (Off Topic/On Politics)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">70285543a6d74bda928447b1ce1598cc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/70285543a6d74bda928447b1ce1598cc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Townhall Review | Conservative Commentary On Today's News : Democrats in a Panic over Sanders Momentum</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Townhall Review &amp;ndash; February 29, 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hughhewitt.com/"&gt;Hugh Hewitt&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.politico.com/"&gt;Politico&lt;/a&gt; senior writer &lt;a href="https://www.politico.com/states/staff/jake-sherman"&gt;Jake Sherman&lt;/a&gt; take a look at the winners and losers from last Tuesday night&amp;rsquo;s Democratic debate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dennisprager.com/"&gt;Dennis Prager&lt;/a&gt; talks about Senator &lt;a href="https://www.sanders.senate.gov/"&gt;Bernie Sanders&lt;/a&gt; defense of some of the policies of late Cuban dictator &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fidel_Castro"&gt;Fidel Castro&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mikeonline.com/"&gt;Mike Gallagher&lt;/a&gt; examines some of the shocking statements from &lt;a href="https://joebiden.com/"&gt;Joe Biden&lt;/a&gt; prior to the debate in South Carolina.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hughhewitt.com/"&gt;Hugh Hewitt&lt;/a&gt; talks with Presidential assistant &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/people/peter-navarro/"&gt;Peter Navarro&lt;/a&gt; about the Trump Administration&amp;rsquo;s efforts to combat the spread of the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/index.html"&gt;Coronavirus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sebgorka.com/"&gt;Sebastian Gorka&lt;/a&gt; talks with &lt;a href="https://danaloesch.com/"&gt;Dana Loesch&lt;/a&gt; about her book, &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href="https://www.regnery.com/9781684510146/grace-canceled/"&gt;Grace Canceled&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;rdquo; and the trend to withhold grace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dennisprager.com/"&gt;Dennis Prager&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.manhattan-institute.org/expert/heather-mac-donald"&gt;Heather MacDonald&lt;/a&gt;, fellow at the &lt;a href="https://www.manhattan-institute.org/"&gt;Manhattan Institute&lt;/a&gt;, talk about her recent speech at a college where students were encouraged to intimidate and interfere with her speech.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sebgorka.com/"&gt;Sebastian Gorka&lt;/a&gt; talk with actor &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dean_Cain"&gt;Dean Cain&lt;/a&gt; about his faith and Hollywood&amp;rsquo;s reaction to those who express their faith.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thr@salemmedia.com (Townhall Review | Conservative Commentary On Today's News)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e1103a322ba749e091884fcc8cfe6acc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e1103a322ba749e091884fcc8cfe6acc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Opening Arguments : OA364: Will The Supreme Court Shield Trump's Taxes?  (No.)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Today's episode takes a deep dive into the just-filed briefs in the &lt;em&gt;Trump v. Mazars&lt;/em&gt; litigation pending before the Supreme Court regarding the legitimacy of the House's subpoenas for Trump's tax returns. Is the law on the House's side? (Yes, yes it is.) Are we confident that the Supreme Court will rule the right way in a case this bad? (Maybe?) In any event, you'll want to listen!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Announcements&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;Don't forget our &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCztCiOpNCnDZ16gk9VYPBDQ"&gt;YouTube Live Q&amp;A&lt;/a&gt; this Sunday, March 1, at 1:30 pm Eastern / 10:30 am Pacific!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;You still have two days to register for &lt;a href= "https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScnCtmS5-QDXrxptP0WtlsqEcC6dfehEwShGw-RoytuQvYQlw/viewform"&gt; Voter Protection Law School Boot Camp&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We begin with an Andrew Was Wrong(-ish) from our good friend Randall Eliason on the actual frequency of below-guidelines sentences in light of Roger Stone's downward variance.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Then it's time for a deep dive into &lt;em&gt;Mazars v. Trump&lt;/em&gt;, where we look at the briefs filed by the parties and evaluate the arguments made by the Trump administration that the subpoenas issued by the House are invalid. How bad are these arguments? They're bad.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Then, it's time to tackle the recent defamation lawsuit filed by the Trump campaign against the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; regarding a March 2019 op-ed by Max Frankel, in which Mr. Frankel argued that the campaign didn't need to coordinate with Russia to benefit from foreign assistance. Does this pave the way for really good discovery? (No.)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;After all that, it's time for a brand-new #T3BE involving a law prohibiting providing assistance to undocumented aliens. Can Thomas start a new winning streak? Listen and find out. And, of course, you can always play along on social media by using the hashtag #T3BE!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Appearances&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;None! If you’d like to have either of us as a guest on your show, drop us an email at &lt;a href= "mailto:openarguments@gmail.com"&gt;openarguments@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show Notes &amp; Links&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;Remember to check out our &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCztCiOpNCnDZ16gk9VYPBDQ"&gt;YouTube Channel&lt;/a&gt; !&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;If you're thinking about Democratic Voter Protection Law School Bootcamp, &lt;a href= "https://documentcloud.adobe.com/link/track?uri=urn:aaid:scds:US:bf5f4e3e-172d-4e64-af77-41412f0eb157&amp;fbclid=IwAR1BsDw_pus3v3j_O717N3XceZoMtjMAtqeNj0Lf2GDkoV9niiUpziGeQ5M"&gt; check out the flyer&lt;/a&gt; and then &lt;a href= "https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScnCtmS5-QDXrxptP0WtlsqEcC6dfehEwShGw-RoytuQvYQlw/viewform"&gt; apply online&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;n the opening segment, Andrew references &lt;a href= "https://www.ussc.gov/sites/default/files/pdf/research-and-publications/federal-sentencing-statistics/state-district-circuit/2018/dcc18.pdf"&gt; the U.S. Sentencing Commission (2018) report&lt;/a&gt; on sentences.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;in &lt;em&gt;Mazars v. Trump&lt;/em&gt;, check out the President's &lt;a href= "https://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/19/19-715/130092/20200127191622299_19-715%20and%2019-760%20Brief%20for%20Petitioners.pdf"&gt; Jay Sekulow-penned brief&lt;/a&gt; as well as &lt;a href= "https://www.speaker.gov/sites/speaker.house.gov/files/Nos%2019%20715%20760%20%20Merits%20Brief%20Final.pdf"&gt; the just-filed response by the House of Representatives&lt;/a&gt;. You can also read the &lt;a href= "https://scholar.google.com/scholar_case?case=11451189210423463329"&gt; &lt;em&gt;Franchise Tax Bd. v. Hyatt&lt;/em&gt; (2019) decision&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Finally, check out the &lt;a href= "http://openargs.com/wp-content/uploads/Draft_NYT_Complaint_NY_State_Court.pdf"&gt; &lt;em&gt;Trump Campaign v. New York Times&lt;/em&gt; defamation lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;-Support us on Patreon at: &lt;a href= "http://patreon.com/law"&gt;patreon.com/law&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;-Follow us on Twitter:  &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/openargs"&gt;@Openargs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;-Facebook:  &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/openargs/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/openargs/&lt;/a&gt;, and don’t forget the &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/YodelMountain"&gt;OA Facebook Community&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;-For show-related questions, check out the &lt;a href= "http://openargswiki.wikidot.com/"&gt;Opening Arguments Wiki&lt;/a&gt;, which now has its own Twitter feed!  &lt;a href= "http://twitter.com/oawiki"&gt;@oawiki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;-And finally, remember that you can email us at &lt;a href= "mailto:openarguments@gmail.com"&gt;openarguments@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>openarguments@gmail.com (Opening Arguments)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6d80347b5f954004b92723deb4a4d658</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6d80347b5f954004b92723deb4a4d658/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:45:31 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hot Zone with Chuck Holton : Episode 293 - Everyone Was Kung-Flu Fighting!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Another look at the Coronavirus Crisis and how it compares to the "normal" flu.  And a short interview with Todd Bensman of the Center for Immigration Studies!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>holtocw@gmail.com (The Hot Zone with Chuck Holton)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a28e6a58474e47379ba85fd1e39572a3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a28e6a58474e47379ba85fd1e39572a3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:29:24 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The SCNS Live Podcast : SCNS Live Season 9 Episode 5 - Special Guest Cole Houston from All-Con</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We got your news, Special guest Patrick from The Lan Cave. And Jedi Cole from All-Con is here to tell us all about All-Con 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit &lt;a href='https://www.all-con.org'&gt;https://www.all-con.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.facebook.com/events/1089169861422169/'&gt; https://www.facebook.com/events/1089169861422169/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;https://www.extra-life.org/index.cfm?fuseaction=donordrive.participant&amp;participantID=403600&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>admin@untitledscns.com (The SCNS Live Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d8807fd0d55d4c2b853bf668630e0c11</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d8807fd0d55d4c2b853bf668630e0c11/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:26:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Today in Focus : Who should lead Labour?</title><description>Ballots went out to Labour members this week as the race to succeed Jeremy Corbyn as leader intensifies. The remaining candidates, Keir Starmer, Rebecca Long-Bailey and Lisa Nandy, all made their pitches to a live audience at this week’s Guardian hustings in Manchester. Help support our independent journalism at &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://www.theguardian.com/infocus&amp;quot;&amp;gt;theguardian.com/infocus&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;</description><author>userhelp@theguardian.com (Today in Focus)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">74dacef72cb84fac80063269ae475381</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/74dacef72cb84fac80063269ae475381/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:00:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MarketBuzz : 444: Sensex, Nifty to open lower; Infosys, HPCL, IndusInd Bank in focus</title><description>Indian shares are expected to extend losses on Friday following heavy sell-offs in Asian and US stocks, triggered by concerns of the coronavirus turning into a pandemic. IndusInd Bank, which appointed a new CEO, and HPCL, which bought an additional stake in Petronet MHB, are among the stocks in the news.</description><author>sunep.imchen@nw18.com (MarketBuzz)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8262f031b1b54dd1b51e8b14832ea0b5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8262f031b1b54dd1b51e8b14832ea0b5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 18:51:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The KrisAnne Hall Show : Episode 1050 Own a Congressman for a Cool $5Mil and other debate moments</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://youtu.be/wwgmrU7re0A"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch The KrisAnne Hall Show on YouTube&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Break down of the Democratic Debate 2020 South Carolina &amp;amp; how the Republicans made the Democrats who they are.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ensure this Excellent Constitution Training Continues! Partner with The KrisAnne Hall Daily Journal and be a part of the force that will restore Americans with their Constitutional Principles!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To JOIN with us just simply &lt;br&gt;
Go to &lt;a href="https://www.krisannehall.com/index.ph..."&gt;https://www.krisannehall.com/index.ph...&lt;/a&gt; and give&lt;br&gt;
OR&lt;br&gt;
Text- impact2020 to 33777&lt;br&gt;
Subscribe to the KrisAnne Hall YouTube Channel&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=krisannehall1"&gt;http://youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=krisannehall1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Books, DVDs and On Demand Seminars by KrisAnne Hall at&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://krisannehall.com/"&gt;https://KrisAnneHall.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Support this podcast: &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/the-krisanne-hall-show/support" rel="payment"&gt;https://anchor.fm/the-krisanne-hall-show/support&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts44+f0b3c04@anchor.fm (The KrisAnne Hall Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">74fcbf8e9682404e8ecdcc34f1bf015d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/74fcbf8e9682404e8ecdcc34f1bf015d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 18:11:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hardball with Chris Matthews : Chris Matthews: Trump sees coronavirus as an opportunity to divide the country</title><description>&lt;p&gt;President Trump blamed the stock market drops of Monday and Tuesday on Tuesday night's Democratic debate, not market concerns about the coronavirus.&amp;nbsp;Chris says “There are times and events, like the threat of the coronavirus, when we need to trust what government health officials are saying.&amp;nbsp;That includes the person at the top. This isn't about the crowd size at his inauguration.”&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (Hardball with Chris Matthews)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ed4e1cddd5aa4371bf249c8f87b55726</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ed4e1cddd5aa4371bf249c8f87b55726/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 17:32:15 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Gettysburg Connection Podcast : The Adams County Emergency Services Center Answers 911 Calls and Prepares for Disasters [Episode 23]</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;Keeping Adams County residents safe is a big job, and it takes a big team to do it.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;The work is handled in part by the staff at the Adams County Emergency Services Center, located on Greenamyer Lane East of Gettysburg. The center coordinates police, fire, and EMS services for the entire county.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;In addition to the 911 center the team also monitors hazardous wastes, and is the home of the county&amp;#8217;s disaster preparation team.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/022820_0123_TheAdamsCou1.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bladen&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;In this episode I talk with the Directory of Emergency Services, Warren P. Bladen, who explains how the 911 center works and all of the other missions of the emergency services center provides.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/022820_0123_TheAdamsCou2.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/022820_0123_TheAdamsCou3.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;img src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/022820_0123_TheAdamsCou4.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;img src="https://gettysburgconnection.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/022820_0123_TheAdamsCou5.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mail@gettysburgconnection.org (Gettysburg Connection Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e7602d71d7504e6b85640a1654094dcb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e7602d71d7504e6b85640a1654094dcb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 17:23:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Campaign HQ with David Plouffe : South Carolina: What to Watch For</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Jaime Harrison served as the chair of the South Carolina Democratic Party from 2013 to 2017, and is an associate chairman of the Democratic National Committee. Harrison is running for the U.S. Senate from South Carolina in the 2020 election against Lindsey Graham. Jamie provides an overview of South Carolina as we head into Saturday’s primary, and his campaign to defeat Graham.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts@cadence13.com (Campaign HQ with David Plouffe)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">822037d6f4ca4c7aa59b1e77d8a568a7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/822037d6f4ca4c7aa59b1e77d8a568a7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 16:44:10 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Is This Happening? with Chris Hayes : BONUS: Introducing Into America</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As a bonus for Why Is This Happening? listeners, we’re sharing a special preview of Into America, a new podcast about politics, about policy, and the power that both have in shaping the lives of the American people. It is hosted by Trymaine Lee and features the journalists of NBC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the first episode, Trymaine heads to East New York, a community that experienced more stops than any other part of New York City under Former Mayor Bloomberg’s stop and frisk policy. In order to have a real shot at the Democratic nomination, Bloomberg needs the support of Black voters. Days before announcing his candidacy, Bloomberg apologized for the policing tactic. But will his past decision to champion the use of stop and frisk hurt his chances? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subscribe to Into America now: &lt;a href="https://link.chtbl.com/7BcTGqT3?sid=description" target="_blank"&gt;https://link.chtbl.com/7BcTGqT3?sid=description&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>think@nbcuni.com (Why Is This Happening? with Chris Hayes)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c7e60170feaf43748e771c86900d1c0c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c7e60170feaf43748e771c86900d1c0c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 15:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Brothers Talk : The Brothers Talk Episode 3</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The African American Black brothers are sharing their perspectives this week on Black-on-Black crime and other aspects of how their communities and culture are affected by media portrayals and the white power structure...&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thebrotherstalk@gmail.com (The Brothers Talk)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e70ca02a0f924632998695f5eb53dd2b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e70ca02a0f924632998695f5eb53dd2b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>We the People : The Executive and the Rule of Law</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The controversy over the sentencing of President Trump’s former associate Roger Stone has raised larger questions about the role of the Department of Justice, presidential power, and the rule of law including: Should the president be able to influence sentencing in individual cases? What level of control should he have over DOJ? And, more broadly, how should the president exercise power? Host Jeffrey Rosen dives into those questions with Professor John Yoo, former Deputy Assistant Attorney General in the Office of Legal Counsel at the Justice Department, and Professor Kim Wehle, former assistant U.S. attorney in Washington, D.C.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Need a refresher on the Stone sentencing controversy? Here’s a &lt;a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/timeline-extraordinary-turn-events-roger-stone-case/story?id=68921601"&gt;timeline of events&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;em&gt;ABC News.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Questions or comments about the podcast? Email us at podcast@constitutioncenter.org.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jmcdermott@constitutioncenter.org (We the People)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cd8ca334150e4073a9a6e7a648f9a5ba</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cd8ca334150e4073a9a6e7a648f9a5ba/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 14:58:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>This Is America with Rich Valdes Podcast : Collectivism &amp; the Commie Clown-show</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, Rich reviews the latest pitch for socialism from AOC. Then, the highlights from the Nevada stop of communist-sympathizing clown-show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comment and follow on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/richvaldes"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://facebook.com/RichValdesCompany"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or visit us at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://richvaldes.com/"&gt;RichValdes.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Portions of today's program are brought to you by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://justfacts.com/rich"&gt;JustFacts.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://paypal.me/RichValdes" rel="payment"&gt;Support the show.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>rsementa@gmail.com (This Is America with Rich Valdes Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">836707bd38ed40609a3d1f0999419004</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/836707bd38ed40609a3d1f0999419004/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 14:52:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Bold and Blunt : Big Brother Grows Bigger</title><description>&lt;p&gt;OK, so we all know we live in a surveillance society nowadays -- or do we? Caleb Kruckenberg is an attorney who's litigating a case against automated license plate readers. And you will not believe what the government's doing now. This is one of the most important court cases to come. I've got the scoop, it's frightening as all get-out, but you can't afford to miss Caleb's warnings.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>media@washingtontimes.com (Bold and Blunt)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4f2476e4e4424dd28f2eb0123848d702</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4f2476e4e4424dd28f2eb0123848d702/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 14:50:39 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MORNINGS with BOB MARRONE on Radio Westchester ™ : Local Westchester Yorktown Heights Top News Stories of the Day - February 27, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://radiowestchester.com/february-27-2020-6-am-10-am/"&gt;February 27, 2020 – 6 AM – 10 AM&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://radiowestchester.com"&gt;Radio Westchester ™ Local NYC Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>production@radiowestchester.com (MORNINGS with BOB MARRONE on Radio Westchester ™)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1b177f46abe547f0a52a91ab0a683af5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1b177f46abe547f0a52a91ab0a683af5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 14:14:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Into America : Into Bloomberg’s Legacy of Stop and Frisk</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Days before announcing his candidacy, Michael Bloomberg&amp;nbsp;apologized for the use of&amp;nbsp;stop-and-frisk,&amp;nbsp;a policing tactic he championed as Mayor of New York City.&amp;nbsp;In their search for weapons, the New York Police Department made nearly 4.5 million stops over the span of a decade. Eighty-eight&amp;nbsp;percent of people stopped&amp;nbsp;were innocent, and the majority were Black and Latino boys and men.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, in order to have a real shot at the Democratic nomination, the former Mayor needs the support of Black voters. But will his decision to support&amp;nbsp;stop and frisk hurt his chances?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this episode, host&amp;nbsp;Trymaine&amp;nbsp;Lee goes into East New York, a community that experienced more stops than any other part of the city. Plus, a look at whether Bloomberg’s efforts to shore up support with Black voters nationwide will pay off.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further Reading:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/bloomberg-says-he-nearly-eliminated-stop-frisk-mayor-he-fought-n1144266" target="_blank"&gt;Bloomberg says he nearly eliminated stop-and-frisk as mayor. But he fought for it to the end.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/debate-rivals-hammer-bloomberg-over-stop-frisk-policing-nyc-n1139356" target="_blank"&gt;Debate rivals hammer Bloomberg over 'stop and frisk' policing in NYC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/bloomberg-apologizes-stop-frisk-police-practice-n1084756" target="_blank"&gt;Bloomberg apologizes for 'stop-and-frisk' police practice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>news.podcasts@nbcuni.com (Into America)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bf222b10829c452a9740493bfda0aa59</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bf222b10829c452a9740493bfda0aa59/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 14:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Rome Daily Sentinel - Cinema Podcast : February 27, 2020 - 'The Call of the Wild"</title><description>Sentinel movie reviewer Sean Ian Mills answers &amp;quot;The Call of the Wild&amp;quot; and embraces his inner sled dog.</description><author>podcasts@rnymedia.com (Rome Daily Sentinel - Cinema Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5bde7f8ea60647dcb6e2d6f203268a1c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5bde7f8ea60647dcb6e2d6f203268a1c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 12:57:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>John Solomon Reports : Here’s why Mike Flynn’s lawyer is pushing for total exoneration</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Sidney Powell says Trump’s former National Security Advisor is the victim of “egregious government misconduct."&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>media@justthenews.com (John Solomon Reports)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b606130d08124cbea080813d1dec24c5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b606130d08124cbea080813d1dec24c5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 12:48:27 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Erick Erickson Show : Important: Coronavirus Update</title><author>erick@theresurgent.com (The Erick Erickson Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0427366174014465b271e5d7492070ce</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0427366174014465b271e5d7492070ce/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 11:54:33 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Australia in the World : Ep. 41: Richard Maude on the Indo-Pacific, models of world politics, and Australian foreign policy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week Allan and Darren interview Richard Maude, who needs no introduction to regular observers of Australian foreign policy. Until recently, Richard was Deputy Secretary, Indo-Pacific Group, in the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade. Prior to that, he headed the task force responsible for drafting the 2017 Foreign Policy White Paper. From 2013-2016, Richard was Director-General of the Office of National Assessments, and before that he was senior adviser on foreign policy and national security to Prime Minister Julia Gillard. Richard has now taken on a new position at the Asia Society Policy Institute as the inaugural Executive Director, Policy, and Senior Fellow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Allan commences the discussion by asking Richard how he thinks about the “Indo-Pacific” and to describe Australia’s Indo-Pacific strategy. How has the world changed since Richard started working on the Australian Foreign Policy White Paper back in 2016? Darren describes his own shock at the events of 2016, and asks Richard whether he has ever been personally surprised by any events in international affairs which, in turn, caused him to update his own “model” of the world. The conversation then returns to a familiar theme of recent episodes of the podcast, sovereignty, and the logic of Prime Minister Scott Morrison’s emphasis on the concept in developing his government’s foreign policy. Allan contrasts the challenges to the rules-based order that shaped the 2017 Foreign Policy White Paper—in particular relating to the Law of the Sea—with those that have come since, especially emanating from Australia’s allies. Is there still an order to defend and how does a country like Australia do it? And in doing so, will Australia need to be willing to accept trade-offs, such as deemphasising liberalism and democracy, in order to get cooperation on global challenges like climate change, war, or trade?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The conversation moves to China, with Darren asking Richard the extent to which China’s domestic politics factors into his model of China’s behaviour on the world stage, and what major questions remain in his mind regarding China over the coming years. Closer to home, Darren asks whether Richard accepts the premise of two warring “tribes” in the Canberra policymaking community regarding China, and Richard’s answer speaks more broadly to the issue of how to integrate security and economic perspectives into policymaking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the final part of the podcast, Allan asks the perennial question of why those who believe that foreign policy is a critical element of Australian statecraft have been unable to convince successive governments to invest in it, while Darren wonders how foreign policy successes can be measured. The podcast concludes with Richard describing his new role with the Asia Society Policy Institute, and reflections on how think tanks and academics can most effectively attract the attention and shape the views of ministers and policy advisers in Canberra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, we invite our listeners to email us at this address: &lt;a href='mailto:australia.world.pod@gmail.com'&gt;australia.world.pod@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; We welcome feedback, requests and suggestions. You can also contact Darren on twitter @limdarrenj &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We thank AIIA intern Isabel Hancock for research and audio editing, Rory Stenning for composing our theme music and Angus Blackman for technical support in studio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Relevant links&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Maude’s biography via the Asia Society Policy Institute: &lt;a href='https://asiasociety.org/policy-institute/richard-maude'&gt;https://asiasociety.org/policy-institute/richard-maude&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Richard Maude, “Charting a Course for Australia in a Changing Asia”, Asia Society Policy Institute, 13 February 2020: &lt;a href='https://asiasociety.org/australia/charting-course-australia-changing-asia'&gt;https://asiasociety.org/australia/charting-course-australia-changing-asia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Kehoe, “The division in Canberra over China”, Australian Financial Review, 2 December 2019: &lt;a href='https://www.afr.com/policy/foreign-affairs/china-power-struggle-in-canberra-20191128-p53f27'&gt;https://www.afr.com/policy/foreign-affairs/china-power-struggle-in-canberra-20191128-p53f27&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>australia.world.pod@gmail.com (Australia in the World)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">aa3f5441fbdc40998ee6ac2d78b618a1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/aa3f5441fbdc40998ee6ac2d78b618a1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 11:03:15 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>FontCast : Setting the record straight with Robin Gray</title><description>&lt;div&gt;FontCast's second season is off with a bang. Former Tasmanian Premier Robin Gray talks exclusively with Brad Stansfield, and Brad Nowland about the release of his new tell-all book Proud to be Tasmanian. The leader of the state's first Liberal majority government opened up about how his political memoirs would set the record straight after his political opponents had spent decades spreading misinformation about the success of his government.&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>samikin@me.com (FontCast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7548f942d5cf474cb03f17b08308e172</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7548f942d5cf474cb03f17b08308e172/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 11:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Andrew Klavan Show : Ep. 852 - Dems Call For Panic</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The coronavirus is the first actual crisis of the Trump presidency — and the Democrats want to make sure it's as bad as possible. Plus Ben Weingarten on Ilhan Omar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out The Cold War: What We Saw, a new podcast written and presented by Bill Whittle at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar&lt;/a&gt;. In Part 1 we peel back the layers of mystery cloaking the Terror state run by the Kremlin, and watch as America takes its first small steps onto the stage of world leadership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like The Andrew Klavan Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: KLAVAN and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/Klavan"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/Klavan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>andrewklavanshow@dailywire.com (The Andrew Klavan Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e25288427f7149a2abeccfca6c5b0332</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e25288427f7149a2abeccfca6c5b0332/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 10:59:52 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Matt Walsh Show : Ep. 434 - The Criminalization of Childhood</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A 6 year old girl was cuffed, arrested, and charged with criminal assault for having a tantrum at school. This is part of a trend where childhood misbehavior is treated as a criminal matter. Meanwhile, other childhood behaviors are treated as symptoms of mental illness. Why are we doing this to our kids? Plus, Elizabeth Warren says the best way to fight a pandemic is to open our borders. And the House has just made lynching illegal. But wasn't it already illegal?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out The Cold War: What We Saw, a new podcast written and presented by Bill Whittle at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar&lt;/a&gt;. In Part 1 we peel back the layers of mystery cloaking the Terror state run by the Kremlin, and watch as America takes its first small steps onto the stage of world leadership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like The Matt Walsh Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: WALSH and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/Walsh"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/Walsh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mattwalshshow@dailywire.com (The Matt Walsh Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e83ac1c6fadc4d849bf07372e9d54b5f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e83ac1c6fadc4d849bf07372e9d54b5f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 10:10:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sara Carter Show : CPAC 2020:  The Coup: Rosenstein &amp; Comey- The Empire Strikes Back</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Sara A. Carter and Rep. Doug Collins look back at the Russia Hoax live from CPAC. Will Congress act to prevent this from happening again and will anyone be indicted? Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>support@thesaracartershow.com (The Sara Carter Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a9a398d72e834262b1e619f79d54b022</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a9a398d72e834262b1e619f79d54b022/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 09:59:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Pega'os En La Mañana con Julio Rivera Saniel : Pega'os en la Mañana - Jueves, 27 de febrero de 2020</title><author>radioisladigital@gmail.com (Pega'os En La Mañana con Julio Rivera Saniel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4745f64b1f894c6a87c3c9602708872c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4745f64b1f894c6a87c3c9602708872c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 09:43:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Yorker: Politics and More : Rebecca Solnit on Harvey Weinstein and the Lies that Powerful Men Tell</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This week, the former film producer Harvey Weinstein was &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/news/our-local-correspondents/the-weinstein-trials-imperfect-moving-conclusion"&gt;convicted on two counts of sexual assault&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;in a New York court. Weinstein, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/books/double-take/the-reporting-that-led-to-harvey-weinsteins-trial-and-conviction"&gt;who has been accused of sexual misconduct&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;by more than ninety women, has become an emblem of misogyny in Hollywood, and of the systems that&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2019/08/05/alan-dershowitz-devils-advocate"&gt;protect wealthy and powerful men&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;from the consequences of&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2020/01/20/how-far-can-abused-women-go-to-protect-themselves"&gt;criminal misconduct&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Rebecca Solnit joins Dorothy Wickenden to discuss whether the Weinstein verdict is a turning point in the #MeToo movement, and what it takes to expose the lies of those in power in business and politics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (The New Yorker: Politics and More)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9b433ca69b804edc8f38df06585f4986</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9b433ca69b804edc8f38df06585f4986/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Carnegie Council Audio Podcast : Carnegie New Leaders Podcast: Cybersecurity, Norms, &amp; Regulations, with Jason Healey</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are there norms when it comes to cybersecurity? How should governments regulate this emerging domain? What's the role of the private sector? Jason Healey, former head of U.S. Cyber Command, discusses all this and more with cybersecurity analyst Alicia Fawcett. Plus, he explains some of the risks associated with cyberattacks and why, so far, they haven't escalated into anything "kinetic."&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>carnegieitunes@cceia.org (Carnegie Council Audio Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5cfcbe35eeff4de1b34a50f9aab4b74b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5cfcbe35eeff4de1b34a50f9aab4b74b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 08:55:37 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Michael Knowles Show : Ep. 502 - Mass (Media-Generated) Hysteria</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Coronavirus reaches the U.S. President Trump is playing it down, Democrats are playing it up, and no one can tell whether this is much ado about nothing or we’re all going to die. We will examine the mass media-generated hysteria. Then, speaking of not knowing whether you’re alive or dead, Joe Biden gets some good news from a new poll out in South Carolina, two different kinds of Republicans are voting for Bernie, and finally the Mailbag!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out The Cold War: What We Saw, a new podcast written and presented by Bill Whittle at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/coldwar&lt;/a&gt;. In Part 1 we peel back the layers of mystery cloaking the Terror state run by the Kremlin, and watch as America takes its first small steps onto the stage of world leadership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like The Michael Knowles Show, become a member TODAY with promo code: KNOWLES and enjoy the exclusive benefits for 10% off at &lt;a href="https://www.dailywire.com/Knowles"&gt;https://www.dailywire.com/Knowles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>michaelknowlesshow@dailywire.com (The Michael Knowles Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f3fdb74614934306af90298d5773181b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f3fdb74614934306af90298d5773181b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 07:57:43 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>2020 Politics War Room : Antjuan Seawright on South Carolina and Amy Dacey on Possible Brokered Convention</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://blueprintstrategyllc.com/antjuan-seawright/"&gt;Blueprint Strategies&lt;/a&gt; founder and CEO &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/antjuansea"&gt;Antjuan Seawright&lt;/a&gt; shares insight on the debate and primary from South Carolina. Former CEO of the DNC and the current Executive Director of the &lt;a href= "https://www.american.edu/sine-institute/"&gt;SINE Institute of Policy and Politics&lt;/a&gt; at American University &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/AmyKDacey"&gt;Amy Dacey&lt;/a&gt; discusses a possible brokered convention. On the 'Back Page', James and Al lament the administration's management of the coronavirus outbreak. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;2020 Politics War Room is produced by &lt;a href= "https://ncpodcasts.com/politicswarroom"&gt;Native Creative Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; from American University in Washington, DC.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>politicswarroom@gmail.com (2020 Politics War Room)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">75a843a0a7e14e06b8d0f7a0aa5e4b52</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/75a843a0a7e14e06b8d0f7a0aa5e4b52/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Throughline : The Invisible Border</title><description>Today, the border that divides Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland is "soft", in most places you could almost forget that it's there. But for decades it was a deadly flash point in the bitter conflict known as "The Troubles" . This week, we share an episode from &lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/today-explained"&gt;Today, Explained&lt;/a&gt; that takes a look at the history of this conflict and how Brexit could jeopardize a fragile peace.</description><author>podcasts@npr.org (Throughline)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ad0b0607e12e4351b4ad480c7b46060d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ad0b0607e12e4351b4ad480c7b46060d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 21:01:12 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Argument : Trump Emboldened</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Less than a month after the end of his impeachment trial, are we witnessing an emboldened President Trump? The columnists discuss Trump’s cascade of norm-breaking following his acquittal by the Senate — and what it portends for the run-up to the November election. Then, would a proposed executive order aimed at “making federal buildings beautiful again” be an aesthetic win for democracy, or mark a descent into architectural kitsch? Plus, feeding cheetahs. For background reading on this episode, visit&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/column/the-argument" target="_blank"&gt;nytimes.com/theargument&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>argument@nytimes.com (The Argument)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f1bf0dad90ed47089a2675f91d7a123a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f1bf0dad90ed47089a2675f91d7a123a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Global Dispatches -- World News That Matters : How to Build Peace and Fight Terrorism at the Same Time with Judy Kimamo</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Boni Forest is a lush coastal ecosystem on the border between Kenya and Somalia. Its location and geography have made it an ideal hideout for &lt;a href= "https://www.theguardian.com/world/al-shabaab"&gt;al Shebaab&lt;/a&gt; -- the Somali terrorist group that has launched some devastating attacks in Kenya over the last decade. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In 2015, Kenyan security forces mounted an operation to rid the region of al Shabaab. But their heavy-handed tactics alienated the local population, disrupting lives and livelihoods of the people who ostensibly the security forces were meant to protect. The military intervention was failing and people were less secure in their livelihoods.  &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That was until my guest today, Judy Kimamo, helped launch a grassroots peace conference for the region, known as the Boni Enclave Stakeholders Conference.  Over 130 groups attended the conference, including local leaders, government and security officials and various members of civil society.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That was in 2017.  Now, nearly three years later, the positive impact of that peacebuilding effort is still being felt. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Judy Kimamo is the Kenya director for Search for Common Ground, an international non-profit specializing in peacebuilding and conflict resolution. We kick off with an extended conversation about the security problems in the Boni Forest region and the government's initial response, before having a wider conversation about what made her peacebuilding efforts so successful -- and what lessons others may draw in how to design a locally lead peace initiative. When it comes to peacebuilding, what she helped to pull off with the Boni Enclave Stakeholders Conference is quite cutting edge and I'm very glad to bring this story to you. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;My conversation with Judy Kimamo is one episode in a series of supported in part from a grant from &lt;a href= "https://www.carnegie.org/"&gt;Carnegie Corporation of New York&lt;/a&gt; to feature African perspectives on peace and security issues in Africa. Please visit &lt;a href= "https://www.globaldispatchespodcast.com/"&gt;GlobalDispatchesPodcast.com&lt;/a&gt; to view and download other episodes of this series.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Also, when I spoke with Judy Kimamo she was near the Boni Forest region and our audio connection was not strong and the audio quality is not what is typical of this podcast. Still she has an incredible story to tell so I have also posted a transcript to our conversation on &lt;a href= "https://www.globaldispatchespodcast.com/"&gt;GlobalDispatchesPodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>globaldispatchespodcast@gmail.com (Global Dispatches -- World News That Matters)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">371ff486f2424cab8bac7e60a040a47d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/371ff486f2424cab8bac7e60a040a47d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>National Review's Radio Free California Podcast : Episode 108: Industrial-Scale Porn</title><description>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;The San Diego assemblywoman behind AB5 now wants the state Department of Industrial Relations to train porn stars. Seven local officials have sued the state over a 2018 ban on speech that might encourage workers to think about leaving their unions. Hoping to solve homelessness, Governor Gavin Newsom just made it worse. Bonus track: Will talks with two real-estate developers about their encounter with California Environmental Quality Act, the biggest hurdle to new home and commercial construction in the Golden State. Intro music by Metalachi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:dbahnsen@thebahnsengroup.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;dbahnsen@thebahnsengroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="mailto:Will@calpolicycenter.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Will@calpolicycenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/DavidBahnsen" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://twitter.com/DavidBahnsen&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849613000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNGDi1THfaDKOc0ykj_aXLypaAsHxQ"&gt;@DavidBahnsen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/WillSwaim" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://twitter.com/WillSwaim&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNGOR9gLKB7YCPCXIT4c5nnDotollw"&gt;@WillSwaim&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TheRadioFreeCA" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://twitter.com/TheRadioFreeCA&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFZk0kXcxBAnwTB8Z9j_Eki_ZKbGg"&gt;@TheRadioFreeCA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Show Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://thebahnsengroup.com/dividend-cafe/special-wednesday-dividend-cafe-on-the-coronavirus-market-correction/?utm_source=weekly%20email&amp;amp;utm_medium=marketo&amp;amp;utm_campaign=dividend%20cafe&amp;amp;mkt_tok=eyJpIjoiT1RVMk16WTBaamt4WTJSaCIsInQiOiJJZ0tYdzFiOFwvWnV3MHRLZ2gyM2FwUEo5dVVnXC9laGZOUTQ5c3FwT01Jb0RVNE5GMVV4U1pZaWJjN1ZGa0VnNFpvdEk2VFdxeGZZZ1wvSlpcLzF5U2dEblpxaDhMUEUyVWhZNmFMTklWa2xMRXhwbkFBNVUyYkZ3V0VXRUh5MTlGZWIifQ%3D%3D" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://thebahnsengroup.com/dividend-cafe/special-wednesday-dividend-cafe-on-the-coronavirus-market-correction/?utm_source%3Dweekly%2520email%26utm_medium%3Dmarketo%26utm_campaign%3Ddividend%2520cafe%26mkt_tok%3DeyJpIjoiT1RVMk16WTBaamt4WTJSaCIsInQiOiJJZ0tYdzFiOFwvWnV3MHRLZ2gyM2FwUEo5dVVnXC9laGZOUTQ5c3FwT01Jb0RVNE5GMVV4U1pZaWJjN1ZGa0VnNFpvdEk2VFdxeGZZZ1wvSlpcLzF5U2dEblpxaDhMUEUyVWhZNmFMTklWa2xMRXhwbkFBNVUyYkZ3V0VXRUh5MTlGZWIifQ%253D%253D&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHtnuHXAHLrrZyk-jy1wB-9vVQ1vQ"&gt;David Bahnsen: Markets and the madness of disease &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/news/progressive-young-turks-founder-cenk-uygur-asked-staff-not-to-unionize/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.nationalreview.com/news/progressive-young-turks-founder-cenk-uygur-asked-staff-not-to-unionize/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHZ8Iad9p95lZGiSaDVxPTOyn3ysQ"&gt;Progressive Young Turks founder Cenk Uygur asked staff not to unionize&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sacbee.com/news/business/article240257176.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.sacbee.com/news/business/article240257176.html&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHuss58Iqxc_oP2_UTaRPJYPnLBKw"&gt;Newspaper chain McClatchy files for bankruptcy protection&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article240513666.html?fbclid=IwAR3Sb3UDUNIhbjSlgZKSD1-3kwX3fxhrHXedP2U6ITXMO2-MV-22p7w-BJk#storylink=cpy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article240513666.html?fbclid%3DIwAR3Sb3UDUNIhbjSlgZKSD1-3kwX3fxhrHXedP2U6ITXMO2-MV-22p7w-BJk%23storylink%3Dcpy&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNGYo2QZs66YuutRUGl_cptFelT_Jw"&gt;Almost every Californian would get $1,000 a month under universal basic income proposal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://reason.com/2020/02/20/california-bill-would-require-occupational-licenses-for-porn-actors-strippers-cam-girls/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://reason.com/2020/02/20/california-bill-would-require-occupational-licenses-for-porn-actors-strippers-cam-girls/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNGW79hxYWUNeFb9YljFU-nawz2xUQ"&gt;California bill would require occupational licenses for porn actors, strippers, cam girls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article240619377.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article240619377.html&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHPKvdYVAm-umElLFZZIO9hAkVYMw"&gt;Back to the earth: Human composting could become legal in California&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://californiapolicycenter.org/7-reasons-to-question-a-state-utility-takeover/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://californiapolicycenter.org/7-reasons-to-question-a-state-utility-takeover/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFtsyTRYWrEsBVPZOGUn-97lZeYjQ"&gt;Seven reasons to question a state utility takeover&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/californias-janus-jiu-jitsu-11582590067" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.wsj.com/articles/californias-janus-jiu-jitsu-11582590067&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNGjfx0GkaRYWN2FpBBhfcsEZyKF5A"&gt;California’s Janus Jiu Jitsu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/want-fewer-homes-try-this-11582500687" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.wsj.com/articles/want-fewer-homes-try-this-11582500687&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNF7jxkE-gczVhaQglv_usuA780mmw"&gt;Want Fewer Homes? Try This&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.city-journal.org/newsom-empty-words-on-homelessness?fbclid=IwAR2t07OzpX1dADFIyemKv-srLNgLL6sXth0M-ZheJDND2APxi2m0_hrtQRk" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.city-journal.org/newsom-empty-words-on-homelessness?fbclid%3DIwAR2t07OzpX1dADFIyemKv-srLNgLL6sXth0M-ZheJDND2APxi2m0_hrtQRk&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHPE_LGAT_s-VpN2U0HWBwsUOMqfw"&gt;Empty words on Homelessness: Recapping the Governor’s State of the State&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://disrn.com/news/california-gov-newsom-doctors-should-be-able-to-write-prescriptions-for-housing?fbclid=IwAR0HqZmYJGowFPfPv7hVfVU5VrBVZWwmvbnlMWmwVpdGNm6Yn4HE_sSOW_A" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://disrn.com/news/california-gov-newsom-doctors-should-be-able-to-write-prescriptions-for-housing?fbclid%3DIwAR0HqZmYJGowFPfPv7hVfVU5VrBVZWwmvbnlMWmwVpdGNm6Yn4HE_sSOW_A&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFkl8H3Fk9HjmZ2VMCk1SAR2yNB0g"&gt;Gavin Newsom sounds off on homelessness on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ocregister.com/2020/02/13/unhoused-symposium-at-usc-gives-federal-state-and-local-decision-makers-forum-to-address-homelessness/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.ocregister.com/2020/02/13/unhoused-symposium-at-usc-gives-federal-state-and-local-decision-makers-forum-to-address-homelessness/&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFWgDDp4H91D87NxoN1QQZFcUSLUg"&gt;Poll: Homelessness, not climate change or immigration, is No. 1 problem in California&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.publicnow.com/view/D1099B36310F4F3FFE0C367DB657BDBA6BA4BE71" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.publicnow.com/view/D1099B36310F4F3FFE0C367DB657BDBA6BA4BE71&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1582832849614000&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNFWVjhYInFU2WPbEzNZuGsYkN5TfA"&gt;UTLA chief: ‘Win the school board in 2020 to win bigger in 2022’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>studio@nationalreview.com (National Review's Radio Free California Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">72738ba6fc194a938b6788cc0e2a007b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/72738ba6fc194a938b6788cc0e2a007b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 15:27:31 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Savage Nation Podcast : Coronavirus a Real Threat PLUS Democrat Debate Notes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;People are misleading the public on the dangers of Coronavirus; San Francisco declares state of emergency; Savage raps on the latest Democrat debate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miguel Hernandez, a building supervisor from New York, is running against AOC and joins the show to talk about his goals and plans. Learn more about him and help him unseat AOC by going to miguelhernandezforcongress.org&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wwopodcasts@westwoodone.com (The Savage Nation Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">56f89eee8ec341b6b83d5d14a7c3ea85</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/56f89eee8ec341b6b83d5d14a7c3ea85/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 14:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hold These Truths with Dan Crenshaw : The New Energy Frontier, with Nigel Jenvey</title><description>&lt;p&gt;What is carbon capture? Can we really use this technology to turn CO2 into a commodity? It might sound like science fiction, but it’s actually the New Energy Frontier in America.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Nigel Jenvey is an industry leader and expert in Carbon Capture, Utilization and Storage (CCUS), having previously held roles such as the chair of the CO2 Capture Project, chair of the North American CCS Association, and program chair of the Society of Petroleum Engineers CCUS Technical Section. He leads the Carbon Management practice at Gaffney-Cline, a global oil and gas consultancy, helping clients understand the wide variety of options available that will ensure continued business success through the energy transition. He has over 23 years of global oil and gas industry experience in technology, exploration, development and production operations with major oil and gas operating companies.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>danny.walden@mail.house.gov (Hold These Truths with Dan Crenshaw)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f5a39f5768b948698dd67b775bf7f523</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f5a39f5768b948698dd67b775bf7f523/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 13:14:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Editors : Episode 192: Just How Concerning Is the Coronavirus?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today on &lt;em&gt;The Editors&lt;/em&gt;, Rich, Michael, Luke, Alexandra, and Jim discuss last night’s dreadful debate, the increasing dangers of the coronavirus, and the disappointing (but not unexpected) defeat of the Born-Alive bill in the Senate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Light Items&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rich: Going to a spring training game.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michael: Having an engineer as a cousin.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Luke: Erik Larson, &lt;em&gt;The Splendid and the Vile&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alexandra: Why Ash Wednesday is one of my favorite days of the year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jim: Demolishing an old backyard swing set.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Editors’ Picks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rich: &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/a-fetus-that-was-born/"&gt;Xan’s Corner post on a CNN report’s ridiculous wordsmithing.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michael: Daniel Tenreiro on &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/02/scientific-stagnation-is-not-inevitable/"&gt;how scientific stagnation isn’t inevitable&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Luke: Brookhiser’s “&lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/magazine/2020/02/24/has-the-presidency-become-impossible/"&gt;Has the Presidency become Impossible?”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alexandra: &lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/the-tuesday/the-poison-of-nostalgia/"&gt;Kevin’s first email newsletter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jim: MBD’s “&lt;a href="https://www.nationalreview.com/2020/02/coronavirus-media-kowtows-to-chinese-government/"&gt;Death by Kowtow&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Editors&lt;/em&gt; is hosted by Rich Lowry and produced by Sarah Schutte.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>studio@nationalreview.com (The Editors)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fcb303abbba940d48eb1472e8fe3b72a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fcb303abbba940d48eb1472e8fe3b72a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 13:12:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Individual 1 podcast : Interview with Cable News Veteran David Shuster</title><description>&lt;div&gt;John interviews/debates cable news veteran anchor David Shuster about his belief that Bernie Sanders will defeat Donald Trump. John also reviews the Democratic Debate and previews the South Carolina Primary. &lt;/div&gt;</description><author>batoul.peters@globalstorynetwork.com (Individual 1 podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b6a7d27ca49a4030a06a9cde081b4e64</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b6a7d27ca49a4030a06a9cde081b4e64/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 12:25:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Full Frontal Honesty in Real Estate  : How To Buy A Home NOW in Phoenix Arizona 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;How do you win the bidding wars to purchase a home in Phoenix right now?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What are the top 5 ways to save money &amp;amp; WIN the bidding war for the nicest homes?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Krista Bergh stops by to chat for a bit&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts37+b93548@anchor.fm (Full Frontal Honesty in Real Estate )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">29ddfe262a8b4f75be4f4f290a5e27d0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/29ddfe262a8b4f75be4f4f290a5e27d0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 10:31:49 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Graham Allen’s Dear America Podcast : EP 69 | The TRUTH About Human Trafficking | Guest: Jaco Booyens</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this very important episode of Dear America, Graham and Producer Jake sit down with Jaco Booyens. Jaco has been leading the charge in combatting human trafficking in the US and around the world. We hear tips about how to keep your kids safe as well as how to start noticing warning signs around you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PatriotMobile.com/Graham&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WeThePeopleHolsters.com/GRAHAM OFFER CODE: Graham&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PrepareWithGraham.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RedArrowWeapons.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>dearamerica76@gmail.com (Graham Allen’s Dear America Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d2d0b2468c834028939e9dcf2c540594</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d2d0b2468c834028939e9dcf2c540594/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Between The Lines Radio Newsmagazine podcast : Between The Lines - Feb. 26, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In Trump’s Run for Re-Election, a Move to Make a Peace Deal with Taliban; Labor Unions and the Fight for Medicare For All; Protests Target FERC for Penalizing Renewable Energy Sources&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visit our website at &lt;a href="https://btlonline.org/"&gt;BTLonline.org&lt;/a&gt; for more information, links, transcripts and in-depth interviews. (Updates after 3 p.m. ET Wednesdays) Follow us on Facebook at BetweenTheLinesRadioNewsmagazine and on Twitter @BTLRadioNews. Join our new Patreon community at Patreon.com/BetweenTheLinesRadioNewsmagazine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="https://secure.givelively.org/donate/squeaky-wheel-productions/support-progressive-voices-to-defend-democracy-and-fight-fascism"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (https://secure.givelively.org/donate/squeaky-wheel-productions/support-progressive-voices-to-defend-democracy-and-fight-fascism)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>contact@btlonline.org (Between The Lines Radio Newsmagazine podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2bab2a620ac4468285b324d2966671e2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2bab2a620ac4468285b324d2966671e2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Commentary Magazine Podcast : SC Debate: Anything Could Have Been Finer...</title><description>...than to be a Democrat in South Carolina in the evening. Last evening. We take apart the train wreck of a debate on today's podcast. Give a listen.</description><author>feeds@soundcloud.com (Commentary Magazine Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e7c56ca458594c2f9813c6a25f28269e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e7c56ca458594c2f9813c6a25f28269e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 08:19:54 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>BE THE PEOPLE : 🎧 What Americans Need to Know About the Coronavirus</title><description>On December 31, 2019, we learned about an outbreak in Wuhan, China of the coronavirus, a deadly respiratory disease spread from contact with infected persons. As of February 25th, the disease had infected more than 78,000 people in 34 nations. More than 50 Americans are infected. Joining me today to discuss the coronavirus (Covid-19) and how we can protect ourselves from this and other infectious diseases is Dr. Marilyn Singleton. Dr. Singleton is a board-certified medical doctor (anesthesiologist, member of the Association of American Physicians and Surgeons, and Physicians for Reform), and an attorney. She is also a conservative activist and a 2012 congressional candidate.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For Further Insight:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Website: &lt;a href="http://www.theconservativepundit.net/meet-the-pundits/dr-marilyn-m-singleton-md-jd/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;http://www.theconservativepundit.net/meet-the-pundits/dr-marilyn-m-singleton-md-jd/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Twitter: &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MSingletonMDJD" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://twitter.com/MSingletonMDJD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Physicians for Reform: &lt;a href="https://www.physiciansforreform.org/"&gt;https://www.physiciansforreform.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Additional Information About the coronavirus. &lt;br /&gt;
Johns Hopkins Website:  &lt;a href="https://systems.jhu.edu/research/public-health/ncov/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://systems.jhu.edu/research/public-health/ncov/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Johns Hopkins Experts:  &lt;a href="https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/02/20/coronavirus-carey-799-em0-art0-qa-health/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://hub.jhu.edu/2020/02/20/coronavirus-carey-799-em0-art0-qa-health/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><author>Talk@AmericaOutLoud.com (BE THE PEOPLE)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6c07d9cddc3e4d31a2c2c5c681ddb8e9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6c07d9cddc3e4d31a2c2c5c681ddb8e9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 06:07:54 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>City Journal's 10 Blocks : How the Plastic Panic Hurts Us—and the Planet</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.city-journal.org/contributor/john-tierney_912" target= "_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;John Tierney&lt;/a&gt; joins &lt;a href= "https://www.city-journal.org/contributor/brian-c-anderson_6" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Brian Anderson&lt;/a&gt; to discuss the campaign to ban the use of plastic products and the flawed logic behind the recycling movement—the subjects of Tierney’s story, "&lt;a title= "https://www.city-journal.org/needless-panic-over-disposable-plastic" href= "https://www.city-journal.org/needless-panic-over-disposable-plastic" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;The Perverse Panic over Plastic&lt;/a&gt;," from the Winter 2020 Issue of &lt;em&gt;City Journal&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hundreds of cities and eight states have outlawed or regulated single-use plastic bags. But according to Tierney, the plastic panic doesn't make sense. Plastic bags are the best environmental choice at the supermarket, not the worst, and cities that built expensive recycling programs—in the hopes of turning a profit on recycled products—have instead paid extra to get rid of their plastic waste, mostly by shipping it to Asian countries with low labor costs. However, the bans will likely continue as political leaders and private companies seek a renewed sense of moral superiority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/CityJournalPodcasts/~4/xE5mB2eBsgo" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>aricks@manhattan-institute.org (City Journal's 10 Blocks)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">833f9b67b42e40359f8972accd0364e7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/833f9b67b42e40359f8972accd0364e7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 04:55:58 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WFUV's Cityscape : 'Fry Bread' Celebrates Native Heritage</title><description>A favorite family recipe has the power to pass love and culture down through generations.    Our guest on this week's Cityscape believes in this power so much that he decided to write a book about it, highlighting his own heritage and hoping he can reach a new audience with it.   Kevin Noble Maillard’s new children’s book&lt;em&gt; Fry Bread&lt;/em&gt; is a celebration of Native American family tradition through a delicious dish. With Juana Martinez-Neal’s illustrations, the book shows a culture Maillard says is all too often excluded from children’s literature.</description><author>newsroom@wfuv.org (WFUV's Cityscape)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">29f51d9107e945c9a47265f90e569532</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/29f51d9107e945c9a47265f90e569532/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Latest : The South Carolina Debate</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On the debate stage in Charleston, candidates went after Senator Bernie Sanders, painting his potential nomination as dangerous for the party and questioning his chances of winning against President Trump. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The Latest,” from the team behind “The Daily,” brings you the most important developments on today’s biggest news stories. You can find more information about it&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/column/the-latest" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thedaily@nytimes.com (The Latest)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a9cf726f0eca478388f160f9e0ebc78b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a9cf726f0eca478388f160f9e0ebc78b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 02:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dispatch Podcast : Arrogance is Folly</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With South Carolina and Super Tuesday on the horizon, Sarah and the guys take a closer look at the Democratic field, examine the Trump administration's search for disloyalty, and weigh in on the Harvey Weinstein verdict and latest on coronavirus.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>caleb@thedispatch.com (The Dispatch Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">be988447fcde4327b2bca99f97b95674</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/be988447fcde4327b2bca99f97b95674/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:17:15 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Views from Hong Kong : Discord between Lam's administration and pro-establishment parties</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to another episode of Views from Hong Kong!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our topics for today are:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- The increasingly public rift between the pro-establishment parties and Carrie Lam's administration.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- A discussion of an Op-ed by the retired Court of Final Appeal judge Henry Litton regarding the anti-mask law. The Op-ed can be found here: &lt;a href="https://www.scmp.com/comment/opinion/article/3046561/why-challengers-hong-kongs-anti-mask-law-have-no-case"&gt;https://www.scmp.com/comment/opinion/article/3046561/why-challengers-hong-kongs-anti-mask-law-have-no-case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have questions/comments, please write to us at viewshk@outlook.com. We would love to hear from you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow us on twitter @viewshk. Located here: https://twitter.com/viewshk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disclaimer: The views and opinions expressed on the podcast are those of the authors only and do not necessarily reflect the views of any other person or organisation. The authors do not give advice via the podcast and do not warrant or represent the accuracy, completeness, correctness, suitability or validity of any information given on the podcast.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>viewshk@outlook.com (Views from Hong Kong)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a5344ffdf35742d5b87d2e7ee3aadf5a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a5344ffdf35742d5b87d2e7ee3aadf5a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>You Decide with Errol Louis : Shira Scheindlin: The Stop-and-Frisk Judge Rules on Mike Bloomberg’s Campaign for President</title><description>&lt;p id="cq-gen278"&gt;Judge Shira Scheindlin spent years handling some of the most high-profile cases in the country, including the stop-and-frisk lawsuit in which she ruled against the Bloomberg administration and changed the policy of the NYPD. She joined Errol to weigh in on Mike Bloomberg’s apology, his run for president, and how criminal justice has changed during her career on the bench.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="cq-gen279"&gt;Join the conversation using the hashtag #NY1YouDecide or give us a call at 212-379-3440 and leave a message.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>michael.zilman@charter.com (You Decide with Errol Louis)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d99fedc0b5b941db9daa66cad01cc2ce</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d99fedc0b5b941db9daa66cad01cc2ce/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Federalist Radio Hour : Matt Walsh On The Death Of The Church And Secularism</title><description>Matt Walsh joins host Ben Domenech to discuss his new book "Church of Cowards: A Wake-Up Call to Complacent Christians," the death of the church, and growing secularism among younger generations.</description><author>info@podcastone.com (The Federalist Radio Hour)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">00dd9744f74c40b09f59d22f8350e2ea</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/00dd9744f74c40b09f59d22f8350e2ea/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Pronoia Now Network : Secrets to Happy Healthy Living - Ep 121</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Learn how to beat those PMS blues for both women AND men!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mysticandwizard@gmail.com (Pronoia Now Network)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0a8f33266eca45cabbc69fe209ea6a06</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0a8f33266eca45cabbc69fe209ea6a06/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 17:34:54 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Beating Around The Bush : S3E6 - EvokeAg, Auctions Plus record, Water harvesting ban lifted, and Rain Guilt</title><description>&lt;div&gt;This week’s take on the news relating to rural and regional Australia with Fleur Anderson and Wade Dabinett.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agribusiness&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Auctions Plus breaks their monthly listings record&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2017-04-11/cattle-auction-website-auctionsplus-breaks-monthly-listings/8434234" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2017-04-11/cattle-auction-website-auctionsplus-breaks-monthly-listings/8434234&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Politics:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Water harvesting ban lifted&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.smh.com.au/national/water-harvesting-ban-lifted-after-direct-pleas-from-farming-lobby-boss-20200220-p542u2.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.smh.com.au/national/water-harvesting-ban-lifted-after-direct-pleas-from-farming-lobby-boss-20200220-p542u2.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Community:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Rain Guilt. Story on ABC Western Qld on FB about Rain Guilt. Talk about the complicated relationship with rain.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/jessicavanvonderenABC/videos/547246955877953/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/jessicavanvonderenABC/videos/547246955877953/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Shoutouts:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Competition update: Don’t forget you’ve got one week left to enter for your chance to win our brilliant little prize pack and a slab (or carton or case depending which side of the border you’re on) of Longtrail’s finest…&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://gleam.io/NCpeb/beating-around-the-bush-30k-giveaway" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://gleam.io/NCpeb/beating-around-the-bush-30k-giveaway&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;My Favourite Plenary is Bonus Episode that will be in feed before this goes to air&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Fleur gives her Top 3 (or maybe 4) take homes from this past week’s Agrifutures EvokeAg Conference in Melbourne.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;﻿Follow Us:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Join the Rural Business Collective community and join the conversation over at &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/ruralbusinesscollective/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/ruralbusinesscollective/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/ruralbusinesscollective/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Beating Around the Bush is the podcast of the &lt;a href="https://www.ruralbusinesscollective.com.au/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Rural Business Collective&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.ruralbusinesscollective.com.au/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;www.ruralbusinesscollective.com.au&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This is a &lt;a href="https://www.cahootsradio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Cahoots Radio&lt;/a&gt; production edited by Skye Manson &lt;a href="https://www.cahootsradio.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;www.cahootsradio.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Hosted by &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/wade-dabinett-947763167" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Wade Dabinett&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/wade-dabinett-947763167/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/in/wade-dabinett-947763167/&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/fleuranderson/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Fleur Anderson&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/fleuranderson/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/in/fleuranderson/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Let us know your favourite news stories for the week on email - &lt;a&gt;podcasts@ruralbusinesscollective.com.au&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>fleur@thecahootsgroup.com.au (Beating Around The Bush)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6e8028b478134786aea0b43ee088e734</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6e8028b478134786aea0b43ee088e734/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Make Me Smart with Kai and Molly : When CDC says “…this might be bad.”</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8230; it&amp;#8217;s bad. There are now 80,000 cases of COVID-19 worldwide, including new diagnoses in Italy, Iran and South Korea. This news has sent American markets plummeting, and prompted the CDC to warn of an outbreak Tuesday morning, but the World Health Organization isn&amp;#8217;t declaring a pandemic yet. Here to talk with us about pandemics past and their economic effects is is Olga Jonas, a senior fellow with the Harvard Global Health Institute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Subscribe to the &amp;#8220;Make Me Smart&amp;#8221; newsletter at Marketplace.org/newsletters and tell your Echo device to &amp;#8220;make me smart&amp;#8221; for daily explainers.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>makemesmart@marketplace.org (Make Me Smart with Kai and Molly)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">511768e7fffa46f4a7afcfbc5675abe9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/511768e7fffa46f4a7afcfbc5675abe9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 16:54:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Jay Talk : Episode 16: Luke Mitchell Joins</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, the boys talk with Creighton soccer player Luke Mitchell. Luke talks about his path to Creighton, the team this year, and his haircut business 'Creighton Cuts.' Follow @CreightonCuts on Instagram and DM him if you are interested in a haircut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Later on in the episode (32:13), Tyger talks with Demi Brown, the founder of the Creighton College Diabetes Network. Either email &lt;a href='mailto:creighton@collegediabetesnetwork.org'&gt;creighton@collegediabetesnetwork.org&lt;/a&gt; or follow @creighton.cdn on Instagram for more information. &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">b8e914ea87e74d75a3968b75a0ec9da4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b8e914ea87e74d75a3968b75a0ec9da4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 14:51:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Brendan O'Neill Show : Claire Fox: inside the European Parliament</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Claire Fox, the former Brexit Party MEP and director of the Academy of Ideas, talks to Brendan O’Neill about her time in the European Parliament, the demonisation of Leave voters, and how to make democracy come alive after Brexit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Claire is also the co-convenor of ‘Changing Politics for Good: What Next?’, which will take place at the Cheshire Conference Centre in Stockport on 29 February. Get tickets: &lt;a href='https://www.changepolitics4good.co.uk/'&gt;https://www.changepolitics4good.co.uk/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thebrendanoneillshow@spiked-online.com (The Brendan O'Neill Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ae797ecf7b6b48449f358350331779c3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ae797ecf7b6b48449f358350331779c3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 12:44:12 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Patriots Fight Media : Q Drops 2/24/20 Obama Insurgency and Clinton Foundation Whistleblowing</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Q poses the question: Was the Obama Administration leading an insurgency against the U.S.? And Clinton Foundation whistleblower Nate Cain tells all in a podcast interview.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ford@patriotsfight.com (Patriots Fight Media)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ac41aada45804dbe8d249bbc1428edac</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ac41aada45804dbe8d249bbc1428edac/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Realignment : Ep. 26: Senator Tom Cotton</title><description>Marshall and Saagar return to Capitol Hill to speak with Arkansas Senator Tom Cotton about the Coronavirus outbreak, the Chinese Communist Party, and the case for American leadership abroad.</description><author>phegseth@hudson.org (The Realignment)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7ab9c272ab3b4483a32ba2218b80c3e1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7ab9c272ab3b4483a32ba2218b80c3e1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 04:00:11 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Effective Compassion : Episode 9: Housing First</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Downtown Austin. Anna Johansen, Charissa Koh, and Marvin Olasky visit two agencies fighting homelessness on the front lines. One agency focuses on short-term emergency shelter; the other on long-term housing. Both organizations are working to get people off the street. But should that be the primary standard of success?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Effective Compassion is a production of WORLD. Learn more at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="http://wng.org/" class="c-link" target="_blank"&gt;wng.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>feedback@worldandeverything.com (Effective Compassion)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a12a4b4ff53344848b9dc450bf48c894</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a12a4b4ff53344848b9dc450bf48c894/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:15:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Who Is? : Who is Mike Pence?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Vice President Mike Pence, who has described himself as “a Christian, a conservative, and a Republican, in that order,” for decades, was born a Catholic Democrat, but rose to prominence as an Evangelical conservative. Once elected to Congress, his friendly attitude toward big business attracted the attention of billionaire donors like Charles Koch. But as Governor of Indiana, Pence became infamous for how his faith informed his politics, from praying for an answer to an HIV outbreak in Scott County, to advocating for a religious freedom policy that enabled business owners to discriminate against LGBTQ+ people. Then came Donald Trump. On the penultimate episode of the first season of Who Is, Sean Morrow turns to Pence biographer Tom LoBianco, to try to understand the man who could be the next President of the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/tomlobianco"&gt;Tom LoBianco&lt;/a&gt;, Reporter and Author of &lt;em&gt;Piety &amp;amp; Power: Mike Pence and the Taking of the White House&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/sarahposner"&gt;Sarah Posner&lt;/a&gt;, a Reporting Fellow at Type Investigations, where she covers the religious right, white nationalism, and more. Her latest book, &lt;em&gt;Unholy: Why White Evangelicals Worship at the Altar of Donald Trump&lt;/em&gt;, is out on May 26, 2020 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/laura_ungar"&gt;Laura Ungar&lt;/a&gt;, a Midwest Editor and Correspondent at Kaiser Health News. Ungar recently returned to Austin, Indiana, for a look at how the city has recovered, and to evaluate the challenges faced by those living in rural America, for Kaiser Health News and NPR. Her extensive coverage of Austin may be found at &lt;a href="https://www.courier-journal.com/"&gt;https://www.courier-journal.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Who Is?)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">24a348572e6d4b88ab41b797abc29320</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/24a348572e6d4b88ab41b797abc29320/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hear the Bern : 46 - Can't Stop Us Now (w/ Dr. Victoria Dooley)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Fresh from his massive win in Nevada, which confirmed his status as front-runner for the Democratic nomination, Bernie has come under attack for being "divisive." Strange, then, that Bernie's support is the most diverse of any campaign in the race, and he routinely wins head-to-head match-ups against both Donald Trump and the other Democratic candidates. Briahna explains why efforts by the establishment to tear down this multiracial, working-class coalition will fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, in our final episode of Black History Month, Briahna chats with a panel of Black Bernie staffers about why they support "the old white guy" and with Dr. Victoria Dooley about the lives Medicare for All would save in her diverse medical practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The panel guests:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sam Adaramola, Media Producer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Terrel Champion, Policy Advisor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Erica England, Operations Manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christopher Moore, Associate Studio Producer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Samaria Phillips, Media Producer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Victoria Dooley on Twitter: &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/DrDooleyMD"&gt;https://twitter.com/DrDooleyMD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hearthebern@berniesanders.com (Hear the Bern)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e5751f54d17543279a38e9132f5e9f03</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e5751f54d17543279a38e9132f5e9f03/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 20:59:48 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MEDIA INDIGENA : Indigenous current affairs : Ep. 198: Political Pundits' Push-Back on 'Protectors'</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week: Choosing our words carefully. When discussing those who oppose resource extraction, how important is it to call them &lt;em&gt;protectors&lt;/em&gt; rather than protesters? And when it comes to the members of a dominant society horny for such extraction, how vital is it that they be called &lt;em&gt;Settlers?&lt;/em&gt; Judging by the dust these debates still kick up, a lot! And wouldn’t you know it, among those kicking was our own Candis Callison, associate professor in the School of Journalism at UBC. Also at the roundtable this week with host/producer Rick Harp is Kim TallBear, associate professor in the Faculty of Native Studies at the University of Alberta.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;// Our theme is 'nesting' by birocratic.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>indigena.group@gmail.com (MEDIA INDIGENA : Indigenous current affairs)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">089031917f554cbeb390398d971aa171</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/089031917f554cbeb390398d971aa171/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 14:21:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>UnAborted : They Actually Think Abortion is Funny | UnAborted Ep. 35</title><description>&lt;p&gt;They said the quiet part out loud folks. They actually think abortion is funny. Last week, Alabama Senator Doug Jones laughed at the question, “should abortion be banned after 5 months?” calling it a stupid question. At the same time in the same state, Representative Rolanda Hollis proposed a law that would require that all men get a vasectomy after they turn 50 or after the birth of their third child. But Rep. Hollis admits that her “vasectomy bill” is a JOKE proposed to neutralize Alabama’s attempted abortion ban in 2019. We will examine why the Left finds abortion so funny and you so stupid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Date: 02/24/20&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>seth@prolifetraining.com (UnAborted)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fa81404538b644c5afcd9f92314e0b16</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fa81404538b644c5afcd9f92314e0b16/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 13:27:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>I'm Calling Bovine Scatology : Food Deserts Are Starving Americans?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The liberals tell us food deserts are starving Americans. Is it true? Phil Valentine calls bovine scatology on that.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>phil@philvalentine.com (I'm Calling Bovine Scatology)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9cfb8530d019495792f7f9a4e05fd622</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9cfb8530d019495792f7f9a4e05fd622/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 10:33:22 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Young Nation Radio : “The Balance”</title><description>Your Hosts Rocky B and Cali Rashad in this episode will express their differences on being an entrepreneur versus working in corporate America.</description><author>podcasts49+1047150c@anchor.fm (Young Nation Radio)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">54f4cc207f4040cbbe0901e8a0649993</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/54f4cc207f4040cbbe0901e8a0649993/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 08:11:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>So You Wanna Be President? with Chris Matthews : 6 - Go Negative</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It's the oldest, worst, and most effective part of American politics: go negative. Voters say they hate it, but it works. There's no way to frame your opponent's weakness any better. Chris deconstructs history's hardest hits—and how they were so effective—with Andrea Mitchell, senior Washington correspondent for NBC News and host of "Andrea Mitchell Reports," and Mike Murphy, who's handled media and strategy for Republicans running for President, the US Senate, and governorships.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>nbcnews.podcasts@gmail.com (So You Wanna Be President? with Chris Matthews)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fedfa350faf4417a9d807d6758dde840</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fedfa350faf4417a9d807d6758dde840/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Catchup : Ep.58 - Blake Ellis: Playing the Support Role, and The Power of Vulnerability</title><description>&lt;p&gt;John and Denison chat with Blake Ellis, a Wichita musician/photographer with a heavy role in leading worship at a local MegaChurch. Episode includes discussion on playing a supporting role vs playing the lead, the growth that comes with being vulnerable, how social media is impacting our honesty, and much more. It's an all-new Catchup with a great guest! Join the discussion!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow us:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/TheCatchupCast/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/TheCatchupCast/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/blakester_97/"&gt;Blake Ellis's Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="https://www.facebook.com/TheCatchupCast/"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (https://www.facebook.com/TheCatchupCast/)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>stratocast24@yahoo.com (The Catchup)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cdd473b4f78243c0ac65b3626d85e444</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cdd473b4f78243c0ac65b3626d85e444/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Left Anchor : Episode 122 PREVIEW - Nevada Results, the Sanders Coalition, and Pete Buttigieg</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.patreon.com/posts/34286410'&gt;Subscribe now to hear the full episode!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>catchment.basin@gmail.com (Left Anchor)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6e43f55f56ce4f238adfade1d1c942fd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6e43f55f56ce4f238adfade1d1c942fd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 20:40:14 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>BTS with CTV News Vancouver : Solidarity, Disruption and Spin: Covering Canada-Wide Demonstrations</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For &lt;a href="https://bc.ctvnews.ca/timeline-rail-disruptions-by-wet-suwet-en-supporters-across-canada-1.4815263"&gt;weeks&lt;/a&gt;, demonstrations in support of hereditary chiefs of the Wet'suwet'en First Nation in northern British Columbia have resulted in in unprecedented rallies, blockaded railroads and intentionally disrupted commuter routes for drivers and transit users alike -- not to mention attempts to stall legislators in the capitol and even taking their placards to the premier's own home. The issue of whether or not to allow the Coastal GasLink natural gas pipeline has &lt;a href="https://bc.ctvnews.ca/here-s-how-b-c-approached-land-rights-after-major-court-ruling-1.4818299"&gt;deeply fractured&lt;/a&gt; the Wet'suwet'en community and Canadians at large have been divided on whether protests are lawful and acceptable expressions of support for First Nations or illegal acts of disruption that should result in arrest. As the days go on, the impacts are increasingly felt by people &lt;a href="'Barricades%20must%20now%20come%20down,'%20PM%20Trudeau%20says%20of%20rail%20blockades"&gt;across the country&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hard at work to report on the daily goings-on and the larger picture of what's at play are journalists scrambling to get to the &lt;a href="https://bc.ctvnews.ca/new-blockade-started-on-train-tracks-in-east-vancouver-1.4824103"&gt;latest barricade&lt;/a&gt;, protest and sit-in -- despite increasing hostility from the demonstrators themselves. It's a challenging but important task, so reporters and videographers are getting creative in order to cover all aspects of the developments, despite significant logistical and geographic hurdles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;BTS with CTV Vancouver&lt;/em&gt; host &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/pennydaflos"&gt;Penny Daflos&lt;/a&gt; discusses the complexities of reporting on this issue with reporter &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/allisonm_hurst"&gt;Allison Hurst&lt;/a&gt; and their colleague, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MelanieNagyCTV"&gt;Melanie Nagy&lt;/a&gt;, Vancouver bureau chief for CTV National News.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>iheartradiopodcasts@bellmedia.ca (BTS with CTV News Vancouver)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a5dbce1e18e2426b8869b215222a2b2f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a5dbce1e18e2426b8869b215222a2b2f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 16:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Al Franken Podcast : Is Democracy in Danger? Legal Experts Dahlia Lithwick and Ian Bassin On Trump, Barr and The Abuse of the Criminal Justice System</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Dahlia Lithwick of Slate and Ian Bassin of Protect Democracy discuss Trump's sickening lurch toward autocracy post-impeachment with the cooperation of Bill Barr.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>paulwoodywoodhull@gmail.com (The Al Franken Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">88eecf4519214c27a8f362a99ce2a133</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/88eecf4519214c27a8f362a99ce2a133/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>HYPAT med Jennifer &amp; Julia : 2.5: Krossad skalle och svar på tal</title><description>&lt;p&gt;I veckans avsnitt berättar Jennifer om hur Coronaviruset på ett eller annat sätt påverkas oss. Julia pratar om den senaste trenden "skull-breaker challenge" och att Finnair placerade sig på en mindre attraktiv lista. Dessutom besvarar vi massa frågor ni ställt oss! Hur är det att bo i USA? Hur ser Jennifers drömkille ut? Och vad är egentligen våra svagheter? Tune in!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jennifer.carp@ymail.com (HYPAT med Jennifer &amp; Julia)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bc0d1b4e040248e581580f48dd32c49d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bc0d1b4e040248e581580f48dd32c49d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 19:20:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>ESPN Chicago GameNight : 2/21 8PM: Ray Flores/Cubs</title><description>"Back Nine": We discuss what Cubs players are really saying about Joe Maddon, and Ray Flores previews Wilder/Fury 2.</description><author>feedback@goodkarmabrands.com (ESPN Chicago GameNight)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3c45a7c32179428cadea8e00f43d7628</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3c45a7c32179428cadea8e00f43d7628/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 19:07:12 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sunflower News Podcast  : Why and how to get free testing for sexually transmitted infections</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for a candid conversation with the staff of Positive Directions Inc. about HIV and some other common sexually transmitted infections (STIs) and learn about the variety of free STI testing services they offer on-campus each month. Tune in to learn more about what to expect when you go to get tested, what happens if you test positive and where to get free condoms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Producer's Note: &amp;nbsp;Some content in this episode may be sensitive for some listeners*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Sunflower News Podcast is a service of &lt;a href="https://thesunflower.com/" rel="ugc noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;The Sunflower &lt;/a&gt;at Wichita State University. This episode was hosted by Audrey E. Korte and produced by Kyle Landolfi and Audrey E. Korte. It also features original music, courtesy of Ramsey Jamaleddine. Check him out on SoundCloud at &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/fury-10" rel="ugc noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;https://soundcloud.com/fury-10&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find The Sunflower News Podcast on eight different podcast platforms, for free - just search for The Sunflower News Podcast or listen to it on Spotify or in your browser at &lt;a href="https://anchor.fm/dashboard/episode/anchor.fm/sunflowernews" rel="ugc noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;anchor.fm/sunflowernews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for tuning in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like what you hear give us a shoutout on social media (#SNPWSU) and remember sharing is caring.&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/sunflowernews/message</description><author>Multimedia@thesunflower.com (The Sunflower News Podcast )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">88ab769eb607421aaa12a08b4cd471a1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/88ab769eb607421aaa12a08b4cd471a1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 15:09:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Trending Stories Taking Over podcast | T.S.T.O. : 022 | Cut-copy-paste dies, Home Alone, Bieber fight, Tesla crash, Whitney lives, Parasite</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Watch the full show: &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/fHgi-MPJq7Q"&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are BACK with another episode of the TSTO!!! &amp;nbsp;This week we discuss the passing away of the man who created cut-copy-paste, Home Alone star Macaulay Culkin, Bieber vs Cruise fight, Teslas being illiterate, Whitney lives, and Parasite.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ALSO...we are doing a NEW giveaway this month. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Here's a link to enter for you chance to win: &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2RmVIEN"&gt;https://bit.ly/2TrAW8B&lt;/a&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let us know what you think in the comments! &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Yahoo!!!!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Todd, Jake, + Kris&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/tsto/message</description><author>tstoshow@gmail.com (The Trending Stories Taking Over podcast | T.S.T.O.)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c89b0e1dceb14b9990a12bb43e1c1625</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c89b0e1dceb14b9990a12bb43e1c1625/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 10:43:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Building Tomorrow : Ethics of Progress (with Jason Crawford)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s easy to assume that things naturally improve. After all, in our lifetimes technology has advanced, life expectancies have risen, and standards of living have improved. Yet in historical terms, progress is a relatively new phenomenon, only invented a few centuries ago. And the danger is that if we take the idea of progress for granted, we might slow or even reverse the rate of progress. That would be a disaster given that we have an obligation to leave a society to future generations that is in better shape than we received it. Technologist Jason Crawford joins the show to talk about the ethical obligation to pursue progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;What are the different types of progress? What is the history of progress? Is progress uniform? What progress have we made that is universally good? Is there an ethical imperative to pursue progress? What is sustainable progress?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>av@libertarianism.org (Building Tomorrow)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c0236d82f15a45b08f8ac8fea46a14cc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c0236d82f15a45b08f8ac8fea46a14cc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 03:15:52 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump, Inc.  : Paying to Protect the President</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Last year, Eric Trump defended his father’s frequent visits to properties owned by the family business, saying that Trump hotels charge far less than others would. “If they were to go to a hotel across the street, they’d be charging them $500 a night, whereas, you know we charge them, like 50 bucks,” &lt;a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/g-7-at-trump-golf-resort-saves-the-us-money-eric-trump-192655739.html"&gt;Eric Trump told Yahoo Finance&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But recent reporting by The Washington Post’s &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Fahrenthold"&gt;David Fahrenthold&lt;/a&gt; revealed that’s not the case: records show that the Secret Service was charged &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/secret-service-has-paid-rates-as-high-as-650-a-night-for-rooms-at-trumps-properties/2020/02/06/7f27a7c6-3ec5-11ea-8872-5df698785a4e_story.html"&gt;rates as high as $650 a night&lt;/a&gt; to stay at Trump properties — then tried to keep that information secret.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not only that Trump has control over this - he’s paying money to himself - but also that we weren’t told,” Fahrenthold said. “You could make the case that if they publicly advertise this and listed these things in public spending databases and you and I knew about this from the beginning, they might be able to make the argument that like, ‘Oh well, the public knows and they're okay with it.’ But we didn't know. They didn't tell us. So there's a real moral distinction.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Related episodes:• &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/trumpinc/episodes/trump-inc-government-bar-tab-mar-a-lago"&gt;The Government's Bar Tab at Mar-a-Lago&lt;/a&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/trumpinc/episodes/trump-inc-nigerian-presidential-candidate-hired-trump-lobbyist-trumps-lobby"&gt;How a Nigerian Presidential Candidate Hired a Trump Lobbyist and Ended Up in Trump’s Lobby&lt;/a&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.wnycstudios.org/podcasts/trumpinc/episodes/trump-inc-podcast-government-employees-spend-your-money-trump-hotels"&gt;Government Employees Spend Your Money at Trump Hotels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Learn more about Fahrenthold and The Post's &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/trump-inc-2020-how-much-has-the-government-spent-at-trumps-properties-it-wont-say"&gt;unanswered questions about government spending at Trump properties&lt;/a&gt;. Stay up to date with &lt;a href="https://nypublicradio.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe?u=4109fdd323aaac7078eadaa8f&amp;amp;id=d943f3fd91" target="_blank"&gt;email updates&lt;/a&gt; about WNYC and ProPublica's investigations into the president's business practices.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wnycdigital@gmail.com (Trump, Inc. )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0a18876ee87345ec8cb7435e8143ff91</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0a18876ee87345ec8cb7435e8143ff91/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Capitol J : Special Edition: Medill in Germany</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Joe Snell and Alec Bose report on their trip to U.S. Army Headquarters Europe in Wiesbaden, Germany. &lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">1ee68bab849d43c2b0c4c2fb5354920d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1ee68bab849d43c2b0c4c2fb5354920d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 06:12:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Twelve O'clock Siren : Episode - 25</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Guy Charles &amp; Taylor Manning of Teleios Financial sit down with the Siren and take a lighter side approach to financial planning. Lots of topics touched in this episode, in one of our longer episodes. Big thank you for hanging out and educating us!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Teleios - "To see through completion, or to mature."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;972-348-6341&lt;a href= "mailto:gcharles@financialguide.com"&gt; gcharles@financialguide.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "mailto:tmanning@financial"&gt;tmanning@financialguide.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jameshartley1@gmail.com (The Twelve O'clock Siren)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3a4aedac7bfa4ca78c67934fefed0f8c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3a4aedac7bfa4ca78c67934fefed0f8c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Under-Told: Verbatim : Zola Nene’s Post-Apartheid Kitchen</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In 1994, Nelson Mandela’s election marked the end of apartheid and the beginning of democracy in South Africa. But the scars of racial segregation haven’t healed yet. Infrastructure designed for 5 million white South Africans has failed to support the majority black population of over 56 million power outages and water shortages are a part of daily life. Zola Nene was 10 years old when apartheid ended. Today her cookbooks and television appearances have made her a famous and beloved celebrity chef. Our director Fred de Sam Lazaro, talked to Zola in a Cape Town coffee shop about cooking in a post apartheid kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>undertold@stthomas.edu (Under-Told: Verbatim)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">508850d7fb9a49a6b706bc119a3d3058</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/508850d7fb9a49a6b706bc119a3d3058/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 14:40:27 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Asset : BONUS-Donald Trump's First Impeachment Trial</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Now that Donald Trump's first Impeachment Trial has wrapped up, Max Bergmann and Peter Ogburn discuss what was lost and gained in the trial and the path forward to saving our democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To hear the full episode and all of our unedited interviews,please subscribe to our Patreon Page.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://www.patreon.com/posts/34081678&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@theassetpodcast.org (The Asset)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">01de8601d50f4f7e8a8da91457d1488c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/01de8601d50f4f7e8a8da91457d1488c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 10:24:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Candace Owens Show : The Candace Owens Show: General Steve Kwast</title><description>Can the creation of a U.S. military space force boost the economy, maintain American sovereignty, and preserve world peace? General Steve Kwast joins Candace Owens this week for a discussion on how a national space force will impact global relations.</description><author>tylerg@prageru.com (The Candace Owens Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c980b12907ed4acfacf34d389effbb4e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c980b12907ed4acfacf34d389effbb4e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hot Take : Feb 16: Live from Amherst, with Wen Stephenson</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In our first live taping, Mary and guest co-host Wen Stephenson talk about how community helps us deal with grief, the line between journalism and activism, and how to keep finding new ways to tell climate stories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wen's book: &lt;a href="https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/250727/what-were-fighting-for-now-is-each-other-by-wen-stephenson/"&gt;https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/250727/what-were-fighting-for-now-is-each-other-by-wen-stephenson/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow us on Twitter:  &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/realhottake"&gt;https://twitter.com/realhottake&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>amy@criticalfrequency.org (Hot Take)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5808e25b4e8643cea24a00d8f5e11a1a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5808e25b4e8643cea24a00d8f5e11a1a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The M-U Experience : Valentine's Day Episode</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today on The M-U Experience, our team is reading the break up letters they have written to things they don't like. We hope you enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>carlie.mobley@moulton-udell.org (The M-U Experience)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8707123143e24e218431d8d73d3034ce</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8707123143e24e218431d8d73d3034ce/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Seattle Now : Introducing Seattle Now</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Trying to keep up with the news can be a chore. Trump did this, the city council did that. News alerts every ten seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's why KUOW is launching a morning news podcast — Seattle Now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We cut through the noise, and explain the stories speeding by in your Twitter feed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Episodes come out every weekday morning at 6 a.m., starting  Monday March 2. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>webhelp@kuow.org (Seattle Now)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4f999a3869184e8f96e84f62984c3501</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4f999a3869184e8f96e84f62984c3501/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 10:31:32 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Commercial Awareness Podcast : Episode 40: Season Finale</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Contact: &lt;a href="mailto:commawarepod@gmail.com"&gt;commawarepod@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram: @&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/commawarepod/?hl=en"&gt;commawarepod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Links for the headlines:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HS2 Green Light&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/live/business-51418693"&gt;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/live/business-51418693&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BP Net Zero Pledge&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e1ee8ab4-4d89-11ea-95a0-43d18ec715f5"&gt;https://www.ft.com/content/e1ee8ab4-4d89-11ea-95a0-43d18ec715f5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Injunction Granted&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/13/technology/amazon-jedi-pentagon-contract-microsoft.html"&gt;https://www.nytimes.com/2020/02/13/technology/amazon-jedi-pentagon-contract-microsoft.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deal News&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.lw.com/news/latham-advises-casper-sleep-inc-in-ipo"&gt;https://www.lw.com/news/latham-advises-casper-sleep-inc-in-ipo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelawyer.com/us-and-french-firms-lead-on-billion-dollar-payments-deal/"&gt;https://www.thelawyer.com/us-and-french-firms-lead-on-billion-dollar-payments-deal/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Govt Considers Flybe Stake&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-51453196"&gt;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-51453196&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Novartis Panel Rules&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelawyer.com/novartis-panel-review-2020/"&gt;https://www.thelawyer.com/novartis-panel-review-2020/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nissan Loss&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cityam.com/nissan-records-losses-amid-backdrop-of-carlos-ghosn-scandal/"&gt;https://www.cityam.com/nissan-records-losses-amid-backdrop-of-carlos-ghosn-scandal/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FTC Investigates Big Tech&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cityam.com/ftc-demands-data-on-startup-purchases-by-tech-giants/"&gt;https://www.cityam.com/ftc-demands-data-on-startup-purchases-by-tech-giants/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Firm Paternity Leave Increase&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelawyer.com/ao-matches-linklaters-with-12-weeks-paternity-leave/"&gt;https://www.thelawyer.com/ao-matches-linklaters-with-12-weeks-paternity-leave/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UK Allows Huawei Involvement&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2020/01/28/huawei-will-allowed-build-parts-britains-5g-network/"&gt;https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2020/01/28/huawei-will-allowed-build-parts-britains-5g-network/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Created and Hosted by: Tapiwa Museba&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Season 3 Begins on 28 February&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts8+75b7794@anchor.fm (The Commercial Awareness Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">069a0fd9c14d45f4b3e51850fc1f63f9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/069a0fd9c14d45f4b3e51850fc1f63f9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 21:47:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The McCarthy Report : Episode 72: The Absurd Roger Stone Controversy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today on &lt;i data-stringify-type="italic"&gt;The McCarthy Report&lt;/i&gt;, Andy and Rich dissect the legal ruckus surrounding Roger Stone’s sentencing, and discuss Bill Barr’s impending House Judiciary Committee testimony.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>studio@nationalreview.com (The McCarthy Report)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c25efbc646f94140ba252ae0d17264fb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c25efbc646f94140ba252ae0d17264fb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 12:02:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Uncommon Knowledge : The World According to Thiel</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Recorded on January 17, 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peter Thiel, the cofounder of PayPal and Palantir; early investor in Facebook, LinkedIn, and SpaceX; and the founder of the Thiel Fellowship, which encourages young people to drop out of college to start their own businesses, is interviewed live on stage in front of the members of the Mont Pelerin Society. This wide-ranging conversation covers globalization, the continuing and ever-growing threat from China and what the United States can and can’t do it about, what the rise of Bernie Sanders means for the future of US capitalism, the “derangement” (Thiel’s phrase) of Silicon Valley in the last decade, the scourge of political correctness on campuses and in society at large, and why Thiel thinks we should rethink the doctrine of American exceptionalism.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>institutionhoover@gmail.com (Uncommon Knowledge)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">53c50814c0c9463084b8e380ea61cbe6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/53c50814c0c9463084b8e380ea61cbe6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 08:42:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Choice : The Argument: Why Endorse Elizabeth Warren and Amy Klobuchar?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Host Katie Kingsbury visits Opinion's other podcast, "The Argument," to defend the editorial board's two endorsements for Senators Elizabeth Warren and Amy Klobuchar against her disagreeing colleagues Ross Douthat, Michelle Goldberg and David Leonhardt. They talk about the current political moment, each of the Democratic contenders, and the path to the nomination. For background reading on this episode, click here or search for &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/23/opinion/the-argument-endorsement-klobuchar-warren.html" target="_blank"&gt;nytimes.com/theargument&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>opinionpodcasts@nytimes.com (The Choice)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">79c3c9035c6a45e7b16b949c5893a9fa</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/79c3c9035c6a45e7b16b949c5893a9fa/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sean Klitzner Show : The #YangGang</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Tonight gets political. We talk about the top democrats running for office. I can't promise anything we say is serious.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>SeanKlitzner@gmail.com (The Sean Klitzner Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4c849be0f5524fbc8b96efe74a78d32e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4c849be0f5524fbc8b96efe74a78d32e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 20:16:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>More Than Enough : 4: We All Deserve An Income Floor: Why the Bold Policy of Guaranteed Income Works</title><description>&lt;div&gt;If guaranteed income is an attempt to provide people with more resources—resources that come with very few restrictions—it demands a conversation with the people who would most benefit from it. It also demands a conversation about deservedness. When we ask “How much would it be?” “Who would get it?” And “How would we pay for it?” what we are really asking is who deserves more and who doesn’t.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;I’m not the only one who thinks Guaranteed income is a realistic option, either—it’s actually being tried out as we speak. Presidential hopeful Andrew Yang advocates for Guaranteed Income as part of his platform. Aisha Nyadoro’s project—The Magnolia Mother’s Trust, which you heard about in Episode 2 [link to episode]—is getting ready to launch their second round of a guaranteed income project in Jackson, Mississippi. The city of Stockton, California, and its mayor Michael Tubbs are also running a demonstration of Guaranteed Income right now—they are working to build an economy that grants everyone the right to have enough to get by.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Over the last two years, I’ve talked to wide-ranging audiences about guaranteed income. One of the things that consistently gets fretted about is the boldness of guaranteed income. People have said to me, What will poor people do with that money? The Right will never go for it. How will we pay for it? And I can’t help but think of the people who thought that ending slavery was too hard, to bold an idea.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Too many of us have become convinced that the rules, as written by fear, scarcity, and avarice, are the ones we must play by.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We don’t. We have to be willing to dream our most courageously when it comes to policy and systems change, because we cut ourselves off from the best possible outcomes if we start compromising our ideal before we begin. So let’s be bold, let’s be courageous, and let’s start by recognizing that this country has more than enough wealth—enough money, enough talent, enough courage—for all of us.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Show Notes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;More Than Enough was developed by Next River Productions. Created and hosted by Mia Birdsong. Audio engineering and music by Nino Moschella. Script development and production by Allison Cook. The content of this podcast was informed by the stories of hundreds of people across the country, only some of whom you heard from. Thank you to everyone who took the time to speak with me and share their story.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Support for the production of More Than Enough was provided by a few generous folks and the Economic Security Project, an organization advancing cash-based interventions in the United States and reigning in corporate monopolies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;More Than Enough is a project of The Nation Magazine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>frank@thenation.com (More Than Enough)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">62b7e1fa81f54ef493dafb2b70d7829b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/62b7e1fa81f54ef493dafb2b70d7829b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Beat – CUNY Podcasts : The Rise and Fall of The Young Lords</title><description>&lt;br /&gt;
One of the most influential groups of the radical &amp;#8217;60s was the Young Lords, an organization of poor and working class Puerto Ricans that began as a street gang and rose to confront the racism of institutions from government to religion. Johanna Fernandez, a professor of history at Baruch College, traces their roots and tells the story of their rise and fall in The Young Lords: A Radical History. She talks about it with Beth Harpaz.&lt;br /&gt;</description><author>webservices@cuny.edu (Book Beat – CUNY Podcasts)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3a08a18ca5c748c798258b7d41e858af</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3a08a18ca5c748c798258b7d41e858af/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 15:38:14 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>DriveTimes Podcast : Episode 14: Elephants, Mangos, and the Chamber of Secrets</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Come one come all to the next episode of the DriveTimes podcast where 2 dads discuss funny, interesting, and good story from throughout the week to give you some hope in life. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>thedadbodsshow@gmail.com (DriveTimes Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">df9a97ebd6694825b1e210232b67ed9a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/df9a97ebd6694825b1e210232b67ed9a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 11:47:16 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>