<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Travel feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My travel episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My Travel feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 06:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>The olive magazine podcast : ep 183 - Learn all about Singaporean food and drink with chef Elizabeth Haigh</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week Ellie chats to Elizabeth Haigh, a Singaporean-born chef who has just opened Mei Mei, a coffee house in Borough Market specializing in the food and drink of Singapore. They chat about why she pursued a career in food after completing a degree in architecture, how she travels across London to source key ingredients and the best places for kopi in Singapore.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>laura.rowe@immediate.co.uk (The olive magazine podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">99483c4a7677426692ea38d6079a4c2f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/99483c4a7677426692ea38d6079a4c2f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 07:39:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Travel Talk Weekly : Themed Cruises -What They Are and Who They are For</title><description>&lt;p&gt;014 - This week Rob and Kerri are talking all about Themed and Specialty Cruises. They will walk you through the three main kinds of themed cruises: Private Group, Cruise Line Specialty Cruises and Full Ship Charters. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'll get to learn about some of the types of specialty cruises you can find on a River Cruise in Europe and some of the more popular themed cruises on the ocean ships. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regardless of what your interests are, there is a good chance there is a themed cruise out there that would fit you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you would like to create your own specialty cruise, reach out to us. We'd love to help you make that happen. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Want to be the first to hear about some cool travel deals? Then text TRAVEL to 888111 to get on our VIP travel friends list. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This show is sponsored by Creating Magic Vacations. For your domestic or international trip, let us help you plan a done for you vacation. Reach out to &lt;a href="https://www.travelleaders.com/travel_agent/Agent-Details.aspx?id=107129&amp;amp;nav=0"&gt;Rob and Kerri&lt;/a&gt; here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>rob@traveltalkweekly.com (Travel Talk Weekly)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3a4733a7738c4355b3d3704d6561e51e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3a4733a7738c4355b3d3704d6561e51e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hashtag Colorado Life : Building Your Colorado Bucket List in 2020</title><description>BONUS #2: What’s on your Colorado bucket list? In this bonus episode Ryan and Carrie talk about the must-see and must-do things to add to your Colorado bucket list. With the mountains in your backyard, an ever-growing food scene, and endless indoor and outdoor activities where do you start? There are so many things to do and cities to explore!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ryan and Carrie share the activities and adventures that are on their Colorado bucket list. They also discuss the places and sights they have already visited. Many of the ideas include iconic Colorado destinations and local favorites, as well as lesser-known but still epic experiences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are looking for the best things to do in Colorado without busting your budget, that’s what this episode is all about. Find out the top 16 things Ryan and Carrie recommend you add to your bucket list. Plus, these are great suggestions for discovering within your first year of living in the square state.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more information and resources about exploring Colorado, visit our website at &lt;a href="http://hashtagcoloradolife.com/"&gt;HashtagColoradoLife.com&lt;/a&gt; or&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/hashtagcoloradolife/"&gt; @HashtagColoradoLife&lt;/a&gt; on Instagram.</description><author>team@hashtagcoloradolife.com (Hashtag Colorado Life)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4580a7f45e174506aa649f38489f2dba</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4580a7f45e174506aa649f38489f2dba/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Overland Journal Podcast : Lois Pryce, Solo Adventure Motorcyclist</title><description>Smitten with life, UK adventuress Lois Pryce has always been on the move. At 13 years of age, an unchaperoned, week-long trip on bicycles through Cornwall’s back roads with friends introduced her to the possibilities of travel by design. And also to the idea of minimalist travel, taking shelter where you can find it, and bringing little more than bare essentials.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;About Lois Pryce: &lt;a href="https://www.loisontheloose.com/"&gt;https://www.loisontheloose.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more of Lois' content in Overland Journal and Expedition Portal: &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://expeditionportal.com/?s=lois+pryce&amp;amp;submit="&gt;https://expeditionportal.com/?s=lois+pryce&amp;amp;submit=&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description><author>scott@overlandinternational.com (The Overland Journal Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d7eec92a637641698ce864bb29aa85b7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d7eec92a637641698ce864bb29aa85b7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Living Adventurously : We Need to Reclaim Time to Think in Our Life if we are to Do Meaningful Things - Living Adventurously #12</title><description>Sophie Stephenson was living the life she’d always wanted. She had a well-paid dream job in Australia, lived in a beautiful place and felt secure in the knowledge that this could go on, indefinitely. But she was, she realised, unfulfilled. She was not, it turned out, truly happy with this life at all.By chance Sophie came across a reference to Nancy Kline’s book Time to Think. She described a way of being with one another that is both incredibly simple, and incredibly rare. We don’t give ourselves, or others, the freedom to think without interruption, or judgment, or time limits, or an obsession with outcomes. We limit our thinking, our conversations, our relationships and our entire lives by confining our minds.Sophie began to question the life she had chosen. She began to ask what she really wanted, to explore the ‘authentic’ me, her instinctive mind, and gradually, she began to reclaim what really mattered. Sophie left corporate life, moved back to the UK, and met the man who is now her husband and father to her two children.We need to reclaim time to think in our life if we are to do meaningful things with our life.I was struck by how deeply Sophie listened and quickly figured me out. It was almost bizarre, in a nice way. I asked her how I could become a better listener, and how to ask better questions - both pretty crucial things for a novice podcaster to get to grips with...&lt;h1&gt;&lt;a href="https://livingadventurously.transistor.fm/subscribe"&gt;PLEASE SUBSCRIBE TO THE LIVING ADVENTUROUSLY PODCAST&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;(It’s completely &lt;strong&gt;free&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;zero hassle&lt;/strong&gt; to do (&lt;a href="https://livingadventurously.transistor.fm/subscribe"&gt;&lt;em&gt;click here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;), but really &lt;strong&gt;helpful&lt;/strong&gt; for me trying to get a new podcast off the ground. If you’re feeling extra kind, please leave a review on the app – that really helps.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Listen on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/living-adventurously/id1489454694"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/2aYqIdvtVJkhIPklHaoXA3"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=486751&amp;amp;refid=stpr"&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://tunein.com/podcasts/Storytelling-Podcasts/Living-Adventurously-p1275719/"&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt; (“Alexa, please play the Living Adventurously podcast”) or on your favourite podcast platform such as Overcast, &lt;a href="https://podcasts.google.com/?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9mZWVkcy50cmFuc2lzdG9yLmZtL2xpdmluZy1hZHZlbnR1cm91c2x5"&gt;Google Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, Pocket Casts, &lt;a href="https://www.breaker.audio/living-adventurously"&gt;Breaker&lt;/a&gt;, Soundcloud, Castbox, Castro.&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.alastairhumphreys.com/podcast"&gt;www.alastairhumphreys.com/podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;THIS PODCAST IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY KOMOOT&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;Komoot&lt;/a&gt; is a route planning and navigation app that inspires and enables great outdoor experiences.Your very own outdoor experiences are waiting for you. Go explore more with &lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;komoot&lt;/a&gt;. Use the voucher code &lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;ADVENTUROUS&lt;/a&gt; to claim your free region bundle.The personalised planning and navigation tools ensure you plan the adventure that’s perfect for &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;. Komoot is Europe’s number 1 outdoor app, with route planning and navigation functionality, and strong community-driven inspirational features in the form of recommended Highlights and inspirational route Collections. It is used by over 8.5 million adventurers worldwide. Komoot is becoming the app of choice for cyclists and hikers the world over, with rapid community growth in the UK, the US and other parts of Europe.&lt;h1&gt;SHOW NOTES&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you enjoy listening to this episode over a cup of coffee and think it might be worth the price, you can &lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;buy me a coffee here:&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;www. ko-fi.com/al_humphreys&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep up to date with future episodes (and my other adventures, projects and books) with my &lt;a href="https://www.alastairhumphreys.com/more/subscribe/"&gt;free monthly newsletter: alastairhumphreys.com/more/subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Say hello on &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Al_Humphreys"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/al_humphreys/"&gt;Instagram: @al_humphreys&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.thethinkingproject.co.uk/about-sophie"&gt;The Thinking Project&lt;/a&gt; helps exceptional purpose-driven women create time and space so they can consciously create lives they love &amp;amp; businesses where everyone thrives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TheThinkProj"&gt;On Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nancy Kline’s book &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Time-Think-Listening-Ignite-Human/dp/0706377451/ref=sr_1_1?keywords=time+to+think&amp;amp;qid=1576162042&amp;amp;sr=8-1"&gt;Time to Think&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need to reclaim time to think in our life if we are to do meaningful things with our life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don't just fill the time with nothing: it needs to be a bit more conscious and structured than that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruminative thinking - we just go over and over the same thoughts time and again (often negative)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our brains try to keep us safe by just thinking the same stuff over and over&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thinking with someone else rather than ourselves helps keep it focussed rather than distracted. Having someone listen to us makes it easier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Usually we come up with lists of all the things we don't want&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First big question: "what do you really want?"&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We jump to assumptions that stop us doing what we want to do, largely without evidence, largely unexamined.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At root there are a couple of major assumptions that stop us: a sense of worthiness, belonging and being enough.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We all have a need for safety, connection and autonomy, but they manifest in different ways for each of us.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thinking is like a seed - it needs the right conditions to thrive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consciously choose what it is that you want and do not want in life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need to warm up to thinking well and more deeply. Ask "so what?" to your answers lots of times.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being a better listener starts with talking less, and choosing to become a better listener. Stop interrupting. Get really interested in other people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get interested in other people. Not necessarily in the subject they are interested in, but in the fact that they are interested in that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To ask better questions, think about what is the purpose of your question?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The best questions are ones that you do not know the answer to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ask either very broad or very specific questions. For example, "what do you want to think about?"&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Her decision-making has changed. It used to be about challenge and proving what a well-lived life entailed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Often we lead the life that we think we Should live, rather than the life of our choice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Change your motivations from being fear-based to doing things that you love.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When making a big change some people leap into the unknown, others establish some breathing space and time and security to cushion the leap.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You don't have to make enormous changes and drastic switches - it can be small steps that are transformative and life-changing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The experiences when we are vulnerable are often those that transform our lives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The relationship between vulnerability and trust&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meditate, drink lots of water, and remove social media from the phone - all simple but not easy and beneficial things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;TRANSCRIPT&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Below is the transcription of our conversation. It’s done by AI so is perhaps a wee bit ropey here and there. If these transcripts prove sufficiently useful then I will make the effort to clean then up and make them better. Do let me know if you think it’s worth my time to do that. (Or, better still, do it for me…!). If you’d like to listen as you read along you can do that here:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://otter.ai/s/hCd1SaUjRMWVUAQC38i12A"&gt;https://otter.ai/s/hCd1SaUjRMWVUAQC38i12A&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" title="★ Support this podcast by donating ★" href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;★ Support this podcast by donating ★&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>alastair@alastairhumphreys.com (Living Adventurously)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">40cfc07c451d4f54b4ef213c3047981b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/40cfc07c451d4f54b4ef213c3047981b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The City : The City recommends new podcast, The Sneak | S E1</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In its first season, The Sneak looks at the case of a former Division I football star who attacked a Brinks Truck guard in 2008 and ran off with $400,000 in cash, before his&amp;nbsp;grand&amp;nbsp;flourish: Escaping in an inner tube down a river. Through new reporting, host Nate Scott discovered it was more than the story of a heist and that at the center was one small town and its secrets. Secrets about what actually happened with that crime back in 2008. And who actually helped pull it off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@thecitypodcast.com (The City)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d8122c1cce3e4c41bf153ad8b11f5cce</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d8122c1cce3e4c41bf153ad8b11f5cce/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>La Lido Loca Cruise Podcast : 7. Mistakes First Time Cruisers Make</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to episode #7 of the La Lido Loca podcast.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Join Jenny and Tony as they talk about cruising!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show Notes:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on YouTube:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;La Lido Loca Podcast: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCLoGEyIWH6f6mkJxDCweDag"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCLoGEyIWH6f6mkJxDCweDag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;La Lido Loca Cruising: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqFivW2VWJtGfvrMreyjNbw"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqFivW2VWJtGfvrMreyjNbw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Let Jenny help with your travel, you can contact her at: &lt;a href= "mailto:jbarnette@cruiseshipcenters.com"&gt;jbarnette@cruiseshipcenters.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Info about La Lido Loca Group Cruises: &lt;a href="http://www.lalidoloca.com/groupcruise" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;http://www.lalidoloca.com/groupcruise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on Social Media: Facebook Page - &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt; Instagram - &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt; Twitter - &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/lalidoloca" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://twitter.com/lalidoloca&lt;/a&gt; Pintrest - &lt;a href="https://www.pinterest.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.pinterest.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Represent the locafam with a t-shirt, check out the latest designs at: &lt;a href="https://teespring.com/stores/lalidoloca-funshop" target= "_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://teespring.com/stores/lalidoloca-funshop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our mailing address is: La Lido Loca 4142 Mariner Blvd #402 Spring Hill, FL 34609&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Support our creative efforts at Patreon: &lt;a href="http://www.patreon.com/lalidoloca" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;http://www.patreon.com/lalidoloca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Please Submit Questions or Comments to &lt;a href= "mailto:tony@lalidoloca.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;tony@lalidoloca.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tony@lalidoloca.com (La Lido Loca Cruise Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">60a13069c960404385c5080b909bf8ef</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/60a13069c960404385c5080b909bf8ef/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 19:28:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Out Alive from BACKPACKER : The Twenty-Ninth Day</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On a 600 mile canoe trip, Alex Messenger encounters a grizzly while hiking alone on the Canadian tundra. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ssebestyen@aimmedia.com (Out Alive from BACKPACKER)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a0b5fa83e3524143a8b72abc0352addd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a0b5fa83e3524143a8b72abc0352addd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Happiest Podcast On Earth : 44 - Drafting A Perfect Disney Day</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In another edition of the Happiest Podcast Draft series, the team drafts their perfect Disney day. What will they choose as their favorite Disney attractions, restaurants, resorts, and more that they would make sure to visit? Listen in to find out! HAPPY LISTENING EVERYONE!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>happiestpodcast@gmail.com (Happiest Podcast On Earth)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b48cf83b7df74c57a388f168969cfb05</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b48cf83b7df74c57a388f168969cfb05/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Disney Cruise Line Show : #001 - Things First Time Disney Cruise Line Cruisers Should Know</title><description>01/15/19 - In this episode, the panel discusses things a first time cruiser should know when preparing and taking a Disney Cruise Line vacation!</description><author>craig@disneyinfo.com (The Disney Cruise Line Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">98ec4d79e03c47d395c21c67b1b6c803</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/98ec4d79e03c47d395c21c67b1b6c803/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 01:00:20 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Trip That Changed Me : Argentina with Nicole Vargas: intuition, digital detoxes, and the art of solo travel</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Back when feminist media company, Unearth Women, was just a twinkle in her eye, Nicole Vargas was an aspiring travel journalist trying to make it New York City. Immersed in the world of advertising and weeks from marrying a man who wasn't the one, Nikki took a solo trip to Argentina. On today’s episode, she recounts the journey that inspired her to quit her job, call off her wedding, and wholeheartedly pursue a career in travel writing. Nikki's story speaks to the importance of trusting intuition, doggedly chasing dreams, and summoning the bravery to start over. Plus, we discuss the next spots on Nikki’s travel bucket list and top tips for travel deals.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@podcastnation.org (The Trip That Changed Me)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c253112a9d0541319d0f0db43945cd05</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c253112a9d0541319d0f0db43945cd05/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 03:00:01 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Peak Northwest : Finding the best fish, chips and chowder on the Oregon coast</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Oregon coast’s signature cuisine can be summarized in four words: fish, chips and chowder. We sit down with Michael Russell, the Oregonian/OregonLive’s restaurant reporter and critic, to discuss where to find the coast’s finest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out Jamie’s 10 &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/life-and-culture/g66l-2019/08/be353c7a986527/our-10-favorite-fish-and-chips-spots-on-the-oregon-coast.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;favorite fish and chips spots&lt;/a&gt; on the Oregon coast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read Michael’s rundown of where to eat &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/dining/2016/06/where_to_eat_on_the_oregon_coa.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;on the North Oregon Coast&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peruse Jamie’s guide to &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/life-and-culture/g66l-2019/02/bbc2001eab9626/welcome-to-the-chowder-belt-of-the-central-oregon-coast.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;the chowder belt of the Oregon coast&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts@oregonian.com (Peak Northwest)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1b609bb1c2c14668beebcab0a51ff246</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1b609bb1c2c14668beebcab0a51ff246/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>A Way To Go : Speeding on a Tuk-Tuk to Save the Elephants with Waris Ahluwalia</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Every two years, actor and designer Waris Ahluwalia embarks on a 500-kilometer madcap adventure through the Indian countryside on behalf of Elephant Family, a charity that protects Asian elephants and their habitat. The five-day Travel to My Elephant Rally is anything but a typical fundraiser, with teams of supporters navigating, partying, and glamping their way via tuk-tuk, motorbike, and vintage cars — raising impressive sums along the way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Find more info about this episode at &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://urldefense.proofpoint.com/v2/url?u=http-3A__Fathomaway.com&amp;amp;d=DwMFaQ&amp;amp;c=GC0NZZhaEw6GOQSjMHI2g15k_drElRoPmOYiK2k0eZ8&amp;amp;r=QQqtrehlQRY19SGPJ2205twNczy34pobDq7ZUMRMscQ&amp;amp;m=ApljJvf9UyXW5O158iPvyTg_wMnrLco6urxYTIBG-6E&amp;amp;s=swiRaK2G8IgJQDgmMAN__6u1ymO51GJICLjahLs8Ogc&amp;amp;e="&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fathomaway.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (A Way To Go)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a692f77d72c04d0fbc97bcd4888511b8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a692f77d72c04d0fbc97bcd4888511b8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Biscuit CLT Podcast : CMCLT Rewind: Manny and Adrienne Threatt</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At the first Creative Mornings Charlotte of the new decade, Manny and Adrienne Threatt of Hope Vibes delivered a stirring presentation in the hall of Myers Park Presbyterian Church. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you're not familiar with Hope Vibes, they're a non-profit organization here in Charlotte that provides basic services to our homeless population.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hosts Tim Miner and Matt Olin talk to Manny and Adrienne about how their upbringing spurred them into action, The Hope Tank (their mobile shower and hygiene station), and what it means to lead the next generation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Stick around through the end as producer Andy Goh asks Creative Mornings attendees what their creative New Year's resolutions for Charlotte are.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tim@charlotteiscreative.com (The Biscuit CLT Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">df59955184fb4253ad7c3ca7fefabb55</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/df59955184fb4253ad7c3ca7fefabb55/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>My Solo Road : She loves Jesus &amp; Auditing Faucets | ft. Kristin Holden</title><description>&lt;p&gt;What if you could do van life without ever having to find remote work? This week Kristin (@wheretheroadforks_) tells us how she asked her boss to go remote and got a YES. We talk religion, ex boyfriends, and good ole solo female van life per usual.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>divineontheroad@gmail.com (My Solo Road)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c80727f69a27492c94619c956bbba02f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c80727f69a27492c94619c956bbba02f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 08:40:57 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>