<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Travel feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My travel episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My Travel feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 03:35:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>Monocle 24: The Menu : Filipino food’s new direction</title><description>How chef Budgie Montoya is reinventing Filipino food in London. Plus: Lisbon’s rising culinary talent, João Sá, and what’s new on Zürich’s restaurant scene.</description><author>info@monocle.com (Monocle 24: The Menu)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a207cfea775f408b84534d673b2e48db</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a207cfea775f408b84534d673b2e48db/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The One Way Ticket Show : Singer/Songwriter - Anthony Nunziata</title><description>&lt;p class="font_8"&gt;Anthony Nunziata is the New York City-based, internationally-acclaimed singer and songwriter who brings his soulful voice to classic jazz, pop standards and his original music.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="font_8"&gt;Anthony has performed over 400 concerts over the past few years headlining major performing arts centers, theaters, symphony concert halls and private events across the country and around the world. The Brooklyn-born, classically trained singer is hailed by Broadwayworld as “an explosion of love and entertainment.” Anthony recently co-headlined Carnegie Hall for two sold-out concerts with the New York Pops Symphony Orchestra. Anthony recently appeared in the Netflix film "The Last Laugh" opposite Chevy Chase and Richard Dreyfuss.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="font_8"&gt;Anthony's original songs include co-write collaborations with Victoria Shaw (No. 1 hits for Garth Brooks, Lady Antebellum) Jim Brickman (21 No. 1 Albums) Jeff Franzel (Josh Groban, Justin Timberlake, Taylor Dayne), Tom Kimmel (Linda Ronstadt, Johnny Cash, Art Garfunkel) Maria Christensen (Celine Dion, Jennifer Lopez), and Nina Ossoff and Porter Carroll Jr. (Daughtry, Patti Austin, The Temptations).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="font_8"&gt;His original pop song "The Gift Is You" - which he wrote honoring his mother's battle with breast cancer (she is now cancer-free) - is currently being used as an anthem for The Susan G. Komen Foundation. His music is featured on his upcoming solo album released in the Fall 2019 which will coincide with his concert tour.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="font_8"&gt;Anthony has brought his fresh take on classic &amp; contemporary songs as well as his movie-bound original tunes across the United States and around the world to performing arts centers, theaters and private events, as well as intimate jazz clubs and symphony concerts with orchestras such as the New York Pops, Detroit Symphony, Cleveland Pops, Colorado Symphony, Lancaster Symphony, Annapolis Symphony, Plymouth Symphony, Cape Cod Symphony, Toledo Symphony, Edmonton Symphony Orchestra and more. He has performed at private events across the United States and recently in England, Spain, Italy and Singapore.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="font_8"&gt;In his 2019-2020 concert tour Anthony brings his soulful and lyrical tenor voice to the greatest love songs ever written. He and his Grammy-winning musicians re-imagine “Unchained Melody,” “Can’t Take My Eyes Off Of You,” “Can’t Help Falling In Love With You,” “When I Fall In Love,” “The Prayer,” “O Sole Mio,” “Somewhere,” originals including “Will You Be My Everyday?” and many more.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="font_8"&gt;Anthony studied music, acting and directing at Boston College, and trained in improv comedy at the famed Upright Citizens Brigade in New York City. Featured on Good Morning America and The Rachael Ray Show, Anthony is most proud of his "ARTS MATTER!" Educational Outreach Initiative and Master Class Workshops that educate and inspire students to fearlessly pursue their passions. Anthony is an avid tennis player, a two-time jr. National Platform Tennis Champion, and can cook up a delicious chicken parmesan. Artist website: &lt;a href= "http://www.AnthonyNunziata.com"&gt;www.AnthonyNunziata.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On this episode, Anthony returns to The One Way Ticket Show where he's Steven's first Weekend Special guest! Anthony shares tunes off his "The Love Album" and talks about his music and more. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Anthony is just one of the dynamic personalities featured on The One Way Ticket Show,  where Steven's guests have included: Nobel Peace Prize Winner, President Jose Ramos-Horta; Legendary Talk Show Host, Dick Cavett; Law Professor, Alan Dershowitz; Fashion Expert, Tim Gunn; Broadcast Legend, Charles Osgood; International Rescue Committee President &amp; CEO, David Miliband; Playwright, David Henry Hwang; Journalist-Humorist-Actor, Mo Rocca; SkyBridge Capital Founder &amp; Co-Managing Partner, Anthony Scaramucci; Abercrombie &amp; Kent Founder, Geoffrey Kent; Travel Expert, Pauline Frommer, as well as leading photographers, artists, chefs, writers, intellectuals and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>steven@theonewayticketshow.com (The One Way Ticket Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8158c7f9728e4cc7a47199abd962d566</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8158c7f9728e4cc7a47199abd962d566/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 11:05:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Happiest Podcast On Earth : 46 - Disney Grammy Awards</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We host our 1st annual Disney Grammy Awards where we look back at all of the great music from Disney parks, movies, and more. The Happiest Podcast on Earth team selects the nominees and will announce the winners that you the listeners will vote on! Will your favorite songs be in any of our nominations? Listen in to find out. HAPPY LISTENING EVERYONE!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>happiestpodcast@gmail.com (Happiest Podcast On Earth)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f0713b2019cf4d77a12898349c717319</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f0713b2019cf4d77a12898349c717319/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Expat Files: Living in Latin America : EXPAT FILES - 02.07.20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Descriptions- EXPAT FILES SHOW #927 FRI, FEB 07 (02-07-2020):&lt;/p&gt;
JOHNNY’S EXPAT FILES WEBSITE NAME CHANGE ANNOUNCEMENT!
 
My new website is &lt;a href='http://www.expatplanb.com/'&gt;www.ExpatPlanB.com&lt;/a&gt;. The old one &lt;a href='http://www.theexpatfiles.com/'&gt;www.theexpatfiles.com&lt;/a&gt; has been retired, so from now on please use &lt;a href='http://www.expatplanb.com/'&gt;www.ExpatPlanB.com&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;p&gt;#1- Your chances of car or motorcycle theft (if you own one) in Latin America&lt;/p&gt;
#2- What you need to know about LED light-bulbs and their rumored negative health effects and toxicity:
Should you worry? Are they safe, or should you revert back to incandescent or even those ugly fluorescent bulbs?
&lt;p&gt;#3- Latinas and their hair extension madness:&lt;/p&gt;
#4- Protecting your Latin American home and/or office from the bad guys:
DYI tips on setting up surveillance cameras  
 
#5- The general state of self-esteem in Latin America and why 95% of Latinos appear to be gringo wannabees:
Think about it, and consider how you’d feel if every day of your life you were reminded of the fact that that you grew up in, and are a product of the 3rd world.
&lt;p&gt;#6- The truth about car insurance in Latin America and why adding full coverage collision may not be worth the extra dough&lt;/p&gt;
#8- Be sure to pick up my new and revised, "LATIN AMERICAN HEALTHCARE REPORT":
It's the new edition for 2020 (and beyond) including the latest "Stem Cell" info and data and my top picks for the best treatment centers for expats and gringos. Just go to &lt;a href='http://www.expatplanb.com/'&gt;www.ExpatPlanB.com&lt;/a&gt; and click on the "Latin American Healthcare Report”.</description><author>karalee@garynull.com (The Expat Files: Living in Latin America)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">82236a61bb8840a09f2332eb627ac0c6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/82236a61bb8840a09f2332eb627ac0c6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 06:04:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The olive magazine podcast : ep 186 - The Future of Fungi - an artistic exploration of the mighty mushroom!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week Ellie chats to writer and curator Francesca Gavin about her new exhibition –&amp;nbsp;Mushrooms: The Art, Design and Future of Fungi at London’s Somerset House, which brings together the work of over 40 artists, designers and musicians. They chat about why she chose to focus on the mushroom, highlight some of the artists involved, and she tells Ellie what to expect from their pop-up fungi dining event.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts@immediate.co.uk (The olive magazine podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e197902a793e4b15a920db934227d62a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e197902a793e4b15a920db934227d62a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mobituaries with Mo Rocca : Anna May Wong: Death of a Trailblazer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Anna May Wong wasn't supposed to be in the movies. Her laundryman father was dead set against it. And Hollywood preferred white actors in "yellow face" for Asian characters. But Wong knew what she wanted. With her talent, beauty and tenacity, she ran a gauntlet of social and legal obstacles to become Hollywood's very first Chinese-American star. Mo talks with comedian Margaret Cho and actress Rosalind Chao about the woman who is finally getting her due.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Mobituaries@simonandschuster.com (Mobituaries with Mo Rocca)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d4f88edef75145e5801480b6c02bc776</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d4f88edef75145e5801480b6c02bc776/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Connecting with Walt - A look into the history of the man behind Mickey Mouse, Disneyland and Walt Disney World : #133 - Valentine's Day Disney+ Movies</title><description>02/07/20 - In this episode, Michael and Craig share their picks for what to watch on Disney+ this Valentine's Day!</description><author>craig@wdwinfo.com (Connecting with Walt - A look into the history of the man behind Mickey Mouse, Disneyland and Walt Disney World)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6dd0a6639c9a4244861ee6d8e8c599ac</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6dd0a6639c9a4244861ee6d8e8c599ac/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>DCL Podcast : 130 Using Special Services for a Family’s first Disney Cruise</title><description>&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img src="http://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/disneymagic.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-800" srcset="http://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/disneymagic.jpg 640w, http://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/disneymagic-300x169.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Listener Chris joins us to discuss his families first cruise with Disney Cruise Line.  They sailed aboard the Disney Wonder out of San Diego this past Fall.  His son is on the Autism Spectrum, so before the cruise he contacted Disney Cruise Lines Special Services to discuss recommendations they had for making their cruise the best it cold be.  We discuss how they set his family up for success on this cruise, along with their experiences on board and in the ports. You can find more about Special Services on the Disney Cruise Line Website, and in the Unofficial Guide to Disney Cruise Line 2020.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Contact Disney Cruise Line Special Services:&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.disneycruise.disney.go.com/special-services"&gt;http://www.disneycruise.disney.go.com/special-services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Phone # (407) 566-3500 (voice)/ (407) 566-7455 (TTY)&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Contact Steve, Christy, or Chris:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="steve@dclpodcast.com"&gt;steve@dclpodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="christy@packyourpixiedust.com"&gt;christy@packyourpixiedust.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="brightdisneybychris@gmail.com"&gt;brightdisneybychris@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Follow us via:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/dclpodcast"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/dclpodcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.instagram.com/dcl_podcast"&gt;http://www.instagram.com/dcl_podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Book your next vacation with Christy:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.packyourpixiedust.com"&gt;http://www.packyourpixiedust.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sekriese@comcast.net (DCL Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">766d266532bb42699ccd9f5ea2b04366</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/766d266532bb42699ccd9f5ea2b04366/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 18:31:42 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Monsters Among Us Podcast : Sn. 8 Ep. 20 Part 1 - Home Town Legends Season Finale!</title><description>Mel's Hole -  &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DauxjPshreU" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3DDauxjPshreU&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1581110331010000&amp;usg=AFQjCNGyx1qpKZZSKok0TpmzKxb9ZTHVcw"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DauxjPshreU&lt;/a&gt;     &lt;p&gt;Sodder Family Disappearance -  &lt;a href= "https://www.smithsonianmag.com/history/the-children-who-went-up-in-smoke-172429802/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.smithsonianmag.com/history/the-children-who-went-up-in-smoke-172429802/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1581110331010000&amp;usg=AFQjCNHFYVbf3IiB_S7XaHEoUDsJ-ZWA4Q"&gt;https://www.smithsonianmag.com/history/the-children-who-went-up-in-smoke-172429802/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; Sodder Children Buzzfeed video - &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z0AKoCMydkc" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3Dz0AKoCMydkc&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1581110331010000&amp;usg=AFQjCNFgiDWtdvKCcLRIIir7F9TzO4X4-A"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z0AKoCMydkc&lt;/a&gt;   Ghost of Bardley Road - &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GV_kBZidb-o" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3DGV_kBZidb-o&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1581110331010000&amp;usg=AFQjCNGcu3uCKTCXjvoz1AROi78SioZrmQ"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GV_kBZidb-o&lt;/a&gt;   Holcomb Road - &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7GprQ73gxbk" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3D7GprQ73gxbk&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1581110331010000&amp;usg=AFQjCNF6D1nw_ACllF3vDY6F1_I9rfFYBg"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7GprQ73gxbk&lt;/a&gt;   Hammond Circus Disaster - &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mGXE7ckAOOU" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3DmGXE7ckAOOU&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1581110331010000&amp;usg=AFQjCNFBfaNCcIFANaN4VYvVTrfACgqB9w"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mGXE7ckAOOU&lt;/a&gt;   Stories With Sapphire - &lt;a href= "https://audioboom.com/channels/5016598"&gt;https://audioboom.com/channels/5016598&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>monstersamonguspodcast@gmail.com (Monsters Among Us Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8f21d58ed0344c7fbaa194e37f865195</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8f21d58ed0344c7fbaa194e37f865195/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 14:54:58 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Far From Home : Revisiting Iran</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In light of the recent political developments that briefly brought the US and Iran to the brink of war, I’m re-releasing an excerpt of a story I produced for the first season of Far From Home. It’s about the time a few years ago when I drove through Iran with my brother Drew and our friends Jane and Rosi as part of an &lt;a href="http://www.teamdonundestan.com" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;11,000 mile road trip we took&lt;/a&gt; across Europe and Asia, raising money for charity. Along the way, we had enlightening conversations with average Iranians that made us see their country in a totally new light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can read more and see photos that accompany this episode &lt;a href="https://farfromhomepodcast.org/news/2017/3/29/an-eye-opening-experience" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;on my website.&lt;/a&gt; To listen to this complete story, as well as my other stories from Iran and the rest of my road trip, go back and check out the first season of this podcast. Note that it’s a series, so it’s best to start at the very beginning and listen to all the episodes in order for the story to make the most sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Far From Home is a podcast where award-winning public radio journalist Scott Gurian visits parts of the world that most people never think about and tells stories they've never heard. For more info, visit &lt;a href="http://farfromhomepodcast.org" title="farfromhomepodcast.org" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;farfromhomepodcast.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@farfromhomepodcast.org (Far From Home)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7cc426f5836f42d8b46e6b85b13dc2fa</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7cc426f5836f42d8b46e6b85b13dc2fa/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 13:09:30 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Gal Pal Show: Solo female travel, backpacking, bucket list inspiration, planning a trip, female travel advice and tips, and off the beaten track ideas. : 92: How to keep your money safe when travelling</title><description>&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt; Deciding how you're going to manage your money when you travel, is an easy. You just need to know few things first...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;Listen to this episode to hear my advice on your money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;I'm also giving you an update on my travel...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://mailchi.mp/ae404f33adb5/travel-planning-worksheet'&gt;Get your FREE Travel planning worksheet &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://mailchi.mp/ae404f33adb5/travel-planning-worksheet'&gt;and start planning your trip here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://galpalacademy.thinkific.com/courses/travel-planning-bootcamp-1'&gt;Want to go travelling?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://galpalacademy.thinkific.com/courses/travel-planning-bootcamp-1'&gt;Join Gal Pal Travel Planning Bootcamp here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jo@galpalacademy.com (Gal Pal Show: Solo female travel, backpacking, bucket list inspiration, planning a trip, female travel advice and tips, and off the beaten track ideas.)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">86a988eb1b354a31adcd06c71c0edbed</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/86a988eb1b354a31adcd06c71c0edbed/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 09:12:34 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Oh Boy, The Podcast : Episode 008 - Disney Villains we STAN, and Ranking the Most Evil</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With Villains After Hours starting tomorrow, we had no choice but to rank the most evil villains Disney has made (uhhhhhh Cruella kills dogs), and also share some of our favorite villains that we stan so hard, including some less thought of ones like GOOB FROM MEET THE ROBINSONS WHO JUST WANTED TO BE LOVED!!! Lot's of those this week lol - stoked to hear which villains you hold near and dear to your heart, and who you think are the worst of the worst!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;luv&lt;br&gt;da lost bros &amp;lt;3&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="http://www.thelostbros.com"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (http://www.thelostbros.com)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@lostbrostradingco.com (Oh Boy, The Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2fc693984eb0458d8116ebce2059fe3a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2fc693984eb0458d8116ebce2059fe3a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Tropical MBA Podcast - Entrepreneurship, Travel, and Lifestyle : TMBA531: A Lot Can Change In a Year</title><description>&lt;p&gt;One of our favorite things to do on this podcast is follow up on some of the entrepreneurial stories that we&amp;#39;ve covered in the past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This time last year, we recorded a podcast with Tommy Joiner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that episode, Tommy spoke about the genesis of his productized content generation service ContentPros.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast forward a year and Tommy has made some massive changes in his life. Not only has he sold ContentPros, but he also chose to part ways with his business partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;#39;s episode, Tommy returns to explain why he decided to move on from ContentPros and to share some insights into the exit process as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Dan@TropicalMBA.com (The Tropical MBA Podcast - Entrepreneurship, Travel, and Lifestyle)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ab1d544c6a044e82a5f776e944846ebf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ab1d544c6a044e82a5f776e944846ebf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WDWNT ParksCenter : ParksCenter - Spider-Man Soarin’ Over California! - Ep. 88</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This is ParksCenter. We cover the top news stories from this week in Disney Parks news in 30 minutes. This week, we’ll be talking about: It looks like Disney’s California Adventure might be getting a jumping, swinging Spider-Man Also in DCA, Soarin’ Over California returns for this year’s Food and Wine Festival We ask you […]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://wdwnt.com/2020/02/watch-parkscenter-88/"&gt;ParksCenter – Spider-Man Soarin’ Over California! – Ep. 88&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://wdwnt.com"&gt;WDW News Today&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>developer@wdwnt.com (WDWNT ParksCenter)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">34bc8a3fc40046c083b7bfbfe123ac82</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/34bc8a3fc40046c083b7bfbfe123ac82/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 04:00:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Trip That Changed Me : Paris with Nicole Smith: Instagram, risk-taking, and the ultimate souvenir</title><description>&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever wanted to capture a moment with a loved one while traveling, you’ve likely faced the awkward encounter of asking a stranger to take a photo, only to realize the final product is entirely subpar. On today’s episode, Nicole Smith shares how a reunion with her best friend in Paris gave her the idea for Flytographer, a company that connects travelers with local photographers around the world, capturing special moments and experiences in a way a selfie never could. While Nicole was satisfied with her career in tech and steady life back home in Canada, she couldn’t ignore the feeling that a need for better travel photography existed and ultimately decided to take the plunge into entrepreneurship. Over the last six years, Flytographer has expanded to three-hundred cities across six continents and has been hailed one of the fastest-growing startups in Canada. Anyone who wants to make an impact on the world of travel or may have a business idea they just can’t shake, this one's for you.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@podcastnation.org (The Trip That Changed Me)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a78daa5c8f2c48bf8a5f8b54b4f65be8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a78daa5c8f2c48bf8a5f8b54b4f65be8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 03:00:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Kentuckiana Sounds : Fun With Giant Gas Jets</title><description>To the average driver seeing it from their commute, The Kentucky Derby Festival Great Balloon Race might seems like a peaceful, placid affair. But as anyone who's ever been to the Balloon Glow or the liftoff of the Great Balloon Race knows, it takes a lot of generator-powered fans and roaring gas jets to get the colorful balloons off the ground. To hear the full recording, explore the sound map, or submit a sound visit www.wfpl.org/sounds or www.kentuckianasounds.org.</description><author>support@louisvillepublicmedia.org (Kentuckiana Sounds)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">42df553e8379436aa5c40b951118982c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/42df553e8379436aa5c40b951118982c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Bob and Sue : 03 Arches National Park: Getting Lost in the Fiery Furnace</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Would you go into a fiery furnace on purpose if you knew you’d probably get lost, have to squeeze through narrow openings, and be forced to crab walk over sketchy boulders? Well, that’s exactly what we did, and we even waited in line for a permit to do it. The Fiery Furnace in Arches National Park is a special treat for visitors as only a limited number of people are allowed permits each day to hike through this magnificent maze of rock formations. We’ve visited the fiery furnace in Arches National Park a couple of times, and in this episode, we talk about our experiences along the trail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this episode we discuss:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Karen's fantasy of being an off-duty park ranger&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our ranger-led tour into the fiery furnace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Returning on our own and getting lost in the slot canyons, and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How we live and work together 24/7&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Links:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dearbobandsue.com/episode-3"&gt;Photos from our trips to the fiery furnace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.recreation.gov/"&gt;Recreation.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/dearbobands"&gt;Join the conversation on Facebook&lt;/a&gt; - we want to hear from you!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dearbobandsue.com/"&gt;Our books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>jonah@puddlecreative.com (Dear Bob and Sue)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f46581561713490f90fc0f42b78a8148</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f46581561713490f90fc0f42b78a8148/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Offbeat Life - become location independent : Extended: How to make passive income with Pinterest.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; What you'll find: &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;The importance of SEO and keywords&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;How to turn a cold audience into a warm audience&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Cross promoting on Pinterest and Instagram&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "http://%20https//www.theoffbeatlife.com/episodes/pinterest-marketer/"&gt; GET THE FULL INTERVIEW WITH MOLLY WHERE SHE SHARES HOW SHE TRAVELS THE WORLD AS A PINTEREST MANAGER.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@theoffbeatlife.com (The Offbeat Life - become location independent)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7e5c65f6433e4f81af4a0184979a7eee</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7e5c65f6433e4f81af4a0184979a7eee/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Puerto Vallarta Travel  Show Podcast : Rodolfo The Blind Singer on The Malecon in Puerto Vallarta, Mexico</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Rodolfo Gutierrez Carbajal is the blind tenor who sings opera as he walks the Malecon in Puerto Vallarta, Mexico. You can hire him to sing at your events. Hire him by going to his website at www.pvsinger.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>pvtravelshow@gmail.com (Puerto Vallarta Travel  Show Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4740bb9b36d448798ca8d33ac54a9d26</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4740bb9b36d448798ca8d33ac54a9d26/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 18:01:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Duolingo Spanish Podcast : Jaime, el artista (Jaime, The Artist)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A Spanish fashion designer works hard to give her autistic son every opportunity—then discovers that he has a special talent and makes him her business partner.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A transcript of this episode is available at https://podcast.duolingo.com.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@duolingo.com (Duolingo Spanish Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4bd6f19586cb4a8288a5c04565de460d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4bd6f19586cb4a8288a5c04565de460d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Books And Travel : Cycling Around The World With ML Buchman</title><description>Sometimes we can only find our true selves by leaving everything we thought we wanted behind. Matt Buchman was a successful business consultant, but when he lost everything, he set off to cycle around the world. It was a way to escape his old life, but also to find a new path. In this interview, he talks about some of the highs and lows of the trip, but it’s also a discussion on what really matters and how to find home again.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.booksandtravel.page/cycling-around-the-world/ml-buchman/" rel="attachment wp-att-1245"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.mlbuchman.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;M.L. Buchman&lt;/a&gt; is the author of over 60 romance, thriller, sci-fi, and fantasy books, as well as nonfiction. And today, we’re talking about his memoir, &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/312oUnX" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Mid-Life Crisis on Wheels: a Bicycle Journey Around the World&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
Show notes&lt;br /&gt;
* How losing everything led to a grand adventure&lt;br /&gt;
* Dealing with fear of the unknown&lt;br /&gt;
* Letting go of a perfect plan in order to learn more about yourself&lt;br /&gt;
* How the lows are just as important as the highs when traveling&lt;br /&gt;
* Looking for a definition of ‘home’&lt;br /&gt;
* Adjusting to ‘normal’ life after an extended period of travel&lt;br /&gt;
* Recommended books about cycling adventures&lt;br /&gt;
You can find ML Buchman at &lt;a href="https://www.mlbuchman.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;MLBuchman.com&lt;/a&gt; and on Twitter @mlbuchman&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Transcript of the interview&lt;br /&gt;
Joanna: M.L. Buchman is the author of over 60 romance, thriller, sci-fi, and fantasy books, as well as nonfiction. And today, we’re talking about his memoir, Mid-Life Crisis on Wheels: a Bicycle Journey Around the World. Welcome to the show, Matt.&lt;br /&gt;
Matt: Hello, and thank you. Hey, Joanna.&lt;br /&gt;
Joanna: It’s great to have you on the show. So, look, this is a hell of a book. It’s really fantastic. But I want to start at the beginning.&lt;br /&gt;
What led up to the decision to cycle around the world? What was happening in your life?&lt;br /&gt;
Matt: I tell people it’s really easy to launch on a trip like this. All you have to do is lose everything.&lt;br /&gt;
I had a business partner with a different definition of the word integrity than mine. I ended up losing not only my job and my business, but my career. And that ended up because I burned bridges from Houston to Calgary to Denver. It was astonishing what the train wreckage was.&lt;br /&gt;
I was going to lose the house. I was sitting in this house I’d spent seven years remodeling with every penny I had, and the few minutes of time. A friend said, ‘Well, if you sell the house,’ and I was like, ‘Okay, I’m going to lose the house …’&lt;br /&gt;
I started looking for the second half of that question. I was out for a walk and got nearly clipped by a cyclist, and it was like, ‘Oh, I could bicycle around the world.’&lt;br /&gt;
Suddenly, it made sense, because nothing else in my life did. I was single, and bummed out, and frustrated, and angry, and a workaholic that had no work. So I sold everything and got on a bicycle.&lt;br /&gt;
Joanna: I love that one. A workaholic without work. I’m a workaholic. I understand that. That’s the pressure to forget everything else.&lt;br /&gt;
It’s interesting because, on a serious note, your life was a train wreck, but you still had this house. So often it seems that we spend a lot of energy, and time, and emotional stress building things like a house, the perfect thing to have, but that’s not what really matters.&lt;br /&gt;
Do you think almost that this was going to happen, that you hadn’t really addressed what was important?&lt;br /&gt;
Matt: Yes and no. I think that what occurred was inevitable because of who I was being. Because at that time in my life, I was still under the belief that if I just try harder, it will work. If it isn’t working, try harder.&lt;br /&gt;
So I designed and built the house for the family I never had time to find.</description><author>jo@booksandtravel.page (Books And Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3ce911fef9c8416bb7e137db7018df9c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3ce911fef9c8416bb7e137db7018df9c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 16:10:02 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Overland Journal Podcast : Principles of Overlanding :: Payload</title><description>To review the show notes, please visit: &lt;a href="https://overlandjournal.com/podcast/principles-of-overlanding-payload/"&gt;https://overlandjournal.com/podcast/principles-of-overlanding-payload/&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>scott@overlandinternational.com (The Overland Journal Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b1ef007b0a944302ac2d8d88afe0f8ff</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b1ef007b0a944302ac2d8d88afe0f8ff/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>CruiseTipsTV Unplugged - Cruise Tips and More : Some of the Most Costly Cruise Blunders</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We've all made them at some point, yes this week we are talking about costly cruise blunders. We asked for your worst cruise blunders, and this week we'll share them with you. Hopefully we can learn from each other's cruise mistakes, and avoid these costly pitfalls.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As always, you can email us your questions at  sheri@cruisetipstv.com. We'd also LOVE if you'd leave a review where you listen to this podcast, and screen shot the show and share it on Instagram using the hashtag #cttvunplugged.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Download our shore day bag checklist, and more cruise packing and planning checklists &amp; videos by joining the CruiseTipsTV Academy. We have a special discount code for our podcast listeners. To redeem the $5.00 discount on our master class enter code UNPLUGGED at &lt;a href= "http://academy.cruisetipstv.com"&gt;http://academy.cruisetipstv.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@cruisetipstv.com (CruiseTipsTV Unplugged - Cruise Tips and More)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6ed9f41502ea4850af5db0e764e516fc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6ed9f41502ea4850af5db0e764e516fc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Parklandia : The District Dudes Explore DC's National Mall</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For season 2 of Parklandia, there are a lot of firsts we were excited about, and new chapters to begin. From the first guest interviews to the first time we called 911 from a national park. And today is another first: it’s our first time covering an urban park! Washington D.C. is just so rich with history and culture. And the omnipresence of memorials and historic sites is inescapable. And while the classical white marble buildings of the National Mall and the memorial parks are a far cry from Yosemite, the city is filled with more national park sites than most states have. In this episode, we'll walk in Nicholas Cage's footsteps, find out what we &lt;em&gt;didn't&lt;/em&gt; know about D.C., and indulge in some of our favorite cookies on the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Parklandia on Instagram at &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/parklandiapod/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;@parklandiapod&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, join the Parklandia Rangers &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/ParklandiaRangers/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and Like our &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/parklandiapod/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Parklandia)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d5c0165500434537b3559eb94931beb5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d5c0165500434537b3559eb94931beb5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WAYPOINTS - with Jim Klug : #21 Jeff Currier: A Lifetime of Fly Fishing The World</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With over forty years of fly fishing the world, Jeff Currier has quite possibly fished more countries (60 and counting) and caught more species (over 400 and counting) with a fly rod than any person alive. Jeff is constantly traveling and developing new techniques for catching the most exotic fish imaginable in places where even the most avid adventurers are at times hesitant to go! As an active lecturer, published author, accomplished artist, IGFA World Record holder, and the subject of numerous films, articles, and media projects, Jeff is a fly fishing personality that is as entertaining and educational as he is legitimate. He is an incredibly reliable source of information and inspiration, the most senior member of the Yellow Dog Ambassador team, and a close friend. And while Jeff can boast one of the most impressive resumes around, he remains one of the most authentic and humble people in the industry – always willing to take his accomplishments one step further by passing on what he has learned. Kicking-off Season 2 of &lt;em&gt;Waypoints&lt;/em&gt; is an episode that scratches the surface of a life deeply devoted to fly fishing the world: a sit-down that is packed with numerous tips and great fishing stories from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jim@yellowdogflyfishing.com (WAYPOINTS - with Jim Klug)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">64812e9a0c2440c3a094312afd187d70</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/64812e9a0c2440c3a094312afd187d70/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Disney Cruise Line Show : #004 - Strategies for Selecting Your Disney Cruise Line Stateroom</title><description>02/05/20 - In this episode, the panel discusses different strategies and important things to know when selecting your stateroom on a Disney Cruise Line sailing!</description><author>craig@disneyinfo.com (The Disney Cruise Line Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0b28328aa0b640fe94c3319dc4f06e06</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0b28328aa0b640fe94c3319dc4f06e06/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Morocco : Why Morocco 030 – Lonely Planet travel writer Helen Ranger on Morocco’s Middle Atlas Mountains</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For the thirtieth episode of Why Morocco, I reached Lonely Planet travel writer Helen Ranger by telephone from my studio in Marrakech. Helen is a friend and colleague, concierge, a fellow Morocco lover albeit one who prefers to call Fez home, and has recently submitted a chapter about Morocco&amp;#8217;s rural Middle Atlas Mountain region for the forthcoming Lonely Planet Morocco guidebooks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In our chat, Helen talks about two of the national parks in the region, trekking options, the Sidi Harazem baths, caves, and what you’ll want to know for planning a Middle Atlas getaway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With nearby waterfalls and caves, nature reserves, a brutalistis thermal bath complex, village markets, and festivals to enjoy, I don’t really understand why more people don’t take advantage of a short-haul long weekend in the Fez countryside. And with all the tips that Helen provides for planning a trip to the rural Middle Atlas region, Fez could double as a base for exploring the old city and a getaway in the countryside. After all, the city is served with international flights to leading European destinations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more Morocco ideas and advise, follow me on Instagram at &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/mandyinmorocco" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;@mandyinmorocco&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My other projects include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tasting Marrakech food and cultural tours in Marrakech &lt;a href="http://tasting-marrakech.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;tasting-marrakech.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel and public relations consulting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Freelance writing for print and digital  &lt;a href="https://mandyinmorocco.com/freelance-writing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;mandyinmorocco.com/freelance-writing/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mandyjsinclair@gmail.com (Why Morocco)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">041358d6095b4f2faab81eacf951a206</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/041358d6095b4f2faab81eacf951a206/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:12:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Familie auf Weltreise -Der Podcast : 74 | Ist das noch gesund? Unsere Beobachtung vom australischen Essverhalten</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Du bist was du isst - den Spruch habe ich gelesen in einem Buch, als wir anfingen uns mit Ernährung intensiver auseinanderzusetzen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wir sind jetzt seit fast einem Jahr in Australien an der Ostküste und fassen unsere eigenen, subjektiven Beobachtungen der australischen Esskultur zusammen. Viel Spass mit Pommes und Cola. ;-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://katrin-fit.net/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sport mit Katrin - Katrin-Fit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/familieaufweltreise"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Der geschlossenen Gruppe "Familie auf Weltreise" beitreten&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.familieaufweltreise.de/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unser neuer Blog&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/familieaufweltreise"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instagram&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://youtube.com/c/familieaufweltreisede"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YouTube&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2WLSqdF"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on Family&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unsere Ressourcen findest Du auf unserer Webseite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.familieaufweltreise.de/ressourcen"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;www.Familieaufweltreise.de/ressourcen&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lust auf ein Reiseguthaben?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;25 € AirBnB Gutschein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2BtQrCo"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://bit.ly/2BtQrCo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;15 € Booking.com Gutschein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://booki.ng/2A67Xwu"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://booki.ng/2A67Xwu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>kontakt@familieaufweltreise.de (Familie auf Weltreise -Der Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c46b294c9d2140d487e090aa59a52212</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c46b294c9d2140d487e090aa59a52212/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Theme Park Rangers : Coaster paparazzi tracks rides coming to Disney, Universal Orlando, SeaWorld, Busch Gardens (Ep. 36)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Self-proclaimed coaster paparazzi Dan Leavelle, owner of Midway Mayhem, makes a living tracking rides as they take shape behind construction walls. He discusses the roller coasters coming to area attractions in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="fs3ks-0-0"&gt;SeaWorld ‘s Ice Breaker (2:02)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="fs3ks-0-0"&gt;Iron Gwazi: Floridians are not ready for this coaster (6:36)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="fs3ks-0-0"&gt;Is there another SeaWorld coaster in the works for 2021 ? (12:12)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="fs3ks-0-0"&gt;995 rides on Mako (14:49)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="fs3ks-0-0"&gt;Coaster yoga (15:37)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="fs3ks-0-0"&gt;Islands of Adventure: Jurassic coaster? (16:07)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="fs3ks-0-0"&gt;The best coaster in town (19:26)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="fs3ks-0-0"&gt;Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind at Epcot (25:14)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="fs3ks-0-0"&gt;Tron at Magic Kingdom (28:05)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="fs3ks-0-0"&gt;Roller coaster wish list (29:17)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="fs3ks-0-0"&gt;Will I-Drive coaster ever be built? (30:36)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>video@orlandosentinel.com (Theme Park Rangers)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">04ea12fb540547778fecb477de2d01f7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/04ea12fb540547778fecb477de2d01f7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 13:26:15 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Exploring the North Shore : Episode 20: Statues of the North Shore</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Martha had to be out of town, so this week we bring you another great history episode! Jaye is joined by the owner of &lt;a href='https://thebiglakelife.com/collections/apparel'&gt;The Big Lake&lt;/a&gt;, Abby Tofte, to discuss the Statues of the North Shore. They discuss the now-gone King of Neptune that once graced Duluth's Canal Park before being destroyed in 1963. Then, they head up to Silver Bay to discuss their favorite North Shore statue: Rocky Taconite! Learn how Jaye's dad played a big role in Rocky's growing popularity in the mid-2010s. Finally, they jump down to Two Harbors to discuss what may be arguably the most well-known statue on the North Shore: Pierre the Pantsless Voyageur of Two Harbors. Find out why Pierre is pantsless, and all about the efforts put into saving him from being destroyed in 2008.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about Neptune, Rocky, and Pierre on the Exploring the North Shore website!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The King of Neptune: &lt;a href='https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/king-of-neptune-statue/'&gt;https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/king-of-neptune-statue/&lt;/a&gt;Rocky Taconite: &lt;a href='https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/rocky-taconite/'&gt;https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/rocky-taconite/&lt;/a&gt;Pierre the Pantsless Voyageur: &lt;a href='https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/?p=46747'&gt;https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/pierre-the-pantsless-voyageur/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join the Rocky Taconite Fan Club: &lt;a href='https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/rocky-taconite/'&gt;https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/rocky-taconite-fan-club/&lt;/a&gt;Join the Pierre the Pantsless Voyageur of Two Harbors Fan Club: &lt;a href='https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/?p=46747'&gt;https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/pierre-the-pantsless-voyageur-fan-club/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out Abby's online store for the Rocky Taconite t-shirt mentioned in the episode: &lt;a href='https://thebiglakelife.com/collections/apparel'&gt;https://thebiglakelife.com/collections/apparel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This episode is sponsored by &lt;a href='https://www.cascadevacationrentals.com/'&gt;Cascade Vacation Rentals&lt;/a&gt;. Use promo code "Podcast" at check-out to receive Cascade's largest available percent off discount (discount changes seasonally). This episode is also sponsored by &lt;a href='https://thebiglakelife.com/'&gt;The Big Lake&lt;/a&gt;. Use promo code "Explore" at check-out to receive 15% off your first online order. Thank you to our wonderful sponsors!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marketing@staycvr.com (Exploring the North Shore)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cda3b34cac1e4023bf81b98be72e8c29</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cda3b34cac1e4023bf81b98be72e8c29/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 04:45:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>A Way To Go : Loving Disney World, Whether You’re a Kid or an Adult with Sally Kohn</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Political commentator and community organizer Sally Kohn grew up on a steady diet of Disney World visits. Though these days she spends a lot of her time talking about political division, diversity, and identity, she also builds a strong case for vacationing in The Happiest Place On Earth, and shares tips for how to make it magical. Go ahead and act like a kid. It’s what you’re here for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Find more info about this episode at &lt;a href="https://urldefense.proofpoint.com/v2/url?u=http-3A__Fathomaway.com&amp;amp;d=DwMFaQ&amp;amp;c=GC0NZZhaEw6GOQSjMHI2g15k_drElRoPmOYiK2k0eZ8&amp;amp;r=QQqtrehlQRY19SGPJ2205twNczy34pobDq7ZUMRMscQ&amp;amp;m=d1OPNDCQPEvSO7R1NQsHNQDBOS5frJVaq_qmSDsO7SM&amp;amp;s=y2BUofGSF6hZjHidDeCMpAoH3XNGJaMBgWoOvjp6r5g&amp;amp;e="&gt;Fathomaway.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (A Way To Go)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">eb59f805c4974baa9759f51fa7e4e425</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/eb59f805c4974baa9759f51fa7e4e425/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>New Books in African Studies : Sean Jacobs, "Media in Postapartheid South Africa: Postcolonial Politics in the Age of Globalization" (Indiana UP, 2019)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newschool.edu/international-affairs/faculty/sean-jacobs/"&gt;Sean Jacobs&lt;/a&gt;, Associate Professor of International Affairs at The New School in New York City. Jacobs is also the founder and editor of the acclaimed &lt;a href="https://africasacountry.com/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Africa is A Country&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; website, a leader His new book &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/0253025427/?tag=newbooinhis-20"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Media in Postapartheid South Africa: Postcolonial Politics in the Age of Globalization&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, published by Indiana University Press in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In it, Jacobs makes a potent argument about the role of the media, in its many new and old forms, as an arbiter of belonging and citizenship in our information-saturated age. Using South Africa since the 1994 “transition” from Apartheid to democracy as his case study, Jacobs analysis demonstrates the importance of not only understanding an ever-changing media landscape as part of any study of politics, but also how the media shapes how public goods as made accessible to whom and how.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Media in Postapartheid South Africa &lt;/em&gt;is also a study of how the processes and structures of colonialism mix with the discursive tricks of political elites during Apartheid and after 1994, and how the media shapes how South Africans see themselves, in advertising, soap operas and reality shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.colgate.edu/about/directory/sthomson"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Susan Thomson&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; is associate professor of peace and conflict studies at Colgate University.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marshallpoe@gmail.com (New Books in African Studies)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a94b919608bc4415862d298da42899a2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a94b919608bc4415862d298da42899a2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dreams Unlimited Travel Show - A Weekly Discussion About Travel and Dreams Unlimited Travel : #167 - Top 5 Money Savings Tips for a Walt Disney World Vacation - Kathy Werling</title><description>02/04/20 - In this episode, Dreams Unlimited Travel agent Kathy Werling shares her personal top five tips to help you save money for your Walt Disney World Vacation!</description><author>craig@wdwinfo.com (Dreams Unlimited Travel Show - A Weekly Discussion About Travel and Dreams Unlimited Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">de3d2781d91941e99bfc5d78c3b0d777</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/de3d2781d91941e99bfc5d78c3b0d777/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>La Lido Loca Cruise Podcast : 9. Big Cruise Ship or Small Cruise Ship?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to episode #9 of the La Lido Loca podcast.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Join Jenny and Tony as they talk about cruising!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show Notes:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on YouTube:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;La Lido Loca Podcast: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCLoGEyIWH6f6mkJxDCweDag"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCLoGEyIWH6f6mkJxDCweDag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;La Lido Loca Cruising: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqFivW2VWJtGfvrMreyjNbw"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqFivW2VWJtGfvrMreyjNbw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Let Jenny help with your travel, you can contact her at: &lt;a href= "mailto:jbarnette@cruiseshipcenters.com"&gt;jbarnette@cruiseshipcenters.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Info about La Lido Loca Group Cruises: &lt;a href="http://www.lalidoloca.com/groupcruise" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;http://www.lalidoloca.com/groupcruise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on Social Media: Facebook Page - &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt; Instagram - &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt; Twitter - &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/lalidoloca" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://twitter.com/lalidoloca&lt;/a&gt; Pintrest - &lt;a href="https://www.pinterest.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.pinterest.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Represent the locafam with a t-shirt, check out the latest designs at: &lt;a href="https://teespring.com/stores/lalidoloca-funshop" target= "_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://teespring.com/stores/lalidoloca-funshop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our mailing address is: La Lido Loca 4142 Mariner Blvd #402 Spring Hill, FL 34609&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Support our creative efforts at Patreon: &lt;a href="http://www.patreon.com/lalidoloca" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;http://www.patreon.com/lalidoloca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Please Submit Questions or Comments to &lt;a href= "mailto:tony@lalidoloca.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;tony@lalidoloca.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tony@lalidoloca.com (La Lido Loca Cruise Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f2abea88d6094cecb1f2624543156a8d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f2abea88d6094cecb1f2624543156a8d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 19:20:19 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Thoughtful Travel Podcast : 173 Anxiety and Travel</title><description>&lt;p&gt;There's a bit of a myth out there that we travellers are brave, confident people who never get anxious. From my own life and knowing many other travel-loving friends who also have experienced anxiety, I can promise you this is wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Episode 173 of The Thoughtful Travel Podcast includes two very special conversations with women who divulge some of their very personal experiences with anxiety and its connection with travel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Firstly, I speak with Megan Blandford (who literally wrote the book on anxiety!) about some of her experiences with anxiety during her travels. Megan gives some really specific examples of how anxiety gripped her on trips to Japan and earlier on a dolphin swim trip and I personally find this one of the best ways to understand more about what anxiety can look like on our travels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I then get the chance to chat with Laura Waters who has just published a book that also features a lot of her anxiety: Laura spend five months hiking from one end of New Zealand to the other and what happened to her anxiety during this trip is fascinating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Megan Blandford &lt;a href="https://meganblandford.net/"&gt;https://meganblandford.net/&lt;/a&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Her book I&amp;rsquo;m Fine (And Other Lies) about postnatal depression and motherhood &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2tY7zAc"&gt;https://amzn.to/2tY7zAc&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Laura Waters &lt;a href="https://soultrekkers.com.au/"&gt;https://soultrekkers.com.au/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Laura&amp;rsquo;s book Bewildered &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2S20zu2"&gt;https://amzn.to/2S20zu2&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to Deal with Travel Anxiety - Episode 93 - &lt;a href="https://notaballerina.com/93"&gt;https://notaballerina.com/93&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Getting Past Travel Anxiety - Episode 71 - &lt;a href="https://notaballerina.com/71"&gt;https://notaballerina.com/71&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My blog post from a few years back about my experiences with anxiety and travel - &lt;a href="https://www.notaballerina.com/2015/02/travel-for-the-anxious-anxiety-prone.html"&gt;https://www.notaballerina.com/2015/02/travel-for-the-anxious-anxiety-prone.html&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join our Facebook group for Thoughtful Travellers -&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/thoughtfultravellers"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/thoughtfultravellers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show notes: &lt;a href="http://notaballerina.com/173"&gt;https://notaballerina.com/173&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>amandakendle@me.com (The Thoughtful Travel Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3c71e9107f824696aa18a0a7d1d134a3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3c71e9107f824696aa18a0a7d1d134a3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 14:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>We Travel There with Lee Huffman : Milwaukee, WI | Riding Harleys and Fear The Deer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We're in Milwaukee, Wisconsin with Jenna Kashou, the author of "100 things to do in Milwaukee before you die." She talks about the Harley Davidson Museum, best eats in the Third Ward, and why you should Fear the Deer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show notes are at &lt;a href="https://WeTravelThere.com/milwaukee" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://WeTravelThere.com/milwaukee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Bluffworks’ stylish clothing is designed with the modern traveler in mind. It is wrinkle-resistant, machine washable, and very comfortable with hidden pockets to protect your valuables. Save 10% with our promo code at &lt;a href= "https://WeTravelThere.com/bluffworks" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;WeTravelThere.com/bluffworks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wetravelthere@gmail.com (We Travel There with Lee Huffman)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9ed7a4fb2dd74164bd5f37abe4841458</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9ed7a4fb2dd74164bd5f37abe4841458/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 09:26:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind The Glass : [S3, E2] The Most 'Affordable' Supercars You Can Buy</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week Tony and I discuss the most 'affordable' supercars you can find on sale today. With prices dropping over the last 12-18 months, you can now find some amazing deals on supercars starting from circa £30k right up to F12 TDFs which are still way over list but have dropped some £200k in recent times. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;02:50 - My Taycan Experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;05:00 - Tony Gets Political&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;08:18 - Alfa Romeo 4C&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;11:31 - Audi R8&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;17:08 - Bentley Continental&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;22:20 - Ferrari F12 TDF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;24:00 - Porsche 911 R&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;26:50 - Is This Price Correction Or A Dip?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;28:30 - Porsche Carrera GT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;29:30 - Classics vs Modern Supercars&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;40:30 - Ferrari FF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;42:00 - McLaren 600LT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;49:00 - AMG GTR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hope you enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>info@seenthroughglass.com (Behind The Glass)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ee1ddb4fb30740058b2b8ae7e9e8a744</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ee1ddb4fb30740058b2b8ae7e9e8a744/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 08:58:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Living Adventurously : "What is it that I want?" - an Adventure with a Raft and a Piano. Living Adventurously 15</title><description>Ben Cummins is on a mission to deliver a piano from Liverpool to London. On a home-made raft. That he propels himself. Within 25 years... So far it has taken Ben seven years to push his raft the 127 miles along the canal from Liverpool to Leeds!&lt;br&gt;This adventure / art project / way of life began when Ben asked himself a brilliant question, "what is it that I want from my life?"&lt;br&gt;Ben invited me onto his charming, quirky, stylish canal boat-cum-raft (built from locally-salvaged and donated materials), cooked me lunch, and told me his story. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;a href="https://livingadventurously.transistor.fm/subscribe"&gt;PLEASE SUBSCRIBE TO THE LIVING ADVENTUROUSLY PODCAST&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(It’s completely free, zero hassle to do (&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://livingadventurously.transistor.fm/subscribe"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;click here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;), but really helpful for me trying to get a new podcast off the ground. If you’re feeling extra kind, please leave a review on the app – that really helps.)&lt;/strong&gt;Listen on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/living-adventurously/id1489454694"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/2aYqIdvtVJkhIPklHaoXA3"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=486751&amp;amp;refid=stpr"&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://tunein.com/podcasts/Storytelling-Podcasts/Living-Adventurously-p1275719/"&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt; (“Alexa, please play the Living Adventurously podcast”) or on your favourite podcast platform such as Overcast, &lt;a href="https://podcasts.google.com/?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9mZWVkcy50cmFuc2lzdG9yLmZtL2xpdmluZy1hZHZlbnR1cm91c2x5"&gt;Google Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, Pocket Casts, &lt;a href="https://www.breaker.audio/living-adventurously"&gt;Breaker&lt;/a&gt;, Soundcloud, Castbox, Castro.&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.alastairhumphreys.com/podcast"&gt;www.alastairhumphreys.com/podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;SHOW NOTES&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you enjoy listening to this episode over a cup of coffee and think it might be worth the price, you can &lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;buy me a coffee here:&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;www. ko-fi.com/al_humphreys&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep up to date with future episodes (and my other adventures, projects and books) with my &lt;a href="https://www.alastairhumphreys.com/more/subscribe/"&gt;free monthly newsletter: alastairhumphreys.com/more/subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Say hello on &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Al_Humphreys"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/al_humphreys/"&gt;Instagram: @al_humphreys&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Piano Raft - A floating centre of excellence. &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/pianoraft/"&gt;@pianoraft&lt;/a&gt; on Instagram. Website &lt;a href="https://pianoraft.weebly.com/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus on "allow" not "how" - let stuff happen rather than worrying too much.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Nick-Weston-Tree-House-Diaries/dp/B00NBH2ONA"&gt;Nick Weston&lt;/a&gt;, who lived in a treehouse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ben Parry, &lt;a href="http://culturalhijack.org/"&gt;artist&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I didn't want to be a numpty, to be irresponsible or unsafe. They were my concerns. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having an anchor or a framework to the project is helpful, even when allowing possibility and serendipity into your life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A 'purposeless mission' allows all the good stuff to happen once you have started.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;THIS PODCAST IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY KOMOOT&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;Komoot&lt;/a&gt; is a route planning and navigation app that inspires and enables great outdoor experiences.Your very own outdoor experiences are waiting for you. Go explore more with &lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;komoot&lt;/a&gt;. Use the voucher code &lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;ADVENTUROUS&lt;/a&gt; to claim your free region bundle.The personalised planning and navigation tools ensure you plan the adventure that’s perfect for &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;. Komoot is Europe’s number 1 outdoor app, with route planning and navigation functionality, and strong community-driven inspirational features in the form of recommended Highlights and inspirational route Collections. It is used by over 8.5 million adventurers worldwide. Komoot is becoming the app of choice for cyclists and hikers the world over, with rapid community growth in the UK, the US and other parts of Europe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" title="★ Support this podcast by donating ★" href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;★ Support this podcast by donating ★&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>alastair@alastairhumphreys.com (Living Adventurously)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9ecf1cbccde1448785083671a4fb4679</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9ecf1cbccde1448785083671a4fb4679/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 02:45:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Sake On Air : Know Your Hosts: Shuso Imada &amp; Chris Hughes</title><description>This week it’s time once again to take a moment to get to know the team here at Sake On Air. We first aired one of these episodes back in October (Episode 27), where you got to know Sebastie Lemoine and Christopher Pellegrini; aka, “little Chris”. This week you’ll be hearing from Christopher’s sake-inspired counterpart, […]</description><author>Frowley3@gmail.com (Sake On Air)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5e7b6469c2d64be4a5677c4b7b4b2605</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5e7b6469c2d64be4a5677c4b7b4b2605/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:46:08 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hoosier Outdoorsmen Podcast : Episode 36 In This Episode I talk to Brandon Tormoehlen about Coon Hunting in Indiana</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode I talk with Brandon Tormorehlen about coon hunting in Indiana and his experiences coon hunting.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Rileyhendrixson@live.com (The Hoosier Outdoorsmen Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1884ac278b8a41b1ab306ac7b298d160</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1884ac278b8a41b1ab306ac7b298d160/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Join Us in France Travel Podcast : UNESCO World Heritage Sites in France, Episode 269</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Annie and Elyse discuss UNESCO World Heritage sites in France, that they are and why it matters. &lt;a href= "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_World_Heritage_Sites_in_France"&gt; France has 44 sites&lt;/a&gt; inscribed on the list and several more are in the process of applying.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Some UNESCO Word Heritage sites in France are man-made and others are natural sites. The fortified city of Carcassonne is one of the man-made sites while the Gulf of Porto in Corsica is a natural site.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Some UNESCO sites are very well defined (Notre Dame Cathedral in Paris) others are harder to describe (the banks of the River Seine for example). Some are extremely famous (the Pont du Gard) and others not as much (the fortifications of Vauban).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Getting listed as a UNESCO World Heritage site can have a big impact on a site. A great example of that is the city center of Albi. It was a bit of a sleepy town for a long time and since getting listed it get large numbers of visitors.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The city center of Toulouse between the Saint Sernin Basilica and the Pont Neuf should probably be listed. But there are still some small medieval streets in that area that haven't been renovated in a long time and don't look great.&lt;/p&gt; What does it mean to be a UNESCO World Heritage site in France? &lt;p&gt;UNESCO World Heritage sites must meet several criteria on a list of 10 that we discuss briefly. Then candidates must submit an application that details why they think they qualify.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In France it is cities and Departments that decide to make such applications with the help of their region. The national government doesn't get involved officially&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;#joinusinfrance #UNESCO #unescoworldheritage #unescosite #unescoheritagesite #unescoworldheritagecity #unescowordheritage #unescoworldculturalheritage&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:%20annie@joinusinfrance.com"&gt;Email&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://joinusinfrance.com/audiotours/"&gt;Annie's VoiceMap Paris Tours&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/joinusinfrance/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href= "https://www.pinterest.fr/France_Travel_Podcast/"&gt;Pinterest&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/addictedtofrance/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ParisPodcast"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>annie@joinusinfrance.com (Join Us in France Travel Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">249b8832da3a40c9a55efac0bcad4b3d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/249b8832da3a40c9a55efac0bcad4b3d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>National Parks Traveler Podcast : National Parks Traveler: Scenic Science In The National Parks, And Bison Management Planning</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Emily Hoff and Maygen Keller discuss their upcoming book, Scenic Science of the National Parks, an Explorers Guide to Wildlife, Geology, and Botany. The book, scheduled to arrive March 31, is a wonderfully new guidebook to help you get the most out of your national park adventures.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tanya Shenk, National Park Service scientist, explains a draft framework for bison stewardship in the Midwest Region of the park system. It’s a region where you can find bison at Tallgrass Prairie National Preserve in Kansas, Badlands National Park and Wind Cave National Park in South Dakota, and Theodore Roosevelt National Park in North Dakota.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>kurt@nationalparkstraveler.org (National Parks Traveler Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f88cd9c3d5494d33b1a14e0154b6d16c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f88cd9c3d5494d33b1a14e0154b6d16c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Australia All Over : Australia All Over highlights podcast</title><description>More great interviews from Australia All Over with Macca</description><author>localfeedback@your.abc.net.au (Australia All Over)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4ceefc319c8e449bba32df856a9cfd79</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4ceefc319c8e449bba32df856a9cfd79/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 11:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Well-Traveled with AAA : The Wonders of Phoenix</title><description>&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Well-Traveled&lt;/em&gt;" Correspondent, Samantha Brown, host of the Emmy-winning PBS program, “&lt;em&gt;Places to Love&lt;/em&gt;,” discovers more than just sunshine and dessert in Arizona’s capital city. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sonixcursions@gmail.com (Well-Traveled with AAA)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">65d3562728c84fcebd4636e3b9b8bccd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/65d3562728c84fcebd4636e3b9b8bccd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Become Nomad - Digital Nomad Lifestyle and Long Term Travel : BN069:  Escapes and attachments of the nomadic lifestyle</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, we will go over some of the recent repeating questions by readers of the blog. We will start by analyzing the concept of a digital lifestyle as a form of escape. We will also dive deep into the fascinating topic of attachments, and how to disconnect or connect to them.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>eli@becomenomad.com (Become Nomad - Digital Nomad Lifestyle and Long Term Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">29eb2f1f1b044ed2a88583e1c0283cad</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/29eb2f1f1b044ed2a88583e1c0283cad/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 10:56:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Normal to Nomad : #12 | Lindsey - Solo Female Nomad &amp; Alaska Native</title><description>&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://normal2nomad.com/podcast/lindsey" target=""&gt;Show Notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>barronlink@gmail.com (Normal to Nomad)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f26b898c376a467a9e56c7c84429fecd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f26b898c376a467a9e56c7c84429fecd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 14:07:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>EarzUp!  : EarzUp! In-Depth | Episode #14</title><description>Photo courtesy of Disney



Some big news this week, as Jason and Jeremy are back on the air. We talk about the coronavirus and how it's impacting the Asian Parks, as well as less life-threatening news about the new "Bambi" remake. Why is it happening? Why is any of this happening? Who knows, but we'll talk about it all - and more!</description><author>jason@earzup-podcast.com (EarzUp! )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6e7a135e4f0646a58209276461b7ec10</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6e7a135e4f0646a58209276461b7ec10/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 11:47:43 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Travel Like a Boss Podcast : Ep 241 – Nate Ginsburg ($650k, FBA, $1M Crypto Loss, Saigon, Chiang Mai)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Nate Ginsburg is an entrepreneur, traveler, and a yogi. He started yoga in 2014, and from then on, he shared this passion with everyone. Nate also developed his thinking and expanded his vision for building a business venture through hard work while traveling around the globe.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;During this episode, Nate shares amazing insights into starting a new business venture abroad, including its foundations, risks, and challenges. He also gives away tips on how to handle hardship in the business industry in order to succeed exceedingly. If you are either starting a business or planning to, this is the episode for you.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Links:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Nate Ginsburg' website: &lt;a href= "https://www.nateginsburg.com/"&gt;https://www.nateginsburg.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Nate's Business: &lt;a href= "https://sellerplex.com/"&gt;Sellerplex.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Nomad Summit Tbilisi: &lt;a href= "http://NomadSummit.com"&gt;NomadSummit.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Sponsor: &lt;a href="http://coworker.com/pass"&gt;Global Pass&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Time Stamps:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;00:28 – The Start of Johnny’s Podcast&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;08:45 – How Nate grew and progressed by traveling&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;10:40 – A nomad’s lifestyle in Vietnam&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;15:56 – Having an inclusive community in Saigon&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;19:31 – What it’s like to live in the city center&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;24:57 – Nate’s everyday routine&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;35:42 – Nate’s journey into becoming a digital nomad&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;36:00 – Battling hardships in his business and life&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;39:50 – “It made sense to me to keep trying and I know that’s really what I wanted” – Nate Ginsberg&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;48:55 – Trailblazing business that is income-generating&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;52:31 – “Be aware of the challenges and risks associated with what you’re doing” – Nate Ginsberg&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;6:43 – A big decision to sell his business&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;01:01:46 – Realizing the value of cash flow vs. paper wealth&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;01:07:36 – “It’s good to be exposed to some of the different perspective and opinions” –Nate Ginsberg&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Enjoyed this episode? Share it with friends!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>johnny@travellikeabosspodcast.com (Travel Like a Boss Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c0c34b81257d4a72b08e9ce73a9f5851</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c0c34b81257d4a72b08e9ce73a9f5851/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 09:06:10 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Biscuit CLT Podcast : Theatre Charlotte's "The Odd Couple"</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You may know that co-Biscuit baker Matt Olin has an extensive history in theatre... in production and direction. His most recent theatre performance was more than twenty years ago! So when he auditioned for, and was cast, in Theatre Charlotte's upcoming production of &lt;em&gt;The Odd Couple&lt;/em&gt;, it was an example of Matt stepping outside of his comfort zone.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;By performing on stage, Matt Olin truly is living out his Creative Mornings motto of everyone being creative, and everyone being welcome.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this episode of The Biscuit CLT Podcast, producer Andy Goh sits in on a rehearsal of the show, and chats with the actors, the director, and even a surprise guest. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For more information and tickets to Theatre Charlotte's production of &lt;em&gt;The Odd Couple&lt;/em&gt;, head to &lt;a href= "http://theatrecharlotte.org"&gt;theatrecharlotte.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tim@charlotteiscreative.com (The Biscuit CLT Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8c933c638fd245788cf454087f85e933</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8c933c638fd245788cf454087f85e933/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The History of Egypt Podcast : 120: Reverend Mother</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Akhenaten (Part 10): Queen Tiye's Retirement. For the first decade of Akhenaten's rule, his mother &lt;strong&gt;Tiye&lt;/strong&gt; was a background figure. But we have more evidence for her later years than you'd expect, including magnificent art and objects. Plus, the Queen herself returned to public life when she made a splendid visit to pharaoh's new city... Images and Bibliography at &lt;a href="www.egyptianhistorypodcast.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.egyptianhistorypodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;, Support the Podcast and get AD-FREE, early release episodes at &lt;a href="www.patreon.com/egyptpodcast" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.patreon.com/egyptpodcast&lt;/a&gt;, Music by Keith Zizza &lt;a href="www.keithzizza.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.keithzizza.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>egyptpodcast@gmail.com (The History of Egypt Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a430974438d94f6d9783a9fa08c04826</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a430974438d94f6d9783a9fa08c04826/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>My Solo Road : Losing a Parent &amp; Livin' The Dream</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Alexa has quickly become one of my best friends.. After losing her father and realizing that she &lt;em&gt;talks&lt;/em&gt; about living the dream, she decided to finally start living hers. We talk about moving through grief, white privilege, and what her dreams look like now.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>divineontheroad@gmail.com (My Solo Road)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">051b0774fe7b4c2cbd725b3343ef73bf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/051b0774fe7b4c2cbd725b3343ef73bf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 14:57:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Disneyland With Kids Podcast : Rise of the Resistance at Disneyland with Kids</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you Resistance Ready? If you are heading to Disneyland Resort and hoping to ride Rise of the Resistance, then this is the episode you have been looking for.&lt;/p&gt; In This Episode - Rise of the Resistance: &lt;p&gt;Becca from This Crazy Adventure Called Life chats with co-hosts Leslie from Trips with Tykes, Jessica from The Happiest Blog On Earth and Julie from Mom Rewritten about Rise of the Resistance at &lt;a href= "https://thiscrazyadventurecalledlife.com/disneyland-star-wars-galaxys-edge/"&gt; Star Wars: Galaxy's Edge&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leslie shares her experience attending the Media Preview for &lt;a href= "https://tripswithtykes.com/star-wars-rise-of-the-resistance/"&gt;Rise of the Resistance&lt;/a&gt;, plus tips on what parents may want to know before taking kids. She gives some spoiler free tips, but we do have a spoiler filled section from the 10:00 (10 minute) mark to 15:25 mark.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Jessica shares her kids thoughts on the ride, and then talks about &lt;a href= "https://thehappiestblogonearth.com/rise-of-the-resistance-strategies/"&gt; obtaining a Rise of the Resistance boarding pass&lt;/a&gt;, how to utilize DAS (&lt;a href= "https://thiscrazyadventurecalledlife.com/disneys-disability-access-service/"&gt;Disney Disability Access Service&lt;/a&gt;) and Rider Switch Pass, as well as some tips.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Julie is sharing her experience doing everything right but still not being able to obtain a boarding pass for the ride. She is giving info on how she prepared her child for this when planning to &lt;a href= "https://www.momrewritten.com/star-wars-galaxys-edge-star-wars-land-with-preschoolers-toddlers/"&gt; visit Star Wars: Galaxy's Edge with kids&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this episode we cover:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;What is Rise of the Resistance&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Spoiler free advice for the ride&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What parents should be aware of (major spoilers from 10:00 - 15:25)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Tips for obtaining a boarding pass&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Utilizing Disney's Disability Access Service with Rise of the Resistance&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Utilizing Rider Switch Pass with Rise of the Resistance&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What happens when you can't get a boarding pass for Rise of the Resistance?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Plan Your Disneyland Vacation:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you want to book a Disneyland vacation we suggest &lt;a title="Get Away Today" href= "https://www.getawaytoday.com/?referrerid=7526" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;booking through our partners at Get Away Today&lt;/a&gt;. If you are traveling in 2020, we suggest booking your vacations NOW to lock in the current ticket pricing. We expect ticket prices to go up in early 2020.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Want to connect with other Disneyland with Kids community members, receive and share tips, and more? &lt;a title="DwK Group" href= "https://facebook.com/groups/disneylandwithkids" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Join the Disneyland with Kids Group on Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect With The Hosts:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can connect with the hosts of Disneyland with Kids at the following locations:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leslie - &lt;a href= "https://tripswithtykes.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Trips with Tykes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Leslie on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Julie - &lt;a href= "https://momrewritten.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Mom Rewritten&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Julie on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/momrewritten"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/momrewritten" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/momrewritten" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Becca - &lt;a href= "https://thiscrazyadventurecalledlife.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;This Crazy Adventure Called Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Becca on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/crazyadventurecalledlife" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/thebeccarobins" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/thebeccarobins" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Jessica - &lt;a href= "https://thehappiestblogonearth.com"&gt;The Happiest Blog On Earth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Jessica on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>becca@disneylandwithkids.info (Disneyland With Kids Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d1b171087929423ea19868c16890040d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d1b171087929423ea19868c16890040d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 12:01:20 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ohio Folklore : Utopia</title><description>Utopia exists.  Not just as a concept, or some philosophical idea.  No, Utopia is a tiny speck of a town off the northern bank of the Ohio River.

Come learn the intriguing story of how this little village has drawn philosophers, dreamers, religious devotees and venture economists.  But was Utopia ever truly utopic?  You betcha.  

For a while anyway…

If you enjoy this episode, please rate, review and subscribe to Ohio Folklore on your chosen podcast platform.  You can also find Ohio Folklore at:

ohiofolklore.com
facebook.com/ohiofolklore

And as always, keep wondering…</description><author>melissa.davies77@outlook.com (Ohio Folklore)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">babd25ef581d4f528621c0bf6d25f1ab</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/babd25ef581d4f528621c0bf6d25f1ab/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 20:48:50 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>This Week in Travel : #260 - The Good Road TV Show on PBS</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This Week in Travel – Travel News Podcast. Regular hosts Gary Arndt, Chris Christensen, and Jen Leo are joined by this week’s guests:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Earl Bridges and Craig Martin, long time philanthropy veterans, globetrotters, and best friends,  are co-hosts of the new PBS Travel Series THE GOOD ROAD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/ThisWeekInTravel/~4/AqMK7b251VE" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>chris2x@amateurtraveler.com (This Week in Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1a4b3bbdee4d46b0b85496985e8f71c7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1a4b3bbdee4d46b0b85496985e8f71c7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 17:51:24 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Out Alive from BACKPACKER : Buried in a Rockslide</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Blue skies in Grand Teton National Park turn gray when a group of hikers are caught in a powerful rockslide. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ssebestyen@aimmedia.com (Out Alive from BACKPACKER)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">207f20e0acb54fb4b3a9358dec4b4724</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/207f20e0acb54fb4b3a9358dec4b4724/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dish Food Travel Show : 49 Pavlova (Australia vs New Zealand)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In This Episode:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* History Of The Pavlova - One of Australia &amp; New Zealand’s favourite desserts* We try to settle the 100 year old debate of who invented it, AUS or NZ?* Plus, was the first Pavlova made with frog’s legs, rather than fruit?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read more stories about food and culinary travel on our blog: &lt;a href='https://foodfuntravel.com'&gt;https://foodfuntravel.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>megsy@foodfuntravel.com (The Dish Food Travel Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">07a722da29f34ac2b0c0d323496d11b1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/07a722da29f34ac2b0c0d323496d11b1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 01:43:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Disney Vacation Club Show : #049 - Disney Vacation Club Annual Dues</title><description>01/27/20 - In this episode, the panel discusses annual dues for Disney Vacation Club, which is something every owner should consider when choosing how many points to purchase.</description><author>craig@disneyinfo.com (The Disney Vacation Club Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b0da73428803463aa51b952e7159ca4d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b0da73428803463aa51b952e7159ca4d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Retro Disney World Podcast : Ep 55 - Backlot Studio Tram Tour</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Episode 55 of the RetroWDW Podcast: "Backstage Tour - MGM" - We appreciate your support and hope you have been enjoying each and every episode. Be sure to check out some of our previous shows!&lt;/p&gt;
Comments &amp; Corrections
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take a listen to our latest mini-episode, &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/podcast/podcast-episode-54-5-bringing-the-world-closer-to-you/'&gt;Bringing The World Closer To You&lt;/a&gt; - this was a quick one but ended up being very good. Enjoy!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;Listener Mail
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/gallery/lake-buena-vista/Frap07.png'&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The mailbag is full and we love that! Every month, you can possibly get on the show, so be sure to write to us at &lt;a href='mailto:podcast@retrowdw.com'&gt;podcast@retrowdw.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rob wrote in, asking about the VIP Lounges at EPCOT. Rob is mainly interested in the Kodak lounge at Journey into Imagination. Brian gives us his take on it. As I was putting this write-up together, I realized Rob is the owner of the site we reference. Check out his collection of VIP lounge pictures and information: &lt;a href='https://www.robyeodesign.com/blog/2016/3/21/future-worlds-s'&gt;Future World's Hidden VIP Lounges&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next letter we discuss purchasing fog machines at Innoventions. Was this actually a thing? We discuss...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dane writes in, regarding ephemera. Do we have any from Toys Fantastique? Todd gets us up to speed on how our photo archive is growing and improving at this very moment. What any RetroWDW fan can do, is use the search and find so many more images! This is great, use this link and give it a try: &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/photo-archive-search/'&gt;Photo Search&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;[listenerfeedback]&lt;/p&gt;
Audio Rewind
&lt;p&gt;Our audio rewind this month is the opening of Holiday Illuminations - Thank you for all the guesses and emails, and we didn't get many!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a winner! Congratulations Beth Goldman!  - you won a set of RetroMagic ornaments!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you think you know the answer to this month's audio rewind, email us! &lt;a href='mailto:contest@retrowdw.com'&gt;contest@retrowdw.com&lt;/a&gt; - This month, the winner will be getting a copy of the Marty Sklar book, Dream it, Do it - All entries due 2/17/2020 and a random winner will be selected.&lt;/p&gt;
Main Topic
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main topic this month is one of the recently closed classics, The Disney-MGM Studios Backlot Tour. There have been so many changes and updates over the years, but we are going to focus on the original, for the most part. How is our guide on this episode, walking us through the entire tram portion of the tour. We take it right back to 1989, going through how the Disney-MGM Studios actually worked. The concept of going past the theme park and then entering the studio - this is how the tour basically began. The walking tour was part of this, but we are not going to discuss this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The backlot tour had so many different aspects including residential street, the boneyard, the various production trailers, and so many other little nuggets. The tour seemed to change often, as far as props and items but the tour wasn't complete with a look at the Streets of America, or the New York street set. You would know this as the set for "The Lottery", which seems to be the only movie filmed here that we ever hear about. To accompany this episode, we have a great video on our YouTube channel - &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_DX0WnRHs8&amp;feature=youtu.be'&gt;click here to watch&lt;/a&gt; after the episode!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/backstage.gif'&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Delta_Dreamflight_L1011_Filming_Set_02.jpg'&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Delta_Dreamflight_L1011_Filming_Set_03.jpg'&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Delta_Dreamflight_L1011_Filming_Set_04.jpg'&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
2020: The Year of Film
&lt;p&gt;To make sure you are the first to know when items are released, &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/retrodisneyworld'&gt;subscribe to us on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;. Be sure to click the notification bell too, that way you are alerted when we post.  Finally, be sure to &lt;a href='https://vimeo.com/retrowdw'&gt;check out Vimeo&lt;/a&gt; if that is your thing, as we will post there as well. This past month we have posted the &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_DX0WnRHs8&amp;feature=youtu.be'&gt;Backlot Tour video&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zqDQLj4rtxM&amp;feature=youtu.be'&gt;a ride around the monorail in 1991&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XU2UJLEBczk&amp;feature=youtu.be'&gt;1994 runDisney Marathon&lt;/a&gt;. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
Next Month
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Join us next time for Episode 56, which we have not fully planned out, but you won't want to miss it  Thanks for joining us! &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>podcast@retrowdw.com (Retro Disney World Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e935163ea548489f94e21df5226cc107</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e935163ea548489f94e21df5226cc107/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 19:59:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Coastin' the Country : Ep. 15: Six Flags Great America Tsunami Surge update, No Coaster Con recap</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Marcus recaps his trip to the American Coaster Enthusiasts No Coaster Con and talks with Six Flags Great America after their presentation there. They give us an update on the construction of their new water coaster Tsunami Surge. We also break down the latest news in the theme park world, including Super Nintendo World coming to Universal Orlando, and the latest rumors about the big 2021 attraction coming to Busch Gardens Williamsburg. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mleshock@wgntv.com (Coastin' the Country)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">759c262424704b788f518e05e28e3b84</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/759c262424704b788f518e05e28e3b84/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The City : The Confrontation | S2 E7</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this Season 2 bonus episode,&amp;nbsp;accusations of sexual assault at the Spice House strip club come to light. Two women who work there head to the club to confront their bosses, their phones secretly set to record.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@thecitypodcast.com (The City)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">edc9803293644e4fa7daa1bcf782e5df</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/edc9803293644e4fa7daa1bcf782e5df/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MiceCast : Acquisition Analysis</title><description>Your hosts discuss the theory that the Lucasfilm acquisition was a failure compared to Pixar and Marvel. We also spend some time talking about the virtual queue for Rise of the Resistance. 2 hours 16 minutes.&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/Micecast/~4/00_v98Zkb2U" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>micecast@gmail.com (MiceCast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">38164a6a54234260b74be0aa2831c8e2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/38164a6a54234260b74be0aa2831c8e2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>In Limbo : "Be Yourself"- Limitations of simplicity and common sense</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode we will discuss the depths and obstacles of advice we've heard time and time again to "be ourselves."&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts14+d507e9c@anchor.fm (In Limbo)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e80c5ae801f94dd1969720f049a238cc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e80c5ae801f94dd1969720f049a238cc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 11:59:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Inside Universal Podcast : The Inside Universal Podcast: New Decade, Same Non-Sense (and Super Nintendo World, too)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The return of Hatetofly! Andy, Brian, and Drew discuss the recent &lt;a href= "http://www.insideuniversal.net/2020/01/universal-orlandos-mardi-gras-2020-concert-line-up-and-details-announced/"&gt; Mardi Gras&lt;/a&gt; announcement, as well as the latest information that was released regarding &lt;a href= "http://www.insideuniversal.net/2020/01/universal-studios-japan-reveals-new-details-on-super-nintendo-world-opening-this-summer/"&gt; Super Nintendo World&lt;/a&gt; at Universal Studios Japan, including the interactive Power Up Bands. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jon@insideuniversal.net (The Inside Universal Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9bf6152d06b04e88b78500c62165b169</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9bf6152d06b04e88b78500c62165b169/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:28:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hashtag Colorado Life : Building Your Colorado Bucket List in 2020</title><description>BONUS #2: What’s on your Colorado bucket list? In this bonus episode Ryan and Carrie talk about the must-see and must-do things to add to your Colorado bucket list. With the mountains in your backyard, an ever-growing food scene, and endless indoor and outdoor activities where do you start? There are so many things to do and cities to explore!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ryan and Carrie share the activities and adventures that are on their Colorado bucket list. They also discuss the places and sights they have already visited. Many of the ideas include iconic Colorado destinations and local favorites, as well as lesser-known but still epic experiences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are looking for the best things to do in Colorado without busting your budget, that’s what this episode is all about. Find out the top 16 things Ryan and Carrie recommend you add to your bucket list. Plus, these are great suggestions for discovering within your first year of living in the square state.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more information and resources about exploring Colorado, visit our website at &lt;a href="http://hashtagcoloradolife.com/"&gt;HashtagColoradoLife.com&lt;/a&gt; or&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/hashtagcoloradolife/"&gt; @HashtagColoradoLife&lt;/a&gt; on Instagram.</description><author>team@hashtagcoloradolife.com (Hashtag Colorado Life)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4580a7f45e174506aa649f38489f2dba</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4580a7f45e174506aa649f38489f2dba/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Wise About Texas : Ep. 78:  The Lady in Blue</title><description>&lt;p&gt; In 1629 a group of Jumano Indians suddenly appeared at a New Mexico mission, eager to learn more about Christianity.  The excited and grateful Franciscan priests wondered what motivated this sudden interest.  The tale the Indians told seemed unbelievable.  A &amp;#8220;lady in blue&amp;#8221; had appeared to them instructing them to seek out the priests and teaching the Indians the sign of the cross.  That sounded incredible enough but what really stunned the priests was that they had just received a letter from Spain relating the story of a nun telling the exact same tale&amp;#8230;half a world away.  Is the Lady in Blue a myth&amp;#8230;or a miracle?  You decide in the latest episode of Wise About Texas.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/WiseAboutTexas/~4/lmVlyLFkRdw" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>Host@wiseabouttexas.com (Wise About Texas)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9f63998fcaeb4eed89b309da28ba42b9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9f63998fcaeb4eed89b309da28ba42b9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 09:36:28 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>