<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Travel feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My travel episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My Travel feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 01:15:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>Parklandia : Bonus Episode! Camping In Yellowstone With Tim Burton</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this past week's episode, we covered Matt's family trip to Yellowstone. Brad visited Yellowstone while on the "maple trail," selling barrel-aged maple syrup for &lt;a href="https://www.burtonsmaplewoodfarm.com/"&gt;Burton's Maplewood Farm&lt;/a&gt; across the country. In this special bonus episode, we sit down with Tim Burton (not the director, the producer...of maple syrup!) in-studio to talk about the journey on the maple trail, camping in the world's first national park inside of a box truck, and the very special people we were traveling with. Tim is a very special person in our lives, as you'll hear, and we're so happy to introduce him to you!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Parklandia on Instagram at &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/parklandiapod/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;@parklandiapod&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, join the Parklandia Rangers &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/ParklandiaRangers/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and Like our &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/parklandiapod/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Parklandia)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">819e502db6964c2a9d536d07d0664454</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/819e502db6964c2a9d536d07d0664454/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Well-Traveled with AAA : The Wonders of Phoenix</title><description>&lt;p&gt;"&lt;em&gt;Well-Traveled&lt;/em&gt;" Correspondent, Samantha Brown, host of the Emmy-winning PBS program, “&lt;em&gt;Places to Love&lt;/em&gt;,” discovers more than just sunshine and dessert in Arizona’s capital city. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sonixcursions@gmail.com (Well-Traveled with AAA)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">65d3562728c84fcebd4636e3b9b8bccd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/65d3562728c84fcebd4636e3b9b8bccd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Monocle 24: The Menu : The perfect match</title><description>How a new London initiative aims to match vacant restaurant spaces with young culinary talent, a J-pop star’s campaign to boost the popularity of sake in Japan, plus Maggie Beer’s campaign for better food in Australia.</description><author>info@monocle.com (Monocle 24: The Menu)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4d0940b2e86447b098058518e2c332b9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4d0940b2e86447b098058518e2c332b9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Become Nomad - Digital Nomad Lifestyle and Long Term Travel : BN069:  Escapes and attachments of the nomadic lifestyle</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, we will go over some of the recent repeating questions by readers of the blog. We will start by analyzing the concept of a digital lifestyle as a form of escape. We will also dive deep into the fascinating topic of attachments, and how to disconnect or connect to them.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>eli@becomenomad.com (Become Nomad - Digital Nomad Lifestyle and Long Term Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">29eb2f1f1b044ed2a88583e1c0283cad</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/29eb2f1f1b044ed2a88583e1c0283cad/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 10:56:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Expat Files: Living in Latin America : EXPAT FILES - 01.31.20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Descriptions- EXPAT FILES SHOW #925 FRI., JAN 31 (01-31-2020):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NOW AN IMPORTANT ANNOUNCEMENT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My new website &lt;a href='http://www.expatplanb.com/'&gt;www.ExpatPlanB.com&lt;/a&gt; is under construction. The old one &lt;a href='http://www.theexpatfiles.com/'&gt;www.theexpatfiles.com&lt;/a&gt; has been retired so from now on please use &lt;a href='http://www.expatplanb.com/'&gt;www.ExpatPlanB.com&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#1- What to consider before installing solar power in your Latin American home or getaway:&lt;/p&gt;
#2- Will you be shipping things from the states to your Latin Home or ordering from eBay, Amazon or other online store?
The word “Aduana” is Spanish for what Latinos call the import and customs departments. They are staffed by the usual suspects- fat assed government parasitic slugs who are out to gouge you and waste your time. Therefore it’s obvious that you want minimum dealings with them if at all possible. That said, long time gringos and expats know some straightforward (and backhanded) ways to minimize or avoid customs and import duties…    
&lt;p&gt; #3- Don’t fall into these common tricks and traps when using Miami freight forwarding services or it may cost you dearly:&lt;/p&gt;
 #4- Be sure to pick up my "LATIN AMERICAN HEALTHCARE REPORT":
It's the new edition for 2020 (and beyond) including the latest "Stem Cell" info and data and my top picks for the best treatment centers for expats and gringos. Just go to &lt;a href='http://www.expatplanb.com/'&gt;www.ExpatPlanB.com&lt;/a&gt; and click on the "Latin American Healthcare Report”.</description><author>karalee@garynull.com (The Expat Files: Living in Latin America)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5294dd8203574eaa86465ee58be78941</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5294dd8203574eaa86465ee58be78941/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 10:49:46 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The olive magazine podcast : ep 185 - JOSE PIZARRO celebrates the food and drink of Andalucia</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week digital editor Alex chats to one of the UK’s most-loved Spanish chefs Jose Pizarro about a part of Spain that’s very close to his heart, Andalucia. They discuss regional dishes, quirky cultural dining habits and Jose’s favourite locals spots to visit in Seville and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts@immediate.co.uk (The olive magazine podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2aa6418a84534f3b8f147680bb20a15e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2aa6418a84534f3b8f147680bb20a15e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 04:21:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Overland Journal Podcast : Are Electric Vehicles the Future of Overlanding?</title><description>The full show notes are available at: &lt;a href="https://overlandjournal.com/electric-overland-vehicles/"&gt;https://overlandjournal.com/podcast/electric-overland-vehicles/&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>scott@overlandinternational.com (The Overland Journal Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">673c316db4dc42cdbf9ab12c1262f0e9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/673c316db4dc42cdbf9ab12c1262f0e9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Connecting with Walt - A look into the history of the man behind Mickey Mouse, Disneyland and Walt Disney World : #132 - Universe of Energy Pt. 2</title><description>01/31/20 - In this episode, Michael and Craig continue their look at Universe of Energy by hopping on the original version of the attraction along with the following versions before closing its doors completely in 2017.</description><author>craig@wdwinfo.com (Connecting with Walt - A look into the history of the man behind Mickey Mouse, Disneyland and Walt Disney World)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4b46149e41784bedb0406b95099b6647</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4b46149e41784bedb0406b95099b6647/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Normal to Nomad : 12 | Lindsey - Solo Female Nomad &amp; Alaska Native</title><description>&lt;p class=""&gt;Show Notes&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>barronlink@gmail.com (Normal to Nomad)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f26b898c376a467a9e56c7c84429fecd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f26b898c376a467a9e56c7c84429fecd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 14:07:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>EarzUp!  : EarzUp! In-Depth | Episode #14</title><description>Photo courtesy of Disney



Some big news this week, as Jason and Jeremy are back on the air. We talk about the coronavirus and how it's impacting the Asian Parks, as well as less life-threatening news about the new "Bambi" remake. Why is it happening? Why is any of this happening? Who knows, but we'll talk about it all - and more!</description><author>jason@earzup-podcast.com (EarzUp! )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6e7a135e4f0646a58209276461b7ec10</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6e7a135e4f0646a58209276461b7ec10/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 11:47:43 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Travel Like a Boss Podcast : Ep 241 – Nate Ginsberg ($650k, FBA, $1M Crypto Loss, Saigon, Chiang Mai)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Nate Ginsberg is an entrepreneur, traveler, and a yogi. He started yoga in 2014, and from then on, he shared this passion with everyone. Nate also developed his thinking and expanded his vision for building a business venture through hard work while traveling around the globe.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;During this episode, Nate shares amazing insights into starting a new business venture abroad, including its foundations, risks, and challenges. He also gives away tips on how to handle hardship in the business industry in order to succeed exceedingly. If you are either starting a business or planning to, this is the episode for you.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Links:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Nate Ginsberg' website: &lt;a href= "https://www.nateginsburg.com/"&gt;NateGinsberg.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Nate's Business: &lt;a href= "https://sellerplex.com/"&gt;Sellerplex.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Nomad Summit Tbilisi: &lt;a href= "http://NomadSummit.com"&gt;NomadSummit.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Sponsor: &lt;a href="http://coworker.com/pass"&gt;Global Pass&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Time Stamps:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;00:28 – The Start of Johnny’s Podcast&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;08:45 – How Nate grew and progressed by traveling&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;10:40 – A nomad’s lifestyle in Vietnam&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;15:56 – Having an inclusive community in Saigon&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;19:31 – What it’s like to live in the city center&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;24:57 – Nate’s everyday routine&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;35:42 –Nate’s journey into becoming a digital nomad&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;36:00 – Battling hardships in his business and life&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;39:50 – “It made sense to me to keep trying and I know that’s really what I wanted” – Nate Ginsberg&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;48:55 – Trailblazing business that is income-generating&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;52:31 – “Be aware of the challenges and risks associated with what you’re doing” – Nate Ginsberg&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;6:43 – A big decision to sell his business&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;01:01:46 – Realizing the value of cash flow vs. paper wealth&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;01:07:36 – “It’s good to be exposed to some of the different perspective and opinions” –Nate Ginsberg&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Enjoyed this episode? Share it with friends!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>johnny@travellikeabosspodcast.com (Travel Like a Boss Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c0c34b81257d4a72b08e9ce73a9f5851</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c0c34b81257d4a72b08e9ce73a9f5851/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 09:06:10 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Biscuit CLT Podcast : Theatre Charlotte's "The Odd Couple"</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You may know that co-Biscuit baker Matt Olin has an extensive history in theatre... in production and direction. His most recent theatre performance was more than twenty years ago! So when he auditioned for, and was cast, in Theatre Charlotte's upcoming production of &lt;em&gt;The Odd Couple&lt;/em&gt;, it was an example of Matt stepping outside of his comfort zone.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;By performing on stage, Matt Olin truly is living out his Creative Mornings motto of everyone being creative, and everyone being welcome.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this episode of The Biscuit CLT Podcast, producer Andy Goh sits in on a rehearsal of the show, and chats with the actors, the director, and even a surprise guest. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For more information and tickets to Theatre Charlotte's production of &lt;em&gt;The Odd Couple&lt;/em&gt;, head to &lt;a href= "http://theatrecharlotte.org"&gt;theatrecharlotte.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tim@charlotteiscreative.com (The Biscuit CLT Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8c933c638fd245788cf454087f85e933</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8c933c638fd245788cf454087f85e933/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Tropical MBA Podcast - Entrepreneurship, Travel, and Lifestyle : TMBA530: Don't Be a Victim of Your Own Success</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Entrepreneurship is something of a gamble, and perhaps very few people understand that better than today&amp;#39;s guest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mike Jackness is a widely respected figure among the eCommerce community and is the host of a brilliant podcast called ECommCrew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mike has owned and exited several successful businesses, the most popular of which being ColorIt, which manufactured and sold coloring books aimed at adults.&lt;br&gt;
On today&amp;#39;s podcast, Mike joins us to talk about the highs and lows of his entrepreneurial career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#39;ll hear how an obsession with poker turned into Mike&amp;#39;s first major foray into entrepreneurship, how he founded and eventually sold ColorIt, and some of the biggest pitfalls that entrepreneurs face in the eCommerce space today.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Dan@TropicalMBA.com (The Tropical MBA Podcast - Entrepreneurship, Travel, and Lifestyle)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">070ab2793414434d93c46fb0b0668cf7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/070ab2793414434d93c46fb0b0668cf7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WDWNT ParksCenter : ParksCenter - Festival of the Arts 2020! - Ep. 86</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This is ParksCenter. We cover the top news stories from this week in Disney Parks news in 30 minutes. This week, we’ll be talking about: FastPass+ tiers change over at Hollywood Studios, and now includes Smuggler’s Run Coronavirus closes down Shanghai and Hong Kong Disneyland Prices for character dining increase And more! Want to watch? […]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://wdwnt.com/2020/01/watch-parkscenter-87/"&gt;ParksCenter – Hollywood Studios Tier Changes – Ep. 87&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://wdwnt.com"&gt;WDW News Today&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>developer@wdwnt.com (WDWNT ParksCenter)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2d80b181f13e4ae0b5684cc6b4b3f844</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2d80b181f13e4ae0b5684cc6b4b3f844/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 04:00:36 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Kentuckiana Sounds : A Man-Made Swamp in Okolona</title><description>The commercial developments around Outer Loop may not seem much like nature sanctuaries, but Kentuckiana Sounds curator Aaron Rosenblum found one hidden water management feature full of busy nocturnal creatures. This recording was made in 2018 as part of the COLLIDER Artist in Residence program at the South Central Regional Library. To hear the full recording, explore the sound map, or submit a sound visit www.wfpl.org/sounds or www.kentuckianasounds.org.</description><author>support@louisvillepublicmedia.org (Kentuckiana Sounds)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c2c890682d5b41d9b74d1dfd808b4439</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c2c890682d5b41d9b74d1dfd808b4439/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>New Books in African Studies : K. Linder et al., "Going Alt-Ac: A Guide to Alternative Academic Careers" (Stylus Publishing, 2020)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re a grad student facing the ugly reality of finding a tenure-track job, you could easily be forgiven for thinking about a career change. However, if you’ve spent the last several years working on a PhD, or if you’re a faculty member whose career has basically consisted of higher ed, switching isn’t so easy. PhD holders are mostly trained to work as professors, and making easy connections to other careers is no mean feat. Because the people you know were generally trained to do the same sorts of things, an easy source of advice might not be there for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, for anybody who wishes there was a guidebook that would just break all of this down, that book has now been written. &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/1620368315/?tag=newbooinhis-20"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Going Alt-Ac: A Guide to Alternative Academic Careers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (Stylus Publishing, 2020) by &lt;a href="https://styluspub.presswarehouse.com/browse/author/2a07e59f-b1c2-4cc9-95e5-57f26cb59fc5/Kathryn-E-Linder?page=1"&gt;Kathryn E. Linder&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://styluspub.presswarehouse.com/browse/author/b942fd05-5d35-4095-8f84-df50f428d8f3/Kevin-Kelly?page=1"&gt;Kevin Kelly&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://styluspub.presswarehouse.com/browse/author/a0500dde-c9b8-476b-b278-24a474aa5399/Thomas-J-Tobin?page=1"&gt;Thomas J. Tobin&lt;/a&gt; offers practical advice and step-by-step instructions on how to decide if you want to leave behind academia and how to start searching for a new career. If a lot of career advice is too vague or too ambiguous, this book corrects that by outlining not just how to figure out what you might want to do, but critically, how you might go about accomplishing that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Zeb Larson is a recent graduate of The Ohio State University with a PhD in History. His research deals with the anti-apartheid movement in the United States. To suggest a recent title or to contact him, please send an e-mail to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:zeb.larson@gmail.com"&gt;&lt;em&gt;zeb.larson@gmail.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marshallpoe@gmail.com (New Books in African Studies)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fe2ecf0283f04a28ae918b5ce7dacf74</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fe2ecf0283f04a28ae918b5ce7dacf74/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The History of Egypt Podcast : 120: Reverend Mother</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Akhenaten (Part 10): Queen Tiye's Retirement. For the first decade of Akhenaten's rule, his mother &lt;strong&gt;Tiye&lt;/strong&gt; was a background figure. But we have more evidence for her later years than you'd expect, including magnificent art and objects. Plus, the Queen herself returned to public life when she made a splendid visit to pharaoh's new city... Images and Bibliography at &lt;a href="www.egyptianhistorypodcast.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.egyptianhistorypodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;, Support the Podcast and get AD-FREE, early release episodes at &lt;a href="www.patreon.com/egyptpodcast" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.patreon.com/egyptpodcast&lt;/a&gt;, Music by Keith Zizza &lt;a href="www.keithzizza.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.keithzizza.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>egyptpodcast@gmail.com (The History of Egypt Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a430974438d94f6d9783a9fa08c04826</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a430974438d94f6d9783a9fa08c04826/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Gal Pal Show: Solo female travel, backpacking, bucket list inspiration, planning a trip, female travel advice and tips, and off the beaten track ideas. : 91: Female travel motivation</title><description>&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt; It's time for a motivational boost for your travel goals this year. In this episode I'm going through 3 ways that you can do, to give yourself a much needed boost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;I'm also giving you an update on my travel plans for this year...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt; Subscribe to the show to keep getting episodes to your phone&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://mailchi.mp/ae404f33adb5/travel-planning-worksheet'&gt;Get your FREE Travel planning worksheet &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://mailchi.mp/ae404f33adb5/travel-planning-worksheet'&gt;and start planning your trip here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://galpalacademy.thinkific.com/courses/travel-planning-bootcamp-1'&gt;Want to go travelling?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://galpalacademy.thinkific.com/courses/travel-planning-bootcamp-1'&gt;Join Gal Pal Travel Planning Bootcamp here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jo@galpalacademy.com (Gal Pal Show: Solo female travel, backpacking, bucket list inspiration, planning a trip, female travel advice and tips, and off the beaten track ideas.)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fab14404056d4948a925b65e82ae85ba</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fab14404056d4948a925b65e82ae85ba/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Offbeat Life - become location independent : Extended: How to prepare for online self-publication.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; What you'll find: &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this episode, Kay shares how to become a self-published author and give practical tips on how to begin!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "http://%20https//www.theoffbeatlife.com/episodes/self-published-author/"&gt; Get the Extended Interview with Kay where she shares how she is able to create extra income as a self-published author&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@theoffbeatlife.com (The Offbeat Life - become location independent)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">65715a7207d943e6958db502694d944e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/65715a7207d943e6958db502694d944e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Duolingo Spanish Podcast : El embajador del Mofongo (The Mofongo Ambassador)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A young Puerto Rican man takes a dish from his homeland and creates a global food sensation. But when Hurricane Maria hits, he finds a new way of using food to help the island he loves.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A transcript of this episode is available at https://podcast.duolingo.com.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@duolingo.com (Duolingo Spanish Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8de0bb1d9bd84e0ab0e5e5c631517de3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8de0bb1d9bd84e0ab0e5e5c631517de3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 19:00:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Familie auf Weltreise -Der Podcast : 73 | Was das Imponiergehabe mit unserem Sportleben zu tun hat</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Schon beim ersten Kennenlernen wurde schnell klar, dass der Sport eine wichtige Rolle in unserem Leben einnehmen wird. Was als Imponiergehabe begann hat in Wahrheit früh den Grundstein gelegt für unseren Lebensstil und unsere heutige Einkommensquelle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wie das alles begann und was uns unsere Eltern in die Wiege gelegt haben, berichten wir ausführlich in dieser spätabends aufgezeichneten Podcast Episode. Viel Spaß beim Reinhören. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://katrin-fit.net/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sport mit Katrin - Katrin-Fit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/familieaufweltreise"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Der geschlossenen Gruppe "Familie auf Weltreise" beitreten&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.familieaufweltreise.de/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unser neuer Blog&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/familieaufweltreise"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instagram&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://youtube.com/c/familieaufweltreisede"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YouTube&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2WLSqdF"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on Family&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unsere Ressourcen findest Du auf unserer Webseite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.familieaufweltreise.de/ressourcen"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;www.Familieaufweltreise.de/ressourcen&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lust auf ein Reiseguthaben?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;25 € AirBnB Gutschein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2BtQrCo"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://bit.ly/2BtQrCo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;15 € Booking.com Gutschein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://booki.ng/2A67Xwu"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://booki.ng/2A67Xwu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>kontakt@familieaufweltreise.de (Familie auf Weltreise -Der Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">db29381b6c504da38fad771cef5a76f8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/db29381b6c504da38fad771cef5a76f8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>My Solo Road : Losing a Parent &amp; Livin' The Dream</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Alexa has quickly become one of my best friends.. After losing her father and realizing that she &lt;em&gt;talks&lt;/em&gt; about living the dream, she decided to finally start living hers. We talk about moving through grief, white privilege, and what her dreams look like now.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>divineontheroad@gmail.com (My Solo Road)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">051b0774fe7b4c2cbd725b3343ef73bf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/051b0774fe7b4c2cbd725b3343ef73bf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 14:57:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Disneyland With Kids Podcast : Rise of the Resistance at Disneyland with Kids</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you Resistance Ready? If you are heading to Disneyland Resort and hoping to ride Rise of the Resistance, then this is the episode you have been looking for.&lt;/p&gt; In This Episode - Rise of the Resistance: &lt;p&gt;Becca from This Crazy Adventure Called Life chats with co-hosts Leslie from Trips with Tykes, Jessica from The Happiest Blog On Earth and Julie from Mom Rewritten about Rise of the Resistance at &lt;a href= "https://thiscrazyadventurecalledlife.com/disneyland-star-wars-galaxys-edge/"&gt; Star Wars: Galaxy's Edge&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leslie shares her experience attending the Media Preview for &lt;a href= "https://tripswithtykes.com/star-wars-rise-of-the-resistance/"&gt;Rise of the Resistance&lt;/a&gt;, plus tips on what parents may want to know before taking kids. She gives some spoiler free tips, but we do have a spoiler filled section from the 10:00 (10 minute) mark to 15:25 mark.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Jessica shares her kids thoughts on the ride, and then talks about &lt;a href= "https://thehappiestblogonearth.com/rise-of-the-resistance-strategies/"&gt; obtaining a Rise of the Resistance boarding pass&lt;/a&gt;, how to utilize DAS (&lt;a href= "https://thiscrazyadventurecalledlife.com/disneys-disability-access-service/"&gt;Disney Disability Access Service&lt;/a&gt;) and Rider Switch Pass, as well as some tips.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Julie is sharing her experience doing everything right but still not being able to obtain a boarding pass for the ride. She is giving info on how she prepared her child for this when planning to &lt;a href= "https://www.momrewritten.com/star-wars-galaxys-edge-star-wars-land-with-preschoolers-toddlers/"&gt; visit Star Wars: Galaxy's Edge with kids&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this episode we cover:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;What is Rise of the Resistance&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Spoiler free advice for the ride&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What parents should be aware of (major spoilers from 10:00 - 15:25)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Tips for obtaining a boarding pass&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Utilizing Disney's Disability Access Service with Rise of the Resistance&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Utilizing Rider Switch Pass with Rise of the Resistance&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What happens when you can't get a boarding pass for Rise of the Resistance?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Plan Your Disneyland Vacation:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you want to book a Disneyland vacation we suggest &lt;a title="Get Away Today" href= "https://www.getawaytoday.com/?referrerid=7526" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;booking through our partners at Get Away Today&lt;/a&gt;. If you are traveling in 2020, we suggest booking your vacations NOW to lock in the current ticket pricing. We expect ticket prices to go up in early 2020.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Want to connect with other Disneyland with Kids community members, receive and share tips, and more? &lt;a title="DwK Group" href= "https://facebook.com/groups/disneylandwithkids" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Join the Disneyland with Kids Group on Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect With The Hosts:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can connect with the hosts of Disneyland with Kids at the following locations:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leslie - &lt;a href= "https://tripswithtykes.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Trips with Tykes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Leslie on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Julie - &lt;a href= "https://momrewritten.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Mom Rewritten&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Julie on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/momrewritten"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/momrewritten" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/momrewritten" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Becca - &lt;a href= "https://thiscrazyadventurecalledlife.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;This Crazy Adventure Called Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Becca on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/crazyadventurecalledlife" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/thebeccarobins" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/thebeccarobins" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Jessica - &lt;a href= "https://thehappiestblogonearth.com"&gt;The Happiest Blog On Earth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Jessica on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>becca@disneylandwithkids.info (Disneyland With Kids Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d1b171087929423ea19868c16890040d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d1b171087929423ea19868c16890040d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 12:01:20 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Oh Boy, The Podcast : Episode 007 - Most Romantic Restaurants at Disney World for Valentines Day</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In the words of Tom Haverford, how well do you know ya boo? Well enough to know where to eat for Valentines Day on a date at Disney World? Well, if not, we got you covered. This week we dive in to our 9 most romantic restaurants at Disney. We cover 3 fun "Disney" restaurants in parks, our 3 picks for fancy restaurants, and 3 bars for a nice drink date!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="http://www.thelostbros.com"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (http://www.thelostbros.com)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@lostbrostradingco.com (Oh Boy, The Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0d8a430398374e12842bca454fe3c4e3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0d8a430398374e12842bca454fe3c4e3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>CruiseTipsTV Unplugged - Cruise Tips and More : Facebook Cruise Questions Answered</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, we answer cruise questions from our Facebook Community. From cruise installment payments plans, to ship tours and solo cruising tips. We'll cover a variety of popular cruise questions.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As always, you can email us your questions at  sheri@cruisetipstv.com. We'd also LOVE if you'd leave a review where you listen to this podcast, and screen shot the show and share it on Instagram using the hashtag #cttvunplugged.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Download our shore day bag checklist, and more cruise packing and planning checklists &amp; videos by joining the CruiseTipsTV Academy. We have a special discount code for our podcast listeners. To redeem the $5.00 discount on our master class enter code UNPLUGGED at &lt;a href= "http://academy.cruisetipstv.com"&gt;http://academy.cruisetipstv.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@cruisetipstv.com (CruiseTipsTV Unplugged - Cruise Tips and More)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">eecd124cafe04e37bd2c68b9d7d9b8d8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/eecd124cafe04e37bd2c68b9d7d9b8d8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Disney Cruise Line Show : #003 - How to Save Money on Your Disney Cruise Line Vacation</title><description>01/29/20 - In this episode, the panel discusses how you can save money on your Disney Cruise Line vacation from booking your vacation as early as possible to paying with Disney Gift Cards purchased from Target with their 5% discount when using a RedCard!</description><author>craig@disneyinfo.com (The Disney Cruise Line Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0f878d14bf974547a6cf263466030b63</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0f878d14bf974547a6cf263466030b63/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ohio Folklore : Utopia</title><description>Utopia exists.  Not just as a concept, or some philosophical idea.  No, Utopia is a tiny speck of a town off the northern bank of the Ohio River.

Come learn the intriguing story of how this little village has drawn philosophers, dreamers, religious devotees and venture economists.  But was Utopia ever truly utopic?  You betcha.  

For a while anyway…

If you enjoy this episode, please rate, review and subscribe to Ohio Folklore on your chosen podcast platform.  You can also find Ohio Folklore at:

ohiofolklore.com
facebook.com/ohiofolklore

And as always, keep wondering…</description><author>melissa.davies77@outlook.com (Ohio Folklore)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">babd25ef581d4f528621c0bf6d25f1ab</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/babd25ef581d4f528621c0bf6d25f1ab/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 20:48:50 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>This Week in Travel : #260 - The Good Road TV Show on PBS</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This Week in Travel – Travel News Podcast. Regular hosts Gary Arndt, Chris Christensen, and Jen Leo are joined by this week’s guests:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Earl Bridges and Craig Martin, long time philanthropy veterans, globetrotters, and best friends,  are co-hosts of the new PBS Travel Series THE GOOD ROAD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/ThisWeekInTravel/~4/AqMK7b251VE" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>chris2x@amateurtraveler.com (This Week in Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1a4b3bbdee4d46b0b85496985e8f71c7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1a4b3bbdee4d46b0b85496985e8f71c7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 17:51:24 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>DCL Podcast : 129 Sailing the Transatlantic East and Westbound</title><description>&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img src="http://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-685" srcset="http://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image1.png 600w, http://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/image1-300x168.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Listener Lauren joins us to discuss sailing the Transatlantic, both East and Westbound on the Disney Magic.  We discuss the extra dining menu&amp;#8217;s and entertainment which is provided on these Sea Day intensive voyages.  She also shares her thoughts on how the many time zone changes effected them during their sailings.  We finish up with a look at some of the incredible ports they were able to visit, during these two bucket list cruises.  So sit back and enjoy, as we compare East to West transatlantic crossings.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;You can support our podcast via Patreon:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.patreon.com/dclpodcast"&gt;http://www.patreon.com/dclpodcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Follow along with us via:&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/dclpodcast"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/dclpodcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.instagram.com/dcl_podcast"&gt;http://www.instagram.com/dcl_podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Contact Steve, Christy, and Chris:&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="steve@dclpodcast.com"&gt;steve@dclpodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="christy@packyourpixiedust.com"&gt;christy@packyourpixiedust.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="brightdisneybychris@gmail.com"&gt;brightdisneybychris@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Book your next vacation with Christy:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.packyourpixiedust.com"&gt;http://www.packyourpixiedust.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sekriese@comcast.net (DCL Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cdc30d861e054232903e70b5cdad71c2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cdc30d861e054232903e70b5cdad71c2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 15:27:50 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Theme Park Rangers : How much are you willing to pay to go to Disney? Weighing cost vs. crowds (Ep. 35)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With Disney’s variable pricing structure, visitors pay the most for tickets when they will probably spend the most time waiting in lines and being frustrated by crowds. In this episode, the Theme Park Rangers weigh rising ticket costs vs. crowds — what is the tipping point?&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="3vbma-0-0"&gt;Supply and demand vs. customer experience (:46)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="3vbma-0-0"&gt;Have the right mental attitude (2:48)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="3vbma-0-0"&gt;May the weather be in your favor (3:47)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="3vbma-0-0"&gt;When will Disney raise ticket prices again? (5:01)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="3vbma-0-0"&gt;Is $200 a ticket the breaking point? (6:09)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="3vbma-0-0"&gt;Disney packages help disguise how much you are paying (8:06)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="3vbma-0-0"&gt;Universal keeps Disney in check (8:31)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="3vbma-0-0"&gt;Is it a moral issue? (12:31)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="3vbma-0-0"&gt;Will Disney lose the nostalgia factor? (13:36)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="3vbma-0-0"&gt;Tips to deal with crowded theme parks (14:12)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>video@orlandosentinel.com (Theme Park Rangers)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1ea1c217b4334eb1addbdb40ea9cc8c6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1ea1c217b4334eb1addbdb40ea9cc8c6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 06:05:56 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>A Way To Go : Tasting Malaysian Culture on Your Tongue, with Auria Abraham</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Homesickness can be a potent instigator. For Auria Abraham, a.k.a. “The Sambal Lady,” founder of Auria’s Malaysian Kitchen, a longing for authentic Malaysian home cooking led her on a path to running a popular supper club and food business in Brooklyn. She recounts taking a group of Americans on a very personal food tour of her home country. Find more info about this episode at Fathomaway.com. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (A Way To Go)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">578fa8d0773c49dfab883f040c385d84</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/578fa8d0773c49dfab883f040c385d84/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Travel Talk Weekly : An Adventure Cruise on the Amazon River</title><description>&lt;p&gt;16 - On this show, Rob and Kerri take you along with them as they cruise on the Amazon River with International Expeditions. You will learn about what to pack for this type of cruise, the types of activities you will experience and what to expect onboard. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus, they will walk you through a few of the stops they experienced on this cruise including some of the local villages, fishing for piranha and exploring a marketplace right off the river. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If adventure on the Amazon in Peru sounds interesting to you, you will enjoy this show. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This show is sponsored by Creating Magic Vacations. For your domestic or international trip, let us help you plan a done for you vacation. Reach out to &lt;a href="https://www.travelleaders.com/travel_agent/Agent-Details.aspx?id=107129&amp;amp;nav=0"&gt;Rob and Kerri&lt;/a&gt; here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>rob@traveltalkweekly.com (Travel Talk Weekly)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ac694bcb3a3a4502a59205a4e4ca4e9e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ac694bcb3a3a4502a59205a4e4ca4e9e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Living Adventurously : One Thing at a Time, as Beautiful as Possible - Living Adventurously 14</title><description>Thom Barnett runs Mamnick, a clothing brand passionate about cycling. The tagline is "one thing at a time, as beautiful as possible". I cajoled Thom out of bed at early o'clock and we cycled out of Sheffield together, nipping down the back alleys and cycle paths he knows so well. &lt;br&gt;Over breakfast I asked the fine arts graduate about life as a fashion designer, loving what you do, and Thom's love for exploring the hills and lanes of the Peak District.&lt;h1&gt;&lt;a href="https://livingadventurously.transistor.fm/subscribe"&gt;PLEASE SUBSCRIBE TO THE LIVING ADVENTUROUSLY PODCAST&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(It’s completely free, zero hassle to do (&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://livingadventurously.transistor.fm/subscribe"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;click here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;), but really helpful for me trying to get a new podcast off the ground. If you’re feeling extra kind, please leave a review on the app – that really helps.)&lt;/strong&gt;Listen on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/living-adventurously/id1489454694"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/2aYqIdvtVJkhIPklHaoXA3"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=486751&amp;amp;refid=stpr"&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://tunein.com/podcasts/Storytelling-Podcasts/Living-Adventurously-p1275719/"&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt; (“Alexa, please play the Living Adventurously podcast”) or on your favourite podcast platform such as Overcast, &lt;a href="https://podcasts.google.com/?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9mZWVkcy50cmFuc2lzdG9yLmZtL2xpdmluZy1hZHZlbnR1cm91c2x5"&gt;Google Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, Pocket Casts, &lt;a href="https://www.breaker.audio/living-adventurously"&gt;Breaker&lt;/a&gt;, Soundcloud, Castbox, Castro.&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.alastairhumphreys.com/podcast"&gt;www.alastairhumphreys.com/podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;THIS PODCAST IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY KOMOOT&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;Komoot&lt;/a&gt; is a route planning and navigation app that inspires and enables great outdoor experiences.Your very own outdoor experiences are waiting for you. Go explore more with &lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;komoot&lt;/a&gt;. Use the voucher code &lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;ADVENTUROUS&lt;/a&gt; to claim your free region bundle.The personalised planning and navigation tools ensure you plan the adventure that’s perfect for &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;. Komoot is Europe’s number 1 outdoor app, with route planning and navigation functionality, and strong community-driven inspirational features in the form of recommended Highlights and inspirational route Collections. It is used by over 8.5 million adventurers worldwide. Komoot is becoming the app of choice for cyclists and hikers the world over, with rapid community growth in the UK, the US and other parts of Europe.&lt;h1&gt;SHOW NOTES&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you enjoy listening to this episode over a cup of coffee and think it might be worth the price, you can &lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;buy me a coffee here:&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;www. ko-fi.com/al_humphreys&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep up to date with future episodes (and my other adventures, projects and books) with my &lt;a href="https://www.alastairhumphreys.com/more/subscribe/"&gt;free monthly newsletter: alastairhumphreys.com/more/subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Say hello on &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Al_Humphreys"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/al_humphreys/"&gt;Instagram: @al_humphreys&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;"One thing at a time, as beautiful as possible". Fine products manufactured in the UK and Japan: &lt;a href="https://www.mamnick.com/"&gt;Mamnick&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mamnick on &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mamnick_sheffield/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I'm a fashion designer, but I also make the cups of tea and post my own clothes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do one thing at a time, as beautiful as possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If it was all about money I'd have a proper job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I wanted to make a living doing something that I enjoy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When cycling you do more chatting than in other sports, and some of the conversations you have can be fantastic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I managed to make a living from my brand after about six months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A lot of the challenge of turning dream into reality is about confidence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Story-telling is really important, but the narrative around this brand just wrote itself and was natural.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You don't want anything to feel phony. You don't want to have to blag it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yomping - your own marching pace - less about training and more about riding your bike, being in the moment, and living at your own pace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I've made life hard for myself at times by being so outspoken&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real things, real places, real people resonate more with real people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My brand has basically become an extension of my own life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can ride so much in the Peaks without going on the same road twice, so I don't feel much desire to load up my bike and cycle round the world. A friend of mine cycled round the world and told me that the Peak District has the best roads.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;TRANSCRIPT&lt;/h1&gt;Below is the transcription of our conversation. It’s done by AI so is perhaps a wee bit ropey here and there. If these transcripts prove sufficiently useful then I will make the effort to clean then up and make them better. Do let me know if you think it’s worth my time to do that. (Or, better still, do it for me…!). If you’d like to listen as you read along you can do that here:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://otter.ai/s/8KjD2nB9Q3y8K5xZUsuWrA"&gt;https://otter.ai/s/8KjD2nB9Q3y8K5xZUsuWrA&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" title="★ Support this podcast by donating ★" href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;★ Support this podcast by donating ★&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>alastair@alastairhumphreys.com (Living Adventurously)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3838a04199df462daaf5b38f520bff3e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3838a04199df462daaf5b38f520bff3e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Thoughtful Travel Podcast : 172 Helping Others When We Travel</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Wanting to help others when we travel is a common theme amongst experienced travellers, because we've all realised how lucky we are and how unlucky many people around the world are. In Episode 172 of The Thoughtful Travel Podcast I'm not giving you all the answers on how to solve the world's problems but I do want to bring you stories from three travellers who've helped others in three different ways.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First up I talk with Veronica from Happily Made about her experiences in Cambodia and beyond, trying to figure out ways to help women in poverty or who need some way to support their children going to school. Veronica's Happily Made business is a great example of a sustainable way to help - she sells toys and other knitted products made by women who work out of their homes in Cambodia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, I chat with Marilyn from the Wow Travel Club who's also had lots of different experiences in helping others when she travels, and she tells the story of how a Dining for Women project she was involved with took her to Vietnam and some really impactful experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Finally, I get to talk with Rafferty, basically my favourite travel-expert 11-year-old, who described an experience he had recently in South Africa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Veronica&amp;rsquo;s Kickstarter - &lt;a href="https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/happilymade/happily-made-gifts-that-give-back"&gt;https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/happilymade/happily-made-gifts-that-give-back&lt;/a&gt; by 1st March 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happily Made - &lt;a href="https://happilymade.com.au"&gt;https://happilymade.com.au&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marilyn Murphy from the Wow Travel Club &lt;a href="https://www.wowtravelclub.com/"&gt;https://www.wowtravelclub.com/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dining for Women - &lt;a href="https://diningforwomen.org/"&gt;https://diningforwomen.org/&lt;/a&gt; - US only&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raff is the boy of his mum Aleney&amp;rsquo;s blog Boy Eats World - &lt;a href="https://boyeatsworld.com.au"&gt;https://boyeatsworld.com.au&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;KASI RC - Shack Art School &amp;amp; Theatre, Cape Town - &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/KhayelitshaArtSchool/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/KhayelitshaArtSchool/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tin Mugs Africa Trust - &lt;a href="https://www.tinmugs.org"&gt;https://www.tinmugs.org&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join our Facebook group for Thoughtful Travellers -&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/thoughtfultravellers"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/thoughtfultravellers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show notes: &lt;a href="http://notaballerina.com/172"&gt;https://notaballerina.com/172&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>amandakendle@me.com (The Thoughtful Travel Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7b166f821ecb4e8d948ab0e1680561c4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7b166f821ecb4e8d948ab0e1680561c4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 14:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind The Glass : [S3, E1] The 2020 Cars We Are Most Excited About</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are back! Season 3 of Behind The Glass kicks off in style with the return of Tony from Gravelwood Car Sales, as well as introducing a new studio where we will be recording episodes each week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this episode, we discuss the cars we are most excited about in 2020:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;03:00 - What Tony Has Been Up To This Week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;04:19 - Which SUV Is A 'Steal' Right Now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;07:00 - My Adventures On The Snow Tour&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;14:00 - Aston Martin DBX&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;19:50 - Audi RS6&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;25:37 - Ferrari Roma&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;32:00 - Jaguar F-Type&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;36:20 - Mercedes AMG 1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;38:00 - Porsche GT3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;40:00 - Toyota Yaris GR4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;42:00 - Porsche 992 Turbo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;42:30 - Porsche Taycan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hope you enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>info@seenthroughglass.com (Behind The Glass)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">40125a4b65f04822944918246828a527</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/40125a4b65f04822944918246828a527/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 10:12:24 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>La Lido Loca Cruise Podcast : 8. Vacation Arguments</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to episode #8 of the La Lido Loca podcast.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Join Jenny and Tony as they talk about cruising!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show Notes:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on YouTube:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;La Lido Loca Podcast: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCLoGEyIWH6f6mkJxDCweDag"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCLoGEyIWH6f6mkJxDCweDag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;La Lido Loca Cruising: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqFivW2VWJtGfvrMreyjNbw"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqFivW2VWJtGfvrMreyjNbw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Let Jenny help with your travel, you can contact her at: &lt;a href= "mailto:jbarnette@cruiseshipcenters.com"&gt;jbarnette@cruiseshipcenters.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Info about La Lido Loca Group Cruises: &lt;a href="http://www.lalidoloca.com/groupcruise" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;http://www.lalidoloca.com/groupcruise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on Social Media: Facebook Page - &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt; Instagram - &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt; Twitter - &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/lalidoloca" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://twitter.com/lalidoloca&lt;/a&gt; Pintrest - &lt;a href="https://www.pinterest.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.pinterest.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Represent the locafam with a t-shirt, check out the latest designs at: &lt;a href="https://teespring.com/stores/lalidoloca-funshop" target= "_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://teespring.com/stores/lalidoloca-funshop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our mailing address is: La Lido Loca 4142 Mariner Blvd #402 Spring Hill, FL 34609&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Support our creative efforts at Patreon: &lt;a href="http://www.patreon.com/lalidoloca" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;http://www.patreon.com/lalidoloca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Please Submit Questions or Comments to &lt;a href= "mailto:tony@lalidoloca.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;tony@lalidoloca.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tony@lalidoloca.com (La Lido Loca Cruise Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">52f320de3360411aa75e8bff6a1c47ab</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/52f320de3360411aa75e8bff6a1c47ab/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 08:39:18 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Out Alive from BACKPACKER : Buried in a Rockslide</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Blue skies in Grand Teton National Park turn gray when a group of hikers are caught in a powerful rockslide. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ssebestyen@aimmedia.com (Out Alive from BACKPACKER)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">207f20e0acb54fb4b3a9358dec4b4724</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/207f20e0acb54fb4b3a9358dec4b4724/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dish Food Travel Show : 49 Pavlova (Australia vs New Zealand)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In This Episode:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* History Of The Pavlova - One of Australia &amp; New Zealand’s favourite desserts* We try to settle the 100 year old debate of who invented it, AUS or NZ?* Plus, was the first Pavlova made with frog’s legs, rather than fruit?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read more stories about food and culinary travel on our blog: &lt;a href='https://foodfuntravel.com'&gt;https://foodfuntravel.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>megsy@foodfuntravel.com (The Dish Food Travel Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">07a722da29f34ac2b0c0d323496d11b1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/07a722da29f34ac2b0c0d323496d11b1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 01:43:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dreams Unlimited Travel Show - A Weekly Discussion About Travel and Dreams Unlimited Travel : #165 - Traveling to Walt Disney World with Boys</title><description>01/27/20 - In this episode, Dreams Unlimited Travel agent Elaine Edwards shares what it's like for her to travel to Walt Disney World with her three boys along with which resorts, restaurants, and attractions they prefer!</description><author>craig@wdwinfo.com (Dreams Unlimited Travel Show - A Weekly Discussion About Travel and Dreams Unlimited Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b9144991caf548dab4b86e50323cad44</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b9144991caf548dab4b86e50323cad44/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>We Travel There with Lee Huffman : Idaho Falls, ID | Splashing in the falls with Miranda</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Miranda Marquit of MirandaMarquit.com takes us to Idaho Falls, Idaho. Miranda and I splash around in the falls, explore nature by hiking and biking, then chow down on a delicious steak at D’Railed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show notes are at &lt;a href="https://WeTravelThere.com/idahofalls" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://WeTravelThere.com/idahofalls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;When you can't travel, you can at least sleep like you're on vacation. For a limited time, listeners will get $125 off &amp; 2 free pillows when you use the link &lt;a href= "https://WeTravelThere.com/nectar" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;WeTravelThere.com/nectar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wetravelthere@gmail.com (We Travel There with Lee Huffman)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3c09ba400c664b0dad741e3d95bc1bec</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3c09ba400c664b0dad741e3d95bc1bec/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Retro Disney World Podcast : Ep 55 - Backlot Studio Tram Tour</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Episode 55 of the RetroWDW Podcast: "Backstage Tour - MGM" - We appreciate your support and hope you have been enjoying each and every episode. Be sure to check out some of our previous shows!&lt;/p&gt;
Comments &amp; Corrections
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take a listen to our latest mini-episode, &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/podcast/podcast-episode-54-5-bringing-the-world-closer-to-you/'&gt;Bringing The World Closer To You&lt;/a&gt; - this was a quick one but ended up being very good. Enjoy!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;Listener Mail
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/gallery/lake-buena-vista/Frap07.png'&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The mailbag is full and we love that! Every month, you can possibly get on the show, so be sure to write to us at &lt;a href='mailto:podcast@retrowdw.com'&gt;podcast@retrowdw.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rob wrote in, asking about the VIP Lounges at EPCOT. Rob is mainly interested in the Kodak lounge at Journey into Imagination. Brian gives us his take on it. As I was putting this write-up together, I realized Rob is the owner of the site we reference. Check out his collection of VIP lounge pictures and information: &lt;a href='https://www.robyeodesign.com/blog/2016/3/21/future-worlds-s'&gt;Future World's Hidden VIP Lounges&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next letter we discuss purchasing fog machines at Innoventions. Was this actually a thing? We discuss...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dane writes in, regarding ephemera. Do we have any from Toys Fantastique? Todd gets us up to speed on how our photo archive is growing and improving at this very moment. What any RetroWDW fan can do, is use the search and find so many more images! This is great, use this link and give it a try: &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/photo-archive-search/'&gt;Photo Search&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;[listenerfeedback]&lt;/p&gt;
Audio Rewind
&lt;p&gt;Our audio rewind this month is the opening of Holiday Illuminations - Thank you for all the guesses and emails, and we didn't get many!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a winner! Congratulations Beth Goldman!  - you won a set of RetroMagic ornaments!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you think you know the answer to this month's audio rewind, email us! &lt;a href='mailto:contest@retrowdw.com'&gt;contest@retrowdw.com&lt;/a&gt; - This month, the winner will be getting a copy of the Marty Sklar book, Dream it, Do it - All entries due 2/17/2020 and a random winner will be selected.&lt;/p&gt;
Main Topic
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main topic this month is one of the recently closed classics, The Disney-MGM Studios Backlot Tour. There have been so many changes and updates over the years, but we are going to focus on the original, for the most part. How is our guide on this episode, walking us through the entire tram portion of the tour. We take it right back to 1989, going through how the Disney-MGM Studios actually worked. The concept of going past the theme park and then entering the studio - this is how the tour basically began. The walking tour was part of this, but we are not going to discuss this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The backlot tour had so many different aspects including residential street, the boneyard, the various production trailers, and so many other little nuggets. The tour seemed to change often, as far as props and items but the tour wasn't complete with a look at the Streets of America, or the New York street set. You would know this as the set for "The Lottery", which seems to be the only movie filmed here that we ever hear about. To accompany this episode, we have a great video on our YouTube channel - &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_DX0WnRHs8&amp;feature=youtu.be'&gt;click here to watch&lt;/a&gt; after the episode!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/backstage.gif'&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Delta_Dreamflight_L1011_Filming_Set_02.jpg'&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Delta_Dreamflight_L1011_Filming_Set_03.jpg'&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Delta_Dreamflight_L1011_Filming_Set_04.jpg'&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
2020: The Year of Film
&lt;p&gt;To make sure you are the first to know when items are released, &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/retrodisneyworld'&gt;subscribe to us on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;. Be sure to click the notification bell too, that way you are alerted when we post.  Finally, be sure to &lt;a href='https://vimeo.com/retrowdw'&gt;check out Vimeo&lt;/a&gt; if that is your thing, as we will post there as well. This past month we have posted the &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_DX0WnRHs8&amp;feature=youtu.be'&gt;Backlot Tour video&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zqDQLj4rtxM&amp;feature=youtu.be'&gt;a ride around the monorail in 1991&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XU2UJLEBczk&amp;feature=youtu.be'&gt;1994 runDisney Marathon&lt;/a&gt;. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
Next Month
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Join us next time for Episode 56, which we have not fully planned out, but you won't want to miss it  Thanks for joining us! &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>podcast@retrowdw.com (Retro Disney World Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e935163ea548489f94e21df5226cc107</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e935163ea548489f94e21df5226cc107/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 19:59:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Puerto Vallarta Travel  Show Podcast : No Way Jose Restaurant in Puerto Vallarta, Mexico</title><description>&lt;p&gt;No Way Jose Restaurant and Bar in Puerto Vallarta has a funny name, and owner Jose Alfredo tells us the history of the place.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>pvtravelshow@gmail.com (Puerto Vallarta Travel  Show Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b636de6727924e00a712c3337fa9eecc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b636de6727924e00a712c3337fa9eecc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 15:24:45 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Join Us in France Travel Podcast : Honeymoon in Provence, Episode 268</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On today’s episode Annie Sargent brings you a conversation with Denise Sum from Canada about her 10-day honeymoon in Provence. The newlyweds  stayed in Avignon, visited Arles, the Pont du Gard, Uzès, drove around the the Petit Lubéron (where they found a lovely bed &amp; breakfast listed below), and ended in Marseille.&lt;/p&gt; How to Plan Your Honeymoon in Provence &lt;p&gt;Listening to this episode will make your own honeymoon planning much easier because Denise did the hard work: she found great accommodations, great restaurants and she even figured out the best way to get around in Provence!&lt;/p&gt; Transportation in Provence &lt;p&gt;Provence is tricky because there are places you can't get to without a car. And yet there are times when having a car in Provence makes everything difficult because there is nowhere to park!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Denise and her husband used a combination of train and &lt;a href= "https://www.rentalcars.com/CountryLandingPage.do?countryCode=fr&amp;affiliateCode=joinusin081&amp;preflang=en"&gt; car rental&lt;/a&gt;, which is the best way to proceed. You definitely don't want to hold on to your rental car in large cities in Provence because parking will drive you nuts!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On the other hand, parking in small Provençal villages in late September / early October wasn't an issue. The key is to plan ahead and book your rental in advance because last-minute car rentals cost a fortune in France!&lt;/p&gt; Is Marseille worth a Visit? &lt;p&gt;In this episode we also discuss the age-old question: is Marseille a good place to visit in Provence? This conversation starts 35 minutes into the episode, but to summarize, we both think Marseille is a wonderful place if moving around multi-cultural environment feels natural to you.&lt;/p&gt; What if You Don't Want to Use Airbnb? &lt;p&gt;More and more people are weary of using Airbnb. Denise found great places to rent through &lt;a href= "https://www.booking.com/searchresults.en.html?region=2745&amp;aid=954523&amp;no_rooms=1&amp;group_adults=2"&gt; Booking&lt;/a&gt;. To find the gems, go to &lt;a href= "https://www.booking.com/searchresults.en.html?region=2745&amp;aid=954523&amp;no_rooms=1&amp;group_adults=2"&gt; this page&lt;/a&gt;, then scroll down and on the left you'll see a lot of criteria, including Apartments, Villas, Hostels, and price range. It's worth mentioning because a lot of people don't know it's a possibility!&lt;/p&gt; Provence Accommodations Recommendations &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.booking.com/hotel/fr/t2-centre-ville-avec-exterieur.en.html?aid=954523&amp;no_rooms=1&amp;group_adults=2"&gt; Great Apartment in Avignon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.booking.com/hotel/fr/la-maison-d-ulysse-chac-teaux-amp-ha-tels-collection-xml.en.html?aid=954523&amp;no_rooms=1&amp;group_adults=2"&gt; Maison d'Ulyse near Pont du Gard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.booking.com/hotel/fr/le-clos-les-eydins.en.html?aid=954523&amp;no_rooms=1&amp;group_adults=2"&gt; Le Clos des Eydins in Bonnieux&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; Restaurants Recommendations &lt;p&gt;Denise’s husband is a chef, so they paid attention to restaurants and have great recommendations for lovely places to eat.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;La Fourchette and L'Agape in Avignon&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Lunch and L'Occitane Spa at La Maison d'Uzes&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Bistrot le 5 in Menerbes&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Le Petit Cabanon and Le Bistro du Cour in Marseille&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Click play to listen or if you'd rather read our conversation click on transcript. You'll also find Denise's notes by visiting the guest notes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://joinusinfrance.com/category/interests/honeymoon-in-france/"&gt; Episodes about Honeymoons in France&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:%20annie@joinusinfrance.com"&gt;Email&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://joinusinfrance.com/audiotours/"&gt;Annie's VoiceMap Paris Tours&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/joinusinfrance/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href= "https://www.pinterest.fr/France_Travel_Podcast/"&gt;Pinterest&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/addictedtofrance/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ParisPodcast"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>annie@joinusinfrance.com (Join Us in France Travel Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9feded0cf8e84b52bf6425b275713e18</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9feded0cf8e84b52bf6425b275713e18/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 09:02:11 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>National Parks Traveler Podcast : National Parks Traveler: New Allosaurus From Dinosaur NM, And Saratoga National Historical Park</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week’s show, our 50th, looks at a Jurassic Period carnivore dubbed "AJ,"  a new species of allosaurus, found in Dinosaur National Monument in Utah, and takes a short Revolutionary War history tour of Saratoga National Historical Park in New York State.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>kurt@nationalparkstraveler.org (National Parks Traveler Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0763c5f850dd410f933d20a41bc4ea9b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0763c5f850dd410f933d20a41bc4ea9b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Happiest Podcast On Earth : 45 - Password - Disney Edition</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Happiest Podcast team goes head to head in a game of password in which a contestant is given a word or phrase related to Disney and using one word at a time, attempts to give hints so their partner can guess the word or phrase. Guaranteed to entertain so HAPPY LISTENING EVERYONE!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>happiestpodcast@gmail.com (Happiest Podcast On Earth)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bc41aaabfd2b454eab6eafa3db7c55a4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bc41aaabfd2b454eab6eafa3db7c55a4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 14:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Australia All Over : Australia All Over highlights podcast</title><description>This week Macca presented the program in front of a live audience in Guyra, NSW.</description><author>localfeedback@your.abc.net.au (Australia All Over)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">923409ab312e4c518627343cf5169381</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/923409ab312e4c518627343cf5169381/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 11:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Coastin' the Country : Ep. 15: Six Flags Great America Tsunami Surge update, No Coaster Con recap</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Marcus recaps his trip to the American Coaster Enthusiasts No Coaster Con and talks with Six Flags Great America after their presentation there. They give us an update on the construction of their new water coaster Tsunami Surge. We also break down the latest news in the theme park world, including Super Nintendo World coming to Universal Orlando, and the latest rumors about the big 2021 attraction coming to Busch Gardens Williamsburg. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mleshock@wgntv.com (Coastin' the Country)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">759c262424704b788f518e05e28e3b84</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/759c262424704b788f518e05e28e3b84/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Trip That Changed Me : Japan with Jacqueline Gifford: memory, childhood nostalgia, and the myth of having it all</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As Editor-in-Chief of &lt;i&gt;Travel + Leisure, &lt;/i&gt;Jacqueline Gifford spends a lot of time out of office exploring far-flung destinations. It’s a career she pursued, in part, thanks to her parents, who encouraged Jacqui’s cultural curiosity from the get-go. On today’s episode, Jacqueline shares a nostalgic trip to Japan, the country where she was born, at a particularly pivotal moment: her own pregnancy. We discuss what it was like to visit her childhood neighborhood after a 20-year absence, how her memories both differed from and reflected reality, and her approach to balancing a busy work life with raising a child. Plus, hear Jacqueline’s number one travel tip and the surprising item she cannot travel without.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@podcastnation.org (The Trip That Changed Me)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3d73e3deb0504130b29d5b288cd0f11b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3d73e3deb0504130b29d5b288cd0f11b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 03:00:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Books And Travel : Sacred Australia And The Northern Territory With Amanda Markham</title><description>In today’s episode, we’re heading for the Northern Territory of Australia as Dr. Amanda Markham talks about some of the Aboriginal Dreaming stories of the area and how the vast landscape impacts living and working there, as well as the best places to visit if you’re traveling. Amanda is of Wiradjuri Aboriginal descent and speaks an Aboriginal language, so it’s fantastic to get her perspective.&lt;br /&gt;
We recorded this episode before the bush fires swept the country and I talked back in &lt;a href="https://www.booksandtravel.page/australia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;episode 20 about my own experience traveling around Australia&lt;/a&gt; and then living there — I mentioned that it’s the weather you have to watch out for, not the snakes or spiders — and Amanda emphasizes again how important it is to prepare for the reality of the outback. We both love Australia and particularly, the Northern Territories — it’s one of the places I would love to go back to —  so I hope you enjoy the adventure in this episode.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://amandamarkham.com/about/" target="_blank" rel="attachment noopener wp-att-1224 noreferrer"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://amandamarkham.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Dr. Amanda Markham&lt;/a&gt; is an archaeologist and anthropologist in the Australian outback, as well as a travel writer and award-winning author of speculative fiction.&lt;br /&gt;
* The three different climates of the Northern Territory&lt;br /&gt;
* Exploring the Top End with Aboriginal guides and some of the Dreaming stories in the landscape&lt;br /&gt;
* Language differences above and below the monsoon line&lt;br /&gt;
* The myths and reality about danger in Australia&lt;br /&gt;
* The Alice Springs Beanie Festival and what makes the outback culture unique&lt;br /&gt;
* Stargazing in the Northern Territory&lt;br /&gt;
* Recommended books set in outback Australia&lt;br /&gt;
You can find Dr. Amanda Markham at &lt;a href="http://traveloutbackaustralia.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;traveloutbackaustralia.com&lt;/a&gt; and at &lt;a href="http://amandamarkham.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;AmandaMarkham.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Transcript of the interview&lt;br /&gt;
Jo Frances Penn: Dr. Amanda Markham is an archaeologist and anthropologist in the Australian outback, as well as a travel writer and award-winning author of speculative fiction. Welcome, Amanda.&lt;br /&gt;
Dr. Markham: Hi. Thanks, Joanna. Thanks very much for having me.&lt;br /&gt;
Jo Frances Penn: It’s great to have you on the show. Your job sounds very cool. I always wanted to be an archaeologist. People think, ‘Oh, archaeology? You must work in ancient Greece or Egypt.’ But you work in the Australian outback.&lt;br /&gt;
Tell us, what does your job involve?&lt;br /&gt;
Dr. Markham: I’ll say that I’ve had two careers working in the outback. First, as an anthropologist, I started working in anthropology in 1997. I went to the Northern Territory to work for an agency, a government agency called The Sacred Sites Authority, and I worked specifically in the protection of Aboriginal sacred sites, working with aboriginal elders, particularly over Central Australia, so the southern half of the Northern Territory.&lt;br /&gt;
I’ll slow down a little bit for listeners who don’t know where the Northern Territory is in Australia. It’s that middle third of Australia, but the northern part, and it’s got three very distinctive climate zones, one of which is the arid zone.&lt;br /&gt;
I don’t want to call it a desert because we don’t really have true deserts in Australia. We do have arid zones, which are often vast savannas and rangelands. Then, you have a sub-tropical area north of that. And then we have the tropics where they actually get a full monsoon, and we call it here in the Northern Territory, we call it the Top End, and that’s where Darwin is.&lt;br /&gt;
So, I went to the Northern Territory to be an anthropologist, work with Aboriginal elders, recording and protecting their sacred sites, so their Dreaming sites. Always,</description><author>jo@booksandtravel.page (Books And Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">de8d1551e0b9434bbb1804bc561ab348</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/de8d1551e0b9434bbb1804bc561ab348/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 16:10:24 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WAYPOINTS - with Jim Klug : #20 Will Blair: Fly Fishing the Legendary Waters of Kamchatka</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Will Blair is one of the godfathers of fly fishing in Kamchatka. Since 1997, Will has helped pioneer some of the top fisheries on the Kamchatka Peninsula, developing and offering what is arguably one of the best rainbow trout fishing experiences found anywhere on the planet. Yellow Dog is proud to partner with Will and his remote Two Yurt and Ozernaya programs, along with the incredibly-unique “Rainbows from Above” customized fly-out program. Because Will knows this mysterious and wild area like no one else, we tracked him down with a long list of questions in-hand. We discuss the factors that make a trip to Kamchatka so special, what gear to bring, the seasonality of the fisheries, species, travel logistics, and the stories you might tell upon returning from one of the greatest rainbow trout destinations in the world. If you’ve ever thought about a trip to Kamchatka, then you will certainly enjoy this exciting episode: the Season 1 finale of the &lt;em&gt;Waypoints Podcast&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jim@yellowdogflyfishing.com (WAYPOINTS - with Jim Klug)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">169f114bcb924038b525fd4d2aa5e1de</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/169f114bcb924038b525fd4d2aa5e1de/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The City : The Confrontation | S2 E7</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this Season 2 bonus episode,&amp;nbsp;accusations of sexual assault at the Spice House strip club come to light. Two women who work there head to the club to confront their bosses, their phones secretly set to record.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@thecitypodcast.com (The City)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">edc9803293644e4fa7daa1bcf782e5df</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/edc9803293644e4fa7daa1bcf782e5df/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MiceCast : Acquisition Analysis</title><description>Your hosts discuss the theory that the Lucasfilm acquisition was a failure compared to Pixar and Marvel. We also spend some time talking about the virtual queue for Rise of the Resistance. 2 hours 16 minutes.&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/Micecast/~4/00_v98Zkb2U" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>micecast@gmail.com (MiceCast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">38164a6a54234260b74be0aa2831c8e2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/38164a6a54234260b74be0aa2831c8e2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Morocco : Why Morocco 029 – Meryam Demnati on Amazigh culture in Morocco</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With a new year and a new decade upon us, I sat down with Meryam Demnati, an Amazigh activitist, to chat about a little-known New Year celebrated in here in Morocco &amp;#8211; Yennayer &amp;#8211; the Amazigh New Year for the latest episode of Why Morocco. Celebrated on 12 January by the native peoples of North Africa, Yennayer marks the shift from extreme cold and milder temperatures and is celebrated by Amazigh (sometimes referred to as Berbers) communities not only in Morocco, but throughout North Africa. Interestingly though, January 1 and the Islamic New Year are observed here in Morocco with official bank holidays, but Yennayer is not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an activist, Meryam also talks about the status of the Amazigh language and Tifinagh alphabet in Morocco, recognition of the Amazigh culture, and the causes the Amazigh movement has and continues to work on since post-independence in Morocco.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more Morocco ideas and advise, follow me on Instagram at &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mandyinmorocco/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;@mandyinmorocco&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My other projects include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tasting Marrakech food and cultural tours in Marrakech &lt;a href="http://tasting-marrakech.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;tasting-marrakech.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel and public relations consulting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Freelance writing for print and digital  &lt;a href="https://mandyinmorocco.com/freelance-writing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;mandyinmorocco.com/freelance-writing/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mandyjsinclair@gmail.com (Why Morocco)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2fab948e5ab44c9eb5855187a0e97bb8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2fab948e5ab44c9eb5855187a0e97bb8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 23:28:14 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The One Way Ticket Show : Search for Common Ground CEO - Shamil Idriss</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Shamil Idriss is the Chief Executive Officer of Search for Common Ground, the world’s largest organization dedicated to peace building.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As CEO, and in previous roles as President, Chief Operating Officer, and Burundi Country Director, Shamil has led Search’s efforts to end violent conflict in more than 35 countries, including conflict zones in the Middle East and Africa.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Starting in 2005, Shamil served as the Deputy Director of the United Nations Alliance for Civilizations, supporting political and religious leaders in improving relations between Western and Muslim-majority countries.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A pioneer in cross-cultural media technologies, Shamil worked from 2008 to 2014 as the CEO of Soliya, a nonprofit at the intersection of technology, peace building, and global education.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Shamil graduated from Swarthmore College with degrees in Economics and Philosophy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On this episode, Shamil shares his one way ticket to meet New Zealand Prime Minister, Jacinda Ardern. Plus, he highlights the phenomenal work being done around the globe by Search for Common Ground.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Shamil is just one of the dynamic personalities featured on The One Way Ticket Show, where Host Steven Shalowitz explores with his guests where they would go if given a one way ticket, no coming back! Destinations may be in the past, present, future, real, imaginary or a state of mind.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Steven's guests have included: Nobel Peace Prize Winner, President Jose Ramos-orta; Legendary Talk Show Host, Dick Cavett; Law Professor, Alan Dershowitz; Fashion Expert, Tim Gunn; Broadcast Legend, Charles Osgood; International Rescue Committee President &amp; CEO, David Miliband; Playwright, David Henry Hwang; Journalist-Humorist-Actor, Mo Rocca; SkyBridge Capital Founder &amp; Co-Managing Partner, Anthony Scaramucci; Abercrombie &amp; Kent Founder, Geoffrey Kent; Travel Expert, Pauline Frommer, as well as leading photographers, artists, chefs, writers, intellectuals and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>steven@theonewayticketshow.com (The One Way Ticket Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e119f0048427434887ec1a2b543d9b96</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e119f0048427434887ec1a2b543d9b96/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 09:20:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Exploring the North Shore : Episode 19: Ice Fishing in the BWCA</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Joe is back for this week's episode all about ice fishing in the BWCA! Joe and Jaye are joined by Matthew Baxley (last heard from in the Haunted House episode), and Chelsea Lloyd. Plus, Chelsea's sister Whitney and friend, Rachel, come along for the adventure. Joe, Matthew, and Chelsea are the hosts of WTIP's Boundary Waters Podcast. In this cross-over episode, the group heads into the BWCA to ice fish on Duncan Lake. Learn the legalities of fishing in the BWCA, along with some tips and tricks from one of the area's most knowledgeable anglers (Joe). Also, listen to find out if we once again get skunked on an Exploring the North Shore fishing episode. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can find more information on fishing in the BWCA on the Cascade Vacation Rentals Website: &lt;a href='https://www.cascadevacationrentals.com/area-info-ice-fishing-bwca.htm'&gt;https://www.cascadevacationrentals.com/area-info-ice-fishing-bwca.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plus, listen and subscribe to WTIP's Boundary Waters Podcast to hear more from Joe, Matthew, and Chelsea: &lt;a href='https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/listing/wtip-boundary-waters-podcast/'&gt;https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/listing/wtip-boundary-waters-podcast/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, check out our new website! Full of fun stories, articles, and a detailed business listing for all things North Shore. If you love the North Shore, be sure to bookmark Exploring the North Shore and let us help you plan your next North Shore adventure! &lt;a href='https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/'&gt;https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This episode is sponsored by &lt;a href='https://www.cascadevacationrentals.com/'&gt;Cascade Vacation Rentals&lt;/a&gt;. Use promo code "Podcast" at check-out to receive Cascade's largest available percent off discount (discount changes seasonally). This episode is also sponsored by &lt;a href='https://thebiglakelife.com/'&gt;The Big Lake&lt;/a&gt;. Use promo code "Explore" at check-out to receive 15% off your first online order. Thank you to our wonderful sponsors!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marketing@staycvr.com (Exploring the North Shore)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">886346c63eba4a2ea8a20813743354aa</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/886346c63eba4a2ea8a20813743354aa/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 04:45:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>In Limbo : "Be Yourself"- Limitations of simplicity and common sense</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode we will discuss the depths and obstacles of advice we've heard time and time again to "be ourselves."&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts14+d507e9c@anchor.fm (In Limbo)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e80c5ae801f94dd1969720f049a238cc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e80c5ae801f94dd1969720f049a238cc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 11:59:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mobituaries with Mo Rocca : Mobituaries LIVE!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In a Mobits first, Mo takes the show on the road! Mo shares his love of obituaries; investigates why we confuse certain dead celebrities; and interviews former New York Times obituary writer Margalit Fox about what it's like to write about the dead for a living. This episode was recorded in Asbury Park, NJ and Fairfield, CT.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Mobituaries@simonandschuster.com (Mobituaries with Mo Rocca)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8c43201ced104373899f6e2057913360</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8c43201ced104373899f6e2057913360/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Monsters Among Us Podcast : Sn. 8 Ep. 19 - Poltergeists, bigfoot’s bones and a few strange UFOs.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Tallman Ghost -  &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aSJqmSfT62c" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3DaSJqmSfT62c&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1579295376542000&amp;usg=AFQjCNEehI4EtJp_xm2MM4xe5OEJZ9msaw"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aSJqmSfT62c&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Strange Familiars - &lt;a href= "https://www.strangefamiliars.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.strangefamiliars.com/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1579295376542000&amp;usg=AFQjCNFM7ArCgSX9BvFoi1wrGseUrHMtSg"&gt; https://www.strangefamiliars.com/&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>monstersamonguspodcast@gmail.com (Monsters Among Us Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">84412af3c94c4bb5bb18ac1be8728702</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/84412af3c94c4bb5bb18ac1be8728702/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 13:47:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Inside Universal Podcast : The Inside Universal Podcast: New Decade, Same Non-Sense (and Super Nintendo World, too)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The return of Hatetofly! Andy, Brian, and Drew discuss the recent &lt;a href= "http://www.insideuniversal.net/2020/01/universal-orlandos-mardi-gras-2020-concert-line-up-and-details-announced/"&gt; Mardi Gras&lt;/a&gt; announcement, as well as the latest information that was released regarding &lt;a href= "http://www.insideuniversal.net/2020/01/universal-studios-japan-reveals-new-details-on-super-nintendo-world-opening-this-summer/"&gt; Super Nintendo World&lt;/a&gt; at Universal Studios Japan, including the interactive Power Up Bands. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jon@insideuniversal.net (The Inside Universal Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9bf6152d06b04e88b78500c62165b169</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9bf6152d06b04e88b78500c62165b169/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:28:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hashtag Colorado Life : Building Your Colorado Bucket List in 2020</title><description>BONUS #2: What’s on your Colorado bucket list? In this bonus episode Ryan and Carrie talk about the must-see and must-do things to add to your Colorado bucket list. With the mountains in your backyard, an ever-growing food scene, and endless indoor and outdoor activities where do you start? There are so many things to do and cities to explore!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ryan and Carrie share the activities and adventures that are on their Colorado bucket list. They also discuss the places and sights they have already visited. Many of the ideas include iconic Colorado destinations and local favorites, as well as lesser-known but still epic experiences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are looking for the best things to do in Colorado without busting your budget, that’s what this episode is all about. Find out the top 16 things Ryan and Carrie recommend you add to your bucket list. Plus, these are great suggestions for discovering within your first year of living in the square state.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more information and resources about exploring Colorado, visit our website at &lt;a href="http://hashtagcoloradolife.com/"&gt;HashtagColoradoLife.com&lt;/a&gt; or&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/hashtagcoloradolife/"&gt; @HashtagColoradoLife&lt;/a&gt; on Instagram.</description><author>team@hashtagcoloradolife.com (Hashtag Colorado Life)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4580a7f45e174506aa649f38489f2dba</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4580a7f45e174506aa649f38489f2dba/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Wise About Texas : Ep. 78:  The Lady in Blue</title><description>&lt;p&gt; In 1629 a group of Jumano Indians suddenly appeared at a New Mexico mission, eager to learn more about Christianity.  The excited and grateful Franciscan priests wondered what motivated this sudden interest.  The tale the Indians told seemed unbelievable.  A &amp;#8220;lady in blue&amp;#8221; had appeared to them instructing them to seek out the priests and teaching the Indians the sign of the cross.  That sounded incredible enough but what really stunned the priests was that they had just received a letter from Spain relating the story of a nun telling the exact same tale&amp;#8230;half a world away.  Is the Lady in Blue a myth&amp;#8230;or a miracle?  You decide in the latest episode of Wise About Texas.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/WiseAboutTexas/~4/lmVlyLFkRdw" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>Host@wiseabouttexas.com (Wise About Texas)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9f63998fcaeb4eed89b309da28ba42b9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9f63998fcaeb4eed89b309da28ba42b9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 09:36:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>San Francisco Real Estate: Escrow Out Loud : To Stage, Or Not to Stage</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In today’s episode of &lt;a href="https://jacksonfuller.com/insight/podcast/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Escrow Out Loud, our San Francisco Real Estate podcast&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;u&gt;,&lt;/u&gt; we have a very special guest star: our friend and client Kay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[00:44] Kay shares a little of her background with us. We also learn how she came to buy her lovely house in Burlingame almost forty years ago which was almost brand new at the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[03:46] Other than the perfect location, the two other features that made Kay fall in love with the house were the easy upkeep and the huge closets!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[05:24] This summer we accidentally found her second dream home, so we needed to get Kay’s home in Burlingame on the market fast. Kay explains it was a challenge of getting her home ready for sale while still living in it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[07:14] Initially, we tried to sell Kay’s house as is, with all her furniture but didn't have much luck. We then moved Kay out, revamped and staged the house before trying again. What was the second process like in comparison to the first time around?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[09:29] The unique thing about selling a house is the emotional component that comes with it. After all the renovations Kay’s home was completely transformed. Did it hurt her feelings having to do this or was it exciting?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[14:30] The house was put on the market the second time and this time it sold within ten days, over asking price. Looking back on all of the drama, was it all worth it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[15:09] Interestingly, after looking at numerous properties, the new house Kay ended up buying was also staged. What advice does she have for anyone considering selling their place while still living in it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[16:46] While selling a home is a very emotional process, the aim is to make as much money as possible. To achieve this, it needs to look as good as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for listening. If you enjoyed this episode leave us a review on your favorite platform, tell your friends and don’t forget to join us again next week!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info+5ab02d3b627e02027cf8604d@mg.pippa.io (San Francisco Real Estate: Escrow Out Loud)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">46419d11ffad450ca04a659535ee3534</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/46419d11ffad450ca04a659535ee3534/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 09:20:48 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>