<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Travel feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My travel episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My Travel feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 15:15:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>Travel Talk Weekly : Travel Tips During a Health Crisis</title><description>&lt;p&gt;023 - On this show, Rob &amp;amp; Kerri give tips and advice on what do to if you have plans to travel and a health crisis breaks out. What has just happened with the Corona Virus has for the most part, shut down the entire travel industry, including all of the Disney parks around the world, and most of the cruise industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What do you do ?&amp;nbsp; Postpone your trip ?&amp;nbsp; Cancel and just wait?&amp;nbsp; You do have options.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-----------------------------------&lt;br&gt;This show is sponsored by Creating Magic Vacations. For your domestic or international trip, let us help you plan a done for you vacation. Reach out to &lt;a href="https://www.travelleaders.com/travel_agent/Agent-Details.aspx?id=107129&amp;amp;nav=0"&gt;Rob and Kerri&lt;/a&gt; here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>rob@traveltalkweekly.com (Travel Talk Weekly)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">86c9d5fbc7a0415bb1f78421cbe87dd0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/86c9d5fbc7a0415bb1f78421cbe87dd0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 05:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Parklandia : Boondocking with Brad: Boondocking</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this bonus episode of Boondocking with Brad, we answer perhaps the most basic question: what is "boondocking?" Basically, it's staying in your RV without hooking up to outside power, and we'll talk you through some of the dos, don'ts, concerns, and things to keep in mind while on... and off... the road.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Got more questions? We'd love to talk! Join the conversation in the Parklandia Rangers &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/ParklandiaRangers/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and Like our &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/parklandiapod/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;! Also be sure to follow Parklandia on Instagram &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/parklandiapod/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;@parklandiapod&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Parklandia)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">edae71827d1b40959d7131eb7fc0f9f1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/edae71827d1b40959d7131eb7fc0f9f1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 03:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Theme Park Rangers : Coronavirus fears force Disney World, Universal, SeaWorld to close (Ep. 42)</title><description>Disney World, Universal Orlando and SeaWorld Orlando are closing Sunday evening for the rest of March because of the coronavirus pandemic — an unprecedented move.  This episode  covers reaction to the closures, what this means to passholders and those with vacation plans, and what it means to live in a theme park town with no theme parks.      &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="8cpeh-0-0"&gt;What is closed; What is open (:31)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="8cpeh-0-0"&gt;Has this happened before? (1:28)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="8cpeh-0-0"&gt;A lot of fear, a lot of uncertainty (2:01)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="8cpeh-0-0"&gt;Visiting parks day after closure announcement (3:39)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="8cpeh-0-0"&gt;Comparing coronavirus to hurricanes (5:52)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="8cpeh-0-0"&gt;Bob Iger on Disney’s resiliency (7:52)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="8cpeh-0-0"&gt;What about annual passholders? (8:46)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="8cpeh-0-0"&gt;Will cast members be paid during closures? (9:08)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="8cpeh-0-0"&gt;Hotel reservation refunds (10:17)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="8cpeh-0-0"&gt;What events are we missing because of park closures? (11:53)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>video@orlandosentinel.com (Theme Park Rangers)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7a439d52da044b98aa164a12dbc1cee5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7a439d52da044b98aa164a12dbc1cee5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 14:24:09 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Monocle 24: The Menu : The real Irish food</title><description>Galway’s top chef, JP McMahon, on what the world doesn’t understand about Ireland’s food culture. Plus: the bartender shaking up Rio de Janeiro’s cocktail scene.</description><author>info@monocle.com (Monocle 24: The Menu)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f3140e478af04af5b740f2537f141136</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f3140e478af04af5b740f2537f141136/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Oh Boy, The Podcast : Episode 012: How We Fell in Love With Disney</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A dose of positivity and reminder for you this crazy week: we each tell our stories and history of how we fell in love with Disney!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="http://www.thelostbros.com"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (http://www.thelostbros.com)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@lostbrostradingco.com (Oh Boy, The Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">85edd7990f4f44adad3cf42a2c4ffee0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/85edd7990f4f44adad3cf42a2c4ffee0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>The Expat Files: Living in Latin America : EXPAT FILES - 03.13.20</title><description>Descriptions- EXPAT FILES SHOW #937 FRI, MAR 13 (03-13-2020):
 
&lt;p&gt;JOHNNY’S EXPAT FILES WEBSITE PERMANENT NAME CHANGE ANNOUNCEMENT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My new website is &lt;a href='http://www.expatplanb.com/'&gt;www.ExpatPlanB.com&lt;/a&gt;. The previous sites have been hacked so please visit &lt;a href='http://www.expatplanb.com/'&gt;www.ExpatPlanB.com&lt;/a&gt; for announcements, upcoming seminar details and special reports.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#1- setting up the best and most economical Utra-HD camera security system- PART 4:&lt;/p&gt;
#2- The last word on H20 purification at your house or on the road:
Forget about buying bottled H20. It ain't really all that pure. You can continuously make your own almost unlimited quantity for about $10 a year. Today we discuss questions about my own portable and under-counter H2O purifiers as well as how to set them up and use them...
 
#3- How to remove fluoride, heavy metals and glyphosate (evil Monsanto’s Roundup) in your H20 supply:
A quick and simple H2O home filter hack that will insure complete removal of said toxins
 
#4- DYK that as of March 1st 2020, there are 1727 companies collecting your online data, your cloud storage, location and search preferences:
How to confuse those A-Holes and/or stop them in their tracks by using a VPN and a free anonymous search engine (like Startpage.com or DuckDuckGo). How to proceed anonymously and still get the results you’d expect from a regular google search.
 
#5- Wasp Nest and Bee Hive control:
Yes, here in Latin America you can expect they will build football sized cities both in around your house or apartment at certain times of the year- if you let them. So today we discuss how to safely manage and eliminate them... without too much stress and without getting stung   
 
 #6- Be sure to pick up my new and revised, "LATIN AMERICAN HEALTHCARE REPORT":
The new edition for 2020 (and beyond) is available now, including the latest "Stem Cell" info and data and my top picks for the best treatment centers for expats and gringos. Just go to &lt;a href='http://www.expatplanb.com/'&gt;www.ExpatPlanB.com&lt;/a&gt; and click on the "Latin American Healthcare Report”.</description><author>karalee@garynull.com (The Expat Files: Living in Latin America)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5df0d3dc39c24ff0bf3251338aa4e554</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5df0d3dc39c24ff0bf3251338aa4e554/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 06:49:55 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Happiest Podcast On Earth : 52 - Most Memorable Views Inside the Walt Disney World Resort</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We rank our favorite views located inside the Walt Disney World Resort and break down our Disney World trip from last week. We also announce the topic for this year's Happiest Podcast on Earth Bracket Challenge so you won't want to miss it!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>happiestpodcast@gmail.com (Happiest Podcast On Earth)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2fc6b6d870c049ec98fedfe2c4457104</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2fc6b6d870c049ec98fedfe2c4457104/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 05:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Living Adventurously : "If I could live my life over I'd have been braver in my 20s." Living Adventurously 21</title><description>Michaela Hanna has completed IronManUK, the Lakeland50 ultra mountain marathon, cycled from Edinburgh to London and across the Western Cape of South Africa. She therefore has personal experience of the significance of precise and relevant nutrition and places a high level of importance on the nutritional value of the food.&lt;br&gt;Having spent time working in fine-dining restaurants, high-end event catering companies and as a private chef alongside her day job, the time came for Michaela to follow her joy and feed people full-time again as a private chef. &lt;h1&gt;&lt;a href="https://livingadventurously.transistor.fm/subscribe"&gt;PLEASE SUBSCRIBE TO THE LIVING ADVENTUROUSLY PODCAST&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(It’s completely free, zero hassle to do (&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://livingadventurously.transistor.fm/subscribe"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;click here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;), but really helpful for me trying to get a new podcast off the ground. If you’re feeling extra kind, please leave a review on the app – that really helps.)&lt;/strong&gt;Listen on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/living-adventurously/id1489454694"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/2aYqIdvtVJkhIPklHaoXA3"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=486751&amp;amp;refid=stpr"&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://tunein.com/podcasts/Storytelling-Podcasts/Living-Adventurously-p1275719/"&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt; (“Alexa, please play the Living Adventurously podcast”) or on your favourite podcast platform such as Overcast, &lt;a href="https://podcasts.google.com/?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9mZWVkcy50cmFuc2lzdG9yLmZtL2xpdmluZy1hZHZlbnR1cm91c2x5"&gt;Google Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, Pocket Casts, &lt;a href="https://www.breaker.audio/living-adventurously"&gt;Breaker&lt;/a&gt;, Soundcloud, Castbox, Castro.&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.alastairhumphreys.com/podcast"&gt;www.alastairhumphreys.com/podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;SHOW NOTES&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you enjoy listening to this episode over a cup of coffee and think it might be worth the price, you can &lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;buy me a coffee here:&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;www. ko-fi.com/al_humphreys&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep up to date with future episodes (and my other adventures, projects and books) with my &lt;a href="https://www.alastairhumphreys.com/more/subscribe/"&gt;free monthly newsletter: alastairhumphreys.com/more/subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Say hello on &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Al_Humphreys"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/al_humphreys/"&gt;Instagram: @al_humphreys&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michaela Hanna - the &lt;a href="http://fitchefharrogate.co.uk/"&gt;Fit Chef&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adventure is embracing the unknown which is scary for me as I'm a bit of a control freak&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My preference is to do short, intense bursts of work and then get away for adventures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being restless and unsettled can be seen as a downside but it drives you forward and keeps you moving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I'm very purposeful and have to find meaning in everything. That can be exhausting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's a problem when nothing is enough and you're always striving for more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I remind myself grateful how lucky I am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working for myself means that for now I'm busy trying to get the money side of my life sorted&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I think it's easier to find a good balance when you're self-employed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I schedule in my free time otherwise it never happens&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the first months I lay in bed thinking 'what on earth have i done'&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's a bit scary but I'd far rather rather work for myself than work for a toxic organisation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always, always follow your joy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I've changed from a steady job, security, control freak to the risky freedom of what I'm doing now&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Put the intention out there, and it will follow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It takes bravery and I'm going to change everything and make this happen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There's no space for mediocrity in life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If I could live my life over I'd have been braver in my 20s. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I'd advise a woman in her 20s to not allow her decision making to be influenced by a relationship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To be truly happy you need to either have everything you want or nothing at all&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;THIS PODCAST IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY KOMOOT&lt;/h1&gt;Your very own outdoor experiences are waiting for you. Go explore more with &lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;komoot&lt;/a&gt;. Use the voucher code &lt;a href="https://www.komoot.com/account/gift/?code=ADVENTUROUS"&gt;ADVENTUROUS&lt;/a&gt; to claim your free region maps bundle.The personalised planning and navigation tools ensure you plan the adventure that’s perfect for &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;. Komoot is Europe’s number 1 outdoor app, with route planning and navigation functionality, and strong community-driven inspirational features in the form of recommended Highlights and inspirational route Collections. It is used by nearly 10 million adventurers worldwide. Komoot is becoming the app of choice for cyclists and hikers the world over, with rapid community growth in the UK, the US and other parts of Europe. &lt;br&gt;You can see my ride’s route on komoot &lt;a href="https://www.komoot.com/collection/900116/-living-adventurously-podcast-tour"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" title="★ Support this podcast by donating ★" href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;★ Support this podcast by donating ★&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>alastair@alastairhumphreys.com (Living Adventurously)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">277abe83a09a4288b9486bcc6936d135</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/277abe83a09a4288b9486bcc6936d135/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 22:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Retro Disney World Podcast : Ep 56 - Good Neighbors - Sea World</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Episode 56 of the RetroWDW Podcast: "Good Neighbors" - We appreciate your support and hope you have been enjoying each and every episode. Be sure to check out some of our previous shows!&lt;/p&gt;
Comments &amp; Corrections
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jake Nelson wrote in about a possible hidden skeleton somewhere inside Catastrophe Canyon. We give our take on this one from the old days of MGM.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reuben wrote us asking about the old shop to the left right inside the entrance to the Disney-MGM Studios. He is referring to Sid Cahuenga's of course! We discuss this store and the various items we have seen there over the years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Joe Barlow wrote in about some backlot vehicles, mainly the Hardcastle and McCormick car. We misidentified it as a Lamborghini, but Joe tells us it really is a kit car from back then.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;Listener Mail
&lt;p&gt;The mailbag is full and we love that! Every month, you can possibly get on the show, so be sure to write to us at &lt;a href='mailto:podcast@retrowdw.com'&gt;podcast@retrowdw.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tom Potter is our first letter and it is all about time capsules. Tom brings up the opening of Coronado Springs and how they placed a capsule back in 1997.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next up is Ron. He asks us about trucks being buried at the Magic Kingdom from way back during the late 60s construction. We hear about some trucks out in the lakes, but as far as the parks, we aren't really sure...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;John wrote us and has been a binge listener since August. He is curious about the EPCOT Center pavilion logos and who designed them and why. This is right in How's wheel-well and is super fun to learn about.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finally, we got a tweet from Michael, giving some major props on the upcoming &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/imageworks/restored-video/horizons-revisited-release-information-schedule/'&gt;Horizons release&lt;/a&gt; we have coming. Todd gives us the updates next...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;Audio Rewind
&lt;p&gt;Our audio rewind this month is El Rio del Tiempo - Thank you for all the guesses and emails!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a winner! Congratulations Jimmy Tucker!  - you won the book by Marty Sklar from Brian.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you think you know the answer to this month's audio rewind, email us! &lt;a href='mailto:contest@retrowdw.com'&gt;contest@retrowdw.com&lt;/a&gt; - This month, the winner will be getting &lt;a href='https://chrissmithbooks.com/'&gt;3 books from author Christopher Smith&lt;/a&gt; - All entries due 4/15/2020 and a random winner will be selected.&lt;/p&gt;
Main Topic
&lt;p&gt;This month, our main topic is Good Neighbors mostly focusing on Sea World. The early days of Lake Buena Vista had just one theme park so people needed more to do and more places to stay. A few years back, we discussed some of the good neighbor hotels and that program back on &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/podcast/podcast-episode-39-hotel-plaza-boulevard/'&gt;Episode 39&lt;/a&gt;. Brian leads us this month through some of the history and how Sea World got it's start. This includes California, Ohio and the other locations as this is all an important part of the story. We walk you through every attraction through the years with personal experiences and also lots of great memories. This includes things like the Dolphin Feeding Pool, original Whale and Dolphin Stadium, Fountain Fantasy, Water Skiing and so much more. The construction history is also discussed, which has changed quite a bit over the years.  This wouldn't be an episode of the RetroWDW Podcast without some food discussions. We take a deep-dive into the Hawaiian Punch Village along with some very detailed discussion about 'Hula Pie'. If you have ever been to Sea World since it opened, this episode will for sure take you back and also give you a look at how it has changed over the years. We hope you enjoy this look at one of our favorite 'Good Neighbors'.&lt;/p&gt;
2020: The Year of Film
&lt;p&gt;To make sure you are the first to know when items are released, &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/retrodisneyworld'&gt;subscribe to us on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;. Be sure to click the notification bell too, that way you are alerted when we post.  Finally, be sure to &lt;a href='https://vimeo.com/retrowdw'&gt;check out Vimeo&lt;/a&gt; if that is your thing, as we will post there as well. This past month we have posted a &lt;a href='https://youtu.be/Doq1KZ8c2s4'&gt;great resort tour from The Disney Channel&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href='https://youtu.be/lkQ26o1ZEo4'&gt;The original DVC Resort Tour&lt;/a&gt;, and a &lt;a href='https://youtu.be/r67HKQ0rnYw'&gt;great Innoventions commercial&lt;/a&gt; from the mid-90s. As a bonus, to accompany this episode &lt;a href='https://youtu.be/O_dfZA_vGYM'&gt;we have released a great new video from 1980 Sea World&lt;/a&gt;. This was shot on Super8 with sound! You are going to love this vintage footage that looks amazing - especially the Whale &amp; Dolphin show.&lt;/p&gt;
Next Month
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Join us next time for Episode 57, which we have not fully planned out, but you won't want to miss it  Thanks for joining us! &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>podcast@retrowdw.com (Retro Disney World Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cc61f2293bd84f44be3f44b0bc889592</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cc61f2293bd84f44be3f44b0bc889592/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 19:45:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind The Glass : 25-year-old Owns London's Coolest Car Dealership</title><description>&lt;p&gt;[Bonus Episode] I meet up with Merlin McCormack who founded London car dealership, Duke of London, in 2014 at the ago of 20.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year he moved the business into a new location in West London and I finally got the chance to visit a few weeks ago and grab the main man for a quick interview.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can follow Merlin here:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://www.instagram.com/duke_of_london/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enjoy&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>info@seenthroughglass.com (Behind The Glass)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fb16331e4dc84d09979663782a953fea</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fb16331e4dc84d09979663782a953fea/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 11:46:55 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Solo Travel Talk with Astrid : Managing Travel Letdowns | Hassle-Free Travel Expectations</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Don’t let unmet expectations steal your travel joy! If you have ever felt disappointment about a destination or a travel sight, this is the Solo Travel Talk podcast episode for you! If you find yourself saying, “That wasn’t worth it” Astrid Clements, your solo travel advisor, has some tips and coaching for you can have a positive travel mindset and manage your expectations no matter what your travel experience. Astrid has a lot of experience turning so-so experiences into winning trips. Get past over-hyped sights and supposed “must-dos” that don’t deliver and get into serendipity, openness, and hassle-free happy expectations.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Mentioned on the show:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- &lt;a href="https://www.astridtravel.com/club"&gt;The AstridTravel Club&lt;/a&gt;: a place for those who want to experience affordable luxury travel or want to go solo that’s not totally solo. &lt;a href= "https://www.astridtravel.com/club"&gt;The AstridTravel Club is the sponsor of the Hassle-Free Travel Series&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- Astrid recommends &lt;a href= "https://www.atlasobscura.com/"&gt;Atlas Obscura&lt;/a&gt; for wonderful “small gem” or off the beaten path travel experiences.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- &lt;a href="https://wikitravel.org/en/Main_Page"&gt;Wikitravel&lt;/a&gt; has lots of travel info that is not overly common or run of the mill.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Some of the questions answered on this episode…&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;What to do if I am not enjoying my trip?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Are most famous travel destinations over-hyped?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;How can I find lesser-known travel destinations?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;How can I have more serendipity in my travel?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What is overtourism?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What is The AstridTravel Club and how do I join?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;We love sharing the most innovative and informative content to get you out there solo. Astrid, your expert Solo Travel Advisor-- has &lt;a href="https://www.astridtravel.com/resources"&gt;a whole section of resources for solo travelers&lt;/a&gt; on her website, &lt;a href="http://astridtravel.com/"&gt;AstridTravel.com&lt;/a&gt;. Follow Astrid on &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/astridtravel/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/AstridTravel"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/astrid.travel/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;. You can subscribe to the podcast on &lt;a href= "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/solo-travel-talk-with-astrid/id1200131350?ign-mpt=uo%3D4&amp;ls=1"&gt; Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/show/350imnwgGxfYyfCIbdv0a9"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "http://www.stitcher.com/podcast/astrid-clements/solo-travel-talk?refid=stpr"&gt; Stitcher&lt;/a&gt;, or with your favorite podcast app. Just go solo!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@astridtravel.com (Solo Travel Talk with Astrid)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ded15e96fca64a019c57407f7cc002a3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ded15e96fca64a019c57407f7cc002a3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 06:36:40 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>The Biscuit CLT Podcast : CMCLT Rewind: Winston Robinson</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It's hard to find someone who is more fiercely proud of being a native Charlottean than Winston Robinson. So much so, that Robinson's nickname of "Wilmo" is inspired by his native neighborhood of Wilmore. That, combined with the work that he's doing as former president of the Lockwood Neighborhood Association, through A Vibe Called Fresh, an annual food and music festival open to all residents, as well as founding an LLC, The Applesauce Group, to support it all.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In today's episode of the The Biscuit CLT Podcast - CMCLT Rewind, hosts Tim Miner and Matt Olin talk to Winston immediately following his talk at the March Creative Mornings event at Divine Barrel Brewing. Tune in now to hear Winston speak about what being a native Charlottean means to him, what he wanted to convey when speaking about codeswitching in his CMCLT speech, and his thoughts on the current state of The Excelsior Club.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tim@charlotteiscreative.com (The Biscuit CLT Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6ff1c8da03fc4836bef0af06d71d86ff</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6ff1c8da03fc4836bef0af06d71d86ff/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 05:15:45 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>The olive magazine podcast : ep 191 - An expert guide to New York's vibrant bakery scene</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week Janine catches up with olive regular Edd Kimber (AKA @theboywhobakes) to talk about the New York bakery scene. Edd has spent a long time researching and visiting these neighbourhood bakeries in his quest for recipe inspiration and we hear all about the different specialities of each, from stripy colourful croissants to deep-fried crullers.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts@immediate.co.uk (The olive magazine podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">622e1bf770bf41678a13de84fa6023d7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/622e1bf770bf41678a13de84fa6023d7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 05:00:35 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>The Tropical MBA Podcast - Entrepreneurship, Travel, and Lifestyle : TMBA536: Are You Really "Unemployable"?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;#39;s episode, we are reaching into the TMBA mailbag yet again and responding to some interesting questions and comments we&amp;#39;ve received from our listeners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a word that gets tossed around in the entrepreneurial community, and it&amp;#39;s actually something that is worn as a sort of badge of honor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We see it on t-shirts and social media, and it&amp;#39;s usually represented by entrepreneurs who have rejected working for an employer at a job where they held no equity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But is it really a good thing to be &amp;quot;Unemployable?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#39;ll hear our thoughts about that on today&amp;#39;s episode, as well as some insight for people who have become frustrated by meet-ups and networking events that aren&amp;#39;t providing enough value.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Dan@TropicalMBA.com (The Tropical MBA Podcast - Entrepreneurship, Travel, and Lifestyle)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a5f07b4b0f584662bbc9f4a396155579</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a5f07b4b0f584662bbc9f4a396155579/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 05:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>WDWNT ParksCenter : ParksCenter - March Madness 2020 Preview! - Ep. 92</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This is ParksCenter. We cover the top news stories from this week in Disney Parks news in 30 minutes. Join us this week as we talk about what’s coming up in WDWNT’s March Madness bracket. This year, we’ll be ranking 64 ideas for the theme parks that never quite came to be… so come learn […]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://wdwnt.com/2020/03/watch-parkscenter-92/"&gt;ParksCenter – March Madness 2020 Preview! – Ep. 92&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://wdwnt.com"&gt;WDW News Today&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>developer@wdwnt.com (WDWNT ParksCenter)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">639df314dad14d828b16d7d1a3cc58a9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/639df314dad14d828b16d7d1a3cc58a9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 04:00:18 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Kentuckiana Sounds : Where is That Hum Coming From?</title><description>While walking down 6th St., Kentuckiana Sounds curator Aaron Rosenblum found himself enveloped in a droning, omnipresent hum reverberating among the buildings on the block. Was it coming from an HVAC system? Or from the service vehicles parked nearby with giant tubes protruding from their trailers? Or from somewhere else entirely? To hear the full recording, explore the sound map, or submit a sound visit www.wfpl.org/sounds or www.kentuckianasounds.org.</description><author>support@louisvillepublicmedia.org (Kentuckiana Sounds)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">21aafcc6a4174b88859993905baf481f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/21aafcc6a4174b88859993905baf481f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 03:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Gal Pal Show: Solo female travel, backpacking, bucket list inspiration, planning a trip, female travel advice and tips, and off the beaten track ideas. : 97: Inspirational Women; Jo Moore's travel adventure</title><description>&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;Have you always wanted to travel, but felt like "it's not for someone like me"? This is exactly how I felt before I decided to go travelling solo around the world...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;This was me. I have now travelled to over 31 countries across 4 continents and started a business and a highly successful podcast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;Listen to today's story all about my story&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;You also have the free&lt;a href='http://galpalacademy.com/jet-popup/travel-planning-worksheet/'&gt; Travel planning worksheet here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://galpalacademy.thinkific.com/courses/travel-planning-bootcamp-1'&gt;Want to go travelling?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://galpalacademy.thinkific.com/courses/travel-planning-bootcamp-1'&gt;Join Gal Pal Travel Planning Bootcamp here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jo@galpalacademy.com (Gal Pal Show: Solo female travel, backpacking, bucket list inspiration, planning a trip, female travel advice and tips, and off the beaten track ideas.)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5da9cb4353264e4a8eb3c128bdf34cce</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5da9cb4353264e4a8eb3c128bdf34cce/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 22:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Monsters Among Us Podcast : Sn. 9 Ep. 2 - Lizardman, aliens, ghosts and a burned up bigfoot.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;LA Lizard City -   &lt;a href= "http://www.reptoids.com/Vault/Schufeltsearch.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.reptoids.com/Vault/Schufeltsearch.htm&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1584025406060000&amp;usg=AFQjCNEUOHE8n-MJtbaXYcP9IUjQz35cHA"&gt;http://www.reptoids.com/Vault/Schufeltsearch.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; Blurry Photos Podcast - &lt;a href= "http://www.blurryphotos.org/"&gt;http://www.blurryphotos.org/&lt;/a&gt; Kickstarter Campaign - &lt;a href= "https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/blurrymonstersmedia/shadows-in-the-desert?fbclid=IwAR2YkDQ97NQerSuIvcYpVk7r3M7wXSgrlKDl2UAUGBUKOolMtmgVJxVFGBA"&gt; https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/blurrymonstersmedia/shadows-in-the-desert?fbclid=IwAR2YkDQ97NQerSuIvcYpVk7r3M7wXSgrlKDl2UAUGBUKOolMtmgVJxVFGBA&lt;/a&gt; Monsters And Myteries Episode - &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8AGn3vJq28o" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3D8AGn3vJq28o&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1584025406060000&amp;usg=AFQjCNF3ON9vrOv2oxqwVz_LVC2yL2-dKg"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8AGn3vJq28o&lt;/a&gt; Lizard People Article -  &lt;a href= "https://documents.latimes.com/jan-29-1934-lizard-people/" target= "_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://documents.latimes.com/jan-29-1934-lizard-people/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1584039985592000&amp;usg=AFQjCNFLBCWyZ6Ie06IharLeB3KLmQxfRQ"&gt;https://documents.latimes.com/jan-29-1934-lizard-people/&lt;/a&gt; Fire in the Sky - &lt;a href= "https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0106912/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0106912/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1584025406060000&amp;usg=AFQjCNEkrFZcMJm_5Avi5zK5sLjD4RreAw"&gt;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0106912/&lt;/a&gt; bear paws - &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/VUSxQMN" target= "_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://imgur.com/VUSxQMN&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1584025406060000&amp;usg=AFQjCNHmtiuHXbPvVQ_qP8ki2SuhxCgS3g"&gt;https://imgur.com/VUSxQMN&lt;/a&gt; Lightning Info - &lt;a href= "https://www.windpowerengineering.com/how-much-power-in-a-bolt-of-lightning/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.windpowerengineering.com/how-much-power-in-a-bolt-of-lightning/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1584025406060000&amp;usg=AFQjCNHOkfzjyhDHNXbMfkYVu2wotdTTiA"&gt;https://www.windpowerengineering.com/how-much-power-in-a-bolt-of-lightning/&lt;/a&gt; Coyote Mythology - &lt;a href= "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coyote_(mythology)" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coyote_(mythology)&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1584025406060000&amp;usg=AFQjCNH0VwXkdC4AmoQ40dWJxsyFURgq6Q"&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coyote_(mythology)&lt;/a&gt; Coyoteman Phantoms &amp; Monsters - &lt;a href= "https://www.phantomsandmonsters.com/2018/11/eyewitness-bizarre-coyote-shapeshifts.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.phantomsandmonsters.com/2018/11/eyewitness-bizarre-coyote-shapeshifts.html&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1584025406060000&amp;usg=AFQjCNHWLfkkfqvr-QFBeE57YFtp8zYSyg"&gt;https://www.phantomsandmonsters.com/2018/11/eyewitness-bizarre-coyote-shapeshifts.html&lt;/a&gt; Coyoteman Beyond Creepy - &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UPSyanoOa_c" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3DUPSyanoOa_c&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1584025406060000&amp;usg=AFQjCNEI3oA770k1d7L-H9lYVBdK9xvdYQ"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UPSyanoOa_c&lt;/a&gt; Battle Mountain Story -  &lt;a href= "http://bigfootevidence.blogspot.com/2011/07/bigfoot-injured-by-forest-fire-was.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=http://bigfootevidence.blogspot.com/2011/07/bigfoot-injured-by-forest-fire-was.html&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1584025406060000&amp;usg=AFQjCNG7kDOJxIP-wg3P2QfftUNGLFpZBw"&gt;http://bigfootevidence.blogspot.com/2011/07/bigfoot-injured-by-forest-fire-was.html&lt;/a&gt; Battle Mountain Fire Report - &lt;a href= "https://www.predictiveservices.nifc.gov/IMSR/1999/19990808IMSR.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.predictiveservices.nifc.gov/IMSR/1999/19990808IMSR.pdf&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1584025406060000&amp;usg=AFQjCNFT-xg630emhhhaAcyYS1KuhxZU8Q"&gt;https://www.predictiveservices.nifc.gov/IMSR/1999/19990808IMSR.pdf&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>monstersamonguspodcast@gmail.com (Monsters Among Us Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f08d5f60684d4713b75e8da6a6391683</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f08d5f60684d4713b75e8da6a6391683/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 21:29:18 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>The Offbeat Life - become location independent : Extended: how to make long term travel more sustainable with remote work.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this episode, Amanda and Ryan discuss how to find different ways to supplement your income, how moving to one specific place can help you extend your travel, why it is cheaper to move abroad and much more!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "http://%20https//www.theoffbeatlife.com/episodes/travel-podcasters/"&gt; GET THE FULL INTERVIEW WITH AMANDA AND RYAN WHERE THEY SHARE HOW THEY ARE ABLE TO ENCOURAGE OTHERS TO SEE THE WORLD AS TRAVEL PODCASTERS.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@theoffbeatlife.com (The Offbeat Life - become location independent)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d3cea0c76963408ebcaa10cddbb5205f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d3cea0c76963408ebcaa10cddbb5205f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 21:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hoosier Outdoorsmen Podcast : Episode 41 Talking to Justin Salsman of Iron Pheonix Forge about Blacksmithing and the IBA</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this Episode I talk to Blacksmith Justin Salsman of Iron Pheonix Forge about Blacksmithing and the IBA. Justin talks about how he got into blacksmithing. He also talks about some of his Mentors and the importance of getting involved with the IBA if you are interested in blacksmithing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Rileyhendrixson@live.com (The Hoosier Outdoorsmen Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8b6170786a344e88a370d7bc48f8538e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8b6170786a344e88a370d7bc48f8538e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 19:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>San Francisco Real Estate: Escrow Out Loud : Meet our Mystery Guest</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In today’s episode of &lt;a href="https://jacksonfuller.com/insight/podcast/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Escrow Out Loud, our San Francisco Real Estate podcast&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;u&gt;,&lt;/u&gt; we talk to a special guest star, who has been solidly attached to the San Francisco scene since the 1970s; can you guess who they are?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[00:40] This is the first ever podcast our guest has ever been on. She is more used to 8-track tapes and cassette tapes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[01:01] Our guest is perfectly proportioned; with a sunny outlook and open with her plan. Did Lizzo dedicate a song to her?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[01:53] One of the things that make her unique is her phenomenal outlook on nature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[03:03] Is our guest trying to meet someone? A serial monogamist, she’s feeling a little empty lately. Sometimes it feels like she is tucked away, but really she’s perched above a canyon in the heart of everything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[04:12] Our guest has a plan. Its open. It features a recently updated kitchen which just flows to the casual/formal dining. Vaulted ceilings, lots of light, and even a fireplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[05:45] Let's play a three question game for the listeners who still need a couple more clues to figure out who our guests is!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[06:49] Our guests facade seems modern and recently updated. How much work has been done on her, exactly?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[07:24] Her number is 495292, so put those digits in the San Francisco MLS or your favourite real estate app. She is open on Sundays or by an appointment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[07:55] With a lovely perspective both eastern and western, she can feel a little insulated from outside noise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[08:31] How can we find our guest and learn more? 82 Malta Drive is the address, you can find her online at homeonmalta.com to see her photo album.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for listening. If you enjoyed this episode, leave us a review on your favorite platform, tell your friends and don’t forget to join us again next week!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href='https://acast.com/privacy'&gt;Acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>info+5ab02d3b627e02027cf8604d@mg.pippa.io (San Francisco Real Estate: Escrow Out Loud)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ed6d3a783306486ab4468f5e04f24c62</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ed6d3a783306486ab4468f5e04f24c62/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 11:05:45 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Disneyland With Kids Podcast : Spring at Disneyland 2020 (Podcast)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Spring is a great time to visit the Disneyland Resort. What special offerings can you expect during Spring 2020? What is new at Disneyland Resort, and how is Rise of the Resistance impacting how you should plan for your Spring vacation?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; In This Episode - Planning for Spring 2020 at Disneyland &lt;p&gt;In this episode, all 4 co-hosts, and founders of the Disneyland with Kids community are sharing about Spring at Disneyland in 2020. Fresh off a trip where all 4 of us were able to attend the Disney California Adventure Food and Wine Festival, view Magic Happens and more! This episode is perfect for those that are hoping to go to &lt;a href= "https://thiscrazyadventurecalledlife.com/spring-break-at-disneyland/"&gt; Disneyland for Spring Break&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Before we get into the show notes... did you see that there is a ticket special going on for Spring 2020? This is the perfect way to enjoy &lt;a href= "https://tripswithtykes.com/disneyland-food-wine-festival/"&gt;Disney California Food and Wine Festival,&lt;/a&gt; Magic Happens and more while saving money. SoCal Residents and all kids ages 3-9 (even if not SoCal Residents) can &lt;a href= "https://www.getawaytoday.com/kids-spring-sale/?referrerid=6233"&gt;save big on 3 day tickets this spring&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you are hoping to head to Disneyland for Food and Wine Festival, we suggest booking these special rates, and other ticket options through our partners at &lt;a href= "https://www.getawaytoday.com/?referrerid=7526"&gt;Get Away Today .&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They have discounted tickets, free hotel nights and more. Be sure to use code DisneyKids when booking a hotel stay of 2 or more nights to save even more!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this episode we cover:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;When is Spring at Disneyland?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The all new &lt;a href= "https://thehappiestblogonearth.com/magic-happens-disneyland-parade/"&gt; Magic Happens Parade&lt;/a&gt;! Where to view, is it worth staking out a spot for and more!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Disney California Adventure Food and Wine Festival: What's new, what kids will love, and the new emphasis on family.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What fireworks show can you see during &lt;a href= "https://www.momrewritten.com/springtime-roundup-at-disneyland/"&gt;Spring 2020&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;How will Rise of the Resistance affect your Spring Break at Disneyland? A lot! Find out our best strategies whether you plan to ride or not.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Are you visiting Disneyland during Disney California Adventure Food and Wine Festival? What are you most looking forward to?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Plan Your Disneyland Vacation:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you want to book a Disneyland vacation we suggest &lt;a title="Get Away Today" href= "https://www.getawaytoday.com/?referrerid=7526" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;booking through our partners at Get Away Today&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Want to connect with other Disneyland with Kids community members, receive and share tips, and more? &lt;a title="DwK Group" href= "https://facebook.com/groups/disneylandwithkids" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Join the Disneyland with Kids Group on Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect With The Hosts:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can connect with the hosts of Disneyland with Kids at the following locations:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leslie - &lt;a href= "https://tripswithtykes.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Trips with Tykes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Leslie on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Julie - &lt;a href= "https://momrewritten.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Mom Rewritten&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Julie on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/momrewritten"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/momrewritten" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/momrewritten" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Becca - &lt;a href= "https://thiscrazyadventurecalledlife.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;This Crazy Adventure Called Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Becca on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/crazyadventurecalledlife" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/thebeccarobins" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/thebeccarobins" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Jessica - &lt;a href= "https://thehappiestblogonearth.com"&gt;The Happiest Blog On Earth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Jessica on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>becca@disneylandwithkids.info (Disneyland With Kids Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4b8ac70b98c447758df815e62f918a1b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4b8ac70b98c447758df815e62f918a1b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 09:27:14 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>CruiseTipsTV Unplugged - Cruise Tips and More : Cruise Question and Answer Session Pt. 2</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode we'll be continuing our cruise question and answer session. We'll answer everything from what makes a good upgrade deal, to how we balance filming and relaxing on a cruise and much more.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As always, you can email us your questions at  sheri@cruisetipstv.com. We'd also LOVE if you'd leave a review where you listen to this podcast, and screen shot the show and share it on Instagram using the hashtag #cttvunplugged. Download our shore day bag checklist, and more cruise packing and planning checklists &amp; videos by joining the CruiseTipsTV Academy. We have a special discount code for our podcast listeners. To redeem the $5.00 discount on our master class enter code UNPLUGGED at http://academy.cruisetipstv.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@cruisetipstv.com (CruiseTipsTV Unplugged - Cruise Tips and More)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">23cb86558a8b470e9df20d767b35706a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/23cb86558a8b470e9df20d767b35706a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 06:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Have Camper Will Travel : Passion Builds, Potty Talk, Branding + *almost* Everything In Between w/ Leah Young</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Freedom to pack up and leave whenever we want? Where do we sign? Leah Young from &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/the_ramblr_rv/"&gt;&lt;u&gt;@the_ramblr_rv&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; joins us today as a guest to chat passion builds, potty talk, branding + pretty much everything in between. Leah + Brennan are stationary in the Sunshine State, but have the luxury of traveling whenever they want. Today she’s sharing her unique perspective, RV essentials, DIY Tips and so much more! If you like today’s episode, please subscribe and follow us over on &lt;a href="http://instagram.com/hcwtpodcast"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Instagram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href="twitter.com/hcwtpodcast"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/havecamperwilltravel/message</description><author>podcasts44+529f5e0@anchor.fm (Have Camper Will Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6e1067a46a1e418481006154e0875213</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6e1067a46a1e418481006154e0875213/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 05:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>The Disney Cruise Line Show : #010 - Disney Cruise Line's Disney Dream Review</title><description>03/11/20 - In this episode, Pete, Sean, and Deni give a mini review of their recent sailing on the Disney Dream out of Port Canaveral to the Bahamas, specifically mentioning embarkation, dining in the main dining rooms, entertainment, and disembarkation!</description><author>craig@disneyinfo.com (The Disney Cruise Line Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5f9c09ff90614abf9e3b319a7bf4fa27</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5f9c09ff90614abf9e3b319a7bf4fa27/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 01:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>La Lido Loca Cruise Podcast : 12. MSC Divina Review</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to episode #12 of the La Lido Loca podcast.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Join Jenny and Tony as they talk about cruising!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show Notes:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on YouTube:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;La Lido Loca Podcast: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCLoGEyIWH6f6mkJxDCweDag"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCLoGEyIWH6f6mkJxDCweDag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;La Lido Loca Cruising: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqFivW2VWJtGfvrMreyjNbw"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqFivW2VWJtGfvrMreyjNbw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Let Jenny help with your travel, you can contact her at: &lt;a href= "mailto:jbarnette@cruiseshipcenters.com"&gt;jbarnette@cruiseshipcenters.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Info about La Lido Loca Group Cruises: &lt;a href="http://www.lalidoloca.com/groupcruise" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;http://www.lalidoloca.com/groupcruise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on Social Media: Facebook Page - &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt; Instagram - &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt; Twitter - &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/lalidoloca" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://twitter.com/lalidoloca&lt;/a&gt; Pintrest - &lt;a href="https://www.pinterest.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.pinterest.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Represent the locafam with a t-shirt, check out the latest designs at: &lt;a href="https://teespring.com/stores/lalidoloca-funshop" target= "_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://teespring.com/stores/lalidoloca-funshop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our mailing address is: La Lido Loca 4142 Mariner Blvd #402 Spring Hill, FL 34609&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Support our creative efforts at Patreon: &lt;a href="http://www.patreon.com/lalidoloca" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;http://www.patreon.com/lalidoloca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Please Submit Questions or Comments to &lt;a href= "mailto:tony@lalidoloca.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;tony@lalidoloca.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tony@lalidoloca.com (La Lido Loca Cruise Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">388ebefd596a40d3a671071e465a6b56</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/388ebefd596a40d3a671071e465a6b56/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 13:33:29 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>The Overland Journal Podcast : The Real Indiana Jones - Bryon Bass, PhD</title><description>The detailed show notes are available here: &lt;a href="https://overlandjournal.com/dr-bryon-bass/"&gt;https://overlandjournal.com/dr-bryon-bass/&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>scott@overlandinternational.com (The Overland Journal Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1c2a3a9d19a44efbad34ca10095986c4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1c2a3a9d19a44efbad34ca10095986c4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Well-Traveled with AAA : Vienna, Austria</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Correspondent, Samantha Brown takes us to Vienna for a preview of the sights, culture, and tastes that await you in one of Europe’s greenest and most walkable cities. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sonixcursions@gmail.com (Well-Traveled with AAA)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d5004fd8cc6f4abeb295763331b00862</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d5004fd8cc6f4abeb295763331b00862/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 05:04:27 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Travel Like a Boss Podcast : Ep 243 - Backpacker Tal</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Tal Braimam is a freelancer and a digital marketing strategist at Support Adventure, an expat outsourcing company. He studied Blockchain at Lassonde School of Engineering and Entrepreneurship at Ted Rogers School of Management – Ryerson University.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;During this episode, Tal shares his career transition from being a backpacker who had carefree travels around the globe to a digital nomad who manages IT support for businesses. He reveals some interesting ideas on how to start your to travel journey, especially for young individuals. Tal inspires us to keep opening the doors of opportunities while reaching for the peak of your dreams.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Links:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Tal's IG - &lt;a href= "http://instagram.com/backpackertal"&gt;Instagram.com/BackpackerTal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Johnny FD's IG - &lt;a href= "http://instagram.com/johnnyfdk"&gt;Instagram.com/JohnnyFDK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Remote Jobs - &lt;a href= "https://www.supportadventure.com/"&gt;SupportAdventure.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Coronavirus Blog Post - &lt;a href= "https://www.johnnyfd.com/2020/03/coronavirus-thoughts-and-travel-plans.html"&gt; Coronavirus Thoughts and Travel Plans as a Digital Nomad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Sponsor:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Nomad Summit - &lt;a href= "http://nomadsummit.com"&gt;NomadSummit.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Time Stamps:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;2:10 – How Johnny created a community in Sri Lanka&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;6:55 – Tal’s exotic journey to the country&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;8:10 – “That was my inspiration, to go and see a bit of Sri Lanka before I settle for a place for a month and be productive” – Tal Braimam&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;10:18 – Tal’s journey to becoming a backpacker&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;14:30 – Knowing the beauty of collecting experience by travel&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;19:01 – “There is still too much to appreciate that I don’t think it’s the right mindset to kind of lookout what I don’t have when there’s so much in front of me that I have and I can appreciate” – Tal Braimam&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;21:00 – Backpackers’ life in Chiang Mai&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;26:55 – Advantages of hiring digital nomads over traditional employees&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;34:24 – The depth of his cultural fusion&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;40:06 – How economic bubble changes the story of the lives of digital nomads&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;44:34 – Finding better and cheaper ways to book an airline ticket&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;47:00 – How fear from virus outbreak will shut down travel opportunities&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;1:00:27 – What it is like to live as a nomad in different places&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;1:02:40 – “Keep your dream alive and do what you can to do your lifestyle because it’s possible” – Tal Braimam&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Enjoyed this episode? Share it with friends!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>johnny@travellikeabosspodcast.com (Travel Like a Boss Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c652925a21dd4ecbb3ed4d4c1a471d50</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c652925a21dd4ecbb3ed4d4c1a471d50/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 03:57:03 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>A Way To Go : Understanding How Coronavirus Travels, with Dr. Jenn Haythe</title><description>&lt;p&gt;How does the coronavirus affect travel? We're still in the early days of the COVID-19 epidemic, and many of us are asking ourselves the same questions: Is it safe to travel now? Will it be safe in the future? Am I staying home forever? These are issues best answered with rational thought and critical analysis, not fear and panic. So we turned to Dr. Jennifer Haythe of Columbia University Medical Center for expert advice. In this episode, she explains how viruses travel and offers tips for staying safe and healthy — right now and always — when traveling. Find links to the resources mentioned in this episode, along with Dr. Jenn’s go-to, must-have travel kit, in the show notes at &lt;a href="https://urldefense.proofpoint.com/v2/url?u=http-3A__Fathomaway.com&amp;amp;d=DwMFaQ&amp;amp;c=GC0NZZhaEw6GOQSjMHI2g15k_drElRoPmOYiK2k0eZ8&amp;amp;r=QQqtrehlQRY19SGPJ2205twNczy34pobDq7ZUMRMscQ&amp;amp;m=PNKKeIUyCoU0QUkFwQKDs7EE2Ob_lRZyOuCD0IiM08E&amp;amp;s=xTcuJQeaO1L-9Sll_eQmO8TY6IsFu6DTdD3-X-Hsd0U&amp;amp;e="&gt;Fathomaway.com&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (A Way To Go)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7e468934389e4c44a1542174dafd38c0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7e468934389e4c44a1542174dafd38c0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 03:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Dreams Unlimited Travel Show - A Weekly Discussion About Travel and Dreams Unlimited Travel : #175 - Top 5 Money Savings Tips for a Walt Disney World Vacation - Tracey Heinrichs</title><description>03/10/20 - In this episode, Dreams Unlimited Travel agent consultant Tracey Heinrichs shares her personal top five tips to help you save money for your Walt Disney World Vacation!</description><author>craig@wdwinfo.com (Dreams Unlimited Travel Show - A Weekly Discussion About Travel and Dreams Unlimited Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0f97374349b54d0ead50c846ea729cf7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0f97374349b54d0ead50c846ea729cf7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 01:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Puerto Vallarta Travel  Show Podcast : Bonito Kitchen and Ramen Ya Restaurants in Puerto Vallarta, Mexico</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Bonito Kitchen and Bar and Ramen Ya Restaurants serve delicious Asian dishes in Puerto Vallarta, Mexico. We talk with the owner Francie Nguyen about her restaurants including the newest one, Bonito Cafe.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>pvtravelshow@gmail.com (Puerto Vallarta Travel  Show Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7e1564662cc84a2385d2c59e93b0ed43</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7e1564662cc84a2385d2c59e93b0ed43/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:25:10 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>The Thoughtful Travel Podcast : 178 Interesting Plane Passengers Sitting Next to You</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Oftentimes you can't choose the passenger sitting next to you on a plane. This can be both good and bad! Episode 178 of The Thoughtful Travel Podcast includes conversations with three different guests who all have interesting tales to tell of someone they sat next to on a flight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First up, Paul Pichugin tells the hilarious tale of ... well, a woman passenger next to him, and I don't want to give the story away - you'll have to listen to it! Excuse my raucous laughter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, I chat with Laura Waters who broke the golden rule of avoiding conversation on a long haul flight - in case you get stuck talking with someone you don't want to talk to for the next ten hours - and it turned into something quite delightful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, I talk to Dale Neill about a particularly intriguing passenger he sat next to on a flight across Australia some years back. Let's just say there was a lot of chocolate milk involved!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paul Pichugin - landscape and travel photographer - &lt;a href="https://paulpichugin.com"&gt;https://paulpichugin.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Laura Waters' website -&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://soultrekkers.com.au/"&gt;https://soultrekkers.com.au/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Laura&amp;rsquo;s book Bewildered -&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2S20zu2"&gt;https://amzn.to/2S20zu2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dale Neill - &lt;a href="http://www.daleneill.com.au"&gt;http://www.daleneill.com.au&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join our Facebook group for Thoughtful Travellers -&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/thoughtfultravellers"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/thoughtfultravellers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show notes: &lt;a href="http://notaballerina.com/178"&gt;https://notaballerina.com/178&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>amandakendle@me.com (The Thoughtful Travel Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">af38db3c35e242749fcd291696f51244</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/af38db3c35e242749fcd291696f51244/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>DCL Podcast : REBROADCAST: 024 Meyer Werft Builder of Disney Ships</title><author>sekriese@comcast.net (DCL Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b16d8dd2fab74dfabfafbb0c10d56fea</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b16d8dd2fab74dfabfafbb0c10d56fea/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 13:31:21 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Travel Eat Explore Podcast : The Sailing Family</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On this episode I am joined by Seth Hynes and his wife, who along with their three kids are The Sailing Family.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Find all their videos on YouTube.com at:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Youtube.com/c/Thesailingfamily&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;More about the family from their Youtube.com channel:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;"We are a family of five sailing around the world on our "dream boat," a performance catamaran named "Archer." Ten years ago, before kids, we sailed a Lagoon 380 named "Honeymoon" halfway around the world from the East Coast of the US to Australia. Along the way we shared our experiences with family and friends via YouTube, and by happenstance created the first "sailing channel." But more than anything, we realized what an incredible experience that first trip was and that someday we wanted to do it again, only this time with our kids. We want to share with them the importance of taking time to be with family. To show them a world outside of the one they grew up in. We want them to appreciate how lucky we are to experience (and to care for) the natural beauty of this world. But mostly we want to spend time with our kids during these formative years and create lasting memories as a family. That's why we are "The Sailing Family."&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ayb@benikovlaw.com (Travel Eat Explore Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b1a5a95e70a7415b9aa8d186d8f822ad</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b1a5a95e70a7415b9aa8d186d8f822ad/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 03:30:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dish Food Travel Show : 52 Lithuanian I: What To Eat. Food History &amp; Potato Fever (inc. Cepelinais)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In This Episode:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A brief history of Lithuania &amp; its culinary landscape&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lithuanian potato culture - from fear to obsession&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plus, some essential potato dishes to eat in Lithuania&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;More info and the full list of dishes at &lt;a href='https://foodfuntravel.com/lithuaniapodcast/'&gt;https://foodfuntravel.com/lithuaniapodcast/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>megsy@foodfuntravel.com (The Dish Food Travel Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9ef0747c55bb48bc971150e88a57c0c3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9ef0747c55bb48bc971150e88a57c0c3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 02:32:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>The Disney Vacation Club Show : #055 - How Are Riviera Sales Going?</title><description>03/09/20 - In this episode, the panel discusses how Disney's Riviera Resort sales are going based on a thread on DISBoards.com!</description><author>craig@disneyinfo.com (The Disney Vacation Club Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f6a27c10a8584e22b75faad4d821435e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f6a27c10a8584e22b75faad4d821435e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 01:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Hammer Lane Legends : 3: Plane Crashes Across Road</title><description>&lt;div&gt;In episode 3, "Plane Crashes Across Road" we talk to Tom about how he got into trucking and some of these things he has seen from the road! He shares about seeing strange lights in the sky, kids dressed in all black coming out of the woods, a plane crashing right in front of his rig and more! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EMAIL US YOUR STORIES&lt;/strong&gt;: HammerLaneLegends@gmail.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Website&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.hammerlanelegends.com/"&gt;www.hammerlanelegends.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Facebook&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/hammerlanelegends"&gt;www.facebook.com/hammerlanelegends&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Instagram Desktop&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/hammerlanelegends"&gt;www.instagram.com/hammerlanelegends&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instagram Mobile: &lt;/strong&gt;@hammerlanelegends&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Twitter Desktop:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/HLLPodcast"&gt;www.twitter.com/HLLPodcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Twitter Mobile:&lt;/strong&gt; @HLLpodcast&lt;/div&gt;</description><author>hammerlanelegends@gmail.com (Hammer Lane Legends)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9395a98d1e674d6ab203dd7d0b9f02d1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9395a98d1e674d6ab203dd7d0b9f02d1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 21:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Join Us in France Travel Podcast : Tours Make a Vacation Better, Episode 274</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In today's episode of the podcast, Annie and Elyse wonder how tours make a vacation better. Won't you have a great time in Paris or anywhere in France even if you don't take a tour? To some extent, yes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But we know from experience that tours make it possible for you to make the most of every minute by taking you straight to the best stuff.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tours greatly enhance the visit because we all like to know what were're looking at, don't we? There is no doubt that if you don't take a tour, you'll miss out. We give several examples of how that's happened to us in the episode!&lt;/p&gt; Tours Make a Vacation Better If You Are a Curious Person &lt;p&gt;We know one thing for sure: Our listeners are curious about France! The best time to feed that curiosity is while you visit France and walking around the place you've heard about. Would you like to hear about the cool things that happened in a particular neighborhood? Of course you do! Would it make a difference to learn that historically significant people lived where you are? We know it does!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But you'll miss out on a lot of wonderful experiences if you walk around with no help. We want you to feed your curiosity about France. Do you need to learn about the cool things that happened in a particular neighborhood? Of course you do!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Some people, Annie used to be one of them, aren't in the habit of taking tours. They wonder will I get bored? Will it be a waste of time? Wouldn't I rather have the freedom to do what I want? Well, VoiceMap tours are designed not to be boring, they get to the point, they let you do what you want because you can pause and resume at will, and they are inexpensive!&lt;/p&gt; How to Purchase Annie and Elyse's Tours &lt;p&gt;You can get &lt;a href= "https://voicemap.me/authors/annie-sargent"&gt;Annie's Tours&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href= "https://voicemap.me/tour/toulouse/the-glory-of-occitania"&gt;Elyse's Tour&lt;/a&gt; directly from the VoiceMapApp or download the App and then unlock the tour by purchasing a code. Elyse also does in-person tours in and around Toulouse. Use the &lt;a href= "http://www.toulouseguidedwalks.com/"&gt;contact form&lt;/a&gt; on her website to inquire or email her: elysart@live.fr&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a href="https://joinusinfrance.com/audiotours/"&gt;Download your Paris tours now!&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="mailto:%20annie@joinusinfrance.com"&gt;Email&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/joinusinfrance/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/addictedtofrance/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href= "https://www.pinterest.fr/France_Travel_Podcast/"&gt;Pinterest&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ParisPodcast"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Did you get my &lt;a href= "https://voicemap.me/authors/annie-sargent"&gt;VoiceMap&lt;/a&gt; Paris tours yet? They are designed for people who want to see the best of Paris neighborhoods &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; put what they are looking at into historical context. There are so many great stories in Paris. Don't walk right past them without having a clue what happened there! You can buy them directly from the VoiceMap app or click &lt;a href="https://joinusinfrance.com/audiotours/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to order activation codes at the podcast listener discount price. &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Discussed in this Episode &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;[04:35] Rediscovering the London Theater District in London with Ian McEwen's tour on VoiceMap&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[06:05] What if you don't normally take tours?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[06:52] Tours make the experience better&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[07:33] Taking tours where you've lived for a long time is surprisingly interesting!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[08:00] Taking audio tours in Museums is interesting even for an art historian like Elyse!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[08:44] You will miss a lot of stuff if you don't take any sort of tour&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[09:03] Paris is a big city with lots of distractions&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[10:03] VoiceMap tours give you maximal freedom&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[10:13} You can run VoiceMap tours without data because everything is downloaded to your phone!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[11:08] Tours are great for curious people&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[12:02] Don't forget to look up!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[12:34] Missing the Procope even though it has signs!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[13:19} More on the complete flexibility of VoiceMap tours&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[15:16] A visit to the Royal Albert Hall with a "serious" guide&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[15:30] Some tour guides are actors and crack more jokes than anything&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[16:45] We understand why some people don't take tours: some live guides sound like robots!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[17:30] Good in-person guides can adjust the tour to their audience&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[18:13] Are VoiceMap tours too cheap?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[20:20] How to buy Annie and Elyse's VoiceMap tours and how they work&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[21:45] Elyse is working on a tour about the occupation and resistance in Toulouse&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[22:00] Annie has Paris tours about Île de la Cité Marais Montmartre and Saint-Germain-des-Prés&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[22:50] Talking to the people who are reluctant about taking tours&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[24:22] Audio tours enhance the experience&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[25:06] Don't be purely and Instagram tourist!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;[26:17] You can actually take Annie and Elyse in your pocket!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>annie@joinusinfrance.com (Join Us in France Travel Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">994eaacf785046c0ab29d0e8497f3c70</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/994eaacf785046c0ab29d0e8497f3c70/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>Ohio Folklore : Ottawa County Spook Lights</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For more than a century, residents and visitors to Ohio’s Ottawa County have witnessed unexplained balls of light rushing toward them while parked on rickety old bridges.&amp;nbsp; Many know the phenomenon as the legend of Elmore Ghost Rider… the glowing spirit of a local man who lost his head in a motorcycle accident.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few understand the larger context behind this legendary story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Come hear the truth.&amp;nbsp; Come hear the history of supernatural claims which pre-date the alleged ghost rider tale. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Something’s been afoot in Ottawa County long before motorcycles even existed.&amp;nbsp; Come hear the details for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you enjoy this episode, please rate, review and subscribe to Ohio Folklore on your chosen podcast platform.&amp;nbsp; You can also find Ohio Folklore at:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ohiofolklore.com&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;facebook.com/ohiofolklore.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And as always, keep wondering…&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>melissa.davies77@outlook.com (Ohio Folklore)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">54252b2b013a445a9ee3219366bb3bd1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/54252b2b013a445a9ee3219366bb3bd1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>National Parks Traveler Podcast : National Parks Traveler: San Jose Mission and The Water Desk</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week we feature Lynn Riddick's segment on Mission San Jose, the first of a four-part series on San Antonio Missions National Historical Park in Texas. We also talk with Mitch Tobin, Director of The Water Desk at the Center for Environmental Journalism at the University of Colorado, to understand why his organization is underwriting journalism revolving around the Colorado River.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>kurt@nationalparkstraveler.org (National Parks Traveler Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1768f18566544b57b2b0ac25afbbcec9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1768f18566544b57b2b0ac25afbbcec9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 05:00:00 -0700</pubDate></item><item><title>EarzUp!  : Preparing For a runDisney Event</title><description>&lt;br /&gt;
Even though Disneyland doesn't do them anymore, we always liked the runDisney events, but outside of our own personal experiences, we knew very little about them. So we invited Erik from our very own &lt;a href="https://earzup-podcast.com/drinks/"&gt;"Drinks at the Disney Resorts" blog&lt;/a&gt;, and our official travel partner &lt;a href="http://www.conciears.com"&gt;ConciEARS&lt;/a&gt;, to come on the show and give us not only a short overview of what to expect from a runDisney event, but how to plan for it!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Photo courtesy of Disney&lt;br /&gt;</description><author>jason@earzup-podcast.com (EarzUp! )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d5f469934b874f03a8efd38e25675206</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d5f469934b874f03a8efd38e25675206/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 11:26:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Rick Steves Over Brunch : Lisbon and the Algarve</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, Allison Green covers for Stephanie to talk all about the 2004 &lt;em&gt;Rick Steves’ Europe &lt;/em&gt;episode “Lisbon and the Algarve.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Chris and Allison talk about travel to Lisbon, how delicious Portuguese food is, and how much Lisbon has changed in the nearly two decades since this episode was filmed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Join our Facebook Group: &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/groups/2382534102070969/"&gt;Rick Steves Over Brunch Podcast Listeners.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Help us out by contributing to &lt;a title="Our Patreon Account" href="https://www.patreon.com/rickstevesoverbrunch"&gt;Our Patreon Account&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For more, find us:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Chris Mitchell&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://travelingmitch.com/"&gt;travelingmitch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.travelingmitch.com/mostrecent/2-days-in-lisbon-itinerary?rq=lisbon"&gt; Lisbon Itinerary&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.travelingmitch.com/mostrecent/sintraportugal?rq=lisbon"&gt; Day Trip to Sintra&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Allison Green&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://eternalarrival.com/"&gt;Eternal Arrival&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://eternalarrival.com/travel-blog/europe/portugal/where-to-stay-in-lisbon-neighborhoods/"&gt; Where to Stay in Lisbon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://eternalarrival.com/travel-blog/europe/portugal/2-days-in-lisbon-itinerary/"&gt; How to Spend 2 Days in Lisbon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Stephanie Craig&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://historyfangirl.com/rick-steves-over-brunch/"&gt;History Fangirl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>stephanie@historyfangirl.com (Rick Steves Over Brunch)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f795a804cb0145829c2fbbed04e535aa</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f795a804cb0145829c2fbbed04e535aa/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 06:04:25 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Connecting with Walt - A look into the history of the man behind Mickey Mouse, Disneyland and Walt Disney World : #137 - From the Archives: Building the Magic</title><description>03/06/20 - In this episode, Craig presents an archived episode discussing the construction of Disneyland Park!</description><author>craig@wdwinfo.com (Connecting with Walt - A look into the history of the man behind Mickey Mouse, Disneyland and Walt Disney World)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f70d63bb75bd4149aa8c3088fa9dc5be</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f70d63bb75bd4149aa8c3088fa9dc5be/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hashtag Colorado Life : Buying a House in Colorado: Is it a Good Investment?</title><description>#27: With housing prices continuing to rise in Colorado, is buying a home a good investment? Ryan and Carrie answer this important question and share their personal journey of buying a house in the square state. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether you are a native or a transplant to Colorado, it can feel like you get very little square footage for the money. But there are lots of other pros and cons to consider.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colorado housing market moves fast and you need a good real estate agent to help give you an edge. Ryan and Carrie also share some little-known home-buying secrets, from using an escalation clause to taking advantage of Colorado mortgage assistance programs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a lot of paperwork and the process can be a slow one. You may lose out on offers, or not get approved for the amount you were hoping for. This episode details an honest look at what it’s like to buy a home in Colorado and if the investment is worth it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more information and resources about exploring Colorado, visit our website at &lt;a href="http://hashtagcoloradolife.com/"&gt;HashtagColoradoLife.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/hashtagcoloradolife/"&gt;@HashtagColoradoLife&lt;/a&gt; on Instagram.</description><author>team@hashtagcoloradolife.com (Hashtag Colorado Life)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a8676a97040048f3af2e628e6bbc0b91</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a8676a97040048f3af2e628e6bbc0b91/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Trip That Changed Me : Morocco with Mallory Solomon: work-life balance, disrupting the Moroccan rug industry, and travel as a remedy for anxiety</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Mallory was born with an entrepreneurial spirit, and though she loved working with businesses to strategize and further their objectives, she was overworked and under-inspired at her New York advertising agency. After cancelling several solo trips due to the demands of her industry, she finally committed to a much-needed getaway in Morocco. On today's episode, Mallory shares experiences from that trip that inspired her to create Salam Hello – a textile company which champions the women artisans behind Morocco's famous rugs and pays them fairly for their work (something that’s outrageously rare in the current middle-man operated system). Learn how Mallory initially met the Berber women she works with now, why nights spent in the desert are different than the rest, and how spending time in Morocco "turns down the temperature" of her anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@podcastnation.org (The Trip That Changed Me)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fcc02a8279894c72a76ead07d5af364d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fcc02a8279894c72a76ead07d5af364d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 03:00:17 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Bob and Sue : 05 RV Adventures in Arizona</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wanted to take an RV on an adventure into the National Parks? So did we, so we rented one in Arizona and toured the southern part of the state for a week. Join us as we explore Chiricahua National Monument and other National Park units from the comfort of a 19-foot recreational vehicle. Along the way, we learn about the dos and don'ts of RV life, meet the nicest people in the RV community, and lament the untimely demise of Matt's tennis shoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this episode we discuss:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Renting an RV from Cruise America&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Going to a gigantic RV show in Kansas City&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hiking in Chiricahua National Monument&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to use the dump station at an RV park&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RVing versus tent camping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Links:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dearbobandsue.com/episode-5"&gt;Photos from our RV trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/dearbobands"&gt;Join the conversation on Facebook&lt;/a&gt; - we want to hear from you!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dearbobandsue.com/"&gt;Our books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>jonah@puddlecreative.com (Dear Bob and Sue)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e53d253f162642fcbaf1930b1d74e589</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e53d253f162642fcbaf1930b1d74e589/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Books And Travel : The Roman Empire And Alternate History With Alison Morton</title><description>Travel can be about place, but it can also be about time, and in this interview, I talk to Alison Morton about how the ancient Roman empire continues to inspire her alternate-history Roma Nova thrillers.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.booksandtravel.page/roman-empire/alison-morton/" rel="attachment wp-att-1355"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://alison-morton.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Alison Morton&lt;/a&gt; is the author of the Roma Nova series, Roman-themed alternate history thrillers with tough heroines.&lt;br /&gt;
Show notes&lt;br /&gt;
* The early genesis of an idea for books about an alternative history based on Ancient Rome&lt;br /&gt;
* How the past and the present are connected by landscape&lt;br /&gt;
* Places that have inspired aspects of the Roma Nova books&lt;br /&gt;
* Bringing Alison’s personal military experience into fiction&lt;br /&gt;
* Language and how it can impact appreciation of a place and culture&lt;br /&gt;
* Recommended books about ancient Rome and some alt-history novels&lt;br /&gt;
You can find Alison Morton at &lt;a href="https://alison-morton.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Alison-Morton.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Transcript of the interview&lt;br /&gt;
Joanna: Alison Morton is the author of the Roma Nova series, Roman-themed alternate history thrillers with tough heroines. Welcome to the show, Alison.&lt;br /&gt;
Alison: Thanks very much, Joanna. It’s an absolute pleasure to be here.&lt;br /&gt;
Joanna: It’s great to talk to you about this because I know you’re such an expert on this.&lt;br /&gt;
What drives your fascination with ancient Rome?&lt;br /&gt;
Alison: How long have you got? It’s a lifelong fascination if you like. It started when I was 11. And I don’t know whether they still do it now but after each holiday, first thing back at school in September you had to do, ‘My holiday project.’&lt;br /&gt;
Although then photography wasn’t up to it, you had to do drawing. So I was drawing this mosaic. There’s this huge Greco-Roman port, Ampurias, which is northeast Spain. I was traveling, you see? And I was drawing all the pretty patterns of the mosaics and all that.&lt;br /&gt;
I asked my father, ‘Who are the people that lived here?’ We touched on Romans at school but touched. And he was a real Roman nut, and he told me all about the sailors and the senators and the slaves and the colonizers and all the rest.&lt;br /&gt;
I said to him, ‘What did the mummies do?’ My mother was a head of geography department; women worked. And he said, ‘Well, they stayed at home and looked after the children.’&lt;br /&gt;
So I went on drawing, and I turned around to him and said, ‘Well, what would it have been like if the mummies and the ladies had run Rome instead of the men?’&lt;br /&gt;
It was a good one. And he looked at me, now he’s clever. And he said, ‘Well, what do you think it would have been like?’ And that sort of went into the back of my brain at 11.&lt;br /&gt;
Joanna: Wow. So wait. At what age did you write the first of the Roma Novans?&lt;br /&gt;
Alison: Oh, many, many decades later.&lt;br /&gt;
Joanna: Seriously? Did you pursue that as you went through school and later?&lt;br /&gt;
Alison: Seriously. I’ve clambered over most of Roman Europe. We know they had a slave society like all the ancient societies. They were arch colonizers, they were exploiters. They were superstitious, but I’m going to end up like Monty Python now.&lt;br /&gt;
They gave us systems and organizations and roads and admin and you can’t but admire somebody that’s that organized, that cultural, that literary, that technological.&lt;br /&gt;
The more I found out about them, as I went through the decades and started reading sources, Pliny and Tacitus and all that, I came to admire them even more.&lt;br /&gt;
Yes, you have to take the fact that they would not have been entirely pleasant to have lived under unless you were white. Well, not so much white because they were very multi-ethnic. Unless you were a male of a senior family and then you were probably okay.&lt;br /&gt;
But because of their complexity, I was totally fascinated.</description><author>jo@booksandtravel.page (Books And Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f0f3cf425306458fb0efaa8efbe07221</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f0f3cf425306458fb0efaa8efbe07221/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 16:10:22 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Morocco : Why Morocco 032 – Amino Belyamani on Moroccan Tapes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For this week&amp;#8217;s episode I chatted with &lt;a href="https://moroccantapes.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;MoroccanTapes.com&lt;/a&gt; founder Amino Belyamani. Amino, who grew up in Casablanca and now lives in Brooklyn, created the site that brings Moroccan tapes of various musical genres, which are typically only available for purchase in Morocco and in regions where the musicians hail, to the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With music in his blood – both his father and brother are musicians &amp;#8211; Amino is an accomplished musician himself having co-founded the band Dawn of Midi. He’s also is involved in Innov Gnawa, a group known for their traditional Moroccan trance emsemble and their track Bambro Koyo Ganda was nominated for a Grammy in 2018 in the best dance recording category.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Listen is as Amino talks about Moroccan Tapes and his plans for the site, what he thinks listeners should be listening to when it comes to the tapes already available and Moroccan music in general.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To listen or learn more, visit: &lt;a href="https://moroccantapes.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;https://moroccantapes.com/&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more Morocco ideas and advise, follow me on Instagram at &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/mandyinmorocco" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;@mandyinmorocco&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My other projects include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tasting Marrakech food and cultural tours in Marrakech &lt;a href="http://tasting-marrakech.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;tasting-marrakech.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel and public relations consulting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Freelance writing for print and digital  &lt;a href="https://mandyinmorocco.com/freelance-writing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;mandyinmorocco.com/freelance-writing/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mandyjsinclair@gmail.com (Why Morocco)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">aef0e2f90fde46889be4e87e99556ba7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/aef0e2f90fde46889be4e87e99556ba7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 12:14:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Coastin' the Country : Ep. 17: Mickey &amp; Minnie's Runaway Railway opens at Disney World</title><description>&lt;p&gt;After a 91 year wait, Mickey Mouse finally has his own ride at Walt Disney World. Mickey &amp;amp; Minnie's Runaway Railway has opened in the former location of the Great Movie Ride at Walt Disney World's Hollywood Studios. We talked with one of the people who rode it on media day, Alan Dalinka of MousePlanet.com. What is the ride like? Is it a worthy replacement to GMR? What kind of changes could be coming to the Disney Parks with the new leadership change? And how is coronavirus impacting Disney Parks? &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mleshock@wgntv.com (Coastin' the Country)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a3e7b418719a438a9ecaf904c1e84e8f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a3e7b418719a438a9ecaf904c1e84e8f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 12:06:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Rebecca Enchanted: A Disney Planning Podcast : Hollywood Studios Attractions &amp; FastPasses, Episode 67</title><description>This episode discusses the attractions at Disney’s Hollywood Studies and the best uses of FastPasses there. This episode is sponsored by FTM Travel, www.ftmtravel.com. Intro/outro music by Cooper Adair.</description><author>podcasts7+423b7e4@anchor.fm (Rebecca Enchanted: A Disney Planning Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5de4bbbc4a684b019fc24321474d9024</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5de4bbbc4a684b019fc24321474d9024/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 08:41:18 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The History of Egypt Podcast : Summary: Akhenaten (Phase 2)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Interlude: More Story So Far...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We've covered a lot since Akhenaten abandoned the traditional capitals and moved to his new home of Akhet-Aten. Now, the second phase of pharaoh's rule lasted between regnal years 6 and 12 (c.1357-1351 BCE). In this time, the King completed many of the goals he initiated back in phase 1. Then, he began to build on those, further refining his ideas and moving forward into new territory...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Date: c.1357 to 1351 BCE (regnal year 6 to 12)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;King: Akhenaten (Nefer-kheperu-Re Wa-en-Re)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Queen: Nefertiti (Nefer-neferu-Aten)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location: Amarna (Akhet-Aten)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Music by Keith Zizza &lt;a href="https://create.acast.com/episodes/d5685ee4-dd5e-46df-9024-45b6e6dab436/www.keithzizza.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.keithzizza.com&lt;/a&gt;, Learn More about the Podcast at &lt;a href="https://create.acast.com/episodes/d5685ee4-dd5e-46df-9024-45b6e6dab436/www.egyptianhistorypodcast.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.egyptianhistorypodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>egyptpodcast@gmail.com (The History of Egypt Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b2cf3a74dd3a451ca58fd8b9a598a112</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b2cf3a74dd3a451ca58fd8b9a598a112/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The One Way Ticket Show : Eddie Perfect - Writer-Lyricist-Composer-Performer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Eddie Perfect is one of Australia's most diverse, respected and prolific writers/composers/performers, having made his mark in the fields of comedy, music theatre composition, playwriting, screenwriting, classical music, jazz and acting for stage and screen. As a composer/lyricist, Eddie's credits include &lt;em&gt;Shane Warne The&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Musical&lt;/em&gt; (Token), &lt;em&gt;Drink Pepsi Bitch&lt;/em&gt; (Malthouse Theatre), &lt;em&gt;Misanthropology&lt;/em&gt; (Sydney Festival), &lt;em&gt;Songs From&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;The Middle&lt;/em&gt; with &lt;em&gt;The Brodsky Quartet&lt;/em&gt; (Sydney Opera House), &lt;em&gt;Strictly Ballroom&lt;/em&gt; (Global Creatures), &lt;em&gt;Vivid&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;White&lt;/em&gt; (Melbourne Theatre Company), &lt;em&gt;King Kong: Alive On Broadway&lt;/em&gt; and most recently, &lt;em&gt;Beetlejuice: The&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Musical&lt;/em&gt; (Warner Bros Theatrical Ventures) which received eight Tony Award Nominations, including "Best Original Score." In 2016 Eddie wrote the hit play &lt;em&gt;The Beast for Melbourne&lt;/em&gt; Theatre Company and wrote the screenplay, musical score and starred in &lt;em&gt;The Future Is Expensive&lt;/em&gt; - an absurdist comedy for ABC television.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Eddie's acting stage credits include &lt;em&gt;The Threepenny Opera&lt;/em&gt; (Macheath), the Lincoln Center/Opera Australia production of &lt;em&gt;South Pacific&lt;/em&gt; (Billis) and &lt;em&gt;Keating The Musical&lt;/em&gt; (Alexander Downer/John Hewson). Eddie can be seen on Australian television's &lt;em&gt;Playschool&lt;/em&gt; where he is a presenter, and on Netflix as Mick Holland in the Australian Drama/Comedy series &lt;em&gt;Offering&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On this episode, Eddie shares his one-way ticket to New York City! He also talks about the hit Broadway musical, "Beetlejuice" for which he wrote the music and lyrics. Plus, Eddie offers his perspective on taking risks in life! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Eddie is just one of the dynamic personalities featured on The One Way Ticket Show, where Host Steven Shalowitz explores with his guests where they would go if given a one way ticket, no coming back! Destinations may be in the past, present, future, real, imaginary or a state of mind.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Steven's guests have included: Nobel Peace Prize Winner, President Jose Ramos-orta; Legendary Talk Show Host, Dick Cavett; Law Professor, Alan Dershowitz; Fashion Expert, Tim Gunn; Broadcast Legend, Charles Osgood; International Rescue Committee President &amp; CEO, David Miliband; Playwright, David Henry Hwang; Journalist-Humorist-Actor, Mo Rocca; SkyBridge Capital Founder &amp; Co-Managing Partner, Anthony Scaramucci; Abercrombie &amp; Kent Founder, Geoffrey Kent; Travel Expert, Pauline Frommer, as well as leading photographers, artists, chefs, writers, intellectuals and more.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>steven@theonewayticketshow.com (The One Way Ticket Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f2fb611051ed47e28bdfc243acce6b77</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f2fb611051ed47e28bdfc243acce6b77/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 08:42:36 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Exploring the North Shore : Episode 22: Dog Sledding with Jasmine Poppovich + An Interview with the Girl of 10,000 Lakes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;What an episode we have for you! We promised a sledding episode, but we didn't say what kind of sledding! Jaye and Martha join Jasmine Poppovich, the head dog musher at the Gunflint Lodge and Outfitters, for a dog sledding adventure on the Gunflint Trail. Jasmine not only takes us for a wild ride to Lonely Lake, but also teaches us more about dog sledding. Martha even goes to work helping to feed the dogs!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, Jaye sits down to interview Jenny Anderson, better known as the Girl of 10,000 Lakes. Jenny and Jaye chat about fishing, being a social media influencer, being a mom who loves the outdoors, and we find out what Jenny's favorite lake is. Follow Jenny on &lt;a href='https://girlof10000lakes.com/'&gt;her blog&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href='https://www.instagram.com/girlof10000lakes/'&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href='https://www.facebook.com/girlof10000lakes/'&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCxMHVOTgqOXYJ_-yBS6PJ1A'&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Places to go dog sledding on the North Shore:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gunflint Lodge (Grand Marais, Gunflint Trail): &lt;a href='https://www.gunflint.com/activities/dog-sledding-at-gunflint-lodge/'&gt;https://www.gunflint.com/activities/dog-sledding-at-gunflint-lodge/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bearskin Lodge / Camp Menogyn (Grand Marais, Gunflint Trail): &lt;a href='http://www.bearskin.com/activities/winter/mushing/'&gt;http://www.bearskin.com/activities/winter/mushing/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Points Unknown (Hovland): &lt;a href='http://www.points-unknown.com/'&gt;http://www.points-unknown.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Endurance Kennels (Duluth): &lt;a href='https://www.endurancekennels.com/'&gt;https://www.endurancekennels.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Positive Energy Outdoors (Duluth): &lt;a href='https://www.outdooredventures.org/'&gt;https://www.outdooredventures.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This episode is sponsored by &lt;a href='https://www.cascadevacationrentals.com/'&gt;Cascade Vacation Rentals&lt;/a&gt;. Use promo code "Podcast" at check-out to receive Cascade's largest available percent off discount (discount changes seasonally). This episode is also sponsored by &lt;a href='https://thebiglakelife.com/'&gt;The Big Lake&lt;/a&gt;. Use promo code "Explore" at check-out to receive 15% off your first online order. Thank you to our wonderful sponsors!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marketing@staycvr.com (Exploring the North Shore)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">56b2fbc274ad4e55948738a7474306bd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/56b2fbc274ad4e55948738a7474306bd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 04:30:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Curiosityness : 077 DeLorean Motor Company: Still Going Strong! | James Espey, Vice President at DMC</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You’ve seen the DeLorean car in Back to the Future and may even remember when it was released in 1981. But, as you’ll find out in this episode, production of the car only lasted until 1983!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tune in to hear the incredible story of John DeLorean, the ups and downs of the DeLorean Motor Company, and the truth about the cocaine bust that bankrupted DMC. Plus, learn about the company today (it still exists!) and discover the new DeLorean's that may be rolling off the production line soon...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To learn more about the DeLorean Motor Company, visit &lt;a href= "https://www.delorean.com/"&gt;https://www.delorean.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For more about the new DeLorean's being produced, visit &lt;a href= "https://www.newdelorean.com/"&gt;https://www.newdelorean.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To tour the DMC facility, visit &lt;a href= "http://deloreantour.com/"&gt;deloreantour.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And to learn more about the history of DeLorean, visit &lt;a href= "https://www.deloreanmuseum.org/"&gt;https://www.deloreanmuseum.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Connect with Curiosityness... Instagram: &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/curiositynesspodcast/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/curiositynesspodcast/&lt;/a&gt; Website: &lt;a href= "https://www.curiosityness.com/"&gt;https://www.curiosityness.com/&lt;/a&gt; Facebook: &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/curiosityness"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/curiosityness&lt;/a&gt; Twitter: &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/Curiositynesstv"&gt;https://twitter.com/Curiositynesstv&lt;/a&gt;   Claim your FREE Curiosityness sticker at &lt;a href= "https://www.curiosityness.com/freesticker/"&gt;https://www.curiosityness.com/freesticker/&lt;/a&gt;   Find me, the host of Curiosityness on Instagram: &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/travderose/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/travderose/&lt;/a&gt; Or send me an email to &lt;a href= "mailto:travis@curiosityness.com"&gt;travis@curiosityness.com&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>travis@curiosityness.com (Curiosityness)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9f03e8579a11406aa2689b4d87fcc4f3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9f03e8579a11406aa2689b4d87fcc4f3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 04:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>New Books in African Studies : David Morton, "Age of Concrete: Housing and the Shape of Aspiration in the Capital of Mozambique" (Ohio UP, 2019)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Who built Africa’s cities? Going beyond the colonial archive and the planner’s gaze, David Morton’s &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/0821423681/?tag=newbooinhis-20"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Age of Concrete: Housing and the Shape of Aspiration in the Capital of Mozambique&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (Ohio University Press, 2019) describes the incremental process through which Maputo’s &lt;em&gt;suburbios&lt;/em&gt; – popular neighborhoods outside the formally planned city – were built and occupied. Through key episode’s in Mozambique’s urban history – from colonial responses to migrant labor to independence-era responses to flooding, he interprets the routine forms of house construction as critical political acts through which ordinary residents of the city have inserted themselves into the city and concretized urban belonging. The materiality of different building materials are central this story. The risks and obstacles of constructing permanent, concrete, housing in the face of politically enforced urban impermanence an d ambiguous legal status kept the popular &lt;em&gt;suburbios&lt;/em&gt; in suspension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David Morton talks to host Jacob Doherty about the ways that the built environment both reflects and shapes the changing aspirations and achievements of the city’s residents. Offering a critical contribution to the process of decolonization in African cities, Morton examines the racial and spatial effects of colonial Portugal’s officially race-blind ideology as well as the ambivalent anti-urban bias of the early FRELIMO regime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://history.ubc.ca/profile/david-morton/"&gt;David Morton&lt;/a&gt; is an assistant professor of African History at the University of British Colombia. He has written about architectural and planning histories, Portuguese colonialism, informal settlements, housing, and citizenship, and decolonization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.san.ed.ac.uk/people/faculty/jacob_doherty"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jacob Doherty&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; is a lecturer in the Anthropology of Development at the University of Edinburgh.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marshallpoe@gmail.com (New Books in African Studies)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0a787a41d37b41b48ab4169a6f4a1bbd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0a787a41d37b41b48ab4169a6f4a1bbd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Far From Home : Touring North Korea with The Radio Vagabond (bonus episode)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;While Far From Home is on a break between seasons, I’m popping into your feed from time to time to share segments from other shows I’ve enjoyed that I think all of you might like as well. Today I’m featuring an episode from &lt;a href="https://www.theradiovagabond.com/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;The Radio Vagabond podcast&lt;/a&gt;, where Danish radio producer Palle Bo tells stories from his travels, kind of like I do. This time he goes to a place I’m not quite brave enough to go myself, at least not right now, and not as a journalist: North Korea. You can read more about Palle’s journey and see some picture he took &lt;a href="https://www.theradiovagabond.com/north-korea-travel/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;on his website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Far From Home is a podcast where award-winning public radio journalist Scott Gurian visits parts of the world that most people never think about and tells stories they've never heard. For more info, visit &lt;a href="http://farfromhomepodcast.org" title="farfromhomepodcast.org" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;farfromhomepodcast.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@farfromhomepodcast.org (Far From Home)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8512944ef534478c802ebd34f00c5253</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8512944ef534478c802ebd34f00c5253/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 17:41:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Normal to Nomad : #13 | Technology We Use</title><description>&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="/podcast" target=""&gt;Show Notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>barronlink@gmail.com (Normal to Nomad)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">00e680f14eb84b4ca7448d5a09866471</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/00e680f14eb84b4ca7448d5a09866471/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 13:28:27 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WDW Escape : WDW Escape 01 Remember Minnie's Walk</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Welcome to WDW Escape, presented by WDW Magazine. In today’s episode, we remember “Minnie's Walk"&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Still missing Walt Disney World? Subscribe to WDW Magazine in Print or Digital format at &lt;a href= "http://wdw-magazine.com/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;wdw-magazine.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;You’ll be transported right back to your happy place. Use coupon code “podcast” for $10 off an Annual Digital Edition. From all of us here at WDW Magazine, have a magical day.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>support@wdwmag.com (WDW Escape)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">55ded58092c041b186b05f5fba0f992f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/55ded58092c041b186b05f5fba0f992f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 08:12:21 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Australia All Over : Australia All Over highlights podcast</title><description>More great interviews from Australia All Over with Macca</description><author>localfeedback@your.abc.net.au (Australia All Over)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fd19e1d073fc44e0828ac343b0a9e8d4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fd19e1d073fc44e0828ac343b0a9e8d4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 11:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Become Nomad - Digital Nomad Lifestyle and Long Term Travel : BN070: Coliving, Remote work and Canary Islands as Digital Nomad Hubs</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, we will interview Nacho Rodriguez, the founder of co-living Canary Islands and Nomad City summit in Las Palmas. Nacho has extensive knowledge on several topics relevant to all of us, including the future of remote work, co-living and why you should consider the Canary Islands as your next nomadic destination.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>eli@becomenomad.com (Become Nomad - Digital Nomad Lifestyle and Long Term Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f861ab53590144cc9d51bcb643261220</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f861ab53590144cc9d51bcb643261220/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 04:12:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Inside Universal Podcast : The Inside Universal Podcast: Mardicharged!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are joined by Joe from Parkscope and Touring Plans to discuss all the happenings at Universal Orlando from the past month - specifically Mardi Gras 2020, where we interview Blake Braswell, Creative Development Group – Show Director for Mardi Gras. We also discuss Running Universal's inaugural Epic Character Race, The Bourne Shoptacular (aka gift shop) opening, and more - including the recent announcement of Bob Chapek becoming Disney's new CEO as Robert Iger steps down. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jon@insideuniversal.net (The Inside Universal Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f08b36ad41d843f4a9894444a2fb522c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f08b36ad41d843f4a9894444a2fb522c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 12:27:38 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Love + Grit : Love + Grit Episode 1</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In the first episode of &lt;em&gt;Love + Grit&lt;/em&gt;,&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;learn why hosts Laiya St. Clair, Rachel Ferguson and Justin Pizzi love Philadelphia as much as they do (and why you should too) before they chat with three women making an impact on the city. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="m_-2571591524528481492MsoListParagraph"&gt;First, they talk to Rashia Bell (&lt;a href='https://www.thecristalline.com/'&gt;The Cristalline&lt;/a&gt;), North Philadelphia native and crystal designer for the &lt;a href='https://www.fourseasons.com/philadelphia/'&gt;Four Seasons Hotel Philadelphia at Comcast Center&lt;/a&gt;, about the healing power of crystals and how special it was for her to return to her hometown. Next, they stop at &lt;a href='http://www.thecoloredgirlsmuseum.com/'&gt;The Colored Girls Museum&lt;/a&gt; to hear from founder Vashti DuBois about Sunday hair sessions, the museum’s unexpected superhero exhibits and the lives and accomplishments of the everyday African-American women featured here. Last, &lt;em&gt;Shark Tank &lt;/em&gt;winner Patrice Banks, founder of &lt;a href='https://girlsautoclinic.com/'&gt;Girls Auto Clinic (GAC)&lt;/a&gt;, gives a quick lesson in car repair with her all-female team of auto mechanics.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@visitphilly.com (Love + Grit)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a92c594dddf246e9b64ece1f1f57c1c7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a92c594dddf246e9b64ece1f1f57c1c7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 09:52:30 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Sake On Air : Tengu Sake with Oliver Hilton-Johnson</title><description>This week we zone in on sake in the U.K. as we welcome the founder and owner of Tengu Sake, Oliver Hilton Johnson to the show. Oliver’s carefully curated portfolio and user-friendly communication are just a handful of the reasons that Tengu Sake has been selected as the Specialist Merchant of the Year in the […]</description><author>Frowley3@gmail.com (Sake On Air)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e3f6050e20cc4abd87db637ce24823a9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e3f6050e20cc4abd87db637ce24823a9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 19:16:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>In Limbo : Answering The Call- Recognizing and protecting ideas/dreams</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode we will discuss what to do with an idea that is not fully formed and how to boost an initial thought of an idea.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts14+d507e9c@anchor.fm (In Limbo)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">528e74f85ee043deb024e043580edf78</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/528e74f85ee043deb024e043580edf78/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 13:14:35 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>My Solo Road : Van Life Breakups &amp; Pearl's Adoption Story</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It's just you and me this week! No guests but I sit down to address my recent relationship status update, tell you all about Pearl's story and how I adopted her, AND I address the lovely hate comments on a recent Instagram post. WOOHOO!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>divineontheroad@gmail.com (My Solo Road)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f1fb4897a4734f59a1011d480c99978f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f1fb4897a4734f59a1011d480c99978f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 10:28:21 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Wise About Texas : Ep. 79: Dorie Miller–A Texas War Hero</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On December 7, 1941, Mess Attendant Doris &amp;#8220;Dorie&amp;#8221; Miller was doing laundry, one of the few jobs available to African American sailors in the U.S. Navy at the time.  When his ship came under attack, Miller rushed to help his fellow sailors.  Though not trained, and not allowed, he manned an anti-aircraft gun and engaged the attacking Japanese planes.  For his bravery and his willingness to go above and beyond the call of duty, Miller was the first African American to be awarded the Navy Cross.  But his heroism affected not only the Navy, but the entire military.  Recently, the U.S. Navy announced yet another tribute to Dorie Miller, a Texas war hero.  Learn more about this brave Texan in the latest episode of Wise About Texas.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/WiseAboutTexas/~4/8ltz90sgCH8" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>Host@wiseabouttexas.com (Wise About Texas)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">45d0f5ccc78b4db780914bceb5c9aa85</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/45d0f5ccc78b4db780914bceb5c9aa85/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 12:11:57 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>