<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Travel feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My travel episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My Travel feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 04:21:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>Monocle 24: The Menu : Crossing borders</title><description>How one chef in Seoul is trying to create a culinary connection between North and South Korea. Plus: a new London venture by Brooklyn’s most talked-about restaurateurs and a family reviving a long-extinct port wine house in Portugal.</description><author>info@monocle.com (Monocle 24: The Menu)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e034600d843a4455accc3fc8b4eac427</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e034600d843a4455accc3fc8b4eac427/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Happiest Podcast On Earth : 49 - Overrated &amp; Underrated Disney Movies</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We discuss our thoughts on what Disney movies we believe are the most overrated and underrated. We also talk about some of your answers for this question and break it all down. HAPPY LISTENING EVERYONE!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>happiestpodcast@gmail.com (Happiest Podcast On Earth)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fad4ec5702104d28b8b046caf4c801ca</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fad4ec5702104d28b8b046caf4c801ca/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The olive magazine podcast : ep 188 - How to find the best ski food and where to travel in 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week Rhiannon and Ellie chat about the best food to indulge in during the ski season, from boozy hot chocolate to Italian pastries, plus where to travel to in 2020, from idyllic Greek islands to UK staycations.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts@immediate.co.uk (The olive magazine podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">34f83f17736245d3aa1b177aa896a3f3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/34f83f17736245d3aa1b177aa896a3f3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 05:07:36 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Familie auf Weltreise -Der Podcast : 76 | Marie und Julien erzählen</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Und da hat es endlich geklappt. Julien und Marie sprechen mit uns vorm Mikrofon. Ein Jahr Australien. Was ist anders, was war besonders toll, was ich euch in Gedächtnis geblieben und viele Lacher in dieser bunt gemischten Episode. Viel Spaß beim Reinhören.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://katrin-fit.net/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sport mit Katrin - Katrin-Fit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/familieaufweltreise"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Der geschlossenen Gruppe "Familie auf Weltreise" beitreten&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.familieaufweltreise.de/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unser neuer Blog&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/familieaufweltreise"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instagram&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://youtube.com/c/familieaufweltreisede"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YouTube&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2WLSqdF"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on Family&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unsere Ressourcen findest Du auf unserer Webseite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.familieaufweltreise.de/ressourcen"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;www.Familieaufweltreise.de/ressourcen&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lust auf ein Reiseguthaben?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;25 € AirBnB Gutschein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2BtQrCo"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://bit.ly/2BtQrCo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;15 € Booking.com Gutschein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://booki.ng/2A67Xwu"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://booki.ng/2A67Xwu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>kontakt@familieaufweltreise.de (Familie auf Weltreise -Der Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b6b9cc64f8014fab80d9f3fbfacf8669</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b6b9cc64f8014fab80d9f3fbfacf8669/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 04:06:09 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Connecting with Walt - A look into the history of the man behind Mickey Mouse, Disneyland and Walt Disney World : #135 - Connecting with Walt in Southern California Pt. 2</title><description>02/21/20 - In this episode, Michael and Craig are joined by Mary Jo from the DIS Unplugged: Disneyland Discussion to continue their discussion on how you can connect with Walt in Southern California by visiting many places important in Walt's history!</description><author>craig@wdwinfo.com (Connecting with Walt - A look into the history of the man behind Mickey Mouse, Disneyland and Walt Disney World)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b8e0c3e60c154fe3b01681cfac6b724d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b8e0c3e60c154fe3b01681cfac6b724d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hashtag Colorado Life : The Best Ski Towns in Colorado and What Makes Each One Great</title><description>#25: During the winter,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Colorado is known for epic skiing and snowboarding. And there are plenty of awesome ski towns to choose from. How can you ever decide? In this episode, Ryan and Carrie discuss their top recommendations for the best ski towns in Colorado and what makes each one great.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You will discover the unique benefits, local features, and skiing options that each town has to offer. Plus, you will learn what’s nearby and what you can do both on and off the slopes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No matter how you plan to enjoy the powder, Colorado has the perfect destination! And the great news is, that most of the major ski resorts in Colorado are within a few hours’ drive of Denver.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ryan and Carrie share local information and insider tips for getting to the resorts, and the must-see attractions that each ski town offers. You won’t be disappointed with these best ski town recommendations!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more information and resources about exploring Colorado, visit our website at &lt;a href="http://hashtagcoloradolife.com/"&gt;HashtagColoradoLife.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/hashtagcoloradolife/"&gt;@HashtagColoradoLife&lt;/a&gt; on Instagram.</description><author>team@hashtagcoloradolife.com (Hashtag Colorado Life)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9b62e67c3c1a4471b69336a0be7d255f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9b62e67c3c1a4471b69336a0be7d255f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Expat Files: Living in Latin America : EXPAT FILES - 02.21.20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Descriptions- EXPAT FILES SHOW #931 FRI, FEB 21 (02-21-2020):&lt;/p&gt;
JOHNNY’S EXPAT FILES WEBSITE PERMANENT NAME CHANGE ANNOUNCEMENT!
My new website is &lt;a href='http://www.expatplanb.com/'&gt;www.ExpatPlanB.com&lt;/a&gt;. The old one &lt;a href='http://www.theexpatfiles.com/'&gt;www.theexpatfiles.com&lt;/a&gt; has been retired so from now on please use &lt;a href='http://www.expatplanb.com/'&gt;www.ExpatPlanB.com&lt;/a&gt;. 
 
#1- Money confiscation at airports and borders- THE FACTS:
Yes, the FEDS, TSA, DEA and Homeland Security have been &lt;em&gt;illegally&lt;/em&gt; confiscating cash from travelers at an accelerating pace (the USA is bankrupt, but you knew that already). Today we discuss what you really need to know before traveling the world with any substantial amounts of cash. You probably know that legally you must report if traveling with cash instruments over $10000, but technically (and legally) you can travel with much much more as long as you report it on the customs forms. However USA alphabet agencies do operate with impunity and will take your cash money. Its today's first "boots on the ground" story
 
#2- HONESTY and Latin Americans:
Some gringos and expats think those two things are mutually exclusive… but the question is... compared to which other cultures? Gringos, Europeans? Today we discuss the results of a large international “Honesty Test”. The results are surprising..
 
#3- How to use that great Latin American Craigslist site called “&lt;a href='http://www.olx.com/'&gt;www.OLX.com&lt;/a&gt;” to buy and sell stuff in Latin America:
Wherever you happen to be on your “Plan B”… &lt;a&gt;http://www.OLX.com is a site you must&lt;/a&gt; be aware of. Today we have some great tips as well as certain red flags that to keep an eye out for while using it.
 
#4- Be sure to pick up my new and revised, "LATIN AMERICAN HEALTHCARE REPORT":
It's the new edition for 2020 (and beyond) including the latest "Stem Cell" info and data and my top picks for the best treatment centers for expats and gringos. Just go to &lt;a href='http://www.expatplanb.com/'&gt;www.ExpatPlanB.com&lt;/a&gt; and click on the "Latin American Healthcare Report”.</description><author>karalee@garynull.com (The Expat Files: Living in Latin America)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">92ce39b8dcfc47e591713a3b5ba06930</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/92ce39b8dcfc47e591713a3b5ba06930/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 12:16:22 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Solo Travel Talk with Astrid : The Hassle-Free Travel Mindset</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Is hassle blocking you from pursuing the travel you want to experience? Do you get filled with a mild (to severe) sense of dread when thinking about hitting the road? Astrid Clements, founder of Astrid Solo Travel Advisor and The AstridTravel Club, brings you the new Solo Travel Talk podcast series—The Hassle-Free Travel Series. On this inaugural episode of the series, Astrid shares the key elements of making travel hassle-free plus introduces what’s coming up in the series.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Mentioned on the show:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- &lt;a href= "https://www.astridtravel.com/astrid-travel-essentials"&gt;Astrid’s Marketplace (where you can find packing cubes, universal adapters, luggage scales, and more.)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- &lt;a href="https://www.astridtravel.com/club"&gt;The AstridTravel Club&lt;/a&gt;: a place for those who want to experience affordable luxury travel or want to go solo that’s not totally solo. &lt;a href= "https://www.astridtravel.com/club"&gt;The AstridTravel Club is the sponsor of the Hassle-Free Travel Series&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Some of the questions answered on this episode…&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Is travel really more hassle-filled these days, or is that just a perception?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What apps can help my travel be easier?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;How can I plan my trip to be hassle-free?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;How can I get a hassle-free travel mindset?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What is The AstridTravel Club and how do I join?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;We love sharing the most innovative and informative content to get you out there solo. Astrid, your expert Solo Travel Advisor-- has &lt;a href="https://www.astridtravel.com/resources"&gt;a whole section of resources for solo travelers&lt;/a&gt; on her website, &lt;a href="http://astridtravel.com/"&gt;AstridTravel.com&lt;/a&gt;. Follow Astrid on &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/astridtravel/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/AstridTravel"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/astrid.travel/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;. You can subscribe to the podcast on &lt;a href= "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/solo-travel-talk-with-astrid/id1200131350?ign-mpt=uo%3D4&amp;ls=1"&gt; Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "https://open.spotify.com/show/350imnwgGxfYyfCIbdv0a9"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href= "http://www.stitcher.com/podcast/astrid-clements/solo-travel-talk?refid=stpr"&gt; Stitcher&lt;/a&gt;, or with your favorite podcast app. Just go solo!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>solotraveltalk@outlook.com (Solo Travel Talk with Astrid)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">533ba952e6394696b6211781de8e5ea3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/533ba952e6394696b6211781de8e5ea3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 10:42:53 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>My Solo Road : Van Life Breakups &amp; Pearl's Adoption Story</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It's just you and me this week! No guests but I sit down to address my recent relationship status update, tell you all about Pearl's story and how I adopted her, AND I address the lovely hate comments on a recent Instagram post. WOOHOO!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>divineontheroad@gmail.com (My Solo Road)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f1fb4897a4734f59a1011d480c99978f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f1fb4897a4734f59a1011d480c99978f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 10:28:21 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Well-Traveled with AAA : National Parks</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Discover the beauty of North America in your own backyard. Whether your staring up a thousand foot canyon walls or down a thousand of earth inspires natural amphitheaters, the awe inspiring of National Parks is essential boundless. Discover the beauty of North America in your own backyard.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sonixcursions@gmail.com (Well-Traveled with AAA)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">512695662be84458a599345f8632f362</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/512695662be84458a599345f8632f362/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 08:16:34 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Overland Journal Podcast : The Ultimate Overland Vehicles</title><description>Detailed Show Notes are available here: &lt;a href="https://overlandjournal.com/ultimate_overlander/"&gt;https://overlandjournal.com/ultimate_overlander/&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>scott@overlandinternational.com (The Overland Journal Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">024f6e4ed91f440ab19515df8631539c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/024f6e4ed91f440ab19515df8631539c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Oh Boy, The Podcast : Episode 010 - Our First Advicecast: Answering Your Questions about Vacationing at Walt Disney World</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Our First Advicecast! We collected all of your guys' biggest questions about vacationing at Disney World. Is the Disney Dining Plan worth it? What's the best way to do Disney with a large group of people? Which character buffets can you skip?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We answered as many questions as we could today, and honestly, this was one of our favorite Podcasts to do ever because it reminded us of one our biggest passions - planning Disney Vacations and helping others. Hope you enjoy :-)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;lt;3 cody, lex, &amp;amp; joe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="http://www.thelostbros.com"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (http://www.thelostbros.com)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@lostbrostradingco.com (Oh Boy, The Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">246d5a27ce0347c480bea05755967df9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/246d5a27ce0347c480bea05755967df9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 07:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Tropical MBA Podcast - Entrepreneurship, Travel, and Lifestyle : TMBA533: From Cryptocurrency to Cowboy Boots</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Will Roman is a veteran entrepreneur who has worked in a number of different fields including eCommerce, physical products, software, and even cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of last year, Will made the decision to leave his crypto exchange business to start Chisos, a product company that manufactures and sells designer cowboy boots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will joins us on the podcast this week to talk about his stressful exit from that company, why he decided to start Chisos, what he has learned from his first year of manufacturing boots, and a whole lot more. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Dan@TropicalMBA.com (The Tropical MBA Podcast - Entrepreneurship, Travel, and Lifestyle)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ec5c027fa7fa43f393ca84cd49c62db1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ec5c027fa7fa43f393ca84cd49c62db1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WDWNT ParksCenter : ParksCenter - Golden Castle Changes, and Regal Eagle Leaves Us Gleeful - Ep. 90</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This is ParksCenter. We cover the top news stories from this week in Disney Parks news in 30 minutes. This week, we’ll be talking about: Cinderella Castle in Florida is going to be getting a permanent, golden makeover this summer Regal Eagle Smokehouse opens in Epcot, and it looks and tastes quite good! And more! […]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://wdwnt.com/2020/02/watch-parkscenter-90/"&gt;ParksCenter – Golden Castle Changes, and Regal Eagle Leaves Us Gleeful – Ep. 90&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://wdwnt.com"&gt;WDW News Today&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>developer@wdwnt.com (WDWNT ParksCenter)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">aa28d9ca0cd34f099efbd6c27fa1ef29</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/aa28d9ca0cd34f099efbd6c27fa1ef29/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 04:00:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Trip That Changed Me : The Entire World with Jessica Nabongo: fearlessness, responsible influencing, and treating the world as your neighborhood</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Jessica Nabongo (@&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/thecatchmeifyoucan/?hl=en" target="_blank"&gt;thecatchmeifyoucan&lt;/a&gt;) has been traveling internationally since she was just four years old, born to Ugandan immigrant parents who were no strangers to adventure and exploration. At a young age, she set a lofty goal for herself – to travel the entire world – and officially met her goal at just 35 years old. On today’s episode, Jessica shares stories from her experience as the first black woman to visit all 195 countries and document her journey along the way. She describes how she became an accidental influencer, the planning that goes into each of her destinations (which surprisingly isn’t too much), and some of the countries that have far exceeded her expectations. Jessica shares a heartwarming story that inspired her to keep going when she was feeling understandably tired and overwhelmed during her journey around the world. And last but not least, who better to give the best tips on packing and deals than Jessica?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@podcastnation.org (The Trip That Changed Me)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">82851ba63087433f9ef7ceb0e34ae26e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/82851ba63087433f9ef7ceb0e34ae26e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 03:00:21 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Kentuckiana Sounds : Flash Dads? Flash Dads!</title><description>Flash Dads is a JCPS program that brings men from the community into JCPS schools to serve as positive role models and welcome students. The volunteers come from throughout the community, and bring their own style to the early morning surprise greeting. On this morning, sanitation workers improvised a chorus of the air horns on their trucks to welcome students to Shelby Traditional Academy, and woke up the neighborhood in the process. To hear the full recording, explore the sound map, or submit a sound visit www.wfpl.org/sounds or www.kentuckianasounds.org.</description><author>support@louisvillepublicmedia.org (Kentuckiana Sounds)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">312a66961ff84f28bd04e8ca2881ba77</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/312a66961ff84f28bd04e8ca2881ba77/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Bob and Sue : 04 Our Favorite National Park Lodges</title><description>&lt;p&gt;What's it like to wake up with a view of Crater Lake from your bedroom window? In this episode, we gleefully revisit some of our favorite National Park lodges and the adventures we had staying in them. We discuss the "parkitechture" and fascinating history to each of the lodges. We regale some hilarious stories from our stays at Crater Lake Lodge and El Tovar lodge at the Grand Canyon. We also talk about how to get reservations and some fantastic places for sunset viewing,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this episode we discuss:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Staying in the largest log structure in the world in Yellowstone NP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watching bears from the deck in Glacier NP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wintertime stay at Zion lodge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ranger programs at Bryce Canyon lodge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twin beds at Paradise Inn in Mt. Rainier NP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;President Roosevelt's stay in Olympic NP on Lake Crescent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An unexpected surprise at Crater Lake Lodge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The mule-train journey taken by Matt's shorts in the Grand Canyon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The public space at the Ahwahnee Lodge in Yosemite NP&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Links:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dearbobandsue.com/episode-4"&gt;Photos from our trips to Yosemite, Yellowstone, and more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/dearbobands"&gt;Join the conversation on Facebook&lt;/a&gt; - we want to hear from you!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dearbobandsue.com/"&gt;Our books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>jonah@puddlecreative.com (Dear Bob and Sue)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">131cc5d4225f46ebba642bf59e82c8f1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/131cc5d4225f46ebba642bf59e82c8f1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Gal Pal Show: Solo female travel, backpacking, bucket list inspiration, planning a trip, female travel advice and tips, and off the beaten track ideas. : 94: How to stay safe when travelling as a female</title><description>&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;If you're thinking of travelling as a solo female, this episode is for you. I'm giving some advice on how to look after yourself a few things we could all do when travelling to minimise the attention...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;Listen to the episode now...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='http://galpalacademy.com/jet-popup/travel-planning-worksheet/'&gt;Get your FREE Travel planning worksheet &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='http://galpalacademy.com/jet-popup/travel-planning-worksheet/'&gt;and start planning your trip here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://galpalacademy.thinkific.com/courses/travel-planning-bootcamp-1'&gt;Want to go travelling?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://galpalacademy.thinkific.com/courses/travel-planning-bootcamp-1'&gt;Join Gal Pal Travel Planning Bootcamp here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jo@galpalacademy.com (Gal Pal Show: Solo female travel, backpacking, bucket list inspiration, planning a trip, female travel advice and tips, and off the beaten track ideas.)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">743081f0dc7a4739a92bd33894a1a644</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/743081f0dc7a4739a92bd33894a1a644/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Offbeat Life - become location independent : Extended: How to take advantage of error airfares to travel cheaper.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this episode, Laura shares how to take advantage of error fares, in order to travel cheaper and longer while still being able to be financially secure. Hear her amazing and useful tips on this episode of the podcast.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.theoffbeatlife.com/episodes/remote-english-teacher/"&gt;GET THE FULL INTERVIEW WITH LAURA WHERE SHE SHARES HOW SHE IS ABLE TO TRAVEL THE WORLD AND CREATE INCOME AS A REMOTE ENGLISH TEACHER.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@theoffbeatlife.com (The Offbeat Life - become location independent)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5c2ea45914f147dc9a5141b7b49d1aa5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5c2ea45914f147dc9a5141b7b49d1aa5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>DCL Podcast : 132 England and France with Adventures by Disney</title><description>&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img src="https://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/image0-1024x1024.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-895" srcset="https://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/image0-1024x1024.jpeg 1024w, https://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/image0-300x300.jpeg 300w, https://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/image0-150x150.jpeg 150w, https://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/image0-768x768.jpeg 768w, https://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/image0.jpeg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Listener Jennifer joins us to discuss her families first vacation with Adventures by Disney.  Besides being their first ABD experience, it was also her first time traveling out of the country with her children.  We have a fun time reliving all of their experiences and adventures along the way, and drop in a lot of tips for those of you thinking/planning your first trip out of the country with kids.  So sit back and relax, as we take you on an Adventure to England and France.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Contact Steve, Chris, or Christy:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="steve@dclpodcast.com"&gt;steve@dclpodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="christy@packyourpixiedust.com"&gt;christy@packyourpixiedust.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="brightdisneybychris@gmail.com"&gt;brightdisneybychris@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Follow us via:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/dclpodcast"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/dclpodcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.instagram.com/dcl_podcast"&gt;http://www.instagram.com/dcl_podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Support our show via Patreon:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.patreon.com/dclpodcast"&gt;http://www.patreon.com/dclpodcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Book your next Vacation with Christy:&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.packyourpixiedust.com"&gt;http://www.packyourpixiedust.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sekriese@comcast.net (DCL Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f87cccd650934fab9f03884839dcc113</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f87cccd650934fab9f03884839dcc113/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 16:43:32 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Books And Travel : Bhel Puri On The Beach, The Gateway To India, And Bollywood. Mumbai With Vikram Chandra</title><description>“Mumbai may not be my city, but it is my kind of city.” Vikas Swarup, author of Q&amp;amp;A, adapted into the film, Slumdog Millionaire.&lt;br /&gt;
Mumbai is a fascinating city with diversity in religion and architecture, and in this interview, Vikram Chandra talks about the colonial impact of the Portuguese and British, as well as the Zoroastrian, Muslim, Hindu and Christian holy places in the city.&lt;br /&gt;
It’s also a feast for the senses, as Vikram evokes the taste of seafood from the harbor and the chaat street food on the beaches, the clang of ships in the dock, as well as the action spectacle of Bollywood films, and the multi-lingual speech of Hindi, Punjabi, English and Bombay slang. &lt;br /&gt;
We discuss how Vikram feels at home both in Mumbai where he grew up and in the Bay area, California, where he now lives and teaches, and he gives some book recommendations if you want to read more about the city.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.vikramchandra.com" target="_blank" rel="attachment noopener wp-att-1293 noreferrer"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Vikram Chandra is the multi-award-winning author of &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2tYzEaD" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Red Earth and Pouring Rain&lt;/a&gt;, which won the Commonwealth Writers Prize for best first book as well as &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2SwtCHP" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Love and Longing in Bombay&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2SuXNPN" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Sacred Games&lt;/a&gt;, adapted into a successful Netflix series set in Mumbai, which has just been listed on ‘The New York Times’ list of the &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/20/arts/television/best-international-tv-shows.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;30 best international TV shows of the decade&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
Show notes&lt;br /&gt;
* On the cultural history of the name Mumbai — and why some still call the city, Bombay.&lt;br /&gt;
* Impact of colonial history — Portuguese and British — on the architecture of Mumbai&lt;br /&gt;
* Religious diversity&lt;br /&gt;
* Bollywood and modern Indian films&lt;br /&gt;
* Influence of the coastal environment&lt;br /&gt;
* Food and restaurant recommendations&lt;br /&gt;
* Tips for getting around the city&lt;br /&gt;
* The challenge of representing the multilingual nature of India in fiction&lt;br /&gt;
* Recommended books set in Mumbai&lt;br /&gt;
You can find Vikram Chandra at &lt;a href="https://www.vikramchandra.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;VikramChandra.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Transcript of the interview&lt;br /&gt;
Joanna: Vikram Chandra is the multi-award-winning author of Red Earth and Pouring Rain, which won the Commonwealth Writers Prize for best first book as well as Love and Longing in Bombay and Sacred Games, adapted into a successful Netflix series set in Mumbai, which has just been listed on ‘The New York Times’ list of the 30 best international TV shows of the decade, which is amazing.&lt;br /&gt;
Welcome, Vikram.&lt;br /&gt;
Vikram: Hi. Pleasure to be here.&lt;br /&gt;
Joanna: I’ve been so excited about this because I love India so much.&lt;br /&gt;
Tell us a bit more about your multicultural background and your connection with the city.&lt;br /&gt;
Vikram: My father was a corporate executive, so we’d moved all over the countryside when I was a kid. And then when I was in 11th grade, we moved to the city and we’ve been there ever since.&lt;br /&gt;
I came to the United States in my second year of college and I’ve been going back and forth ever since. All of my work has to do with Bombay as you can tell from the titles of at least one of my books. And my immediate family and a lot of my friends are there.&lt;br /&gt;
Joanna: Fantastic. I haven’t been but I did want to ask you because it’s so interesting, I always say Mumbai because I thought that’s what we have to say now. But you use the term Bombay in your book title.&lt;br /&gt;
What is the cultural history of the name Mumbai/Bombay?&lt;br /&gt;
Vikram: There are various stories about how the city got its name. So there are texts written in the early 16th century which refers to the ci...</description><author>jo@booksandtravel.page (Books And Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1c51da112d804f69a21566dbd2cc7a2b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1c51da112d804f69a21566dbd2cc7a2b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 16:10:35 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>San Francisco Real Estate: Escrow Out Loud : A Bridge (Loan) To Your Next Home</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In today’s episode of &lt;a href="https://jacksonfuller.com/insight/podcast/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Escrow Out Loud, our San Francisco Real Estate podcast&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;u&gt;,&lt;/u&gt; we are talking about bridge loans with our special guest from Opes Advisers, sales manager and senior loan advisor Tracy Andreini.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[00:40] A lot of people think about selling their property at this time of year. The nice thing about bridge loans is that they make it possible for people to buy their next home allowing them to move out and stage their house for sale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[01:04] We have been working with Opes for over a decade now. Tracy tells us a little bit about Opes Advisers and her background. She also explains what a bridge loan is and what are some of its major benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[06:24] One feature of bridge loans is that they are short term loans, typically having a term of only six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[07:21] Another feature is that with a bridge loan there are no monthly payments. The only out of pocket costs are the 3% initial deposit and closing costs. Tracy explains how this works.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[09:12] The interest rates on a bridge loan are time plus 2.5. Currently this would be 7.25%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[10:18] What is the difference between a bridge loan and a regular equity line? Tracy goes over some issues with a HELOC that you don’t get with a bridge loan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[13:32] If anyone has more questions or wishes to apply for a bridge loan Tracy recommends getting in touch with her on her cell-phone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[14:00] Tracy talks about appraisals required for a bridge loan. What is different to the normal process that’s good to be aware of?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[15:38] As we learned earlier a bridge loan is a six month product and this is sufficient for a large majority of cases. But what happens when the six month period goes by and the house has still not sold? Are there extensions given?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[17:18] Most people are not aware of this product but it takes a lot of anxiety and pressure away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[18:38] Matt wraps up with a quick summary of points covered today!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for listening. If you enjoyed this episode leave us a review on your favorite platform, tell your friends and don’t forget to join us again next week!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info+5ab02d3b627e02027cf8604d@mg.pippa.io (San Francisco Real Estate: Escrow Out Loud)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2ef1889eed194be88f4554cb954e0166</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2ef1889eed194be88f4554cb954e0166/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 12:04:35 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Theme Park Rangers : Behind the scenes at Madame Tussauds – The care and feeding of wax figures (Ep. 38)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A look behind the scenes of Madame Tussauds revealed Wonder Woman in curlers, Will Smith missing an earring and Ryan Gosling in a state of disarray. Learn how the staff gets these wax stars camera-ready.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;The care and feeding of wax figures (2:11)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;Wonder Woman in curlers? (4:20)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;Early morning inspection (5:47)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;How to get your best picture (7:23)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;Don’t steal Will Smith’s earring (7:50)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;Ryan Gosling has a hickey (8:33)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;Wax figure casualties: Ears (9:32)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;The making of a wax figure (10:10)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;Madame Tussauds was a real woman (12:47)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;Mixing modern technology with old practices (13:39)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;When wax figure leave the museum (14:24)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;Celebrity side-by-sides (15:37)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;Getting Justin Bieber’s tattoos just right (16:10)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f8f7a-0-0"&gt;Icon Park details (19:22)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>video@orlandosentinel.com (Theme Park Rangers)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ab24b7b2a2e44c59ba4455dbad72b61b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ab24b7b2a2e44c59ba4455dbad72b61b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 11:56:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>EarzUp!  : EarzUp! In-Depth | Episode #15</title><description>Photo courtesy of Disney



If you want to see the best of Disneyland, like the new "Magic Happens" parade, be prepared to pay more than ever, as both Disneyland and Disney World rolled out new pricing structures recently. We also talk about, the coronavirus and its impact on Hong Kong Disneyland, and some current lawsuits happening now. It's all exciting, as usual.</description><author>jason@earzup-podcast.com (EarzUp! )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">aba82cd6e30143abb0c591097a8709cc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/aba82cd6e30143abb0c591097a8709cc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 11:11:43 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>CruiseTipsTV Unplugged - Cruise Tips and More : The Unwritten Guide to Cruise Courtesies</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode we are sharing what we call "The unwritten guide to cruise courtesies". These are things that the Cruise line won't necessarily tell you about, but they are good habits of seasoned cruisers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As always, you can email us your questions at  sheri@cruisetipstv.com. We'd also LOVE if you'd leave a review where you listen to this podcast, and screen shot the show and share it on Instagram using the hashtag #cttvunplugged.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Download our shore day bag checklist, and more cruise packing and planning checklists &amp; videos by joining the CruiseTipsTV Academy. We have a special discount code for our podcast listeners. To redeem the $5.00 discount on our master class enter code UNPLUGGED at &lt;a href= "http://academy.cruisetipstv.com"&gt;http://academy.cruisetipstv.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@cruisetipstv.com (CruiseTipsTV Unplugged - Cruise Tips and More)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">88154135045143c1b7da1bc032125cc0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/88154135045143c1b7da1bc032125cc0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Have Camper Will Travel : Making A Tiny House A Home + Sharing A New Perspective on Infertility w/ Abigail Sikma</title><description>&lt;p&gt;After marrying her high school sweetheart and deciding to make the best out of their 4+ year struggle with infertility, Abigail (Aby) and her husband sold their house and made the decision to live tiny. “..We wanted to do something with what stones we were given.” In today's episode, you'll hear about her journey with PCOS, infertility and how they made the best out of their situation. Aby is also sharing her best tips to make a tiny house a home, and how to start a blog that can turn into a business.&lt;/p&gt;

--- 

Send in a voice message: https://anchor.fm/havecamperwilltravel/message</description><author>podcasts44+529f5e0@anchor.fm (Have Camper Will Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e91025b7078a4da0812c464974dbd1fc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e91025b7078a4da0812c464974dbd1fc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Parklandia : I Was Promised Bison: Yellowstone Part 2 Full Throttle</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On our Yellowstone first-parter, we talked about both of our individual first trips to America’s O.G. national park, along with info on thermal features and a supervolcano that you don’t really need to worry about. Now it’s time for the sequel episode, Yellowstone: Full Throttle. Because just like that insane sequel to Charlie's Angels, our part 2 episode of Yellowstone is filled with stunts and sights that defy logic and possibility. And subbing in for Cameron Diaz, Drew Barrymore, and Lucy Liu, we have the two of us and Finn. And grizzly bears instead of an evil Demi Moore. Plus, we'll sit down with Parklandia's researcher, Jesslyn Shields, to talk about biodiversity! There’s a lot of ground for us to cover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Parklandia on Instagram at &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/parklandiapod/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;@parklandiapod&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, join the Parklandia Rangers &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/ParklandiaRangers/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and Like our &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/parklandiapod/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Parklandia)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">233c61bde24f4d78b1b21705873c0823</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/233c61bde24f4d78b1b21705873c0823/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>New Books in African Studies : Peter Cole, "Dockworker Power: Race and Activism in Durban and the San Francisco Bay Area" (U Illinois Press, 2018)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/0252083768/?tag=newbooinhis-20"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dockworker Power: Race and Activism in Durban and the San Francisco Bay Area&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (University of Illinois Press, 2018) is a fascinating, densely researched account of dockworkers and their organized responses to seismic economic and technological changes in the shipping industry between the 1940s and 1970s. &lt;a href="http://www.wiu.edu/cas/history/cole.php"&gt;Peter Cole&lt;/a&gt; examines the International Longshore and Warehouse Union (ILWU) and San Francisco’s Local 10 from its desegregation through its involvement in local and regional civil rights and anti-apartheid struggles. In Durban, Cole shows how South African unionists’ used stay-aways and strikes to fight racial capitalism, ultimately setting off a wave of protest in the early 1970s, only a few years before the Soweto Uprisings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dockworker Power&lt;/em&gt; is a refreshing mixture of two methodological approaches that situates the study of black internationalism among workers. Cole boosts our understanding of the radical tradition on the world’s docks by dexterously shifting between comparative and transnational analysis. This approach importantly reveals the global consequences of containerization on workers who tried to insulate themselves from the excesses of technological change. Cole’s book shows the significance of dockworkers as power-players in regional politics, the world economy, and transnational social movements, as they fought for, established, and wielded their collective power to secure their own prosperity and assist others in struggles near and far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Amanda Joyce Hall is a Ph.D. Candidate in History and African American Studies at Yale University. She is writing an international history on the global movement against South African apartheid during the 1970s and 1980s. She tweets from @amandajoycehall&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marshallpoe@gmail.com (New Books in African Studies)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8ced4fe85204443d9216723ebfb5616f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8ced4fe85204443d9216723ebfb5616f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Disney Cruise Line Show : #006 - Alaska Cruises on Disney Cruise Line</title><description>02/19/20 - In this episode, the Pete and Sean share their experience from their 2019 Alaskan cruise on Disney Cruise Line sailing out of Vancouver up the Inside Passage to Dawes Glacier with stops at Skagway, Juneau, and Ketchikan!</description><author>craig@disneyinfo.com (The Disney Cruise Line Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2a6e5c6498164618ad1ce22a1ec6e0c0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2a6e5c6498164618ad1ce22a1ec6e0c0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Morocco : Why Morocco 031 – Touria El Glaoui on the 1:54 Contemporary African Art Fair</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With the third edition of the &lt;a href="https://www.1-54.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;1-54 Contemporary African Art Fair&lt;/a&gt; kicking off on 20 February 2020 in Marrakech, I chatted with fair founder Touria el Glaoui by telephone in the lead up to the event. The fair is designed to provide exposure to artists from the 54 countries that make up the continent. Touria talked about the changing landscape and dialogue surrounding African contemporary art since she began researching the idea for an African contemporary art fair about ten years ago. Touria launched the first 1-54 Contemporary African Art Fair in in London in 2013 before travelling to New York in 2015 and finally to Marrakech in 2018. And today, the fair is one of the highlights of my social calendar each year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With galleries openings, studio visits, talks and roundtables, and meetings with artists planned throughout the four-day event, the programme is rich!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Listen is as Touria talks about the fair, the contemporary art industry, and what visitors can expect during the third edition of the 1:54 Contemporary African Art Fair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more Morocco ideas and advise, follow me on Instagram at &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/mandyinmorocco" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;@mandyinmorocco&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My other projects include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tasting Marrakech food and cultural tours in Marrakech &lt;a href="http://tasting-marrakech.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;tasting-marrakech.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel and public relations consulting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Freelance writing for print and digital  &lt;a href="https://mandyinmorocco.com/freelance-writing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;mandyinmorocco.com/freelance-writing/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>mandyjsinclair@gmail.com (Why Morocco)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e2c08780a105483ab9364c221dbf70d3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e2c08780a105483ab9364c221dbf70d3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 19:56:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Rebecca Enchanted: A Disney Planning Podcast : Amy’s Walt Disney World RunDisney Trip Report, Episode 65</title><description>Hear all about Amy’s RunDisney experience and Walt Disney World trip! Follow Amy on Instagram: alarsen.ariseandshinefitness or on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/alarsen.ariseandshinefitness/. You can learn more about RunDisney training here: https://www.rundisney.com/running-training-programs/. This episode is sponsored by FTM Travel, info@ftmtravel.com or www.ftmtravel.com. Intro/outro music by Cooper Adair.</description><author>podcasts7+423b7e4@anchor.fm (Rebecca Enchanted: A Disney Planning Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fe4f27531d4a4081ab431c0d12407a9d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fe4f27531d4a4081ab431c0d12407a9d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 14:18:46 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>La Lido Loca Cruise Podcast : 11. The Perfect Sea Day!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to episode #11 of the La Lido Loca podcast.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Join Jenny and Tony as they talk about cruising!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show Notes:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on YouTube:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;La Lido Loca Podcast: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCLoGEyIWH6f6mkJxDCweDag"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCLoGEyIWH6f6mkJxDCweDag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;La Lido Loca Cruising: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqFivW2VWJtGfvrMreyjNbw"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqFivW2VWJtGfvrMreyjNbw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Let Jenny help with your travel, you can contact her at: &lt;a href= "mailto:jbarnette@cruiseshipcenters.com"&gt;jbarnette@cruiseshipcenters.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Info about La Lido Loca Group Cruises: &lt;a href="http://www.lalidoloca.com/groupcruise" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;http://www.lalidoloca.com/groupcruise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on Social Media: Facebook Page - &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt; Instagram - &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt; Twitter - &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/lalidoloca" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://twitter.com/lalidoloca&lt;/a&gt; Pintrest - &lt;a href="https://www.pinterest.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.pinterest.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Represent the locafam with a t-shirt, check out the latest designs at: &lt;a href="https://teespring.com/stores/lalidoloca-funshop" target= "_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://teespring.com/stores/lalidoloca-funshop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our mailing address is: La Lido Loca 4142 Mariner Blvd #402 Spring Hill, FL 34609&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Support our creative efforts at Patreon: &lt;a href="http://www.patreon.com/lalidoloca" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;http://www.patreon.com/lalidoloca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Please Submit Questions or Comments to &lt;a href= "mailto:tony@lalidoloca.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;tony@lalidoloca.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tony@lalidoloca.com (La Lido Loca Cruise Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c6ccd0f24c6a41bda4e0e07db007794f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c6ccd0f24c6a41bda4e0e07db007794f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 09:46:15 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Curiosityness : 076 Stonehenge: It’s Not Really a Mystery | Susan Greaney</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It’s a bit of a misnomer to say that Stonehenge is a mystery. We actually know a lot about the structure, the people who built it, and why they built it. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tune in to learn all about Stonehenge!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To learn more about Stonehenge, visit &lt;a href= "https://www.english-heritage.org.uk/"&gt;https://www.english-heritage.org.uk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Curiosityness...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/curiositynesspodcast/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/curiositynesspodcast/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Website: &lt;a href= "https://www.curiosityness.com/"&gt;https://www.curiosityness.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Facebook: &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/curiosityness"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/curiosityness&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Twitter: &lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/Curiositynesstv"&gt;https://twitter.com/Curiositynesstv&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Claim your FREE Curiosityness sticker at &lt;a href= "https://www.curiosityness.com/freesticker/"&gt;https://www.curiosityness.com/freesticker/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Find me, the host of Curiosityness on Instagram: &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/travderose/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/travderose/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Or send me an email to &lt;a href= "mailto:travis@curiosityness.com"&gt;travis@curiosityness.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>travis@curiosityness.com (Curiosityness)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3d4005ca02d2493189165980b0c1de04</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3d4005ca02d2493189165980b0c1de04/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Exploring the North Shore : Episode 21: Snowshoeing + Interview with Ashley Bredemus, Emily Theisen, &amp; Jordan Mileski</title><description>&lt;p&gt;What an episode we have for you! To kick things off, Martha is back! Jaye and Martha hit the Gunflint Trail and find themselves on a snowshoeing adventure on the Honeymoon Bluff Trail. Listen in as Martha enjoys her very first snowshoe experience. Be sure to check out the video companion to this episode on our YouTube channel (&lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCq-_rqJ-kkCLud4NlJljFVQ'&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCq-_rqJ-kkCLud4NlJljFVQ&lt;/a&gt;) as the audio does not do their shenanigans justice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out the Snowshoeing Guide on Exploring the North Shore for more tips and tricks to getting out and enjoy the Northwoods in the wintertime: &lt;a href='https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/snowshoeing/'&gt;https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/snowshoeing/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, Jaye sits down with three local Instagram influencers you will want to follow if you enjoy following outdoor adventure Instagram accounts. Ashley Bredemus documents her life living in the Pepper Shack, a small, secluded cabin at the end of the Gunflint Trail. But, really, it's her dog Arlo's Instagram. She just guest stars every now and then! Emily and Jordan do not live on the North Shore, but they are frequent visitors and their outdoor adventures will inspire you! Listen in as they talk about what they love most about the North Shore, and, of course, their favorite lake!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Ashley: &lt;a href='https://www.instagram.com/ashleybredemus'&gt;https://www.instagram.com/ashleybredemus&lt;/a&gt;Follow Emily: &lt;a href='https://www.instagram.com/emilytheisen_'&gt;https://www.instagram.com/emilytheisen_&lt;/a&gt;Follow Jordan: &lt;a href='https://www.instagram.com/jordan.mileski/'&gt;https://www.instagram.com/jordan.mileski/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We apologize for the audio quality in the interview half of the episode. The conditions were interesting! But we hope you listen in, lots of good information!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ashley runs the Birchwood Wilderness Camp for Boys, along with her father. You can find more information on sending your son on a Boundary Waters Canoe Area Wilderness Adventure by visiting their website: &lt;a href='https://birchwoodwildernesscamp.com/'&gt;https://birchwoodwildernesscamp.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This episode is sponsored by &lt;a href='https://www.cascadevacationrentals.com/'&gt;Cascade Vacation Rentals&lt;/a&gt;. Use promo code "Podcast" at check-out to receive Cascade's largest available percent off discount (discount changes seasonally). This episode is also sponsored by &lt;a href='https://thebiglakelife.com/'&gt;The Big Lake&lt;/a&gt;. Use promo code "Explore" at check-out to receive 15% off your first online order. Thank you to our wonderful sponsors!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marketing@staycvr.com (Exploring the North Shore)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">18ea067467c347f4ade31e6ba0ea0cd2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/18ea067467c347f4ade31e6ba0ea0cd2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 04:45:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>A Way To Go : Advocating for Millions of Refugees and Displaced People, with Susan McPherson</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For many of us, travel is about vacations and special occasions. For 71 million refugees and displaced people around the world, travel is about survival. Susan McPherson, a board member for USA for the United Nations High Commission for Refugees, shares what she’s witnessed in such global hotspots as the border of Venezuela and Colombia and the camps in Jordan — and gives us reasons for hope and strategies to help. Find more info about this episode at &lt;a href="https://urldefense.proofpoint.com/v2/url?u=http-3A__Fathomaway.com&amp;amp;d=DwMFaQ&amp;amp;c=GC0NZZhaEw6GOQSjMHI2g15k_drElRoPmOYiK2k0eZ8&amp;amp;r=QQqtrehlQRY19SGPJ2205twNczy34pobDq7ZUMRMscQ&amp;amp;m=uAppD4M5dBD29M_K0sdL8a7sHEzsc4WrXMOC1-_zau0&amp;amp;s=O9qN4bd5qTtxocz3Ga9z11cQkvNhfrURazO38N5oYNs&amp;amp;e="&gt;Fathomaway.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (A Way To Go)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">20e8558e9b444e5280cc7940e7d73525</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/20e8558e9b444e5280cc7940e7d73525/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The One Way Ticket Show : Bret Stephens - NY Times Op-Ed Columnist &amp; Associate Editor</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Bret Stephens is an Op-Ed Columnist and Associate Editor for the New York Times since 2017. Mr. Stephens began his newspaper career at the Wall Street Journal in 1998 as an editor in New York, and later wrote editorials and articles for the newspaper from Brussels. In January 2002, at age 28, he was named editor-in-chief of the Jerusalem Post at the height of the second intifada.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Mr. Stephens returned to the Wall Street Journal in late 2004 and reported from around the world and interviewed dozens of world leaders, including Presidents Bush, Obama, and Trump and every Israeli Prime Minister since Shimon Peres. In June 2017 he added senior political analyst for NBC to his portfolio.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He is the recipient of the 2013 Pulitzer Prize for distinguished commentary, awarded to him “for his incisive columns on American foreign policy and domestic politics, often enlivened by a contrarian twist.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;His essays and articles have appeared in Foreign Affairs, Commentary magazine and many other publications. He is a frequent guest on RealTime With Bill Maher, Morning Joe, Hardball and many other news and talk shows.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Mr. Stephens has twice been chairman of Pulitzer Prize juries and is a national judge of the Livingston Awards for young journalists. He holds three honorary doctorates, most recently from Yeshiva University, and many other distinctions from organizations dedicated to promoting the values of liberal democracy in the face of rising populism and authoritarianism.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He is the author of "America In Retreat: The New Isolationism and the Coming Global Disorder," which was published in 2014 to wide acclaim.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Mr. Stephens is a widely acclaimed public speaker. In 2017 he delivered the Daniel Pearl Memorial Lecture at UCLA, later republished in Time magazine and read by over two million people.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Mr. Stephens was born in New York and raised in Mexico City. He holds a Bachelor of Arts with honors from the University of Chicago and a Master’s of Science from the London School of Economics. He is married to Corinna da Fonseca-Wollheim, a classical music and opera critic for the New York Times. They live in New York City with their three children.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On this episode, Bret shares his one-way ticket to New York City in 2112 and what the future holds for both him and Gotham. He also shares his thoughts on the band RUSH, the regeneration of cities and societies, and what every budding journalist should know.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Bret is just one of the dynamic personalities featured on The One Way Ticket Show, where Host Steven Shalowitz explores with his guests where they would go if given a one way ticket, no coming back! Destinations may be in the past, present, future, real, imaginary or a state of mind.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Steven's guests have included: Nobel Peace Prize Winner, President Jose Ramos-orta; Legendary Talk Show Host, Dick Cavett; Law Professor, Alan Dershowitz; Fashion Expert, Tim Gunn; Broadcast Legend, Charles Osgood; International Rescue Committee President &amp; CEO, David Miliband; Playwright, David Henry Hwang; Journalist-Humorist-Actor, Mo Rocca; SkyBridge Capital Founder &amp; Co-Managing Partner, Anthony Scaramucci; Abercrombie &amp; Kent Founder, Geoffrey Kent; Travel Expert, Pauline Frommer, as well as leading photographers, artists, chefs, writers, intellectuals and more.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>steven@theonewayticketshow.com (The One Way Ticket Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">afeecade65314aa0992fba1ea01fb8b2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/afeecade65314aa0992fba1ea01fb8b2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dreams Unlimited Travel Show - A Weekly Discussion About Travel and Dreams Unlimited Travel : #171 - Top 5 Money Savings Tips for a Walt Disney World Vacation - John Magi &amp; Kevin Klose</title><description>02/18/20 - In this episode, Dreams Unlimited Travel owner John Magi and Dreams Unlimited Travel Client Services Manager Kevin Klose shares their personal top five tips to help you save money for your Walt Disney World Vacation!</description><author>craig@wdwinfo.com (Dreams Unlimited Travel Show - A Weekly Discussion About Travel and Dreams Unlimited Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e2b7ca9ea9104800ab49d8732d1cb4ba</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e2b7ca9ea9104800ab49d8732d1cb4ba/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Living Adventurously : What you don't know you can learn by doing - Living Adventurously 17</title><description>Tim Frenneaux is a former martial arts instructor, nine to fiver and audio visual artist, turned ethical entrepreneur, microadventurer, climate activist and punk philosopher. &lt;br&gt;His redemption started when the brief and fragile nature of existence became painfully real as he hit the big 40 in the same month that his Dad died. Unhappy conjunctures like that are a great way of forcing you to focus on what you want from “your one wild and precious life” (to quote the dear departed Mary Oliver)Tim decided to return to the outdoor life that had brought him so much happiness growing up, and that the best way to make the difference he wanted to see in the world, was to start a business founded on social and environmental principles: &lt;a href="https://gatheroutdoors.co.uk/"&gt;Gather Outdoors.&lt;/a&gt;Now he’s on a mission to encourage and enable folk to make the most of their fleeting presence on planet earth by spending more time outdoors. In doing so he hopes that great teacher, Mother Earth, will help them to reach their own understanding of the immense value of nature.&lt;h1&gt;&lt;a href="https://livingadventurously.transistor.fm/subscribe"&gt;PLEASE SUBSCRIBE TO THE LIVING ADVENTUROUSLY PODCAST&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(It’s completely free, zero hassle to do (&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://livingadventurously.transistor.fm/subscribe"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;click here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;), but really helpful for me trying to get a new podcast off the ground. If you’re feeling extra kind, please leave a review on the app – that really helps.)&lt;/strong&gt;Listen on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/living-adventurously/id1489454694"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/2aYqIdvtVJkhIPklHaoXA3"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=486751&amp;amp;refid=stpr"&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://tunein.com/podcasts/Storytelling-Podcasts/Living-Adventurously-p1275719/"&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt; (“Alexa, please play the Living Adventurously podcast”) or on your favourite podcast platform such as Overcast, &lt;a href="https://podcasts.google.com/?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9mZWVkcy50cmFuc2lzdG9yLmZtL2xpdmluZy1hZHZlbnR1cm91c2x5"&gt;Google Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, Pocket Casts, &lt;a href="https://www.breaker.audio/living-adventurously"&gt;Breaker&lt;/a&gt;, Soundcloud, Castbox, Castro.&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.alastairhumphreys.com/podcast"&gt;www.alastairhumphreys.com/podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;THIS PODCAST IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY KOMOOT&lt;/h1&gt;Your very own outdoor experiences are waiting for you. Go explore more with &lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;komoot&lt;/a&gt;. Use the voucher code &lt;a href="https://www.komoot.com/account/gift/?code=ADVENTUROUS"&gt;ADVENTUROUS&lt;/a&gt; to claim your free region maps bundle.The personalised planning and navigation tools ensure you plan the adventure that’s perfect for &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;. Komoot is Europe’s number 1 outdoor app, with route planning and navigation functionality, and strong community-driven inspirational features in the form of recommended Highlights and inspirational route Collections. It is used by nearly 10 million adventurers worldwide. Komoot is becoming the app of choice for cyclists and hikers the world over, with rapid community growth in the UK, the US and other parts of Europe. &lt;br&gt;You can see my ride’s route on komoot &lt;a href="https://www.komoot.com/collection/900116/-living-adventurously-podcast-tour"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;h1&gt;SHOW NOTES&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you enjoy listening to this episode over a cup of coffee and think it might be worth the price, you can &lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;buy me a coffee here:&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;www. ko-fi.com/al_humphreys&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep up to date with future episodes (and my other adventures, projects and books) with my &lt;a href="https://www.alastairhumphreys.com/more/subscribe/"&gt;free monthly newsletter: alastairhumphreys.com/more/subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Say hello on &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Al_Humphreys"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/al_humphreys/"&gt;Instagram: @al_humphreys&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://gatheroutdoors.co.uk/"&gt;Gather Outdoors website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Starting a business was an excuse to get outdoors more and meet interesting people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He feels guilty that his work doesn't feel like hard work and a struggle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compartmentalising work and not-work is an important thing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trying to rewild myself by reading lots of books&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The first step in changing direction is realising that things are not quite right.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The imposter syndrome is how everyone feels and shouldn't be a burden and a barrier&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What you don't know you can learn by doing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The modern day life experience cocoons us from the natural world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The importance of reading on paper versus a screen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We all have time; we just need to make time. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Turn off the screens and embrace boredom&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Barefoot running has made a big beneficial change to his life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Starting a business saw his income plummet, but also taught Tim and his family what is enough. It taught him about balance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recognise when you are slipping into a fur-lined rut, and then clamour to get out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" title="★ Support this podcast by donating ★" href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;★ Support this podcast by donating ★&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>alastair@alastairhumphreys.com (Living Adventurously)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">96c7707b38ea417aa5a3ace80a8443fb</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/96c7707b38ea417aa5a3ace80a8443fb/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Thoughtful Travel Podcast : 175 Walking and Hiking Travels</title><description>&lt;p&gt;If you've ever wondered what it's really like to head out for days or even months and just keep walking, Episode 175 of The Thoughtful Travel Podcast will give you many insights into hiking and walking experiences on your travels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I start off speaking with Laura Waters, who spent five months tramping from the top of New Zealand to the bottom. As you can imagine this is no easy feat at all (but there is a bonus to it all involving chocolate!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, Suzanne Moore describes a much shorter hike in Japan, and an experience that made us both laugh. Suzy will be back in a future episode describing a longer hike she did in south-west Australia - but this climb at Mt Yote is such a fun story!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, I chat to Rick Antonson who agreed - without even knowing where it was or anything about it - to walk the Kokoda Track with his neighbour. This was also not a simple trip but like nearly any trip that requires a lot of effort, it was incredibly rewarding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hiking When You Travel, Episode 124 - &lt;a href="http://notaballerina.com/124"&gt;notaballerina.com/124&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Laura Waters&amp;rsquo; website - &lt;a href="https://soultrekkers.com.au/"&gt;https://soultrekkers.com.au/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Laura&amp;rsquo;s book Bewildered - &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2S20zu2"&gt;https://amzn.to/2S20zu2&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suzanne Moore &lt;a href="https://www.suzannemoorewriter.com/"&gt;https://www.suzannemoorewriter.com/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suzanne&amp;rsquo;s book The Place Between - &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/31KM6aD"&gt;https://amzn.to/31KM6aD&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rick Antonson - &lt;a href="http://www.rickantonson.com"&gt;www.rickantonson.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rick&amp;rsquo; book Walking With Ghosts in Papua New Guinea - &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/37n1fzS"&gt;https://amzn.to/37n1fzS&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join our Facebook group for Thoughtful Travellers -&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/thoughtfultravellers"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/thoughtfultravellers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show notes: &lt;a href="http://notaballerina.com/175"&gt;https://notaballerina.com/175&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>amandakendle@me.com (The Thoughtful Travel Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0085e7f38eeb49c485486df2c4c30d23</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0085e7f38eeb49c485486df2c4c30d23/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 14:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind The Glass : [S3, E4] How To Make Money From YouTube w/ Adnan Ebrahim</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Tony and I are joined by Car Throttle founder, Adnan Ebrahim. Whilst most of you might know Alex &amp;amp; Ethan as the 'face' of Car Throttle, Adnan was the brains behind the scenes, building an empire out of nothing and recently selling the business to Dennis Publishing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adnan's story is fascinating and provides a great insight in to one of the ways you can make money from social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;06:17 - Who Is Adnan Ebrahim&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;08:45 - How Did Car Throttle Start&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;11:40 - How Did Car Throttle Grow&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;18:45 - Are Entrepreneurs Born or Made?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;21:30 - How Did Car Throttle Secure Investment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;27:30 - Growing the Car Throttle Empire&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;30:00 - How Did STG &amp;amp; Car Throttle Meet?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;32:00 - STG Was Part of the Car Throttle Family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;38:00 - Alex Loves Sh*tboxes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;43:00 - What Next For Adnan&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;45:00 - The Pressure of YouTube&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;51:00 - Should We Be Scared of TikTok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;59:30 - Adnan's Nissan GTR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>info@seenthroughglass.com (Behind The Glass)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0b38be19b173460886ad88f4257cb822</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0b38be19b173460886ad88f4257cb822/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 08:59:22 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Disney Vacation Club Show : #052 - Best DVC Resort for Foodies</title><description>02/17/20 - In this episode, the panel discusses the results of a DVC Fan poll about which resort is the best for foodies!</description><author>craig@disneyinfo.com (The Disney Vacation Club Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ef2147c8e00744bbafd85065d204ae67</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ef2147c8e00744bbafd85065d204ae67/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>We Travel There with Lee Huffman : Boston, MA | Freedom Trail, Lobster Rolls and Cannolis with Kali</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We're in Boston, Massachusetts with Kali Roberge of BeyondYourHammock.com. Kali and I talk about walking the Freedom Trail, where to find the best lobster rolls, and eating pizza at Regina’s in the North End.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show notes are at &lt;a href="https://WeTravelThere.com/boston" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://WeTravelThere.com/boston&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Miles &amp; points make travel affordable, but tracking them is difficult. That's why I use AwardWallet to monitor my rewards, reservations, &amp; free night certificates. Sign up for free at &lt;a href="https://WeTravelThere.com/awardwallet" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;WeTravelThere.com/awardwallet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wetravelthere@gmail.com (We Travel There with Lee Huffman)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3b28b79e9c0b4b00874954c5b48e9b92</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3b28b79e9c0b4b00874954c5b48e9b92/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hoosier Outdoorsmen Podcast : Episode 38 talking to Jordan Fromer about Duck Gun Chronicles and the Duck Gun Podcast</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this Episode I talk to Jordan Fromer about his youtube channel The&amp;nbsp; Duck Gun&amp;nbsp; Chronicles&amp;nbsp; his podcast The Duck Gun Podcast. We also talked about his duck and goose season this year.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Rileyhendrixson@live.com (The Hoosier Outdoorsmen Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1687583342494085807b1c86e4e6538d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1687583342494085807b1c86e4e6538d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Puerto Vallarta Travel  Show Podcast : La Isla Fashion Village in Puerto Vallarta, Mexico</title><description>&lt;p&gt;La Isla Fashion Village is a Beautiful Outdoor Shopping Mall in Puerto Vallarta, Mexico. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>pvtravelshow@gmail.com (Puerto Vallarta Travel  Show Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">23a9467bd07e479cb97abb31b9a2c743</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/23a9467bd07e479cb97abb31b9a2c743/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 14:08:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ohio Folklore : Rogues Hollow</title><description>Few Ohioans know the tale of Rogues Hollow, a small tract of wilderness in coal territory.  It became known for its lawlessness and unbridled violence during the 19th century.  Its history provokes scenes reminiscent of the Wild West.  All this, here in our own backyard.

Come hear the story of one Ohio Folklore listener who claims to have encountered a full-bodied apparition there, at Chidester Mill.  This replica of an original 1828 structure remains today, and is open to the public during the summer months.  It seems someone, however, stays all year round, guarding the place.

Don’t say I didn’t warn you.

You never know what you’ll encounter in these hills.

If you enjoy this episode, please rate, review and subscribe to Ohio Folklore on your chosen podcast platform.  You can also find Ohio Folklore at:

ohiofolklore.com
facebook.com/ohiofolklore

And as always, keep wondering…</description><author>melissa.davies77@outlook.com (Ohio Folklore)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6dd486fbcef749419d1d7458aedf3f4f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6dd486fbcef749419d1d7458aedf3f4f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 13:15:17 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Wise About Texas : Ep. 79: Dorie Miller–A Texas War Hero</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On December 7, 1941, Mess Attendant Doris &amp;#8220;Dorie&amp;#8221; Miller was doing laundry, one of the few jobs available to African American sailors in the U.S. Navy at the time.  When his ship came under attack, Miller rushed to help his fellow sailors.  Though not trained, and not allowed, he manned an anti-aircraft gun and engaged the attacking Japanese planes.  For his bravery and his willingness to go above and beyond the call of duty, Miller was the first African American to be awarded the Navy Cross.  But his heroism affected not only the Navy, but the entire military.  Recently, the U.S. Navy announced yet another tribute to Dorie Miller, a Texas war hero.  Learn more about this brave Texan in the latest episode of Wise About Texas.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/WiseAboutTexas/~4/8ltz90sgCH8" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>Host@wiseabouttexas.com (Wise About Texas)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">45d0f5ccc78b4db780914bceb5c9aa85</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/45d0f5ccc78b4db780914bceb5c9aa85/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 12:11:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Join Us in France Travel Podcast : An Assortment of French Movies, Episode 271</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Annie and Elyse love a great assortment of cookies, but they also love a great assortment of French movies, which is what we bring you on today's episode!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;One of our listeners asked a thought-provoking question: what French movies portrait France well? And while we were thinking about that, several people pipped in with the name of their favorite French movies.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The thing is, a French person's idea of a great French movie is not the same as what English speakers consider good French movies. The most popular movies in France are mostly silly. French people love nothing more than a good slap-stick comedy!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;My American friends love movies like The Hundred-Foot Journey. A feel-good movie that takes place in a mythical version of France. I went to Saint Antonin Noble Val to see where the movie was shot. I recognized nothing that looks like the movie at all. Having said that, Saint Antonin is still a nice place to visit.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:%20annie@joinusinfrance.com"&gt;Email&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://joinusinfrance.com/audiotours/"&gt;Annie's VoiceMap Paris Tour&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href= "https://www.facebook.com/joinusinfrance/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href= "https://www.pinterest.fr/France_Travel_Podcast/"&gt;Pinterest&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/addictedtofrance/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ParisPodcast"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;#joinusinfrance #frenchmovies #frenchculture #travel #podcast&lt;/p&gt; The Assortment of French Movies Discussed in this Episode &lt;p&gt;We don't present the movies and TV series in any particular order, we just followed our train of thought :-)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/37FtevP"&gt;Le Père Noël est une ordure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2uIab5m"&gt;Les Bronzés&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2GCpcsc"&gt;L'aile ou la cuisse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/3aWXsMD"&gt;La Chèvre&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2RZTkCZ"&gt;Le dîner de cons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2S529eX"&gt;Les Visiteurs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2u6gpvZ"&gt;La vérité si je mens&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2tfNrJK"&gt;100 foot journey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/31hsniF"&gt;Midnight in Paris&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/37GLbtZ"&gt;Amélie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2GzrtnM"&gt;Bienvenue chez les Ch'tis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/3aXbSwg"&gt;Les Intouchables&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2vzx6jQ"&gt;Asterix and Obelix&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2OdB2Nz"&gt;A Good Year&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2RUUUG8"&gt;Breathless (A bout de souffle)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The Passion of Joan of Arc&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A Trip to the Moon (???)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/3aUTLHp"&gt;The Grand Illusion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2OcpVEG"&gt;Chocolat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/38SlEhG"&gt;Ratatouille&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2RFqWHB"&gt;Les Revenants (TV Series)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/3aXG8Hp"&gt;The Chorus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A Very Secret Service (Au service de la France TV Series)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Versailles (TV)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A French Village (TV)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/36FajQq"&gt;Les Aventures de Rabi Jacob&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/318mCnd"&gt;Jean de Florette&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2OcgvZN"&gt;Manon des Sources&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/38Vgm4H"&gt;Camille Claudel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2u2Hy2S"&gt;Cyrano de Bergerac&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/3173ZQm"&gt;Le Chateau de Ma Mère&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/3173ZQm"&gt;La Gloire de Mon Père&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>annie@joinusinfrance.com (Join Us in France Travel Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">247aa938f755416b81331c41dcdb7dc4</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/247aa938f755416b81331c41dcdb7dc4/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>National Parks Traveler Podcast : National Parks Traveler: Special Report On The Colorado River, Grand Portage NM</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week’s show kicks off our coverage of the Colorado River and how its health, or lack of health, impacts Canyonlands National Park and Glen Canyon National Recreation Area in Utah. We also take a peek at Grand Portage National Monument in Minnesota and what awaits intrepid park travelers who put it on their to-do list.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>kurt@nationalparkstraveler.org (National Parks Traveler Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b582b3efbab54330ac62d47b2907b9de</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b582b3efbab54330ac62d47b2907b9de/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Australia All Over : Australia All Over highlights podcast</title><description>Some of Macca's most interesting phone calls from this week, plus a studio guest.</description><author>localfeedback@your.abc.net.au (Australia All Over)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ded7f8c942894ec8821cf7aeaa4298b1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ded7f8c942894ec8821cf7aeaa4298b1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 11:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>In Limbo : Smothered by Time- Lack of resources and nothing but time</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode we discuss how time is not always on your side when it comes to the formation of a rut. We will talk about how to dissolve it when working with limited resources.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts14+d507e9c@anchor.fm (In Limbo)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4f4f0ae75230492587df41a5e9c01fe2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4f4f0ae75230492587df41a5e9c01fe2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 11:54:12 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Coastin' the Country : Ep. 16: What should Cedar Point add in 2021?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Marcus Leshock talks with Cedar Point's Tony Clark about everything the amusement park is doing for their 150th season in 2020 - and we look ahead to what could be coming in 2021. We also talk about the latest news in the amusement park industry. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mleshock@wgntv.com (Coastin' the Country)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9b18cea5e498433f8c67b17a86346b6b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9b18cea5e498433f8c67b17a86346b6b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Monsters Among Us Podcast : Sn. 8 Ep. 20 Part 2 - Home Town Legends Season Finale!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Floyd Collins News Story -  &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yh3Oms7xwTQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3Dyh3Oms7xwTQ&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1581707331320000&amp;usg=AFQjCNGeslovZjDiZrrydBRLOVhPJGn1Rg"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yh3Oms7xwTQ&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Floyd Collins News Story (archive) - &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Trm-0bEZN14" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3DTrm-0bEZN14&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1581707331320000&amp;usg=AFQjCNG-J811w3vtWEtiF4k9OfkMm7aFhQ"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Trm-0bEZN14&lt;/a&gt;    Death of Floyd Collins - &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vb6GxUnPGgw" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3Dvb6GxUnPGgw&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1581707331320000&amp;usg=AFQjCNHZLIMwBzl8rYQZ6hadGFC2UzL5qw"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vb6GxUnPGgw&lt;/a&gt;   Brown Mountain Lights - &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w9SgUOuyzfg" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3Dw9SgUOuyzfg&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1581707331320000&amp;usg=AFQjCNGt5auVbdtNEXstD1J2QEaUL3ryZA"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w9SgUOuyzfg&lt;/a&gt;   Ball Lightning Video - &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s1iT8ITGZ0E" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3Ds1iT8ITGZ0E&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1581707331320000&amp;usg=AFQjCNGzXftA3ZkNSHP2dBGJTJ6xdKunJw"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s1iT8ITGZ0E&lt;/a&gt;   Ball Lightning Video Fake - &lt;a href= "https://www.snopes.com/fact-check/video-of-a-globular-bolt-real/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.snopes.com/fact-check/video-of-a-globular-bolt-real/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1581707331320000&amp;usg=AFQjCNHsNduDco4g8fGZea7IS9FZdpb4Lg"&gt;https://www.snopes.com/fact-check/video-of-a-globular-bolt-real/&lt;/a&gt;   Ghost Train Tragedy - &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eEgZT1fEVo8" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3DeEgZT1fEVo8&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1581707331320000&amp;usg=AFQjCNHKCdUL3Mg4NSFCJSydHV29Nse5vg"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eEgZT1fEVo8&lt;/a&gt;   Stories with Sapphire - &lt;a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5016598"&gt;https://audioboom.com/channels/5016598&lt;/a&gt;   Hillbilly Horror Stories - &lt;a href= "https://www.hillbillyhorrorstories.com/"&gt;https://www.hillbillyhorrorstories.com/&lt;/a&gt;   Donkey Tree - &lt;a href= "http://theresashauntedhistoryofthetri-state.blogspot.com/2018/04/the-donkey-tree-of-kentucky.html"&gt; http://theresashauntedhistoryofthetri-state.blogspot.com/2018/04/the-donkey-tree-of-kentucky.html&lt;/a&gt;       &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>monstersamonguspodcast@gmail.com (Monsters Among Us Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2ac1545bd9ac4d728213e30eaee88e8c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2ac1545bd9ac4d728213e30eaee88e8c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 13:52:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Biscuit CLT Podcast : CMCLT Rewind: Stacy Cassio</title><description>&lt;p&gt;At the February edition of Creative Mornings Charlotte held at The Comedy Zone, Stacy Cassio delivered a moving talk about the global theme of "Invest." As the head of Pink Mentor Network, Stacy is leading by example by investing in women in the city of Charlotte. Her organization is helping empower women by providing a network or resources and support, leading to a more equitable environment in the Queen City.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In today's CMCLT Rewind, Tim Miner and Matt Olin speak to Stacy immediately following her featured speech at The Comedy Zone about moving to Charlotte thirteen years ago, the feeling of not having a proper mentor network, and what she would say to someone becoming a mentor.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tim@charlotteiscreative.com (The Biscuit CLT Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">00b589d5c5ff4f7b9eaba011302f3c83</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/00b589d5c5ff4f7b9eaba011302f3c83/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Disneyland With Kids Podcast : Fastpass vs MaxPass: The Showdown!</title><description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is the debate we have been anticipating... Fastpass vs MaxPass! Two very similar systems to avoid the lines at Disneyland, but one is free and one is an additional charge. Find out the similarities, and which one may be right for you in this episode of the Disneyland with Kids Podcast.&lt;/p&gt; In This Episode - Fastpass and MaxPass at Disneyland: &lt;p&gt;Becca from &lt;a href= "https://thiscrazyadventurecalledlife.com"&gt;This Crazy Adventure Called Life&lt;/a&gt; and Leslie from &lt;a href= "https://tripswithtykes.com"&gt;Trips with Tykes&lt;/a&gt; have been waiting for this epsiode. Which one is better, Fastpass or MaxPass? The answer depends. We may have also had to bring in someone to moderate this debate to make sure we stuck to the facts and didn't get passionate about our personal bias towards each system.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Before we get into the show notes... Disneyland increased the price of MaxPass (and tickets) just days after we recorded, and the day before this episode went live. So it is important to note that ticket prices and MaxPass prices can change.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you are listening before February 20, 2020, you can still lock in the old prices of both MaxPass and Disneyland tickets through our partner at &lt;a href= "https://www.getawaytoday.com/?referrerid=7526"&gt;Get Away Today&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this episode we cover:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;What is the &lt;a href= "https://thiscrazyadventurecalledlife.com/disneylands-fastpass-maxpass-compare/"&gt; Fastpass System&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What attractions utilize the Fastpass system&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;How does traditional, free Fastpass work&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href= "https://tripswithtykes.com/disneyland-maxpass-questions-answered/"&gt; What is MaxPass&lt;/a&gt; and how does it work&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The down side to each system&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Who is Fastpass good for&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Who is MaxPass good for&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Why Leslie is responsible for the increase in MaxPass... Okay we don't outright say she is responsible for the latest increase, but listen to when we talk about how much she is willing to pay... totally her fault!&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts? &lt;a href= "https://www.loveourcrazylife.com/disneylands-maxpass-worth-cost/"&gt;Is MaxPass worth the new, higher cost&lt;/a&gt;? Tell us below!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Plan Your Disneyland Vacation:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you want to book a Disneyland vacation we suggest &lt;a title="Get Away Today" href= "https://www.getawaytoday.com/?referrerid=7526" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;booking through our partners at Get Away Today&lt;/a&gt;. If you are traveling in 2020, we suggest booking your vacations NOW to lock in the current ticket pricing. We expect ticket prices to go up in early 2020.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Want to connect with other Disneyland with Kids community members, receive and share tips, and more? &lt;a title="DwK Group" href= "https://facebook.com/groups/disneylandwithkids" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Join the Disneyland with Kids Group on Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect With The Hosts:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can connect with the hosts of Disneyland with Kids at the following locations:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leslie - &lt;a href= "https://tripswithtykes.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Trips with Tykes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Leslie on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Julie - &lt;a href= "https://momrewritten.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Mom Rewritten&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Julie on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/momrewritten"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/momrewritten" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/momrewritten" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Becca - &lt;a href= "https://thiscrazyadventurecalledlife.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;This Crazy Adventure Called Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Becca on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/crazyadventurecalledlife" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/thebeccarobins" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/thebeccarobins" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Jessica - &lt;a href= "https://thehappiestblogonearth.com"&gt;The Happiest Blog On Earth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Jessica on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>becca@disneylandwithkids.info (Disneyland With Kids Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3bd083a79fd64ab89a01027caa151b9f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3bd083a79fd64ab89a01027caa151b9f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 18:45:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Golden City : The Golden City E8 - The Tuesday Noon Siren</title><description>&lt;p&gt;For decades, every Tuesday at noon, San Francisco residents heard a siren followed by a public safety message via a network of loudspeakers. In a city that was forged in a crucible of earthquakes and fire, the 15-second message was a reminder to prepare for the worst — even if many residents ignored it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In December 2019, the city's &lt;a href="https://sfdem.org/tuesday-noon-siren"&gt;Department of Emergency Management&lt;/a&gt; announced that it was taking the system offline for two years to improve reliability and security in an overhaul that could cost as much as $2.5 million.&amp;nbsp;Now that the tradition has been interrupted, has the rhythm of city life lost a step? Also, who's likely to hear the Tuesday noon siren and what does it say about class and privilege?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And finally, what's in &lt;strong&gt;your&lt;/strong&gt; earthquake kit?&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Podcasts17+df5a6b0@anchor.fm (The Golden City)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fca5b68cf16f4fbfac63ba1a105fb882</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fca5b68cf16f4fbfac63ba1a105fb882/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 03:28:41 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Travel Like a Boss Podcast : Ep 242 – Kristy and Bryce (Minimalism, Digital Nomads vs. FIRE - Financial Independence Retire Early)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Kristy Shen and Bryce Leung are co-founders of Millenial Revolution, a platform dedicated to helping people find financial freedom and let them retire early – Financial Independence Retire Early (FIRE) Movement. They went against the status quo and managed to build a 7-figure portfolio, which allowed them to retire in their 30s and travel the world!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;During the episode, Kristy and Bryce give us a better understanding of the benefits of the FIRE movement and the Nomad movement. They share their own experiences and learning while on their nomad journey. They also share a ton of powerful points about becoming financially free and finding true happiness.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Links:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Website: &lt;a href= "https://www.millennial-revolution.com/"&gt;Millennial-Revolution.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Book: &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2uclouY"&gt;Quit Like a Millionaire&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Conference: &lt;a href= "http://nomadsummit.com"&gt;NomadSummit.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Youtube: &lt;a href= "http://youtube.com/nomadsummit"&gt;YouTube.com/NomadSummit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Sponsor:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Global Pass: &lt;a href= "https://www.coworker.com/pass"&gt;Coworker.com/Pass&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Time Stamps:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;02:23 – “It’s more about how to turn your money into a passive income stream” - Bryce Leung&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;02:29 – What does passive income mean?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;03:36 – How they started the FIRE and Nomad Movement&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;11:42 – How much is needed to become financially independent?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;12:35 – Advantages of combining both FIRE and Nomad Movement&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;16:04 – “You don’t need to start your own online business to become a digital nomad” - Bryce Leung&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;17:20 – Enjoying your life NOW&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;18:54 – “Now that we actually live this life, traveling the world, our health improved dramatically” – Kristy Shen&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;21:17 – Expenses in Toronto vs. Chiang Mai&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;22:42 – The downside of owning so much stuff&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;23:28 – “You don’t need to own a lot of things to be happy; it’s the experience that makes you happy” – Kristy Shen&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;33:15 – Why is it advisable to travel light?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;38:08 – What can the FIRE community learn from the nomad community?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;52:34 – Discovering Georgia&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;54:26 – What can the nomad community learn from the FIRE community?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;54:28 – “It’s not enough to earn money; you have to have a strategy on what to do about it” - Bryce Leung&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;1:03:21 – The Immigrant Rebound Effect&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;1:08:30 – What is the recipe for happiness?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Enjoyed this episode? Share it with friends!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>johnny@travellikeabosspodcast.com (Travel Like a Boss Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2be81364f28f4c578f60475e3daa0dbd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2be81364f28f4c578f60475e3daa0dbd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 14:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dish Food Travel Show : 50 Dream Menu I</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We create our dream menus - A four course meal made up of the best dishes we've ever eaten after traveling to 95 countries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our dream menu special - celebrating reaching our 50th episode of &lt;a href='https://foodfuntravel.com/thedish/'&gt;The Dish&lt;/a&gt; podcast, is a homage to one of our favourite food comedy podcasts, &lt;a href='https://www.offmenupodcast.co.uk/'&gt;Off Menu&lt;/a&gt; with Ed Gamble and James Acaster. On their show, they are joined each week by a different guest who describes their own dream menu, made up of whatever dishes they want from their life and from around the globe, brought to them in an imaginary way by the genie waiter, James Acaster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On our show, we (Tommo &amp; Megsy) interview each other about our perfect dream menu options from all over the world. The best bread, starter, Main, side dish &amp; dessert. It's going to get a little ridiculous as we go all out with our ultimate favourites...&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>megsy@foodfuntravel.com (The Dish Food Travel Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8ca6beb71dde442dbadd72bed755ffb8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8ca6beb71dde442dbadd72bed755ffb8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 01:55:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mobituaries with Mo Rocca : Anna May Wong: Death of a Trailblazer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Anna May Wong wasn't supposed to be in the movies. Her laundryman father was dead set against it. And Hollywood preferred white actors in "yellow face" for Asian characters. But Wong knew what she wanted. With her talent, beauty and tenacity, she ran a gauntlet of social and legal obstacles to become Hollywood's very first Chinese-American star. Mo talks with comedian Margaret Cho and actress Rosalind Chao about the woman who is finally getting her due.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Mobituaries@simonandschuster.com (Mobituaries with Mo Rocca)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d4f88edef75145e5801480b6c02bc776</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d4f88edef75145e5801480b6c02bc776/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Far From Home : Revisiting Iran</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In light of the recent political developments that briefly brought the US and Iran to the brink of war, I’m re-releasing an excerpt of a story I produced for the first season of Far From Home. It’s about the time a few years ago when I drove through Iran with my brother Drew and our friends Jane and Rosi as part of an &lt;a href="http://www.teamdonundestan.com" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;11,000 mile road trip we took&lt;/a&gt; across Europe and Asia, raising money for charity. Along the way, we had enlightening conversations with average Iranians that made us see their country in a totally new light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can read more and see photos that accompany this episode &lt;a href="https://farfromhomepodcast.org/news/2017/3/29/an-eye-opening-experience" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;on my website.&lt;/a&gt; To listen to this complete story, as well as my other stories from Iran and the rest of my road trip, go back and check out the first season of this podcast. Note that it’s a series, so it’s best to start at the very beginning and listen to all the episodes in order for the story to make the most sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Far From Home is a podcast where award-winning public radio journalist Scott Gurian visits parts of the world that most people never think about and tells stories they've never heard. For more info, visit &lt;a href="http://farfromhomepodcast.org" title="farfromhomepodcast.org" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;farfromhomepodcast.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@farfromhomepodcast.org (Far From Home)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">7cc426f5836f42d8b46e6b85b13dc2fa</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/7cc426f5836f42d8b46e6b85b13dc2fa/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 13:09:30 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Duolingo Spanish Podcast : Jaime, el artista (Jaime, The Artist)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A Spanish fashion designer works hard to give her autistic son every opportunity—then discovers that he has a special talent and makes him her business partner.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A transcript of this episode is available at https://podcast.duolingo.com.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@duolingo.com (Duolingo Spanish Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4bd6f19586cb4a8288a5c04565de460d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4bd6f19586cb4a8288a5c04565de460d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WAYPOINTS - with Jim Klug : #21 Jeff Currier: A Lifetime of Fly Fishing The World</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With over forty years of fly fishing the world, Jeff Currier has quite possibly fished more countries (60 and counting) and caught more species (over 400 and counting) with a fly rod than any person alive. Jeff is constantly traveling and developing new techniques for catching the most exotic fish imaginable in places where even the most avid adventurers are at times hesitant to go! As an active lecturer, published author, accomplished artist, IGFA World Record holder, and the subject of numerous films, articles, and media projects, Jeff is a fly fishing personality that is as entertaining and educational as he is legitimate. He is an incredibly reliable source of information and inspiration, the most senior member of the Yellow Dog Ambassador team, and a close friend. And while Jeff can boast one of the most impressive resumes around, he remains one of the most authentic and humble people in the industry – always willing to take his accomplishments one step further by passing on what he has learned. Kicking-off Season 2 of &lt;em&gt;Waypoints&lt;/em&gt; is an episode that scratches the surface of a life deeply devoted to fly fishing the world: a sit-down that is packed with numerous tips and great fishing stories from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jim@yellowdogflyfishing.com (WAYPOINTS - with Jim Klug)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">64812e9a0c2440c3a094312afd187d70</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/64812e9a0c2440c3a094312afd187d70/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Sake On Air : Know Your Hosts: Shuso Imada &amp; Chris Hughes</title><description>This week it’s time once again to take a moment to get to know the team here at Sake On Air. We first aired one of these episodes back in October (Episode 27), where you got to know Sebastie Lemoine and Christopher Pellegrini; aka, “little Chris”. This week you’ll be hearing from Christopher’s sake-inspired counterpart, […]</description><author>Frowley3@gmail.com (Sake On Air)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">5e7b6469c2d64be4a5677c4b7b4b2605</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/5e7b6469c2d64be4a5677c4b7b4b2605/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:46:08 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Become Nomad - Digital Nomad Lifestyle and Long Term Travel : BN069:  Escapes and attachments of the nomadic lifestyle</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Today, we will go over some of the recent repeating questions by readers of the blog. We will start by analyzing the concept of a digital lifestyle as a form of escape. We will also dive deep into the fascinating topic of attachments, and how to disconnect or connect to them.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>eli@becomenomad.com (Become Nomad - Digital Nomad Lifestyle and Long Term Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">29eb2f1f1b044ed2a88583e1c0283cad</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/29eb2f1f1b044ed2a88583e1c0283cad/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 10:56:47 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Normal to Nomad : #12 | Lindsey - Solo Female Nomad &amp; Alaska Native</title><description>&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;a href="https://normal2nomad.com/podcast/lindsey" target=""&gt;Show Notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>barronlink@gmail.com (Normal to Nomad)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f26b898c376a467a9e56c7c84429fecd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f26b898c376a467a9e56c7c84429fecd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 14:07:44 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The History of Egypt Podcast : 120: Reverend Mother</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Akhenaten (Part 10): Queen Tiye's Retirement. For the first decade of Akhenaten's rule, his mother &lt;strong&gt;Tiye&lt;/strong&gt; was a background figure. But we have more evidence for her later years than you'd expect, including magnificent art and objects. Plus, the Queen herself returned to public life when she made a splendid visit to pharaoh's new city... Images and Bibliography at &lt;a href="www.egyptianhistorypodcast.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.egyptianhistorypodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;, Support the Podcast and get AD-FREE, early release episodes at &lt;a href="www.patreon.com/egyptpodcast" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.patreon.com/egyptpodcast&lt;/a&gt;, Music by Keith Zizza &lt;a href="www.keithzizza.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.keithzizza.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>egyptpodcast@gmail.com (The History of Egypt Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a430974438d94f6d9783a9fa08c04826</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a430974438d94f6d9783a9fa08c04826/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Out Alive from BACKPACKER : Buried in a Rockslide</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Blue skies in Grand Teton National Park turn gray when a group of hikers are caught in a powerful rockslide. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ssebestyen@aimmedia.com (Out Alive from BACKPACKER)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">207f20e0acb54fb4b3a9358dec4b4724</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/207f20e0acb54fb4b3a9358dec4b4724/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Retro Disney World Podcast : Ep 55 - Backlot Studio Tram Tour</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Episode 55 of the RetroWDW Podcast: "Backstage Tour - MGM" - We appreciate your support and hope you have been enjoying each and every episode. Be sure to check out some of our previous shows!&lt;/p&gt;
Comments &amp; Corrections
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take a listen to our latest mini-episode, &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/podcast/podcast-episode-54-5-bringing-the-world-closer-to-you/'&gt;Bringing The World Closer To You&lt;/a&gt; - this was a quick one but ended up being very good. Enjoy!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;Listener Mail
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/gallery/lake-buena-vista/Frap07.png'&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The mailbag is full and we love that! Every month, you can possibly get on the show, so be sure to write to us at &lt;a href='mailto:podcast@retrowdw.com'&gt;podcast@retrowdw.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rob wrote in, asking about the VIP Lounges at EPCOT. Rob is mainly interested in the Kodak lounge at Journey into Imagination. Brian gives us his take on it. As I was putting this write-up together, I realized Rob is the owner of the site we reference. Check out his collection of VIP lounge pictures and information: &lt;a href='https://www.robyeodesign.com/blog/2016/3/21/future-worlds-s'&gt;Future World's Hidden VIP Lounges&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next letter we discuss purchasing fog machines at Innoventions. Was this actually a thing? We discuss...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dane writes in, regarding ephemera. Do we have any from Toys Fantastique? Todd gets us up to speed on how our photo archive is growing and improving at this very moment. What any RetroWDW fan can do, is use the search and find so many more images! This is great, use this link and give it a try: &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/photo-archive-search/'&gt;Photo Search&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;[listenerfeedback]&lt;/p&gt;
Audio Rewind
&lt;p&gt;Our audio rewind this month is the opening of Holiday Illuminations - Thank you for all the guesses and emails, and we didn't get many!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a winner! Congratulations Beth Goldman!  - you won a set of RetroMagic ornaments!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you think you know the answer to this month's audio rewind, email us! &lt;a href='mailto:contest@retrowdw.com'&gt;contest@retrowdw.com&lt;/a&gt; - This month, the winner will be getting a copy of the Marty Sklar book, Dream it, Do it - All entries due 2/17/2020 and a random winner will be selected.&lt;/p&gt;
Main Topic
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main topic this month is one of the recently closed classics, The Disney-MGM Studios Backlot Tour. There have been so many changes and updates over the years, but we are going to focus on the original, for the most part. How is our guide on this episode, walking us through the entire tram portion of the tour. We take it right back to 1989, going through how the Disney-MGM Studios actually worked. The concept of going past the theme park and then entering the studio - this is how the tour basically began. The walking tour was part of this, but we are not going to discuss this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The backlot tour had so many different aspects including residential street, the boneyard, the various production trailers, and so many other little nuggets. The tour seemed to change often, as far as props and items but the tour wasn't complete with a look at the Streets of America, or the New York street set. You would know this as the set for "The Lottery", which seems to be the only movie filmed here that we ever hear about. To accompany this episode, we have a great video on our YouTube channel - &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_DX0WnRHs8&amp;feature=youtu.be'&gt;click here to watch&lt;/a&gt; after the episode!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/backstage.gif'&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Delta_Dreamflight_L1011_Filming_Set_02.jpg'&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Delta_Dreamflight_L1011_Filming_Set_03.jpg'&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Delta_Dreamflight_L1011_Filming_Set_04.jpg'&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
2020: The Year of Film
&lt;p&gt;To make sure you are the first to know when items are released, &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/retrodisneyworld'&gt;subscribe to us on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;. Be sure to click the notification bell too, that way you are alerted when we post.  Finally, be sure to &lt;a href='https://vimeo.com/retrowdw'&gt;check out Vimeo&lt;/a&gt; if that is your thing, as we will post there as well. This past month we have posted the &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_DX0WnRHs8&amp;feature=youtu.be'&gt;Backlot Tour video&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zqDQLj4rtxM&amp;feature=youtu.be'&gt;a ride around the monorail in 1991&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XU2UJLEBczk&amp;feature=youtu.be'&gt;1994 runDisney Marathon&lt;/a&gt;. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
Next Month
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Join us next time for Episode 56, which we have not fully planned out, but you won't want to miss it  Thanks for joining us! &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>podcast@retrowdw.com (Retro Disney World Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e935163ea548489f94e21df5226cc107</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e935163ea548489f94e21df5226cc107/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 19:59:00 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>