<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Travel feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link><description>My travel episodes</description><atom:link href="http://thoughtfox.co/" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://thoughtfox.co/public/misc%20images/fox.png</url><title>My Travel feed</title><link>http://thoughtfox.co/</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 15:20:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>Parklandia : Bonus Episode! Traveling Eats: Sweet (And Savory) Home Chicago</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We love our life on the road, but it's hard not to long for some of the familiar sights...and tastes...of our old home in Chicago. In this episode of Traveling Eats with Matt, we'll start in our old neighborhood of Ukrainian Village and go over our favorite places to grab a bite and a drink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Parklandia on Instagram at &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/parklandiapod/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;@parklandiapod&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, join the Parklandia Rangers &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/ParklandiaRangers/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and Like our &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/parklandiapod/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Facebook page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Learn more about your ad-choices at &lt;a href="https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers"&gt;https://news.iheart.com/podcast-advertisers&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (Parklandia)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cdc11c82478c4417bb5e922e618caa2d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cdc11c82478c4417bb5e922e618caa2d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Offbeat Life - become location independent : My Offbeat Journey: How to turn your business from hobby to profitable Business</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, we talk about taking out your mental block with your beliefs about creating income and how to turn your business from hobby to profitable business. &lt;/p&gt; --------------- Hey Offbeat Family, I really your listening to this episode. I would love to hear more from you and what you think of the podcast.  &lt;p&gt;Contact me: &lt;a href= "mailto:hello@theoffbeatlife.com"&gt;hello@theoffbeatlife.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show credits: Audio Engineer: &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/ben_smith_/"&gt;Ben Smith&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@theoffbeatlife.com (The Offbeat Life - become location independent)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">425bec5d3ce74bb3ba28a53771d8b43d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/425bec5d3ce74bb3ba28a53771d8b43d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Monocle 24: The Menu : Supplying the world’s best chefs</title><description>How Franco Fubini’s Natoora supplies fine European produce to the world’s best chefs. Plus: the son of Salvatore Ferragamo tastes success in the wine industry and why some of Japan’s top chefs will be cooking in Europe.</description><author>info@monocle.com (Monocle 24: The Menu)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a7562dfbd4e3487e960214fbd519439d</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a7562dfbd4e3487e960214fbd519439d/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Expat Files: Living in Latin America : EXPAT FILES - 01.24.20</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Descriptions- EXPAT FILES SHOW #923 FRI, JAN 24 (01-24-2020):&lt;/p&gt;
#1- Guns and Gringos in Latin America:
What you absolutely need to know about owning guns and ammo in Latin America. DYK that the laws in 4 out of the 20 Latin American countries make it nearly impossible for you to own a gun. However, in the 16 other Latin countries it’s a completely different story…      
 
#2- The two largest countries in Latin America have some of the highest murder and gun crime rates in the world:
They also have some of the strictest gun laws. If you think Mexico has idiotic gun laws you haven’t studied what they are like in Brazil…
&lt;p&gt;#3- Valuable lessons learned in Latin America concerning Guns and Ammo that North Americans deny or don’t want to hear about.&lt;/p&gt;
#4- Be sure to pick up my "LATIN AMERICAN HEALTHCARE REPORT":
It's been revised for 2020 (and beyond) including the latest "Stem Cell" info and data and my top picks for the best treatment centers for expats and gringos. Just go to &lt;a href='http://www.theexpatfiles.com/'&gt;www.theexpatfiles.com&lt;/a&gt; and click on the "Latin American Healthcare Report”.
&lt;p&gt;#5- Check out my “The Expat Files” You Tube channel. See all the fun slides and photos that go along with each show. There are now more than 150 shows posted on my YouTube channel so have a look.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>karalee@garynull.com (The Expat Files: Living in Latin America)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3e2ac8f3cf9e446499e227325a0cdbb8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3e2ac8f3cf9e446499e227325a0cdbb8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 06:55:08 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The olive magazine podcast : ep 184 - The coolest (and best value) foodie travel destinations for 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week editor Laura Rowe joins travel editor Rhiannon Batten at the Adventure Travel Show in London for a live podcast. They discuss how to track down the best culinary travel experiences, why you don’t need to spend big to eat out abroad, and the upcoming foodie destinations to look out for in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>laura.rowe@immediate.co.uk (The olive magazine podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">cc64575c816c40cc9b78c9da322656fc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/cc64575c816c40cc9b78c9da322656fc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 05:56:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Familie auf Weltreise -Der Podcast : 72 | Darf man eigentlich seine Lehrer umarmen?</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Marie rennt ihrer Lehrerin in die offenen Arme und "knuddelt" sie. Ist das normal? In wenigen Tagen startet die Schule in Australien und wir haben heute bereits die neuen Klassenräume erkundet und die neuen Klassenlehrer kennengelernt. Wir nehmen dich in dieser Podcast Episode mit durch unsere emotionale Schul-Welt in Australien,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In der Podcast Episode #58 sprechen wir übrigens über den Unterschied zwischen der deutschen und der australischen Schule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/familieaufweltreise"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Der geschlossenen Gruppe "Familie auf Weltreise" beitreten&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.familieaufweltreise.de/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unser neuer Blog&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/familieaufweltreise"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instagram&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://youtube.com/c/familieaufweltreisede"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YouTube&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2WLSqdF"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on Family&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://katrin-fit.net/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sport mit Katrin - Katrin-Fit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unsere Ressourcen findest Du auf unserer Webseite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.familieaufweltreise.de/ressourcen"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;www.Familieaufweltreise.de/ressourcen&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lust auf ein Reiseguthaben?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;25 € AirBnB Gutschein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bit.ly/2BtQrCo"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://bit.ly/2BtQrCo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;15 € Booking.com Gutschein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://booki.ng/2A67Xwu"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://booki.ng/2A67Xwu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>kontakt@familieaufweltreise.de (Familie auf Weltreise -Der Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a929d652307c49fa9cb65d3e645c58c6</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a929d652307c49fa9cb65d3e645c58c6/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 05:39:31 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Coastin' the Country : Ep. 15: Six Flags Great America Tsunami Surge update, No Coaster Con recap</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Marcus recaps his trip to the American Coaster Enthusiasts No Coaster Con and talks with Six Flags Great America after their presentation there. They give us an update on the construction of their new water coaster Tsunami Surge. We also break down the latest news in the theme park world, including Super Nintendo World coming to Universal Orlando, and the latest rumors about the big 2021 attraction coming to Busch Gardens Williamsburg. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mleshock@wgntv.com (Coastin' the Country)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">759c262424704b788f518e05e28e3b84</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/759c262424704b788f518e05e28e3b84/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Kentuckiana Sounds : Clemson (and a Freight Train) at UofL</title><description>The sounds of a college football game can travel pretty far. So can the sounds of a freight train. Drawn to the periphery of Cardinal Stadium by the Clemson at UofL game in 2015, Kentuckiana Sounds curator Aaron Rosenblum found that the adjacent railroad tracks were as noisy as the game itself. To hear the full recording, explore the sound map, or submit a sound visit www.wfpl.org/sounds or www.kentuckianasounds.org.</description><author>support@louisvillepublicmedia.org (Kentuckiana Sounds)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6a002a20f0c54590bba1d9c8763f79ba</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6a002a20f0c54590bba1d9c8763f79ba/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 07:04:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Tropical MBA Podcast - Entrepreneurship, Travel, and Lifestyle : TMBA529: The Price of Progress</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We here at the Tropical MBA are always fascinated with people who raise questions that challenge the social narratives that most people follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s no wonder then that Christoper Ryan caught our attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christopher is a New York Times bestselling author, the host of a brilliant podcast called Tangentially Speaking, and is perhaps best known for his 2010 book Sex at Dawn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christopher recently published a new book called Civilized to Death, which argues that so-called &amp;quot;progress&amp;quot; has actually adversely affected the way we live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He joins us today to talk about his unconventional path to becoming a published author, and why civilization might not represent progress.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Dan@TropicalMBA.com (The Tropical MBA Podcast - Entrepreneurship, Travel, and Lifestyle)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0af7765d764346058fdacc6239f0bab5</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0af7765d764346058fdacc6239f0bab5/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WDWNT ParksCenter : ParksCenter - Festival of the Arts 2020! - Ep. 86</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This is ParksCenter. We cover the top news stories from this week in Disney Parks news in 30 minutes. This week, we’ll be talking about: Festival of the Arts has begun! Find out what our highlights, and lowlights, of the festival are! (And check out our free PDF guide to the festival!) 3 new films […]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://wdwnt.com/2020/01/watch-parkscenter-86/"&gt;ParksCenter – Festival of the Arts 2020! – Ep. 86&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://wdwnt.com"&gt;WDW News Today&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>developer@wdwnt.com (WDWNT ParksCenter)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">af80de32f178437495b63932b418638c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/af80de32f178437495b63932b418638c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 04:00:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Trip That Changed Me : Japan with Jacqueline Gifford: memory, childhood nostalgia, and the myth of having it all</title><description>&lt;p&gt;As Editor-in-Chief of &lt;i&gt;Travel + Leisure, &lt;/i&gt;Jacqueline Gifford spends a lot of time out of office exploring far-flung destinations. It’s a career she pursued, in part, thanks to her parents, who encouraged Jacqui’s cultural curiosity from the get-go. On today’s episode, Jacqueline shares a nostalgic trip to Japan, the country where she was born, at a particularly pivotal moment: her own pregnancy. We discuss what it was like to visit her childhood neighborhood after a 20-year absence, how her memories both differed from and reflected reality, and her approach to balancing a busy work life with raising a child. Plus, hear Jacqueline’s number one travel tip and the surprising item she cannot travel without.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@podcastnation.org (The Trip That Changed Me)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3d73e3deb0504130b29d5b288cd0f11b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3d73e3deb0504130b29d5b288cd0f11b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 03:00:05 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Peak Northwest : How yurts helped save Oregon parks</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This week’s episode of the Peak Northwest podcast dives into the surprising history of yurts in Oregon — and why campers went nuts for them. Jamie and Jim are joined by Craig Tutor, the former state parks manager who first put yurts into parks back in the early 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>podcasts@oregonian.com (Peak Northwest)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9d63acc612124ec8bf68d2148d8eca45</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9d63acc612124ec8bf68d2148d8eca45/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Gal Pal Show: Solo female travel, backpacking, bucket list inspiration, planning a trip, female travel advice and tips, and off the beaten track ideas. : 90: Solo female travel is about finding yourself</title><description>&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;Now, I know that might make you cringe, but travelling really does get you to find yourself. You learn what you really like, what you really dislike, and you get to know yourself. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;It is an exceptional reason why travelling as a solo female traveller is a great idea...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;Listen to this episode now...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://mailchi.mp/ae404f33adb5/travel-planning-worksheet'&gt;Get your FREE Travel planning worksheet &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://mailchi.mp/ae404f33adb5/travel-planning-worksheet'&gt;and start planning your trip here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://galpalacademy.thinkific.com/courses/travel-planning-bootcamp-1'&gt;Want to go travelling?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align:center;"&gt;&lt;a href='https://galpalacademy.thinkific.com/courses/travel-planning-bootcamp-1'&gt;Join Gal Pal Travel Planning Bootcamp here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jo@galpalacademy.com (Gal Pal Show: Solo female travel, backpacking, bucket list inspiration, planning a trip, female travel advice and tips, and off the beaten track ideas.)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e9c11446bb3b4e159a9417d72194eb04</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e9c11446bb3b4e159a9417d72194eb04/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Biscuit CLT Podcast : Liner Notes: Cyanca</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Neo soul and R&amp;B singer/songwriter Cyanca released &lt;em&gt;I'm Staying Home&lt;/em&gt;, her second EP in the spring of 2019. By the end of the year, her lead single "Patti Mayonnaise" had been named song of the year by Queen City Nerve. This success has helped lead to live performances across the country, but she remains loyal to her home state of North Carolina.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In today's episode of the Biscuit CLT podcast, producer Andy Goh talks to Cyanca for another segment of Liner Notes. Cyanca talks about her background in music, the &lt;em&gt;Home&lt;/em&gt; EP, and how losing her mother to a drunk driver at the age of two irreversibly damaged her relationship with her uncle.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tim@charlotteiscreative.com (The Biscuit CLT Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">51dd9e53f4124172bd9d9560e92485bf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/51dd9e53f4124172bd9d9560e92485bf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 22:34:30 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Oh Boy, The Podcast : Episode 006 - Design Your Own Land at Disney Game</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you ever think you've come up for the best land Disney has ever seen? Sit there and dream about everything there could be? Attractions, restaurants, all of your imagineering dreams coming true? WELL we certainly did this week. We played a fun game where we each spent the week picking a land to replace at Disney with each of our own dream "lands"! Goodbye Tom Sawyer Island and hello Neverland. Thats exactly the game we played, and we came up with some insane ideas! Take a listen and make sure to let us know who had the best big dream, and what your dream Disney land would be!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" href="http://www.thelostbros.com"&gt;Support the show&lt;/a&gt; (http://www.thelostbros.com)&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>hello@lostbrostradingco.com (Oh Boy, The Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">209abc55d5e5474b8a3f323046003844</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/209abc55d5e5474b8a3f323046003844/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Overland Journal Podcast : Building the Jeep Gladiator for Overlanding</title><description>Matt Scott shares details and insights about selecting the best Gladiator model to purchase and how to modify it for backcountry travel, including suspension, tires and wheels, bumpers, and overland campers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Makes the Jeep Gladiator So Special?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;1. Jeep Capability&lt;br&gt;2. Proper payload, easily greater than most of its competitors.&lt;br&gt;3. Easily modified for a wide range of conditions.&lt;br&gt;4. Solid front and rear axles with available locking differentials. &lt;br&gt;5. Available manual transmission&lt;br&gt;6. Available diesel motor (late 2020) &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the best model Gladiator for overland travel?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matt- &lt;a href="https://www.jeep.com/bmo.gladiator.2020.html#/build/exterior/85202/CUJ202011JTJS98A/2TR/ERC,DFT,DMF,TW2,WFJ,AL,SDD,UAQ,AEK,ALP,AM2,ADE,AD6,AJ1,ABR,CWA,RC4,HT1,MM3,CHD,XNY,XBM,MC6,X9,PX8,24R,APA"&gt;The Rubicon because of the locking differentials and other accessories like swaybar disconnect, etc.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;Scott- &lt;a href="https://www.jeep.com/bmo.gladiator.2020.html#/build/exterior/85202/CUJ202011JTJL98B/2TS/ERC,DFT,DMF,TTH,WAC,A7,SDW,UAA,AJQ,HT1,T5,PW7,24S,APA"&gt;The Sport with the Max Tow Package. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some Inspiration:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.xoverland.com/videos/truck-builds/2019-jeep-gladiator-build/"&gt;The XOverland Odin, built by Clay Croft and his team&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://expeditionportal.com/the-jeep-gladiator-wayout/"&gt;Jeep Gladiator Wayout&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suspension?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matt had the factory Mopar 2-inch suspension lift installed, which he has been happy with, save the rear Fox shocks. The spring rate is appropriate for Matt's load, but the rear shocks were valved for an unloaded truck. As a result, the blow through the available travel (rebound was also lacking). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott and Matt discuss other suspension options, and Matt is most anticipating the AEV kit due to proper spring rates and history of good valving. However, that kit is not currently available. Old Man Emu was also discussed as a good option, but it is also not available. The only kit currently on the market that meets Matt's expectations is the &lt;a href="http://iconvehicledynamics.com/shop/744-2020-up-jeep-gladiator-jt"&gt;Icon Vehicle Dynamics kit. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tires and Wheels?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matt chose the &lt;a href="https://www.methodracewheels.com/collections/trail-series-1/products/702-bronze-1"&gt;Method Racing wheels in bronze&lt;/a&gt;, and selected the &lt;a href="https://www.falkentire.com/tires/light-truck-suv-cuv-tires/wildpeaka/t3w-tire"&gt;Falken A/T3W in&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.falkentire.com/tires/light-truck-suv-cuv-tires/wildpeaka/t3w-tire"&gt;37" diameter. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winch?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.warn.com/zeon-10s-platinum-winch-92815"&gt;Warn Zeon 10-S&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Camping Accessories?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://expeditionportal.com/the-jeep-gladiator-camper/"&gt;AT Overland Habitat &lt;/a&gt;(The camper that Matt chose)&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://expeditionportal.com/fiftyten-camper-available-for-gladiator-in-usa/"&gt;The FiftyTen Camper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://pcor4x4.com.au/trays.php"&gt;Patriot Campers PCOR System&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT IS THE OVERLAND JOURNAL PODCAST?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Overland Journal Podcast features the travelers, topics, and news related to the overlanding community and industry. This podcast is hosted by Scott Brady and Matt Scott, and is a production of the Overland Journal Magazine and the expeditionportal.com website.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Host Bios:&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;br&gt;Scott Brady&lt;br&gt;Scott is the publisher and co-founder of &lt;em&gt;Expedition Portal&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Overland Journal&lt;/em&gt;, and is often credited with popularizing overlanding in North America. His travels by 4WD and adventure motorcycle span all seven continents and include three circumnavigations of the globe. His polar travels include two vehicle crossings of Antarctica and the first long-axis crossing of Greenland. &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/globaloverland/?hl=en"&gt;@globaloverland&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matthew Scott&lt;br&gt;Matthew is a leading expert in automotive adventure. He has extensively explored the world's most-remote places by 4WD, and is considered an industry authority on overland travel. Matt is the only American to ever become an editor of a major Australian 4WD publication, and has over 15 years of competitive auto racing experience. &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mattexplore/?hl=en"&gt;@mattexplore&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description><author>scott@overlandinternational.com (The Overland Journal Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">14516fca44ca4c43803d5d6fc4b7e68e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/14516fca44ca4c43803d5d6fc4b7e68e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 19:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Duolingo Spanish Podcast : La herencia del mezcal (The Mezcal Inheritance)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Yola grew up watching her grandfather make mezcal. When he died, she took up the mantle. But how would she transform her grandfather’s hobby into a mezcal for the masses?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Study materials and a transcript of this episode are available at https://podcast.duolingo.com.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@duolingo.com (Duolingo Spanish Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bc59d105fdb848228aa0792d3fa6ebf9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bc59d105fdb848228aa0792d3fa6ebf9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Books And Travel : Sacred Australia And The Northern Territory With Amanda Markham</title><description>In today’s episode, we’re heading for the Northern Territory of Australia as Dr. Amanda Markham talks about some of the Aboriginal Dreaming stories of the area and how the vast landscape impacts living and working there, as well as the best places to visit if you’re traveling. Amanda is of Wiradjuri Aboriginal descent and speaks an Aboriginal language, so it’s fantastic to get her perspective.&lt;br /&gt;
We recorded this episode before the bush fires swept the country and I talked back in &lt;a href="https://www.booksandtravel.page/australia/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;episode 20 about my own experience traveling around Australia&lt;/a&gt; and then living there — I mentioned that it’s the weather you have to watch out for, not the snakes or spiders — and Amanda emphasizes again how important it is to prepare for the reality of the outback. We both love Australia and particularly, the Northern Territories — it’s one of the places I would love to go back to —  so I hope you enjoy the adventure in this episode.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://amandamarkham.com/about/" target="_blank" rel="attachment noopener wp-att-1224 noreferrer"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://amandamarkham.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Dr. Amanda Markham&lt;/a&gt; is an archaeologist and anthropologist in the Australian outback, as well as a travel writer and award-winning author of speculative fiction.&lt;br /&gt;
* The three different climates of the Northern Territory&lt;br /&gt;
* Exploring the Top End with Aboriginal guides and some of the Dreaming stories in the landscape&lt;br /&gt;
* Language differences above and below the monsoon line&lt;br /&gt;
* The myths and reality about danger in Australia&lt;br /&gt;
* The Alice Springs Beanie Festival and what makes the outback culture unique&lt;br /&gt;
* Stargazing in the Northern Territory&lt;br /&gt;
* Recommended books set in outback Australia&lt;br /&gt;
You can find Dr. Amanda Markham at &lt;a href="http://traveloutbackaustralia.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;traveloutbackaustralia.com&lt;/a&gt; and at &lt;a href="http://amandamarkham.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;AmandaMarkham.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Transcript of the interview&lt;br /&gt;
Jo Frances Penn: Dr. Amanda Markham is an archaeologist and anthropologist in the Australian outback, as well as a travel writer and award-winning author of speculative fiction. Welcome, Amanda.&lt;br /&gt;
Dr. Markham: Hi. Thanks, Joanna. Thanks very much for having me.&lt;br /&gt;
Jo Frances Penn: It’s great to have you on the show. Your job sounds very cool. I always wanted to be an archaeologist. People think, ‘Oh, archaeology? You must work in ancient Greece or Egypt.’ But you work in the Australian outback.&lt;br /&gt;
Tell us, what does your job involve?&lt;br /&gt;
Dr. Markham: I’ll say that I’ve had two careers working in the outback. First, as an anthropologist, I started working in anthropology in 1997. I went to the Northern Territory to work for an agency, a government agency called The Sacred Sites Authority, and I worked specifically in the protection of Aboriginal sacred sites, working with aboriginal elders, particularly over Central Australia, so the southern half of the Northern Territory.&lt;br /&gt;
I’ll slow down a little bit for listeners who don’t know where the Northern Territory is in Australia. It’s that middle third of Australia, but the northern part, and it’s got three very distinctive climate zones, one of which is the arid zone.&lt;br /&gt;
I don’t want to call it a desert because we don’t really have true deserts in Australia. We do have arid zones, which are often vast savannas and rangelands. Then, you have a sub-tropical area north of that. And then we have the tropics where they actually get a full monsoon, and we call it here in the Northern Territory, we call it the Top End, and that’s where Darwin is.&lt;br /&gt;
So, I went to the Northern Territory to be an anthropologist, work with Aboriginal elders, recording and protecting their sacred sites, so their Dreaming sites. Always,</description><author>jo@booksandtravel.page (Books And Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">de8d1551e0b9434bbb1804bc561ab348</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/de8d1551e0b9434bbb1804bc561ab348/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 16:10:24 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>EarzUp!  : EarzUp! Indepth | Episode # 13</title><description>Photo courtesy of Disney
			 
			 
				
				
			 
				
				
			 
				
				
				
				
					
				
				
				
				
				
				
				Welcome to the year 2020, friends! This is the first In-Depth episode of the new year, and as always, we bring you some good Disney-themed news to think about. Jeremy talks about the new runDisney clubs, Jason babbles on about the new SoCal-priced tickets, and more!</description><author>jason@earzup-podcast.com (EarzUp! )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3b70f961e88c43e8b9a9ec36972eb080</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3b70f961e88c43e8b9a9ec36972eb080/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 15:13:03 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Happiest Podcast On Earth : Disney News - January 21, 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you caught up on all of the latest Disney news? No? Well listen in to this episode to hear all the latest relating to all things Disney!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>happiestpodcast@gmail.com (Happiest Podcast On Earth)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">0c3c6f19294e47b983f54a464328e1d7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/0c3c6f19294e47b983f54a464328e1d7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>DCL Podcast : 127 Run Disney: 2020 Marathon Weekend Recap</title><description>&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-resized"&gt;&lt;img src="http://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Run-Disney.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-476" width="619" height="825" srcset="http://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Run-Disney.jpg 720w, http://secureservercdn.net/166.62.108.230/dd3.e6f.myftpupload.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Run-Disney-225x300.jpg 225w" sizes="(max-width: 619px) 100vw, 619px" /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Join us as we look back at our experiences during the 2020 Walt Disney World Marathon Weekend.  We discuss where we stayed, transportation to and from the events, the Expo, and race day experiences over this fun weekend.  So lace up your shoes, and get ready to have fun looking back at this years Marathon Weekend.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;You can support our show via Patreon:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.patreon.com/dclpodcast"&gt;http://www.patreon.com/dclpodcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Connect with the show via:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/dclpodcast"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/dclpodcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.instagram.com/dcl_podcast"&gt;http://www.instagram.com/dcl_podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Connect with Steve, Christy, and Chris:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="steve@dclpodcast.com"&gt;steve@dclpodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="christy@packyourpixiedust.com"&gt;christy@packyourpixiedust.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="brightdisneybychris@gmail.com"&gt;brightdisneybychris@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sekriese@comcast.net (DCL Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">f5151a49db124dd2b0e3fd812276e33c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/f5151a49db124dd2b0e3fd812276e33c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 13:34:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>CruiseTipsTV Unplugged - Cruise Tips and More : Instagram Cruise Questions Answered</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, we answer cruise questions from our Instagram followers. From Spa questions to the benefits of staying on the ship during port days. We'll cover a variety of popular cruise questions.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As always, you can email us your questions at  sheri@cruisetipstv.com. We'd also LOVE if you'd leave a review where you listen to this podcast, and screen shot the show and share it on Instagram using the hashtag #cttvunplugged.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Download our shore day bag checklist, and more cruise packing and planning checklists &amp; videos by joining the CruiseTipsTV Academy. We have a special discount code for our podcast listeners. To redeem the $5.00 discount on our master class enter code UNPLUGGED at &lt;a href= "http://academy.cruisetipstv.com"&gt;http://academy.cruisetipstv.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcast@cruisetipstv.com (CruiseTipsTV Unplugged - Cruise Tips and More)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6e6cd08979ed405b95bbf2deca0fbd5e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6e6cd08979ed405b95bbf2deca0fbd5e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>WAYPOINTS - with Jim Klug : #20 Will Blair: Fly Fishing the Legendary Waters of Kamchatka</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Will Blair is one of the godfathers of fly fishing in Kamchatka. Since 1997, Will has helped pioneer some of the top fisheries on the Kamchatka Peninsula, developing and offering what is arguably one of the best rainbow trout fishing experiences found anywhere on the planet. Yellow Dog is proud to partner with Will and his remote Two Yurt and Ozernaya programs, along with the incredibly-unique “Rainbows from Above” customized fly-out program. Because Will knows this mysterious and wild area like no one else, we tracked him down with a long list of questions in-hand. We discuss the factors that make a trip to Kamchatka so special, what gear to bring, the seasonality of the fisheries, species, travel logistics, and the stories you might tell upon returning from one of the greatest rainbow trout destinations in the world. If you’ve ever thought about a trip to Kamchatka, then you will certainly enjoy this exciting episode: the Season 1 finale of the &lt;em&gt;Waypoints Podcast&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jim@yellowdogflyfishing.com (WAYPOINTS - with Jim Klug)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">169f114bcb924038b525fd4d2aa5e1de</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/169f114bcb924038b525fd4d2aa5e1de/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 02:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Disney Cruise Line Show : #002 - How to Book a Walt Disney World/Disney Cruise Line Land/Sea Vacation</title><description>01/22/20 - In this episode, the panel discusses how to book and plan a Walt Disney World/Disney Cruise Line Land/Sea vacation with tips on the order of your vacation and mistakes to avoid!</description><author>craig@disneyinfo.com (The Disney Cruise Line Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b1e63c7d95a44479a0d23a6fdfe61930</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b1e63c7d95a44479a0d23a6fdfe61930/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The City : The Confrontation | S2 E7</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this Season 2 bonus episode,&amp;nbsp;accusations of sexual assault at the Spice House strip club come to light. Two women who work there head to the club to confront their bosses, their phones secretly set to record.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info@thecitypodcast.com (The City)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">edc9803293644e4fa7daa1bcf782e5df</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/edc9803293644e4fa7daa1bcf782e5df/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:05:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>MiceCast : Acquisition Analysis</title><description>Your hosts discuss the theory that the Lucasfilm acquisition was a failure compared to Pixar and Marvel. We also spend some time talking about the virtual queue for Rise of the Resistance. 2 hours 16 minutes.&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/Micecast/~4/00_v98Zkb2U" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>micecast@gmail.com (MiceCast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">38164a6a54234260b74be0aa2831c8e2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/38164a6a54234260b74be0aa2831c8e2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Morocco : Why Morocco 029 – Meryam Demnati on Amazigh culture in Morocco</title><description>&lt;p&gt;With a new year and a new decade upon us, I sat down with Meryam Demnati, an Amazigh activitist, to chat about a little-known New Year celebrated in here in Morocco &amp;#8211; Yennayer &amp;#8211; the Amazigh New Year for the latest episode of Why Morocco. Celebrated on 12 January by the native peoples of North Africa, Yennayer marks the shift from extreme cold and milder temperatures and is celebrated by Amazigh (sometimes referred to as Berbers) communities not only in Morocco, but throughout North Africa. Interestingly though, January 1 and the Islamic New Year are observed here in Morocco with official bank holidays, but Yennayer is not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an activist, Meryam also talks about the status of the Amazigh language and Tifinagh alphabet in Morocco, recognition of the Amazigh culture, and the causes the Amazigh movement has and continues to work on since post-independence in Morocco.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more Morocco ideas and advise, follow me on Instagram at &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mandyinmorocco/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;@mandyinmorocco&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My other projects include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tasting Marrakech food and cultural tours in Marrakech &lt;a href="http://tasting-marrakech.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;tasting-marrakech.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel and public relations consulting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Freelance writing for print and digital  &lt;a href="https://mandyinmorocco.com/freelance-writing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;mandyinmorocco.com/freelance-writing/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>mandyjsinclair@gmail.com (Why Morocco)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">2fab948e5ab44c9eb5855187a0e97bb8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/2fab948e5ab44c9eb5855187a0e97bb8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 23:28:14 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The One Way Ticket Show : Search for Common Ground CEO - Shamil Idriss</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Shamil Idriss is the Chief Executive Officer of Search for Common Ground, the world’s largest organization dedicated to peace building.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As CEO, and in previous roles as President, Chief Operating Officer, and Burundi Country Director, Shamil has led Search’s efforts to end violent conflict in more than 35 countries, including conflict zones in the Middle East and Africa.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Starting in 2005, Shamil served as the Deputy Director of the United Nations Alliance for Civilizations, supporting political and religious leaders in improving relations between Western and Muslim-majority countries.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A pioneer in cross-cultural media technologies, Shamil worked from 2008 to 2014 as the CEO of Soliya, a nonprofit at the intersection of technology, peace building, and global education.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Shamil graduated from Swarthmore College with degrees in Economics and Philosophy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On this episode, Shamil shares his one way ticket to meet New Zealand Prime Minister, Jacinda Ardern. Plus, he highlights the phenomenal work being done around the globe by Search for Common Ground.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Shamil is just one of the dynamic personalities featured on The One Way Ticket Show, where Host Steven Shalowitz explores with his guests where they would go if given a one way ticket, no coming back! Destinations may be in the past, present, future, real, imaginary or a state of mind.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Steven's guests have included: Nobel Peace Prize Winner, President Jose Ramos-orta; Legendary Talk Show Host, Dick Cavett; Law Professor, Alan Dershowitz; Fashion Expert, Tim Gunn; Broadcast Legend, Charles Osgood; International Rescue Committee President &amp; CEO, David Miliband; Playwright, David Henry Hwang; Journalist-Humorist-Actor, Mo Rocca; SkyBridge Capital Founder &amp; Co-Managing Partner, Anthony Scaramucci; Abercrombie &amp; Kent Founder, Geoffrey Kent; Travel Expert, Pauline Frommer, as well as leading photographers, artists, chefs, writers, intellectuals and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>steven@theonewayticketshow.com (The One Way Ticket Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e119f0048427434887ec1a2b543d9b96</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e119f0048427434887ec1a2b543d9b96/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 09:20:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Theme Park Rangers : Universal’s Epic Character Race: Routes, photo ops, and staying healthy surrounded by theme park temptations (Ep. 34)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you think you can outrun a Minion? How about a velociraptor? In this episode of Theme Park Rangers, get some insight into the upcoming Universal Orlando’s Epic Character Race: 5K and 10K routes, character photo ops, tips on race prep and how to stay healthy surrounded by theme park temptations.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f4g1t-0-0"&gt;Why run a race at a theme park? (1:17)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f4g1t-0-0"&gt;The event before the event: Planning costume (1:57)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f4g1t-0-0"&gt;New Year’s resolution: Healthy steps (5:33)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f4g1t-0-0"&gt;Universal team member embraces running (6:47)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f4g1t-0-0"&gt;How do you avoid temptation of theme park food? (9:03)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f4g1t-0-0"&gt;Prepping for your first race (10:49)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f4g1t-0-0"&gt;5K, 10K race routes (12:34)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li class= "public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr" data-offset-key="f4g1t-0-0"&gt;Can you outrun a Minion? (13:13)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>video@orlandosentinel.com (Theme Park Rangers)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d6a332ce1d074a21973bfd4aeed32849</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d6a332ce1d074a21973bfd4aeed32849/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 05:59:16 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Exploring the North Shore : Episode 19: Ice Fishing in the BWCA</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Joe is back for this week's episode all about ice fishing in the BWCA! Joe and Jaye are joined by Matthew Baxley (last heard from in the Haunted House episode), and Chelsea Lloyd. Plus, Chelsea's sister Whitney and friend, Rachel, come along for the adventure. Joe, Matthew, and Chelsea are the hosts of WTIP's Boundary Waters Podcast. In this cross-over episode, the group heads into the BWCA to ice fish on Duncan Lake. Learn the legalities of fishing in the BWCA, along with some tips and tricks from one of the area's most knowledgeable anglers (Joe). Also, listen to find out if we once again get skunked on an Exploring the North Shore fishing episode. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can find more information on fishing in the BWCA on the Cascade Vacation Rentals Website: &lt;a href='https://www.cascadevacationrentals.com/area-info-ice-fishing-bwca.htm'&gt;https://www.cascadevacationrentals.com/area-info-ice-fishing-bwca.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plus, listen and subscribe to WTIP's Boundary Waters Podcast to hear more from Joe, Matthew, and Chelsea: &lt;a href='https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/listing/wtip-boundary-waters-podcast/'&gt;https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/listing/wtip-boundary-waters-podcast/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, check out our new website! Full of fun stories, articles, and a detailed business listing for all things North Shore. If you love the North Shore, be sure to bookmark Exploring the North Shore and let us help you plan your next North Shore adventure! &lt;a href='https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/'&gt;https://www.exploringnorthshore.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This episode is sponsored by &lt;a href='https://www.cascadevacationrentals.com/'&gt;Cascade Vacation Rentals&lt;/a&gt;. Use promo code "Podcast" at check-out to receive Cascade's largest available percent off discount (discount changes seasonally). This episode is also sponsored by &lt;a href='https://thebiglakelife.com/'&gt;The Big Lake&lt;/a&gt;. Use promo code "Explore" at check-out to receive 15% off your first online order. Thank you to our wonderful sponsors!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marketing@staycvr.com (Exploring the North Shore)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">886346c63eba4a2ea8a20813743354aa</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/886346c63eba4a2ea8a20813743354aa/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 04:45:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>A Way To Go : Designing to Connect to Travelers with AvroKO’s Adam Farmerie</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Fueled in no small part by the rise of Instagram. Pinterest, and HGTV, design has become a cultural obsession, and this is having a big impact on travel and hospitality. Adam Farmerie, one of the four principals at award-winning design firm AvroKO, is responsible for many of the hotels, private clubs, bars, and restaurants that are topping our must-see travel lists. He talks about how and why he designs these provocative spaces. Find more info about this episode at Fathomaway.com. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>applepodcast@howstuffworks.com (A Way To Go)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">64df826bf481480fb4aa5a3697f5d117</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/64df826bf481480fb4aa5a3697f5d117/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 03:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>New Books in African Studies : Catherine Besteman, "Making Refuge: Somali Bantu Refugees and Lewiston, Maine" (Duke UP, 2016)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.colby.edu/directory/profile/catherine.besteman/"&gt;Catherine L. Besteman&lt;/a&gt;'s book &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/0822360446/?tag=newbooinhis-20"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Making Refuge: Somali Bantu Refugees and Lewiston, Main&lt;/em&gt;e&lt;/a&gt; (Duke University Press, 2016) is an important contribution to our understanding of the process of remaking one’s way of life after war in a new place, and in a new culture. Besteman writes about her ethnographic encounter in the 1980s with Somalis from the village of Banta who she then re-encounters in 2006 in the town of Lewiston, the so-called “Armpit of Maine.” The result is an intimate account of the trajectory of Somali Bantus from their home in the Jubba Valley, their experience flight to refugee camps in neighboring Kenya and their eventual relocation to cities and towns in the United States. Readers also learn that assimilation is not just a one-sided affair, as Besteman narrates how the arrival of Somali Bantus in Lewiston impacts residents there, neighbors and government officials alike. As such, &lt;em&gt;Making Refuge&lt;/em&gt; reminds us that resettlement is more than the arrival of refugees; it is also a process by which receiving communities adapt to their foreign neighbors. In other words, Besteman’s work is a study of mutual transformation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.colgate.edu/about/directory/sthomson"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Susan Thomson&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; is associate professor of peace and conflict studies at Colgate University.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>marshallpoe@gmail.com (New Books in African Studies)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">69252506ac614638b03e5c8c0feb04d0</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/69252506ac614638b03e5c8c0feb04d0/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Living Adventurously : There is a Broken Connection Between Cities and Wildness - Living Adventurously 13</title><description>Professor Ian Rotherham is an expert on a range of environmental issues, including urban wildlife, extreme weather, flooding and climate change. He has published extensively in academic journals, and has released a number of books on UK wildlife and the environment. Ian is a man positively bursting with enthusiasm and knowledge and ideas.Ian poured forth a cheerful stream of lessons on the environment, eco-tourism and rewilding. &lt;br&gt;We talked about the cultural severance between cities and wildness, and the reassuring dictum that you &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; change the world, a little bit at a time: perhaps by beginning with rewilding your back garden.&lt;h1&gt;&lt;a href="https://livingadventurously.transistor.fm/subscribe"&gt;PLEASE SUBSCRIBE TO THE LIVING ADVENTUROUSLY PODCAST&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(It’s completely free, zero hassle to do (&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://livingadventurously.transistor.fm/subscribe"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;click here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;), but really helpful for me trying to get a new podcast off the ground. If you’re feeling extra kind, please leave a review on the app – that really helps.)&lt;/strong&gt;Listen on &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/living-adventurously/id1489454694"&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/2aYqIdvtVJkhIPklHaoXA3"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=486751&amp;amp;refid=stpr"&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://tunein.com/podcasts/Storytelling-Podcasts/Living-Adventurously-p1275719/"&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt; (“Alexa, please play the Living Adventurously podcast”) or on your favourite podcast platform such as Overcast, &lt;a href="https://podcasts.google.com/?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9mZWVkcy50cmFuc2lzdG9yLmZtL2xpdmluZy1hZHZlbnR1cm91c2x5"&gt;Google Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;, Pocket Casts, &lt;a href="https://www.breaker.audio/living-adventurously"&gt;Breaker&lt;/a&gt;, Soundcloud, Castbox, Castro.&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.alastairhumphreys.com/podcast"&gt;www.alastairhumphreys.com/podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;THIS PODCAST IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY KOMOOT&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;Komoot&lt;/a&gt; is a route planning and navigation app that inspires and enables great outdoor experiences.Your very own outdoor experiences are waiting for you. Go explore more with &lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;komoot&lt;/a&gt;. Use the voucher code &lt;a href="http://www.komoot.com/g"&gt;ADVENTUROUS&lt;/a&gt; to claim your free region bundle.The personalised planning and navigation tools ensure you plan the adventure that’s perfect for &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;. Komoot is Europe’s number 1 outdoor app, with route planning and navigation functionality, and strong community-driven inspirational features in the form of recommended Highlights and inspirational route Collections. It is used by over 8.5 million adventurers worldwide. Komoot is becoming the app of choice for cyclists and hikers the world over, with rapid community growth in the UK, the US and other parts of Europe.&lt;h1&gt;SHOW NOTES&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you enjoy listening to this episode over a cup of coffee and think it might be worth the price, you can &lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;buy me a coffee here:&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;www. ko-fi.com/al_humphreys&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep up to date with future episodes (and my other adventures, projects and books) with my &lt;a href="https://www.alastairhumphreys.com/more/subscribe/"&gt;free monthly newsletter: alastairhumphreys.com/more/subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Say hello on &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Al_Humphreys"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/al_humphreys/"&gt;Instagram: @al_humphreys&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ian Rotherham's &lt;a href="https://ianswalkonthewildside.wordpress.com/"&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ecotourism should not only be "take only photographs, leave only footprints", but we also need to try to help people in a benign way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adventure literature is often about "defeating nature" rather than pausing for a while or caring for the landscape.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We need more respect and awareness when dealing with the vulnerable resource of the natural world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How best to minimise your damage and maximise your positive impact&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.rewildingbritain.org.uk/"&gt;Rewilding&lt;/a&gt;, in all its guises, (including rewilding the mind) can save the NHS millions, as well as all the other benefits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://savesheffieldtrees.org.uk/"&gt;Sheffield Trees Action Group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The communities that are able to protest about their environment are usually the most affluent ones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trees give you a sense of place and seasonality. They are therapeutic and spiritually uplifting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The new urban wild and bringing wild to the people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultural severance in urban landscapes - a broken connection between cities and wildness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/product/014197558X/ref=as_li_qf_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=alastahumphr-21&amp;amp;creative=6738&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;creativeASIN=014197558X&amp;amp;linkId=9476054b7b4c2faa01487c58e194eb59"&gt;Feral - George Monbiot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/product/1904098665/ref=as_li_qf_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=alastahumphr-21&amp;amp;creative=6738&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;creativeASIN=1904098665&amp;amp;linkId=4192ea28f39be88c3b72c37d981aa8fc"&gt;Shadow woods - Ian Rotherham&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can change the world, even incrementally and a bit at a time. Rewilding your garden is a good start.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Globally and in Britain, in terms of nature conservation, biodiversity and sustainability we are indeed in a very bad way – essentially the ecosystem is broken and we need to mend it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The problems are not as simple as carbon = climate change = plant lots of trees! Such naïve thinking is actually dangerously misconceived&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rewilding offers a radical new approach to resolving many of the issues in ways which are, paraphrased from Lawton (2010), bigger, bolder, better, more joined …..However, this idea needs to connect with a far wider community especially in urban areas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Additionally, approaches have to be paid for and not just with ‘ecosystem services which are community goods’ – but with MONEY ….. (This is a fact not popular with politicians for example!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I suggest that farmers &amp;amp; farming have to be part of the SOLUTION and are not, as often portrayed, the problem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1&gt;TRANSCRIPT&lt;/h1&gt;Below is the transcription of our conversation. It’s done by AI so is perhaps a wee bit ropey here and there. If these transcripts prove sufficiently useful then I will make the effort to clean then up and make them better. Do let me know if you think it’s worth my time to do that. (Or, better still, do it for me…!). If you’d like to listen as you read along you can do that here:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://otter.ai/s/4mbmzPCyRr2gYKfRXYdvbQ"&gt;https://otter.ai/s/4mbmzPCyRr2gYKfRXYdvbQ&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a rel="payment" title="★ Support this podcast by donating ★" href="https://ko-fi.com/al_humphreys"&gt;★ Support this podcast by donating ★&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>alastair@alastairhumphreys.com (Living Adventurously)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">353f20553e6a450b8517cba13faaf9df</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/353f20553e6a450b8517cba13faaf9df/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 21:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Out Alive from BACKPACKER : Stranded on Mt. Rainier</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Yev Krasnitskiy and his three climber partners find themselves stranded without supplies while a storm prevents rescuers from reaching them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about your ad choices. Visit &lt;a href="https://megaphone.fm/adchoices"&gt;megaphone.fm/adchoices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>ssebestyen@aimmedia.com (Out Alive from BACKPACKER)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4a31055e063e435a8f2195e0059bfd83</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4a31055e063e435a8f2195e0059bfd83/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 17:08:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Puerto Vallarta Travel  Show Podcast : Meet and Greet Podcast at Kelly's Pour Favor in Puerto Vallarta. Mexico</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Listeners to The Puerto Vallarta Travel Show Talk about what they are doing in paradise at our get together at Kelly's Pour Favor. Also meet Singer and Dancer Hannah Brady.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>pvtravelshow@gmail.com (Puerto Vallarta Travel  Show Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6e91917aa8454e55a75d71245e07e225</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6e91917aa8454e55a75d71245e07e225/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 15:00:40 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>This Week in Travel : #259 - 2020</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This Week in Travel - Travel News Podcast. Regular hosts Gary Arndt, Jen Leo, Spud Hilton, and Chris Christensen talk about 2019 and 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/ThisWeekInTravel/~4/CY76qPFbqLo" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>chris2x@amateurtraveler.com (This Week in Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ecf2ff889b5c4cbca26311bbf2bfca35</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ecf2ff889b5c4cbca26311bbf2bfca35/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 14:50:32 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Thoughtful Travel Podcast : 171 Moving to Another Country</title><description>&lt;p&gt;It's one thing to travel to a foreign country, but to completely migrate and move to another country is another level of experience entirely! In Episode 171 of The Thoughtful Travel Podcast I'm chatting with three guests who've made the big move: one to Mexico, one to Japan, and one from Brazil to Australia. We've got half the world covered!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First up, I talk with Queen D Michele who retired from her job as a school teacher in the United States and moved to Mexico. I asked her what her family and friends thought about her big move which opened up one of the most amazing stories of all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, I chat to Suzanne Kamata who is an American married to a Japanese man and living in a fairly rural part of Japan. It's interesting for me to hear how she feels there after several decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, Luana Marchi explains about the decision she and her husband made to leave their home country of Brazil and migrate to Australia - though at the start, they weren't so sure of their lifelong plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Episode 162 on Choosing Where to Live Abroad - &lt;a href="https://notaballerina.com/162"&gt;https://notaballerina.com/162&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Queen D Michele&amp;rsquo;s book Considerations: A Guide For Moving Abroad - &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2WWjHf0"&gt;https://amzn.to/2WWjHf0&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suzanne Kamata - &lt;a href="http://www.suzannekamata.com/"&gt;http://www.suzannekamata.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suzanne&amp;rsquo;s book, Squeaky Wheels - &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2qPbCNQ"&gt;https://amzn.to/2qPbCNQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Luana Marchi - health and wellness coach - &lt;a href="https://luanamarchi.com.au/"&gt;https://luanamarchi.com.au/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Join our Facebook group for Thoughtful Travellers -&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/thoughtfultravellers"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/thoughtfultravellers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show notes: &lt;a href="http://notaballerina.com/171"&gt;https://notaballerina.com/171&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>amandakendle@me.com (The Thoughtful Travel Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d934fab4b5ec4dbb83a8e770c0f37e68</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d934fab4b5ec4dbb83a8e770c0f37e68/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 14:01:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>In Limbo : "Be Yourself"- Limitations of simplicity and common sense</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode we will discuss the depths and obstacles of advice we've heard time and time again to "be ourselves."&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>podcasts14+d507e9c@anchor.fm (In Limbo)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">e80c5ae801f94dd1969720f049a238cc</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/e80c5ae801f94dd1969720f049a238cc/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 11:59:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Dreams Unlimited Travel Show - A Weekly Discussion About Travel and Dreams Unlimited Travel : #164 - Royal Caribbean Harmony of the Seas &amp; Perfect Day at Coco Cay</title><description>01/20/20 - In this episode, Tracey discusses a recent cruise on Royal Caribbean Cruise Line's Harmony of the Seas as well as her first experience stopping at a Perfect Day at Coco Cay!</description><author>craig@wdwinfo.com (Dreams Unlimited Travel Show - A Weekly Discussion About Travel and Dreams Unlimited Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9d3b9d3ec24f49218cb01e31e43aa63b</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9d3b9d3ec24f49218cb01e31e43aa63b/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>We Travel There with Lee Huffman : Cutler Bay, FL | Ride bikes at the marina with Lorena</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We're in Cutler Bay, Florida with Lorena Tomasini of Malmins.com &amp; the 12 Minute Talks podcast. We explore the gardens of the Charles Deering estate, ride bikes at the marina, and discover Biscayne National Park.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show notes are at &lt;a href="https://WeTravelThere.com/cutlerbay" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://WeTravelThere.com/cutlerbay&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;When booking hotels, use the Dosh cash back app. You'll receive competitive rates at over 600,000 hotels around the world plus earn up to 20% cash back on your stay! Use promo code "Timmy" when you open your free account at &lt;a href="https://WeTravelThere.com/dosh" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;WeTravelThere.com/dosh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>wetravelthere@gmail.com (We Travel There with Lee Huffman)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">fbc50b35d05a45509d737d07280d18e3</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/fbc50b35d05a45509d737d07280d18e3/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hoosier Outdoorsmen Podcast : Episode 33  talking to John LaGue and Greg Robinson about waterfowl season</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this Episode I talk to John LaGue about his waterfowl season and his preparations for Turkey Season I also talked to Greg Robinson about his waterfowl season.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Rileyhendrixson@live.com (The Hoosier Outdoorsmen Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6b71966429874c579215922302826d9a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6b71966429874c579215922302826d9a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Join Us in France Travel Podcast : Fall in Love with Corsica, Episode 267</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode of the podcast, Annie and her guest Michael Grove give you many reasons to fall in love with Corsica. Specifically upper Corsica or Haute-Corse.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Michael spent a whole month exploring Corsica and wrote about it on his &lt;a href="https://mlgroves.com/"&gt;travel blog&lt;/a&gt;. He shares his favorite places, hidden gems that took his breath away, details about the food you'll find in Corsica and more.&lt;/p&gt; Hotels Michael Used on this Trip &lt;p&gt;Bastia—&lt;a href= "https://www.booking.com/hotel/fr/ha-tel-napola-c-on.en.html?aid=954523&amp;no_rooms=1&amp;group_adults=2"&gt;Hotel Napoleon&lt;/a&gt;, 43 Boulevard Paoli&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Rogliano—&lt;a href= "https://www.booking.com/hotel/fr/u-sant-agnellu.en.html?aid=954523&amp;no_rooms=1&amp;group_adults=2"&gt;Hotel U Sant Agnellu&lt;/a&gt; (perched village with great view from the dining room and from rooms facing Mediterranean Sea)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Centuri—&lt;a href= "https://www.booking.com/hotel/fr/restaurant-le-vieux-moulin-centuri.en.html?aid=954523&amp;no_rooms=1&amp;group_adults=2"&gt;Hotel Vieux Moulin&lt;/a&gt; (overlooks small port and has good restaurant)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Cargèse—&lt;a href= "https://www.booking.com/hotel/fr/residence-roc-e-mare.en.html?aid=954523&amp;no_rooms=1&amp;group_adults=2"&gt;Residence Roc E Mare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; Places Michael Visited &lt;p&gt;He'll take us to (not necessrily in that order, see map in the show notes) Bastia, Rogliano, Centuri, Saint-Florent, L’Île-Rousse, Calvi, Porto, Cargèse, Corte, Patrimonio, the Calanques de Piana, the Réserve naturelle de Scandola, Pigna, Nonza, and Sant'Antonino.&lt;/p&gt; Great Foods from Corsica &lt;p&gt;And the foods sound out of this world: brocciu, beignets au chaud sucré (ou salé), coppa, lonzu, figatellu. Don't know what those are? I didn't know either! Let Michael explain! If you're having a hard time with all the Corsican words, follow along with the transcript. I've done my best to spell all those names correctly 🙂&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/2sG4J2o"&gt;Corsica: Recipes and Stories from a Mediterranean Island&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The restaurant Michael mentions where he couldn't remember the name in Pigna is called A Mandria di Pigna. To see more of his restaurant recommendations click on Guest Notes below.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:%20annie@joinusinfrance.com"&gt;Email&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/joinusinfrance/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/addictedtofrance/"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href= "https://www.pinterest.fr/France_Travel_Podcast/"&gt;Pinterest&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ParisPodcast"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; Did you get my &lt;a href= "https://voicemap.me/authors/annie-sargent"&gt;VoiceMap&lt;/a&gt; Paris tours yet? They are designed for people who want to see the best of Paris neighborhoods &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; put what they are looking at into historical context. There are so many great stories in Paris. Don't walk right past them without having a clue what happened there! You can buy them directly from the VoiceMap app or click &lt;a href="https://joinusinfrance.com/audiotours/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to order activation codes at the podcast listener discount price. &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Discussed in this Episode &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Balagna Area [04:16]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bastia [10:04]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;In the high or medium season don't try to wing it with the hotels [11:34]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Strong regional culture in Corsica [12:10]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Prices in Corsica [16:12]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Corte and the citadel [17:51]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Nonza and La Sassa outdoor restaurant [20:32]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Col de Teghime {23:06]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Calanques de Piana [24:55]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Réserve naturelle de Scandola [25:21]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;How to visit the calanques [26:12]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Hicking in the Haute Corse [28:04]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The village of Pigna [29:47]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The village of Sant'Antonino [30:23]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The gastronomy of Corsica: we mention a lot of local specialties in this segment! [34:05]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Is Corsica a vacation for couples or families or adventure seekers? [40:31]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;How is Corsica different from the rest of France? [42:01]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Thank you patrons and donors! [45:05]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Annie's new Saint-Germain-des-Prés tour on the VoiceMap App [47:07]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;A little bit of a health scare [48:03]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Quick update about the current strikes in France [50:42]&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>annie@joinusinfrance.com (Join Us in France Travel Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">b73644e8afe44ce0b50fa188f253c09f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/b73644e8afe44ce0b50fa188f253c09f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 11:39:06 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>National Parks Traveler Podcast : National Parks Traveler: Public Lands, Federal Regulatory Changes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;John Freemuth, who holds the Cecil D. Andrus  Endowed Chair for Environment and Public Lands at Boise State University, and Nada Culver, the vice president for public lands and senior policy counsel at the National Audubon Society, discuss efforts in Washington to tweak the National Environmental Policy Act as well as the Endangered Species Act.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>kurt@nationalparkstraveler.org (National Parks Traveler Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">eec3ffedd36b4253955955e29b36e93a</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/eec3ffedd36b4253955955e29b36e93a/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Mobituaries with Mo Rocca : Mobituaries LIVE!</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In a Mobits first, Mo takes the show on the road! Mo shares his love of obituaries; investigates why we confuse certain dead celebrities; and interviews former New York Times obituary writer Margalit Fox about what it's like to write about the dead for a living. This episode was recorded in Asbury Park, NJ and Fairfield, CT.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Mobituaries@simonandschuster.com (Mobituaries with Mo Rocca)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">8c43201ced104373899f6e2057913360</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/8c43201ced104373899f6e2057913360/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 01:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Monsters Among Us Podcast : Sn. 8 Ep. 19 - Poltergeists, bigfoot’s bones and a few strange UFOs.</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Tallman Ghost -  &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aSJqmSfT62c" target="_blank" rel= "noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v%3DaSJqmSfT62c&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1579295376542000&amp;usg=AFQjCNEehI4EtJp_xm2MM4xe5OEJZ9msaw"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aSJqmSfT62c&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; Strange Familiars - &lt;a href= "https://www.strangefamiliars.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl= "https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.strangefamiliars.com/&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1579295376542000&amp;usg=AFQjCNFM7ArCgSX9BvFoi1wrGseUrHMtSg"&gt; https://www.strangefamiliars.com/&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>monstersamonguspodcast@gmail.com (Monsters Among Us Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">84412af3c94c4bb5bb18ac1be8728702</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/84412af3c94c4bb5bb18ac1be8728702/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 13:47:07 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Inside Universal Podcast : The Inside Universal Podcast: New Decade, Same Non-Sense (and Super Nintendo World, too)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The return of Hatetofly! Andy, Brian, and Drew discuss the recent &lt;a href= "http://www.insideuniversal.net/2020/01/universal-orlandos-mardi-gras-2020-concert-line-up-and-details-announced/"&gt; Mardi Gras&lt;/a&gt; announcement, as well as the latest information that was released regarding &lt;a href= "http://www.insideuniversal.net/2020/01/universal-studios-japan-reveals-new-details-on-super-nintendo-world-opening-this-summer/"&gt; Super Nintendo World&lt;/a&gt; at Universal Studios Japan, including the interactive Power Up Bands. &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>jon@insideuniversal.net (The Inside Universal Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9bf6152d06b04e88b78500c62165b169</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9bf6152d06b04e88b78500c62165b169/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:28:59 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Travel Tales : Andrew Bender</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Travel Writer Andrew Bender has lived as far away as Japan and Poland, and has spent over 20 years contributing to newspapers, magazines, and travel guides. He also leads tour groups through Japan.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>traveltalespodcast@gmail.com (Travel Tales)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">6cb4edd675734acf8a6751099cc42e1e</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/6cb4edd675734acf8a6751099cc42e1e/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 22:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Disneyland With Kids Podcast : Disney Princess Dining Adventures at Disneyland with Kids</title><description>In This Episode - Disney Princess Breakfast Adventures: &lt;p&gt;Leslie from &lt;a href= "https://tripswithtykes.com"&gt;Trips with Tykes&lt;/a&gt; and Jessica from &lt;a href="https://thehappiestblogonearth.com"&gt;The Happiest Blog on Earth&lt;/a&gt; are sharing all about Disney Princess Breakfast Adventure, a character dining experience at the Disneyland Resort.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leslie and Jessica reminisce on visiting Napa Rose together to experience Disney Princess Breakfast Adventure. With a high $125/person price point, we often find people asking if this experience is worth it in the &lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/groups/disneylandwithkids"&gt;Disneyland with Kids Group&lt;/a&gt;. In this episode we cover:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;What is Disney Princess Breakfast Adventure&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Where is it located&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What is the cost of Disney Princess Breakfast Adventure&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What food will you get to eat&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What princesses will you see at Disney Princess Adventure&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What else is included with the price&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Tips for Disney Princess Adventure&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Plan Your Disneyland Vacation:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you want to book a Disneyland vacation we suggest &lt;a title="Get Away Today" href= "https://www.getawaytoday.com/?referrerid=7526" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;booking through our partners at Get Away Today&lt;/a&gt;. If you are traveling in 2020, we suggest booking your vacations NOW to lock in the current ticket pricing. We expect ticket prices to go up in January or February of 2020.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Want to connect with other Disneyland with Kids community members, receive and share tips, and more? &lt;a title="DwK Group" href= "https://facebook.com/groups/disneylandwithkids" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Join the Disneyland with Kids Group on Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect With The Hosts:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can connect with the hosts of Disneyland with Kids at the following locations:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leslie - &lt;a href= "https://tripswithtykes.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Trips with Tykes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Leslie on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/tripswithtykes"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Julie - &lt;a href= "https://momrewritten.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Mom Rewritten&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Julie on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/momrewritten"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/momrewritten" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/momrewritten" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Becca - &lt;a href= "https://thiscrazyadventurecalledlife.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;This Crazy Adventure Called Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Becca on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/crazyadventurecalledlife" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/thebeccarobins" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/thebeccarobins" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Jessica - &lt;a href= "https://thehappiestblogonearth.com"&gt;The Happiest Blog On Earth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Connect with Jessica on:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://facebook.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://instagram.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://twitter.com/disneylandplan" target="_blank" rel= "noopener noreferrer"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>becca@disneylandwithkids.info (Disneyland With Kids Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">12072d25fbc4472288c3cec42f4945d8</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/12072d25fbc4472288c3cec42f4945d8/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 09:38:12 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Well-Traveled with AAA : Encore: A Journey Through France</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This was taken from our interview with Trafalgar French travel expert Marie Dubois, which you can find on the Well-Traveled with Triple-A feed on iTunes and Spotify. We hope you’ll rate us or leave a comment and let us know what you think.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sonixcursions@gmail.com (Well-Traveled with AAA)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">df0d5416ca894b818f2970138d0e5f66</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/df0d5416ca894b818f2970138d0e5f66/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The History of Egypt Podcast : Mini Episode: An Intact Tomb</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Kha and Merit, an Intact Tomb. In 1906, a remarkable discovery came to light: the tomb of a middle-class couple, who lived in the town of Deir el-Medina. Here, amid the craftsmen and specialists who made tombs, a man named Kha and a woman named Merit enjoyed an affluent lifestyle. When they died, they were interred with all their worldly possessions and slept undisturbed for 3300 years. Then, a wonderful discovery occurred and an ancient story came to life... The History of Egypt Podcast is supported by Patrons, get early access and ad-free listening at &lt;a href="https://create.acast.com/episodes/c8530076-4db3-4326-b377-6a676931ff74/www.patreon.com/egyptpodcast" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.patreon.com/egyptpodcast&lt;/a&gt;... Images and Bibliography at &lt;a href="https://create.acast.com/episodes/c8530076-4db3-4326-b377-6a676931ff74/www.egyptianhistorypodcast.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.egyptianhistorypodcast.com&lt;/a&gt;... Music by Keith Zizza &lt;a href="https://create.acast.com/episodes/c8530076-4db3-4326-b377-6a676931ff74/www.keithzizza.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;www.keithzizza.com&lt;/a&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;  For information regarding your data privacy, visit &lt;a href="https://www.acast.com/privacy"&gt;acast.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;</description><author>egyptpodcast@gmail.com (The History of Egypt Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">be7991cdc62b4028a5a4fee23a03ef4c</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/be7991cdc62b4028a5a4fee23a03ef4c/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:45:30 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Travel Like a Boss Podcast : Ep 240 - Felipe Caceres (Cold in Canada to Earning $11,000 a month in Chiang Mai, Thailand)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Felipe Caceres is a freelance job website developer and started making money online at a very young age online. Through hard work and determination, he led himself to success. Felipe also travels around the globe in pursuit of a better lifestyle while searching for his dream.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;During this episode, Felipe shares his exciting journey from living a simple life towards reaching his dreams. He also shares how his perspective on home-based jobs changed, which paved the way for his online career. Listen in and discover the life secret that helped him earn $11,000 a month.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Links:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Dropshipping Course - &lt;a href= "http://AntonMethod.com"&gt;AntonMethod.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Conference - &lt;a href= "http://NomadSummit.com"&gt;NomadSummit.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Book 1 - &lt;a href= "http://12weeksinThailand.com"&gt;12weeksinThailand.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Book 2 - &lt;a href= "http://LifeChangesQuick.com"&gt;LifeChangesQuick.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Time Stamps:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;03:49 – Exploring ideas for a good venture&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;07:37 – The carefree life in Bali&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;13:20 – Living in different places in the world&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;19:46 – The reason that pushed Felipe to live in Chiang Mai&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;26:04 – Benefits of Home-Based jobs&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;33:21 – Felipe’s childhood urge to live in a temperate country&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;36:20 – How did he start earning online?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;39:41 – “Think about the lifestyle you want, put a dollar amount to it and work backward” – Felipe Caceres&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;40:29 – Figuring out your problem &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;47:54 – Making money as a youth&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;53:06 – Felipe’s website brands&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;01:04:01 – “I think the biggest thing was taking the leap, moving out here and moving out of your comfort zone” – Felipe Caceres&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Enjoyed this episode? Share it with friends!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>johnny@travellikeabosspodcast.com (Travel Like a Boss Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">d11367e1f7a147979c846c4d323cd4bf</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/d11367e1f7a147979c846c4d323cd4bf/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 06:17:13 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Hashtag Colorado Life : Building Your Colorado Bucket List in 2020</title><description>BONUS #2: What’s on your Colorado bucket list? In this bonus episode Ryan and Carrie talk about the must-see and must-do things to add to your Colorado bucket list. With the mountains in your backyard, an ever-growing food scene, and endless indoor and outdoor activities where do you start? There are so many things to do and cities to explore!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ryan and Carrie share the activities and adventures that are on their Colorado bucket list. They also discuss the places and sights they have already visited. Many of the ideas include iconic Colorado destinations and local favorites, as well as lesser-known but still epic experiences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are looking for the best things to do in Colorado without busting your budget, that’s what this episode is all about. Find out the top 16 things Ryan and Carrie recommend you add to your bucket list. Plus, these are great suggestions for discovering within your first year of living in the square state.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more information and resources about exploring Colorado, visit our website at &lt;a href="http://hashtagcoloradolife.com/"&gt;HashtagColoradoLife.com&lt;/a&gt; or&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/hashtagcoloradolife/"&gt; @HashtagColoradoLife&lt;/a&gt; on Instagram.</description><author>team@hashtagcoloradolife.com (Hashtag Colorado Life)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">4580a7f45e174506aa649f38489f2dba</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/4580a7f45e174506aa649f38489f2dba/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dish Food Travel Show : 48 Piri Piri Chicken</title><description>IN THIS EPISODE:

&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The story of piri piri chicken, what is piri piri sauce and where did it come from?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plus, a short history of Nandos, the international piri piri chicken chain restaurant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partial Transcript at &lt;a href='https://foodfuntravel.com/history-of-piri-piri-chicken/'&gt;https://foodfuntravel.com/history-of-piri-piri-chicken/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The history of piri piri chicken, one of the world's most popular spicy grilled chicken dishes. From its origins, to modern chain restaurant success as part of the Nando's restaurant chain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who invented the original piri piri sauce? And how did that become piri piri chicken and part of an international craze. Plus, the best piri piri chicken is certainly not at Nandos... We explore the local chicken scene in a European country where it has almost become a national dish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>megsy@foodfuntravel.com (The Dish Food Travel Show)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bdac9d32026142b3821d3ad07c3bd926</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bdac9d32026142b3821d3ad07c3bd926/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 02:13:01 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Ohio Folklore : Legend of the Fiddler's Green</title><description>Long before the Civil War, in the quiet darkness of moonless nights, lonesome fiddle music could be heard wafting over the surface of the Ohio River.  The source of the melody was unknown to some.  But to others, it brought the promise of freedom and the protection of one pledged to shelter them.

Still today, many claim to hear this music.  Unsuspecting hikers and passersby also report seeing a shining green light, resembling a handheld lantern.  Both emanate from a historic cemetery situated on the northern bank of the Ohio River.    

Come hear the Legend of the Fiddler’s Green.  It’s the tale of one Henry Darby, a 19th century man of high standing in the Cincinnati community.  He was a rumored clandestine supporter of runaway slaves.  His reputation is still debated today.  Is it true?  Did he guide freedom-seekers across the Ohio River with his music?

Come decide for yourself.

If you enjoy this episode, please rate, review and subscribe to Ohio Folklore on your chosen podcast platform.  Your can also find Ohio Folklore at:

ohiofolklore.com
facebook.com/ohiofolklore

And as always, keep wondering…</description><author>melissa.davies77@outlook.com (Ohio Folklore)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">3747b971e1624020abfd9d36f6730e96</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/3747b971e1624020abfd9d36f6730e96/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 15:36:04 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Wise About Texas : Ep. 78:  The Lady in Blue</title><description>&lt;p&gt; In 1629 a group of Jumano Indians suddenly appeared at a New Mexico mission, eager to learn more about Christianity.  The excited and grateful Franciscan priests wondered what motivated this sudden interest.  The tale the Indians told seemed unbelievable.  A &amp;#8220;lady in blue&amp;#8221; had appeared to them instructing them to seek out the priests and teaching the Indians the sign of the cross.  That sounded incredible enough but what really stunned the priests was that they had just received a letter from Spain relating the story of a nun telling the exact same tale&amp;#8230;half a world away.  Is the Lady in Blue a myth&amp;#8230;or a miracle?  You decide in the latest episode of Wise About Texas.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/WiseAboutTexas/~4/lmVlyLFkRdw" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</description><author>Host@wiseabouttexas.com (Wise About Texas)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">9f63998fcaeb4eed89b309da28ba42b9</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/9f63998fcaeb4eed89b309da28ba42b9/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 09:36:28 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Retro Disney World Podcast : Ep 54.5 - Bringing the World Closer to You</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Episode 54.5 of the RetroWDW Podcast: "Bringing the World Closer to You" - We appreciate your support and hope you have been enjoying each and every episode. Be sure to check out some of our previous shows! &lt;/p&gt;
Main Topic
&lt;p&gt;Back in &lt;a href='https://www.retrowdw.com/podcast/podcast-episode-42-communicore-west/'&gt;Episode 42 (Communicore West)&lt;/a&gt; we interviewed Lisa Bastoni, granddaughter of Walter Einsel, the designer of the Age of Information Exhibit at Futurecom in Communicore West. Through her grandfather's notes and a correct search of the song, we were able to locate the author and lyricist of the song, Tom Tierney! In this episode we speak with Tom about the creation of the song, how he developed the melody and lyrics and his interaction with Walter and Naiad Einsel. We top it off with a special version of Bringing the World Closer to you performed at RetroMagic by Lisa Bastoni!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tom's other works currently in production:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;NARNIA&lt;/em&gt; (based on &lt;em&gt;The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe&lt;/em&gt;) is at the Serenbe Playhouse in Atlanta, GA through January 12, 2020. It's an "immersive" production - here’s a link…&lt;a href='http://www.serenbeplayhouse.com/narnia'&gt;http://www.serenbeplayhouse.com/narnia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.NarniaTheMusical.com'&gt;http://www.NarniaTheMusical.com&lt;/a&gt;    And coming up in January, &lt;em&gt;ELEANOR – An American Love Story&lt;/em&gt; at the Media Theatre in Media, PA (near Philadelphia) playing January 29 to February 23, 2020. It's about the young Eleanor &amp; Franklin Roosevelt. For info and tickets, here’s the link…&lt;a href='https://mediatheatre.org/event/eleanor-an-american-love-story/'&gt;https://mediatheatre.org/event/eleanor-an-american-love-story/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.eleanorthemusical.com/'&gt;www.EleanorTheMusical.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find Lisa's music at &lt;a href='http://www.lisabastoni.com'&gt;www.lisabastoni.com&lt;/a&gt; and on itunes!&lt;/p&gt;
2020: The Year of Film
&lt;p&gt;We have quite a year coming up and we want you to be a part of it, every step of the way. The 'How Bowers Archive' has been digitized, we have tons of restored film movies and so much more, just waiting to get posted. To make sure you are the first to know when items are released, &lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/retrodisneyworld'&gt;subscribe to us on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;. Be sure to click the notification bell too, that way you are alerted when we post.  Finally, be sure to &lt;a href='https://vimeo.com/retrowdw'&gt;check out Vimeo&lt;/a&gt; if that is your thing, as we will post there as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
Next Month
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Join us next time for Episode 55, where we take you back to The Disney-MGM Studios! &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description><author>podcast@retrowdw.com (Retro Disney World Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">21348e7bf4a449bdbdd5b53a9b754bc7</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/21348e7bf4a449bdbdd5b53a9b754bc7/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 14:02:55 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>My Solo Road : She loves Jesus &amp; Auditing Faucets | ft. Kristin Holden</title><description>&lt;p&gt;What if you could do van life without ever having to find remote work? This week Kristin (@wheretheroadforks_) tells us how she asked her boss to go remote and got a YES. We talk religion, ex boyfriends, and good ole solo female van life per usual.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>divineontheroad@gmail.com (My Solo Road)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">c80727f69a27492c94619c956bbba02f</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/c80727f69a27492c94619c956bbba02f/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 08:40:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>San Francisco Real Estate: Escrow Out Loud : To Stage, Or Not to Stage</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In today’s episode of &lt;a href="https://jacksonfuller.com/insight/podcast/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Escrow Out Loud, our San Francisco Real Estate podcast&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;u&gt;,&lt;/u&gt; we have a very special guest star: our friend and client Kay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[00:44] Kay shares a little of her background with us. We also learn how she came to buy her lovely house in Burlingame almost forty years ago which was almost brand new at the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[03:46] Other than the perfect location, the two other features that made Kay fall in love with the house were the easy upkeep and the huge closets!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[05:24] This summer we accidentally found her second dream home, so we needed to get Kay’s home in Burlingame on the market fast. Kay explains it was a challenge of getting her home ready for sale while still living in it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[07:14] Initially, we tried to sell Kay’s house as is, with all her furniture but didn't have much luck. We then moved Kay out, revamped and staged the house before trying again. What was the second process like in comparison to the first time around?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[09:29] The unique thing about selling a house is the emotional component that comes with it. After all the renovations Kay’s home was completely transformed. Did it hurt her feelings having to do this or was it exciting?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[14:30] The house was put on the market the second time and this time it sold within ten days, over asking price. Looking back on all of the drama, was it all worth it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[15:09] Interestingly, after looking at numerous properties, the new house Kay ended up buying was also staged. What advice does she have for anyone considering selling their place while still living in it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;[16:46] While selling a home is a very emotional process, the aim is to make as much money as possible. To achieve this, it needs to look as good as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for listening. If you enjoyed this episode leave us a review on your favorite platform, tell your friends and don’t forget to join us again next week!&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>info+5ab02d3b627e02027cf8604d@mg.pippa.io (San Francisco Real Estate: Escrow Out Loud)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">46419d11ffad450ca04a659535ee3534</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/46419d11ffad450ca04a659535ee3534/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 09:20:48 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Betty in the Sky with a Suitcase! : 173 People's Distress</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Episode 173 Jan 7, 2020&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This show has stories about horses, Cuba, bad behavior, a survival story and the magnificent night sky.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Contact...  flywithbetty@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Music for the show was recorded on the street in Madrid.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thetravellinghousesitters.com/about-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;The traveling house sitters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://www.npr.org/2019/12/04/784852433/she-had-me-i-had-her-robyn-crawford-opens-up" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;NPR story on Whitney Houston&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://simpleflying.com/latam-a350-ceiling-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Overhead falls down story&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= "https://atlanticmirror.com/anthropology-and-history/people/this-flight-attendant-plunged-to-earth-from-33330-feet-but-somehow-she-lived-to-tell-the-tale/?l=a&amp;utm_source=AOL.com&amp;utm_medium=Referral&amp;utm_campaign=Direct" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Survival Story&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Get fun stuff at... www.patreon.com/bettyinthesky&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You can find all of my books on my website:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;www.bettyinthesky.com&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Instagram &lt;a href= "https://www.instagram.com/bettyinthesky/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/bettyinthesky&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/bettyinthesky/"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><author>flywithbetty@gmail.com (Betty in the Sky with a Suitcase!)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">ba69d85d11c4498383d43fb8b3f15cc2</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/ba69d85d11c4498383d43fb8b3f15cc2/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 09:05:21 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>La Lido Loca Cruise Podcast : 7. Mistakes First Time Cruisers Make</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to episode #7 of the La Lido Loca podcast.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Join Jenny and Tony as they talk about cruising!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Show Notes:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on YouTube:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;La Lido Loca Podcast: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCLoGEyIWH6f6mkJxDCweDag"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCLoGEyIWH6f6mkJxDCweDag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;La Lido Loca Cruising: &lt;a href= "https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqFivW2VWJtGfvrMreyjNbw"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCqFivW2VWJtGfvrMreyjNbw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Let Jenny help with your travel, you can contact her at: &lt;a href= "mailto:jbarnette@cruiseshipcenters.com"&gt;jbarnette@cruiseshipcenters.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Info about La Lido Loca Group Cruises: &lt;a href="http://www.lalidoloca.com/groupcruise" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;http://www.lalidoloca.com/groupcruise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Follow us on Social Media: Facebook Page - &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt; Instagram - &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt; Twitter - &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/lalidoloca" target= "_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;https://twitter.com/lalidoloca&lt;/a&gt; Pintrest - &lt;a href="https://www.pinterest.com/lalidoloca/" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://www.pinterest.com/lalidoloca/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Represent the locafam with a t-shirt, check out the latest designs at: &lt;a href="https://teespring.com/stores/lalidoloca-funshop" target= "_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;https://teespring.com/stores/lalidoloca-funshop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our mailing address is: La Lido Loca 4142 Mariner Blvd #402 Spring Hill, FL 34609&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Support our creative efforts at Patreon: &lt;a href="http://www.patreon.com/lalidoloca" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;http://www.patreon.com/lalidoloca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Please Submit Questions or Comments to &lt;a href= "mailto:tony@lalidoloca.com" target="_blank" rel= "noopener"&gt;tony@lalidoloca.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>tony@lalidoloca.com (La Lido Loca Cruise Podcast)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">60a13069c960404385c5080b909bf8ef</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/60a13069c960404385c5080b909bf8ef/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 19:28:51 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Extremities : St Helena's Decisive Decade</title><description>&lt;p&gt;On January 1st, 2020, St Helena enters what will potentially be the most important and consequential decade in its history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extremities is made possible by Curiosity Stream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sign up for a &amp;nbsp;Curiosity Stream subscription at &lt;a href="http://CuriosityStream.com/ext"&gt;http://CuriosityStream.com/ext&lt;/a&gt; and get a free subscription to Nebula--the streaming video site that Wendover Productions helped found. On Nebula, find The World's Most Useful Airport--the documentary we produced about St Helena's airport.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>sam@wendover.productions (Extremities)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">1f264a6627bd48c89a255b94ca017e62</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/1f264a6627bd48c89a255b94ca017e62/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 09:47:25 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Break Into Travel Writing Podcast  : BITW 150: 11 Keys To Long-term Success As a Travel Writing Freelancer with Rachel Cavanaugh (Part 2)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;My guest today is Rachel Cavanaugh.  This is part two of our conversation about the 11 Keys To Long-term Success As A Freelance Travel Writer. We chat about getting over perfectionism when writing, how to write faster and prioritize your workload. To subscribe to the podcast, please use the links below: Click Here to Subscribe [...]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://breakintotravelwriting.com/keys-to-long-term-success-as-a-travel-writing-freelancer-with-rachel-cavanaugh-part-2/"&gt;BITW 150: 11 Keys To Long-term Success As a Travel Writing Freelancer with Rachel Cavanaugh (Part 2)&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://breakintotravelwriting.com"&gt;Break Into Travel Writing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>alexa@alexameisler.com (Break Into Travel Writing Podcast )</author><guid isPermaLink="false">bba3b5d931aa478389dbc2be0e6cf7cd</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/bba3b5d931aa478389dbc2be0e6cf7cd/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 11:52:57 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Sake On Air : Aroma &amp; Sake</title><description>What exactly is the scent of sake? For our final episode of 2019, Chris Hughes, Rebekah Wilson-Lye, and Sebastie Lemoine gather to discuss the nature and role of aroma in sake. Seeing as how the smells that we experience impart so much influence on our perception of taste and our associated memories, this is a […]</description><author>jpotts0011@yahoo.co.jp (Sake On Air)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">a04c7cc6f4714ae781310c862b2722c1</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/a04c7cc6f4714ae781310c862b2722c1/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 01:23:26 -0800</pubDate></item><item><title>Become Nomad - Digital Nomad Lifestyle and Long Term Travel : BN068: Freelance remote Writing with BecomeNomad new Editor</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, Eli will interview Dan Rozenblum, BecomeNomad new podcast and blog editor. We will over why Dan decided to reach join BecomeNomad, his recent trip representing BecomeNomad in Kazakhstan, and some tips for digital nomads who would like to sustain their travel by becoming writers.&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>eli@becomenomad.com (Become Nomad - Digital Nomad Lifestyle and Long Term Travel)</author><guid isPermaLink="false">91b06bcdd9384b9f955d18c4b4984ece</guid><enclosure url="https://www.listennotes.com/e/p/91b06bcdd9384b9f955d18c4b4984ece/" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 07:35:49 -0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>